[Scarlet Heart: Ryeo]
KoreanDramaX.com
[Episode 9]
It's raining!
It's raining! It's rain!
The heavens have answered us!
It is finally raining.
It is raining!
It is finally raining!
Rain!
Gwangjong.
A hero is born. A hero.
How did he hide that scar anyway?
I think he used cosmetics.
I don't know who did it,but she is very skilled.
The heavens chose ourfourth brother for a reason.
You must not treat So carelessly anymore.
It was the 4th Prince.
Prince Wang So is Gwangjong.
His brothers, nephews,and longtime subjects...
they say he killed them all.
He's that Gwangjong.
He killed them?
Your Highness, you have saved us!
You are our savior!
You have saved us all!
Thank you!
Is he going to becomea king because of me?
Because I covered his scar?
No, his name was alreadyrecorded in history.
Even if I hadn't done it,he would've become a king.
But is Prince Wang So really going to...
Soo, it's raining now.
The king will celebrate this rain.
Soo, what is it?
Will they all die because of me?
What?
That person...
is he becoming like thatbecause of me?
Is he?
You have to be safe, Your Highness.
The 4th Prince was chosen by the heavens.
There is no way the heavens chose him.
It should have been me.
That was my seat.
I should have brought the rain!
Mother.
How could you losean opportunity like that?
If someone tries to take what is yours
you must tear his throat outto protect it if you must!
You should have taken it,no matter what!
A mistake... it was a mistake.
- I can make mistakes too!- No.
There are no mistakes.
If I am to rise up as a king's mother,you must be persistent and ruthless.
Court Lady Hae from the Damiwon...
I am positive she covered upSo's scar with the use of makeup.
I am to raise you up, Mother?
Damiwon, Damiwon, Damiwon!
The girls at Damiwon are all troublesome.
I will burn that place down.
The 4th Prince So is hereto see His Majesty.
Prince Wang So,you have accomplished a great feat.
You have saved this country.
I only led the rain ritualin place of the Crown Prince.
Why is that important?
I was delayed by a pack of thieves.I could not make it to the ritual.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
How many years has it been since you'veshown your face to your father?
You have kept that scar to yourselffor so many years.
I have caused you to worry.
Father.
Show your bare face to the world nowand be confident.
Devote yourself to helping theCrown Prince make a good nation.
You must becomea great source of strength.
Your father trusts you.
I accept your orders.
We can avoid the rain here for now.Someone will bring us rain clothes soon.
Was it you who covered So's scar?
You can get into trouble fortouching the face of a prince.
You did a good thing.You do not need to worry.
Also...
So may have stood in place of theCrown Prince at the rain ritual.
But that does not change anything.
Really?
Of course not.
But things have to change.
Are they not going to change?
Now that the rain has fallen,the king will celebrate.
It has been a long time since a courtlady has been released from service.
I'm certain that is what it will be.
I can't just do nothing.
- I need to find out.- Soo.
Do you know who the next king will be?
I suppose it will be the Crown Princeas long as nothing happens.
Then... what aboutafter the Crown Prince?
After him?
Gwangjong... that's what you said.
What?
You called Prince Wang So "Gwangjong".
I said that without realizing it.
It just came out.
I think I must have beenabout four or five.
They say I nearly drowned to death.
No! They say that I did die.
But I woke up after a day.
You died... and came back to life?
My mother would often say to me
that once I came back to life,I seemed completely different.
She said I seemed wise beyond my years.
I've never told anyone about this.
Often, I see scenes pass before my eyes
and I don't know ifthey're real or dreams.
I see a big bird thatcarries people in the sky.
I've even seen stairs anda room that moves on its own.
I saw a building as high as the skyfilled with many, many people.
Is this person from the future like me?
Maybe he can't rememberbecause he was too young.
I heard that you also died and came back.
So I wondered if you hadthe gift of foresight like I do.
Now ask me the questionyou truly want to.
What is it that you reallywant to know, Lady Soo?
Is Prince So really Gwangjong?Is he going to kill everyone?
What about Prince Wang Wook?What is his future like?
What...
should I do?
Nothing.
You mustn't do anything.
Whatever it is you saw,let things flow naturally.
You cannot get involved.
What if I can change things?
I can stop trouble from occurring.
I can make something badinto something good.
You have already laid your handson Prince Wang So's face.
So...
the prince's future...
will it change?
I do not know that.
The moment humans realize heaven's will,that is called fate.
Did it changeor was it always meant to be?
Who knows these things?
We humans cannot escapethe will of the heavens.
Leave things to play outthe way they are meant to be.
That is what will keep you safe.
So has made it rain.
Now he will receive the King's trust.
Yes, he will.
If the Crown Prince was notgoing to be the master of the ritual
you should have beenthe one standing there.
It was a good opportunity.
It was a seat that was given to So.
It was necessary for Soto be in that seat.
I should not be greedyfor something like that.
Once you receive the favor of the king
it is easy to getother ideas in your head.
I am only saying that we have anotherperson to be wary of in the palace.
Hae Soo said So would be different too.
Are you saying that, as well?
As for So...
why shouldn't he receivethe king's trust and confidence?
Think about the harsh treatmenthe has received all this time.
Hae Soo warned you tobe careful of our 4th brother?
Why?
The person who helped Sotake off his mask was...
Hae Soo.
She is afraid that somethingwill happen because of that.
As for me...
there must be a seat thatis necessary for me to fill.
What could it be?
I am very...
curious.
It's me.
It was so sudden.
You came at me so suddenly.
I didn't mean anything by it.
I was just so surprised, really.
I'm sorry.
Did I say anything about it?
You don't need to be sorry. I'm sorry.
For the first time in my life,I called the king "Father."
It had been 15 years since he lookedat my face and my eyes properly.
He told me to be more confident.
After I heard those words,all the pain I had just disappeared.
I'll have to be a great supportto the Crown Prince, like he said.
Everyone keeps thanking me.
No one says I'm scaryor calls me a beast.
It's funny.
I'm starting to like myself this way.
Also...
the person who made this way...
Hae Soo, it was you.
A person like this is going tobecome that cruel?
I can't believe it.
Choi Ji Mong said I shouldnever get involved.
I could help him andchange Gwangjong's future.
No matter how angry you get,you must hold it in.
Don't ever kill anyone.
You won't have any reasonto be hurt in the future.
Everyone will like you and treat youas a precious person, okay?
Gosh, you and your lectures.
This is nice.
I can do it.
I won't ignore it.
I won't let anyone get hurt.
Lady Mong Ryang Won asked meto find a suitable match for Soon Deok.
So, I'm thinking of choosingone of the princes.
One of the princes?
The 14th Prince would be asuitable match for Lady Soon Deok.
They both love the martial arts andtheir horoscopes are a good fit.
Come now. What if husbandand wife got into a fight?
The two of them wouldtear the house down.
Then how about the 13th Prince, Baek Ah?
He is Songak's best looking man.
She will be the envy ofall the girls in Goryeo.
She might be stoned to deathby them all. I don't think so.
The 4th Prince.
I don't know about the others.
However, they once learnedmartial arts together
so there must be affection there.
One was busy killing bears andthe other was busy killing wolves.
They have never even met before.
If you don't like any of them,then what shall we do?
Ah... the 8th Prince.
He should remarry, but his dispositionis so different from Lady Soon Deok.
Hey! You should count properly.Why are you skipping over people?
Look... you forgot one.
What?
Oh, do you really mean it?
Soo, I have something for you.See me later.
Yes.
His Majesty, the king, is entering.
Hello, Your Majesty.
You've all been working hard.
Especially you, 4th Prince.
You relieved us from the droughtand I want to reward you.
Is there anything you want?
I thought of giving you Songak landto build a home and some farmland.
Thank you, Your Majesty, but there issomething I want more than land.
All right, tell me.
Please give me Damiwon'sCourt Lady Hae Soo.
What?
All right.
I suppose it would be goodto keep her close by to help you.
In recognition of your efforts
Damiwon's Hae Soo will promotedto Senior Court Lady.
From now on, you mustactively assist the 4th Prince.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I will accept your command.
To celebrate the rain,we will have a prince's marriage.
We will set a date soon.
It will be the Grand General'sdaughter, Soon Deok
and the 10th Prince, Eun,who will be getting married.
Eun, you are getting married!Congratulations.
I do not want to get married.
Are you shy?
You should have in-laws anddo your part as a royal family member.
There's still our fourth brother,and our eighth brother is single again.
I'm still very young.
And that Park girl...
I just don't like it!I refuse... I refuse to get married.
Your Majesty, please withdraw your words.
I really do not want this.
If you insist on this marriage...
I would rather die.
Instead than do what I ask,you would rather die?
You would rather dishonoryour father and die instead?
Your Majesty, he must be so excitedthat he does not know what he is saying.
Eun, go on and thank the king.  Go on.
Thank you for your great benevolence.
Eun, women are only differenton the first night.
After that, all women are the same.
I even get the names of my firstand second wife confused sometimes.
I do not want to live like you.
Oh, wait!
It's better not to see.
I feel down so I want to see.
I think it's better not to.
Move.
Go! You got it!
Great soldier, great soldier,great soldier!
Eun, Eun.
She's really amazing.
Sister-in-law can beat any man.
She really is a great soldier.
Eun, I envy you.
She's a great soldier... a soldier.
I'm marrying a great soldier.
Great soldier, great soldier,great soldier!
A great soldier?
Great soldier, great soldier,great soldier, great soldier!
I was only practicing a sword dance.
There's no need to be afraid.I won't hurt you.
Here are some treats.
- Me too.- Me too!
Eat it slowly.
- Yes.- Share.
- Get going.- Thank you.
I saw you before, right?
From Hubaekje?
You should pay forthe drawings you ripped.
If you have nothing to give me,you could show me your sword dance.
I saw you before, right?
That money insect.
Money insect?
Drawings and instruments.
You work hard to please the nobles.
You're diligent.
You came because of my music, right?
Anyone in Songak who dances can't helpbut move once my music starts.
Let me see you dance.
You never know.I might play my great music.
I don't dance for strange men.
You're very picky.
Then, we can introduce ourselves.
I'm Baek Ah. How about you?
Baek Ah?
If you are Baek Ah,I am one of your attendants.
You don't have any honestyin you at all.
It's a waste of your talents,so don't live that way.
I really am Baek Ah.
Ah, you must not know becauseyou haven't been in Songak very long.
I'm the 13th...
She disappeared again.
This thing... it's unique like its owner.
She called me an insect.
I shouldn't live my life this way?
I've only met you twice,but you are so nosy about my life.
Well...
I guess it's for the bracelet you got me.
Or to celebrate me leaving the palace.
Myung Hee said that youalways had many worries.
She said I should make you thatso that you could sleep well.
Thank you.
I have something for you too.
It's a book.
I'll study very hard.
Look at it closely.
I know this.
I used to do this with my friends.
Did you draw this yourself?
Yes.
Wow.
Eun is getting married.
So, this time around...
a court lady will not be releasedto celebrate the rain.
I'm sure we will get another chance.
I am Court Lady Oh's right hand woman.
I was actually worried abouthow she'd get by without me.
I got promoted too.
I do not know whenanother chance will come.
If you are willing to wait, Your Highness
I can wait.
You know, I think I'veseen this somewhere.
I didn't want to say that I was worried.
That's why I asked you to wait.
Because I felt likesomething would go wrong.
When it snows again...let's walk here.
Just the two of us.
I will wait.
I... love you.
The king prefers wild plant teasover leaf teas.
You need to pay attention to details.
He's had headaches andhis eyesight is not good.
He eats cassia seeds andChinese matrimony vine fruit often.
He often gets thirstyand wakes up in the night.
It is good to give himherbal medicine for that.
Yes, Court Lady Oh.
Be careful of Prince Wang So.
What?
You tried to care for him andnow he learned how to care from you.
If you cannot give him your whole heart,you need to make that clear.
What if...I can change that person's life?
Should I still turn my back on him?
Before I came into the palace,I gave my heart to a man.
He was an unknown commander whowould pick flowers and herbs with me.
I thought he would forget his ambitionsand live a normal life with me.
In the end, he rose to a placewhere I couldn't dare to touch him.
Do you understand?
People do not change for others.
So you need to throw out the beliefthat you can change a person.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
You're Hae Soo, aren't you?We must go to the 10th Prince now.
What?
You're the only one who canget through to the prince.
I'm afraid something might happen to him.
You have to go to him.
I don't know what this is about,but I shouldn't get involved.
You can even be his second wife!
As long as you serve the prince well...
I am fine with it.
I will speak to the kingand my father about it.
Should I really do this?
Eun will die if he does not go.
Do it if you want to save his life.
Wait!
It's me, Hae Soo.
Open the door now.
You shouldn't be doing this. Go now.
Open this door now!
I won't ever speak to you againif you don't open it.
Does it change anything to get drunk?
If you get drunk,does that mean you don't have to marry?
You do not know I feel.
You like me, but now you mustmarry someone you don't like.
You knew? But why...
Then... then Soo...
Will you be my second wife?
The king and my brothers have many wives.
It is not a bad thing.
Even if you are not the first wife,I will only be good to you.
- So, Soo--- No.
I cannot live that way.
I can't share my husbandwith several women.
I don't want to grow old whilewaiting for him to come to me.
Liar.
Even if I had asked youto be my first wife
you would have said no.
I'm stupid. I know that.
While my brothers finish reading 10 books
I only manage to finish one.
Even when my father speaksor the teacher instructs us...
I never understand right away.
I have always been stupid.
That is probably why you don't like me.
I was happiest while I was with you,Your Highness.
You laugh when you're happyand you know to cry when you're sad.
So I never felt anxious with you,Your Highness.
I was able to laugh, cry,and get angry to my heart's content.
I do not want that kind of consolation.
You are a mean girl.
I knew from the beginning.
You would never become mine.
If I said that I was sorry,that would be truly mean, right?
So...
I am not going to apologize.
Did you...
ever even like me?
I still like you very much now.
Please be happy.
Oh, Eun! Grab him!
There's no need for that.
I will go there on my own.
Aren't we getting married?
We have to hurry! We'll be late.
I have prepared five rolls of finecloth and fabric for you, Sister-in-law.
Please make my brother happywith some good clothes.
These are pearls.I hope you are blessed with children.
Use this bronze mirror andlive a pure married life, Eun.
This is silver, Eun.
"Hyun Hyun Yeok Saek."
It means that the kindness of heartis what's important in a marriage
not the appearance.
Therefore, all of this is an added bonus.
I will use them all well.
Our 10th brother has married well.
That cold girl. Is she that happy?
If she smiles any wider,her mouth will tear apart.
I have sent a tree that blooms flowersand bears fruits to your home.
You can enjoy its shade in thesummer and enjoy its fruit in the fall.
Once it grows leaves,I will invite you all over.
It would be perfect towrestle in the shade.
Why would you wrestle a bride?
You want to lose to me again?
You should do it! Wrestle! Try it.
Soo!
Are you all right? Soo!
Be careful of Prince Wang So.
Avoid him.
You cannot try to stop him.If you do...
You will all die if you do.
Look at me. Look at me, Soo.
What are you talking about?What do you mean we'll die?
I want to leave this place.
I want to go far away from the palace,wherever that is.
All right, let's do that.
I'll do that for you.
Don't worry, Soo. Calm down.
You'll  be all right, Soo.
The reason I asked to see you twowas to assign new tasks to you.
3rd Prince Yo,I need you to leave Songak.
Visit every region andinspect the grain storehouses.
There are many of the storehouses.
I know there are many thievesthat are attacking them.
Last year, the general in charge ofthe storehouses came back dead.
That is why I am sending you.
A prince must step forwardin order for things to change.
Keep your group small.
I will accept your command.
Your Majesty, what about the militarysupplies the 3rd Prince was in charge of?
I will put 4th Prince So in charge of it.
I accept your orders, Your Majesty.
Is the king throwing me away?
What? I doubt that.
He would assign a hard taskto a person he trusts more.
You said somethingwhen you gave my seat to So.
Because of a father's favoritism,two sons are tearing each other apart.
Is this the heavens' will, as well?
You've had greed for what belongs tothe Crown Prince since you were young.
Now you must findyour place in the world.
Then keep your eye on me.
Watch and see wheremy place ends up being.
We only want to have a family meal.Why is it so surprising?
Isn't that right, Mother?
How nice it is to see your bare face.
You now have the king's trust.I am proud of you.
I have waited so longfor a day like this.
Let's forget the past.
Let us eat. Eat.
This is my first timeeating with you, So.
I was already in Shinjuwhen you were born.
We should forget the past mistakesand see each other often as brothers.
Yes, Yo.
You liked meat very muchwhen you were young.
I still like it very much.
Eat up.
You are taking on Yo's job.You have much to learn.
I will have to leave Songak.
It is best to learnfrom the Crown Prince.
I will do that.
Then you'll have many opportunitiesto see the Crown Prince.
There will be times when itwill be just the two of you.
What?
Of course.
There was something you wanted from me.
Kill the Crown Prince.
It wouldn't be the first timeyou've killed someone for me.
Will you do it?
Mother, you shouldn't saysuch things, even as a joke.
Has there been a king who hasn't killedhis brothers after rising to the throne?
If I do not become the king,we are all dead.
We have to make a move.
The Crown Prince is not like that.He would not kill his brothers.
Is that what you really want?
I want it.
Then... I will do it.
After I do...
I will sit on the throne.
What?
You want a son of yours to become king.
It shouldn't matter if it is me.
Once I am on the throne...I will not harm Yo or Jung.
Don't act like you're so great.
If I had performed the rain ritual,I would be the one who brought rain.
You think you can eye the throneover something like that?
I have the heavens' will.
You have nothing except your in-laws.
The Crown Prince has lowly in-laws.
So, do you agree thathe should be removed?
Your brother is blessedby the heavens to become king.
Who do you think you are dealing with?
You are all makingsuch a fuss over a joke.
I keep getting other ideas in my head.
King?
That seat that everyone wants so much,what if I happened to take it?
You think you can do anythingbecause of a few brush strokes.
Do you really thinkyou've become something?
You were chosen for the rain ritual.
They felt that it'd be all rightfor you to be beaten to death
instead of the Crown Prince.
You were a shield for any arrows ormisfortune that would've come his way.
You had no idea that your fatherhad manipulated you.
I was not manipulated.
I knew and crawled into that seat.
The food I ate here was not so bad.
Still, you should just eatwith your family.
Do not call me in here again.
As I thought, it is too difficultto reconcile with him.
We will need to cut ties.
You are all too much.
You ask him to murder a personat a family dinner?
If you were going to raise us as enemies
why did you give birth to us, Mother?
What is he saying...
Jung!
How foolish.
What were you expecting?
Be careful of Wang So?
You cannot try to stop him...
Be careful of Wang So.
You cannot try to stop him.
Soo.
Please let me go.
Just for a moment.
Stay with me.
I need to rest.
I don't want to!
I'm afraid of you, Your Highness.
You said you were not afraid of me.
I thought I could change things.
I was wrong.
You will ruin everyone in the end!
Go. You're better off far away!
Not you too!
Don't push me away.
Don't tell me leave.
Don't tell me that I bring misfortuneand that I'm an animal.
At the very least,you can't do that to me.
You are... my person.
I am not your person, Your Highness.
You are my person.
You belong to me. You are mine!
Without my permission,you cannot leave me.
You cannot die either.
You are completely my person.
KoreanDramaX.com
[Scarlet Heart: Ryeo]
I'm going to ask the kingto allow me to marry Hae Soo.
I will change my goal starting now.
I will no longer be adaughter or sister of a king.
I will be like a god above the king.
Neither you nor I will be safe anymore.
Who are you after? Think carefully.
Who will it be the most fun to target?
I know we may be married,but I cannot accept you as my wife.
Try to stop the Crown Prince'spoisoning if you can.
A court lady who brings the tea will dieand the Crown Prince will be gone.
Things will not go as you plan.