(The following program may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 10)
This is the law?
How can such a law exist?
Stop being so clingy.
Geum Bi made her decision.
Geum Bi.
What's going on? Why did you do that?
You didn't mean to say that, right?
Get off of her.
Get away from my daughter.
Give me a week.
I'll come and pick her up tomorrow at two.
Pack only what she really needs and wait.
She said she wants a week of time.
One night will be more than enough.
- Are you... - Dad.
Ms. Yoo Joo Young?
Please come in.
Yes.
I got it.
I've seen many cases of people who gave up...
after exercising their parental rights.
She's a very good kid.
Don't make her regret her decision.
All right. Mind your own business.
What's wrong with you?
Talk to me.
Do you not want to live with me?
I do. Until the moment I die.
Then why?
Don't you know what kind of person that woman is?
What have you done to my daughter?
Gosh.
I need to teach you a lesson.
You jerk. Come back here.
Geum Bi.
I feel like if I leave that lady alone,
she'll die before I do.
I can't live with all three of you...
under the same roof.
To be honest,
I'm skeptical about your credentials as a parent.
But that girl said,
"I wish that lady would have a good life, too."
"In order to do that,"
"I think I need to be by her side."
Wear those shoes when you go.
I don't want to ruin them.
They're just shoes.
I could buy you thousands of them.
You can wear them whenever you want.
Geum Bi.
Can't you just...
live with your dad and me?
I wish everything would stay like this.
What?
I wish nothing would change...
when I come back here.
You will come back, right?
But you can't call me.
Why not?
I need to be by that lady's side.
If I hear you or Dad's voice,
I'll want to come back right away.
That's nonsense.
Even if we don't see or hear from each other,
you won't forget me, will you?
When that lady can start being on her own,
I will come back.
But what if I run out of time?
I don't have much time.
Stop talking nonsense.
If you don't come back, I'll come for you.
I'll leave it like this...
until you come back.
Nothing will change.
Let's do that thing.
What?
That thing.
The hand thing.
I told you.
This isn't as easy as robbing a piggy bank.
You don't have to push me.
I'll give it to you in time.
- Unbelievable. - Pardon me?
Who are you to say that you'll give it to me or not?
The procedures are...
What procedures?
I'll take care of it as soon as possible.
It's not like you're marrying her off. That's too much.
You should've packed just the necessities.
I wrote down things like...
her favorite food and her doctor's number.
She has to adapt,
so don't call her.
You, too.
Let's go.
Goodbye, then.
Bye.
One hour!
If you call, I'll be there in an hour wherever you are!
Okay, Geum Bi?
Geum Bi...
One, eight, one, two.
They're like card pairs. Easy, right?
You must like gambling.
Hwi Cheol taught me a long time ago.
He only taught me bad things.
Try it yourself.
I don't need to do it.
You said it's 1, 8, 1, 2.
You know too much for a kid. How will you turn out?
How did you want to turn out when you were a kid?
Me?
I wanted to be a model.
Hey, don't give me that look.
I couldn't be a model because I got pregnant with you.
One, eight, one, two.
What?
I can clean up.
What's wrong with you?
Is this a house for humans?
Of course, it is.
I'm not a dog.
This smells.
My goodness. It doesn't smell.
You're too sensitive.
I can't smell anything.
I can wear it for a few more days.
What?
Those things are bad for you.
What do you want me to do?
Fine. I'll wash them.
You didn't have any detergent.
My gosh. When did you notice that?
I'm thirsty.
I'll get some detergent.
How did she manage to live?
Did you drink beer?
Water.
Did I drink them all?
That can't be.
The sink drank it all.
What?
I threw them out.
Threw what out?
I drained them out in the sink.
Why would you do that?
- Promise me. - What?
Those were expensive beers.
It's such a waste!
Promise me that you won't drink.
Hey. You can never trust anyone...
who promises to quit smoking and drinking.
You have no idea.
I guess you missed this one.
Don't you dare drink.
Then what?
I'm telling on you to child welfare...
that you're an alcoholic.
What? That little brat.
Don't you dare open that bottle.
Don't you dare call them.
What are you going to do?
I'll chug this down.
Do you know what will happen?
That little brat.
My gosh, you are tenacious.
- I'm calling... - Hey, fine.
I won't drink.
This is apartment 307 in Haru Studio Apartments.
I'd like to order a fried chicken.
Give us a fat one, please.
Hey! That little brat.
This is such a waste.
Darn it.
- That tickles. - My goodness.
Wait, come on. That really tickles.
Hwi Cheol.
Now that we got to live together,
let's get along well, okay?
Dig in. Do you want the drumstick?
No. I'll have the wings.
Do you think we'll enjoy each other's company, Miss?
How can you call me, "Miss"?
Should I call you by your name, then?
That's how you addressed that woman.
Forget it.
If you keep calling me that...
Miss.
Hey!
If you want me to call you "Mom",
sign this.
What's this?
(Contract)
"Quit drinking", "Be home by 10pm"?
This is ridiculous.
Are you intending on starting a fight at a club again?
That was...
"Take a picture together once a day"?
You're so childish.
"Keep a diary"?
What on earth is this?
They don't have to be long.
But you have to write one every day.
"Cook a meal once a week"?
Am I allowed to cook instant meals?
Fine.
I'll drink twice a week.
I'm not doing the curfew.
Then I'll sign it.
If you want to do this,
just do as I tell you to.
Who says I want to do this?
You said you don't want me to call you "Miss".
Fine. Have it your way.
We're evil daughter and evil mom.
It doesn't matter what you call me.
Who's the evil dad, then?
Why did you give birth to me?
Are you going to sleep over there?
I've always slept alone.
I can't sleep when there's someone beside me.
Where are you going?
I'm going to get some air.
Geum Bi asked you a question.
You have to tell her.
The memory you've been trying to erase...
The reason why you blamed yourself...
and drank away your pain...
What do you want to be when you grow up, Geum Bi?
A super model, painter,
and a forestry researcher.
You want to be all that?
Yes.
I'm sure you can be...
whatever you want to be, Geum Bi.
First, you need to eat balanced meals.
Here.
Let's give it a try.
Good girl.
I really don't want to get involved in this.
Don't tell anyone that I gave you this.
This was a hard one,
so I'll have to charge you 20,000 dollars.
I was right.
A man named Gong Gil Ho was at the site...
when Hwi Cheol's dad died.
I'm not going to keep all 20,000 dollars to myself.
I'll have to give half of it to my informant.
He used to be a detective.
At first, he wasn't willing to give up the information.
He must not be doing so well.
He started talking when I promised him 10,000 dollars.
I'll cut you open if this turns out to be a lie.
I'm not the one who should be threatened.
Think carefully.
I'll do whatever it takes to collect that money.
(Karaoke Bar)
You idiot.
How could you not recognize him after what happened?
How could you be so stupid, Gong Gil Ho?
Gosh.
You wench. You almost gave me a heart attack.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean what am I doing here?
Are you...
hiding something from me?
- Jae Gyung. - Tell me.
Don't...
look for me.
That little... Stop right there.
You'll never outrun me.
You're a dead man.
Door is opened.
Door is locked.
Geum Bi.
Gosh, you reek of alcohol.
Move over.
I have a headache.
Hwi Cheol.
Father.
Is Jun Hee your only child?
The death of children is equally painful...
whether it's one or all that die.
It's been 15 years now, Father.
I lost her forever.
How could I forget her in just 15 years?
She's my daughter.
Please, Father.
I'm sorry.
It seems like...
no one can fill her spot.
I don't think...
I can fill her spot, either.
However,
thanks to such a blessed child,
I got the courage to face that void, Father.
Next week is open class. Do you remember?
- Yes. - Yes.
Write down the date and time on your agenda.
Make sure you show it to your parents.
- Okay. - Okay.
My stomach hurts.
She's going to sleep until next Thanksgiving.
Will you get up?
Why?
I need food.
Food?
Darn it.
The rice will begin to cook now.
There's an open class.
Really?
I hope it goes well.
Don't you know what it is?
Oh, that thing.
What about it?
It's Friday at 1pm.
Can I be your mom from next week?
We don't even have any soup or stew.
Are we eating rice by itself?
No way.
Ta-da.
Do you know how good this is?
You'll be surprised.
- Look, it's a fire. - Call 911.
- Is that a fire? - Doesn't a kid live there?
- Oh, no. - You're right.
They should come out.
Hello? Is this the 911?
- Hurry up. - There's a fire.
Yoo Joo Young!
Joo Young, get up.
- What's going on? - Are you okay?
Geum Bi, get up.
I'll take her.
Let's go.
Did you set this fire?
Why are you stalking and bullying me?
Let's go.
(Emergency Medical Services)
Let's check other places, too.
Okay.
Hey.
You pretended to sleep to kill me, didn't you?
That's nonsense. That would kill me, too.
My gosh. You fell asleep, that's why.
I thought I turned off the gas.
- That's weird. - You didn't.
Who did that, then? A ghost?
You should've turned it off.
You fell asleep, too.
Don't be so proud.
I would've lived even if it wasn't for you.
Don't be mistaken.
I kept you alive because you owe me.
What did the lawyer say?
When will he give you the money?
I thought you were a bad guy.
I am.
The kitchen is all burnt. What will I do?
My landlord will go crazy.
My gosh, whatever.
I'll eat some eggs.
What's that scar on your stomach?
Did you see that? You have good eyes.
Good places don't even leave scars.
This is all because I went to a cheap hospital.
I can't even wear cropped shirts.
Why?
Do you know where babies come from?
Well, kind of.
I don't know what it means, though.
Sometimes, babies come out...
from a different place than other babies.
Like you.
Is that how I was born?
It hurt really badly.
Is that why you couldn't become a model?
Forget about that. How good could a model be??
What did you want to be, then?
A celebrity.
What do you want to be?
I'm not sure.
What?
I'm not sure what I should want to be.
You don't have to be something.
You can just live happily day by day.
- Day by day? - Yes.
People always worry and live in the future.
But one day, there will be no tomorrow.
What if you regret your choices then?
What's important is to be happy here and now.
Do you understand?
Do you like where you are, then?
My gosh. No way.
I burnt down my house...
and now, I'm peeling eggs here.
Did you write your diary?
Hey, I didn't sign that paper yet.
Come on, write it. And we'll take a picture.
Hey, are we taking it here?
How can we take a picture here?
My goodness.
Hey, wait.
Say cheese.
You're home.
You're still up.
I couldn't sleep.
Everything's so strange.
I lived here for over 30 years,
but it's like a stranger's house.
I was making dumplings to eat tomorrow.
Do you want to taste one?
It's...
so hard for me to come back to this house.
Hwi Cheol.
I can't live like the way I did before.
But I can't continue to live like this.
It's the same for me. But...
What should I do now?
Geum Bi said...
she will come back.
Geum Bi...
doesn't have much time.
We shouldn't be like this.
Did you forget what she said?
She said she wanted nothing to change.
What will you do about this?
I knew this would happen!
This was our last packet of noodles!
I have no money to buy more!
I told you it would rain.
It's raining,
Geum Bi.
If you're going to do it, do it properly.
Properly how?
You don't just slap it on your face.
It just goes on your face. What's the difference?
No, no, no, no.
Come here.
Let me see.
From the center of your face...
and out towards your ears.
Massage it in with a circular motion.
Make sure it goes on evenly, okay?
Next, it has to be absorbed.
I don't do this for just anyone.
Turn around.
This is very important.
Your skin has to absorb it all.
There's no point if it doesn't.
What time's your open class?
Friday at 1pm.
Today, we'll experiment on observing various rocks...
that form a stratum.
- Okay. - Okay.
Are you all wearing your goggles and gloves?
- Yes. - Yes.
You need to be...
extra careful with diluted hydrochloric acid.
- Okay. - Okay.
Hey.
Give me that.
What? Okay.
(Danger)
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
I'm okay.
I don't think you're okay.
Here you go, Sil La.
Is that medicine from the hospital?
It's an extra-super, ultra vitamin for children.
It's my secret.
If you ever need my help,
tell me anytime.
Okay.
Do I have to wear this for an open class?
That's silly.
Hello?
I don't know what you've heard,
but there's nothing for you.
I know there is.
That's why I called.
What do you know?
I lost all my money on stocks.
I lost the key money to my apartment...
and I haven't paid rent in months.
Then find yourself a rich guy instead of calling me.
Half is too much.
Give me a third.
Then I won't tell about the drug trafficking.
I'm going to move to China.
If the police find out,
do you think they'll let you go?
How can they let me go?
I'll have to drag you down with me.
I will do what I say.
I have nothing to fear.
I didn't do this alone.
Some of my friends know your kid's school.
Hey!
Why do you look so surprised?
I can even guess...
who her dad is.
You witch.
Don't test me.
We drank so much together over the years.
Do you remember what you said when you were drunk?
What?
All you have against me...
are my drunk ramblings?
I had a feeling you wouldn't take me seriously.
That's why I'm going to send my friends over.
To tell your kid an old story.
What?
You didn't tell Young Ji, did you?
What you did to the little girl.
This is the least I can do to make sure...
you take me seriously and cooperate.
(Department Store Lady)
(Joo Young)
What do you want?
What?
What do you...
Hey.
(We'll be there for you!)
(Buil Elementary School)
Excuse me.
Do you know her?
- No. - No.
What do you want?
Did the cocktail waitress send you?
Let's not upset the kids.
Move along.
I won't say it again.
Today,
we invited your parents to an open class.
- Yes. - Yes.
I hope it'll be a special day for you all.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's begin the class.
Open your books to page 89.
Did you bring what I told you to?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Well done. - Let's go.
Let's go, Sil La.
- Can we talk, Miss? - Sure.
Sil La, wait for me outside.
You almost had an accident during an experiment.
I bet you didn't know.
What kind of accident?
I think it should be taken seriously.
You know Geum Bi.
This is her medicine.
I do feel sorry for her,
but she could cause an accident.
I want you to do something for the safety of the kids.
What are you talking about?
Geum Bi has...
What? Did she do something wrong?
What's all this?
Until Geum Bi comes back,
I won't change like a pair of enchanted underwear.
Hwi Cheol, your shoes are really cute.
Newbie, come and hold this for me.
You're getting better at this.
Do you need money? I heard you're working two jobs.
My kid's sick.
You can't do anything else when your kid's sick.
That's why I keep working, so I have no time to think.
I need to earn a lot of money, too.
If you don't mind doing some rough work,
I can set you up with a job that pays a bit better.
- Do it. - Should I?
Just a moment.
Hold on.
(Geum Bi's Teacher)
Hello.
What?
Sure. I will.
(Cha Chi Soo)
I don't know what you want,
but I'm in no mood to talk.
Leave me alone. I'm hanging up.
Have you talked to Geum Bi?
What? Geum Bi?
Why do you care about her?
She's inside the tent.
Isn't it yours?
Joo Young asked me to keep an eye on her.
You jerk. If you so much as touch her...
If you hurt her, I will crush you.
Joo Young disappeared. Find her.
She might do something crazy so find her.
You lived with her for a few months.
Try to remember her usual hangouts.
That witch.
Where are you going?
Hey!
- Hey. - What are you doing here?
I don't know. I don't know anything.
I know you know something.
Was Joo Young here?
I don't know. I didn't do anything.
What do you know?
Nothing.
Tell me everything you know.
Exactly what happened and at what time.
Tell me everything before I beat you up.
Now!
What a mess.
Are you Catholic?
No.
Then why do you keep coming here?
Are temples only for Buddhists?
If you see in movies,
the dirt poor sometimes gets a windfall.
Do you believe in miracles?
What a stupid thing to believe in.
I just like the atmosphere here.
It feels like my soul's taking a shower.
I like the high ceilings, too.
- Don't you? - Is this a cafe?
It's not a place to come for good atmosphere.
I go to cafes and bars with different people.
It must be great to have many boyfriends.
You're the first.
What do you mean first?
I'm just one of them.
You're the first I brought to the cathedral.
Really?
It's my first, too.
- How so? - You're the first girl...
I didn't hold hands for over a month.
Really?
Give me your hand.
What for?
Come on.
It won't fall off, will it?
You're like a cunning wolf.
Here you go.
Dad.
What, Geum Bi?
You're my dad, aren't you?
I am.
But...
Mom keeps saying you aren't.
She doesn't know better.
I know.
I love you so much.
I can't live without you.
Wait just a bit longer.
I'll be back soon.
I can wait until your enchanted underwear...
becomes old and ragged.
What should I do about Mom?
Just give her some time.
I don't have much time.
Don't worry. She won't be too late.