[EPISODE 11]
Do whatever you want.
You can take Geum Bi back.
You can laugh at how pathetic I am.
You can do whatever you want.
Did you take her
so you could act this way?
You don't know anything.
Leave me alone and get lost.
Wasn't it enough that
you almost killed her once?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Geum Bi stepped up to try to save you.
She felt like you would die before her
if she left things the way they were.
She couldn't stand by and watch.
What's the point of
saving someone like me?
Because you want to change!
You want to be different.
If you disappear now and never look back
I can live with Geum Bi until she dies.
But I'm holding on to you now!
It was all my fault.
You don't need to change.
You just need to go back
to the way you used to be.
What?
When you got pregnant with Geum Bi,
you came to look for me, right?
I pretended not to know.
I knew you were there, looking at me.
But I laughed it up with other girls
and I pretended not to know.
Did you?
Still, you had Geum Bi.
You knew how hard it would be,
yet you still gave birth to her.
You're that kind of woman.
Yeah, if I had embraced you back then
Geum Bi would've
grown up well by my side.
It wasn't you.
It was me who nearly killed Geum Bi.
You didn't do anything wrong.
So return to Geum Bi now.
If you disappear again like this...
Geum Bi would be so pitiful.
What's with you?
She doesn't have a drop of your blood.
You're not her dad or anything.
So why have you put
your life on the line for her?
Even while we're here like this...
Geum Bi is running out of time.
Geum Bi...
She's using up pieces of her
precious time to find you.
I can't go.
Geum Bi won't even see me as her mom...
She won't even see me as a human being.
Geum Bi doesn't know anything.
Chi Soo stopped
those men from telling her.
Why do you keep following me?
Your mom owes me something.
And?
She ran off and I can't find her.
Of course you can't find her.
That's her specialty.
She showed up this time after nine years.
Next time, I don't know
how long she'll take.
Where are you going?
Wherever.
Are you going to live here then?
Do you have money?
No, I don't.
What will you do then?
You said my mom owes you money.
- So?
- You can add this to that.
Hey.
Why aren't you eating?
You're probably hungry.
Put Geum Bi on the phone.
[MO HWI CHUL]
She doesn't want to talk.
What about Joo Young?
Hold on.
Tell him I'll be there soon.
She'll be home soon.
Geum Bi is okay, isn't she?
Just worry about yourself.
I'll going to end you...
Don't even think about
hiding behind a child.
It won't work.
Your mom will be coming.
- How did you know?
- Know what?
You knew that my mom
was alive and my dad...
You knew he wasn't my dad.
You can find out if you investigate.
Then do you know who my real father is?
You can ask your mom that stuff.
Yeah, I'm sure you thought she was mine.
I couldn't bring myself
to get an abortion.
It was the baby of someone I liked.
I figured I could handle it
once I had the baby.
I wasn't fit to take care a baby.
Making a living was a secondary concern.
Whenever the baby would cry
I felt like I was going insane
and I couldn't deal with it.
I lost my mind a few times.
I cut my wrists.
I started to think I might
really kill the baby.
So, I left Geum Bi with Young Ji.
I asked for a ticket to
any flight going far away.
By the way, who is it?
Geum Bi's real dad.
Why are you suddenly asking that?
I was just curious. That's all.
What's the point?
Yeah, why is that important?
Geum Bi is my daughter.
You've changed a little.
I don't really know why,
but I can't live like I did before.
You should go home.
What?
She seems like a good woman.
What are you saying?
Don't pretend you don't know, punk.
Gosh, that rotten woman.
You still have 10,000 years to go
before you become a real human being.
Do you really not know?
What?
What I asked you earlier.
Your mom is coming.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
If you glare at me like that, are lasers
going to come out of your eyes?
Where did you go?
- Did you eat?
- Why are you changing the subject?
I asked if you ate.
Where did you go?
You little brat.
You sure do talk a lot.
Where are you going?
Aren't you going home?
I'm going to go eat.
What a pain. Why didn't you eat earlier?
- Be quiet.
- I already ate.
Just eat again.
Why did I have to leave the house?
I'm going to freeze out here,
at this rate.
What's with you?
I'm back.
What a joke.
"I'll be back."
You have to say that before leaving
in order to say "I'm back."
Well, what happened was...
You just walked out, you punk!
Kang Hee, did you drink, by any chance?
Why? Am I not allowed to drink?
Of course, you're allowed.
Why wouldn't you be?
I thought you were back.
Why aren't you coming inside?
Lock the door!
Hey! Sit.
Right there.
You punk... if you run away one more time
I'll twist your neck
around 360 degrees. No...
I'll twist it around 720 degrees.
Yes, you should.
Drink!
I'm back.
Are you really planning on
doing that to Hwi Chul?
You're going to instigate him to avenge
his dad's murder and end his own life?
You have no idea how
scary Jong Won is, do you?
If he finds out what you're up to,
you won't be safe either.
Don't you feel pity for Hwi Chul at all?
He's been living in the pits
as an orphan his whole life.
He's just barely starting
to form a life for himself.
That's why I'm ending him now.
What?
He ended things for my family,
so how can he live a normal life?
You harassed him endlessly for years.
Why does that matter?
He hasn't paid for it.
You crazy bastard!
Don't stay by Hwi Chul's side
unless you want to be crushed too.
Don't do it. Don't.
You can't do it. Don't do it!
You can't do it.
Ouch. That stings.
What is it?
What happened to your mouth?
Forget it. Mind your business.
It was Chi Soo, wasn't it?
Just don't get involved
and don't do anything.
What did you threaten Gong Gil Ho with?
You rotten punk.
Your elder is talking to you.
That punk is actually
really good looking.
Do you not want to live?
Why wouldn't I want to live?
The world is so much fun.
I really hate inequality.
Is that so?
I feel the same way.
Hey! That hurts.
Hey, you wench.
If they can inject stem cells,
ask for "fear cells" and inject them.
You have no fear, girl.
Gosh, that bastard is all about equality.
He doesn't differentiate
between men and women.
He has decent looks and all.
What's going on, anyway?
What does he have on you
that you're so afraid of him?
Shut your mouth.
The medicine keeps
dripping into your mouth.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[KEEP YOUR PROMISES
OR CONSUME FISH OIL EXTRACT.]
I can't trust you. I just can't.
I knew you would be like this.
Can you trust me now?
How many more bottles do you have hidden?
Gosh, you're suspicious for a little kid.
Have you been lied to all your life?
I've been lied to a lot all this time.
Are you close to Mister Chi Soo?
Chi Soo?
No way. He's so gloomy.
I suppose he's a pitiful guy
if you think about it.
How long have you known him?
I guess it's been over 10 years already.
How awful.
When did I get so old?
10 years?
How did the two of you meet?
What do you mean, how?
I met one person who introduced me
to another person, then another person.
I met him through a bunch of people.
How did you get mixed up with him?
I don't know!
It's been so long, I don't remember.
Aren't you going school though?
Do I really have to go?
What are you saying?
Don't you want to go?
It's not that.
I don't feel good
about saying this either.
Shil La's mother.
I'm just worried that
something might happen.
I looked into her illness.
Her personality will change.
She can become violent, as well.
What should we do?
Geum Bi is not that bad.
Also, it will be vacation time soon.
An accident could occur
even tomorrow, Teacher Kang.
I told you that she almost broke
the bottle of hydrochloric acid.
It's watered down.
It would only cause the skin
to turn slightly red...
Teacher Kang Min Ah,
why are you being so frustrating?
If there is an accident,
it could cause trouble for you, too.
If something were to happen,
you could be disciplined for it.
They can discipline me if they want.
I am a teacher.
Do you know what it means to be
an elementary school teacher?
Why are you going so overboard?
At school, I am the children's mother.
What mother in this world would
throw out her child because she is ill?
I won't let Geum Bi go!
Jae Ha, why don't you
wait outside for a bit?
No.
Oh my, I thought you
were a nice and polite boy.
I am not polite.
I'm going to attend school with Geum Bi.
If you don't let Geum Bi come
to school, I won't come either.
Geum Bi.
Jae Ha.
It's okay.
I told you when we went to the beach.
I have to go.
40 multiplied by 50 equals?
- 2,000!
- 2,000.
2,000 divided by 4 equals?
- 500!
- 500.
500 divided by 11.
The remainder is?
No one has solved it yet?
Then the remainder is?
It's eight!
Good job.
I feel like my teaching has paid off.
Thank you.
Then, is there really no other way?
There is nothing in the world
where there's no other way.
But it's pretty much
like there's no other way.
There is a clinical trial protocol
program being conducted abroad.
What is it?
I guess they're using a different drug
and administering it in a different way.
Can she get better if she tries that?
It hasn't been that effective.
The chances have depended on the patient.
The expectations depend on that.
Then there is hope.
Kang Hee.
The hope is as small
as a strand of thread.
[MO HWI CHUL,
MO GEUM BI]
Mo Geum Bi.
Kang Hee, are you busy?
Can you go somewhere with me?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Is this the right way to do it?
My mom and dad didn't
like alcohol very much.
Is today the anniversary of their death?
No, I never cared much
about those things.
I figured, they're already dead,
so why does it even matter?
Then why did you want to come,
all of a sudden?
I just... started to think of my dad.
I never thought about him much.
Then you could have come alone.
Why did you bring me?
My mom and dad could be
around here somewhere.
If they happen to be here...
If they are here?
I brought a good person with me,
so I wanted them to see her.
Did I do something useless
without even asking you first?
If Joon Hui were sick
like Geum Bi, my father...
he would never have given up.
I'm not going to
give up on Geum Bi either.
You feel the same, right?
It will be so hard, you'll want to die.
I have someone to go through that with.
Why did you ask to see me?
You said I wouldn't be able to handle it.
I did and I still feel that way.
Then what is different?
I can't be certain that I will be able to
endure it when things get extreme.
Still, I know what Geum Bi's illness is.
I know what Geum Bi's end will be like.
I've reflected on it repeatedly
and prepared myself.
You haven't.
What do I have to do?
What do I have to do from now on?
What should I do?
I don't want to fight
and pull out your hair.
I'm asking because
I don't know where to start.
First, I suppose you
need to know the facts.
Still, there must be a treatment.
There is none.
How can a doctor say that?
How can there not be, in this world?
I'm sure there's one if you look.
Medicine. There are medications.
Geum Bi's been taking them.
They are only delaying the symptoms.
It is not a cure.
Then what about surgery?
She can get surgery.
That's enough.
What do you mean?
She's going to die.
Did you come this far
without realizing that?
Should I just watch it happen
with my eyes open?
Did you try another hospital?
It could be an error.
What about going abroad?
If she goes abroad...
Are you going to be like this
in front of her?
Are you going to cry and
whine in front of Geum Bi, too?
If you can't handle it,
don't even start.
Right now, it would be best to let her
feel at ease and give her stability.
I heard there is a clinical trial.
I also heard there could be
a treatment within 10 years.
What is that about?
The effectiveness of it
hasn't been proven.
There could be adverse side effects,
and the costs are very high.
Who told you to worry about money?
I'll give you what you need.
Just fix her.
The treatment method is only
a chance, and it's hypothetical.
I hope they succeed more than anyone.
But I cannot tell you something
you want to hear because I wish to.
Stop saying it can't be done!
You should be trying to make her better.
You're a doctor!
Calm down and listen.
But we can try the
clinical trials, right?
What is taking so long?
It's not even real estate. It's cash.
The money in the bank won't go anywhere.
All of the inheritance is now yours,
Yoo Joo Young.
I don't know why you're in such a rush.
How can I not be?
A child's life is on the line.
What?
Are you, perhaps,
trying to keep that money from me?
You're right.
What?
Honestly, I am not satisfied
with the inheritance going to you.
I knew there was no chance.
Regarding the issue of custody
I wanted Geum Bi
to live with Mo Hwi Chul.
I just cannot trust you.
I am Geum Bi's mom.
I would never harm her.
Can I really trust you with her?
Who are you to determine
whether I'm trustworthy or not?
Just give me the money!
I'll take care of it soon.
Did Geum Bi take that?
Yes.
It was inside the tent.
Good job.
You have her hanging around the place
you ran off to when you were homeless.
Do you want to see it?
"Mo Geum Bi."
It feels completely different because
she changed that one character.
What do you think Geum Bi was thinking
when she changed her surname?
What do you think?
Through life or death,
Hwi Chul is her dad.
That's probably what she was thinking.
That makes me feel good.
When I was looking at that,
it made me think to myself...
If I were Geum Bi,
I would wonder who my real dad was.
I would've wondered that, at least once.
Even if she doesn't say it,
Geum Bi is probably curious.
Some things are better left unknown.
I think it would be good to show Geum Bi
her father's face before it's too late.
Why do you keep bringing up
this useless topic?
What's the point of bringing that up now?
Don't raise your voice.
Just help me find what Geum Bi wants.
We should do something.
How do you know
that's what Geum Bi wants?
Then who is Patzzi's dad?
Don't be like that.
Is there anything you remember?
Anything you can recall.
[GANGSTER DO JONG WON STOOD TO BENEFIT
MOST FROM DETECTIVE MO JIN BEOM'S DEATH.]
[DO JONG WON WAS SEEN IN THE VICINITY...]
[DO JONG WON]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
How did you know my number?
I asked the lady.
Why?
I had some questions to ask you.
What?
Are you close to my mom?
Why would I be close to her?
She's a mean, awful person.
Then why are you always meeting her?
When have I "always" met her?
I just meet her when
I have business to discuss.
You must have a lot of business with her.
What do you want to know?
How did you meet her 10 years ago?
What nonsense are you...
You're not possibly thinking...
Run, Geum Bi!
Hurry!
You're stabbing me
in the back. Is that it?
Who is this?
She was with him so we brought her, Boss.
You... who are you?
Don't tell him.
Stop that!
What's your name?
Shil La.
Like Goryeo Baekje Silla?
No. Shil La spelled differently.
Hong Shil La.
Oh, I see. Hong Shil La.
Is she your daughter?
Is my surname Hong?
Then what's your
relationship to this kid?
So this is where all the
bad punks were gathered.
What? You little brat.
We're your elders. Is that how
your father taught you to speak?
You ugly thing.
Wow, this is just...
It was when things were
really bad between us.
I had something for
one night with a guy.
He was shy and couldn't drink well.
He was different than the guys
I usually saw, so I was drawn to him.
He had a unique name,
so I still remember it.
I remember the school he went to.
What? Oh, you're not him.
Then do you happen to know the contact
info of the person who used this number?
I...
I was in the middle of talking.
You probably wouldn't know.
Hello?
You're an alumnus of
Myungsung University, right?
I'm looking for someone.
I'll talk to you later.
Are you related to that cop somehow?
You say I killed Detective Mo?
Talk now, you punk.
I want to leave before the sun goes down.
Everyone here has family at home.
I heard that your siblings
don't treat you like a human being
since your parents died.
You have no wife or child.
No friend in the world.
You used the money you had left
to become a loan shark.
You live a screwed up life,
taking money from people.
You lived crawling in dirt like a bug.
You haven't lived to see a good day,
and today is the end!
The end! Is that what you want?
Really?
What is the big secret that you're
keeping that stinky mouth shut?
Huh?
Tell me now, you punk!
Let the kid go and we'll talk.
I want to do that too.
Why did you do something so stupid?
The kid! Why would you bring a kid here?
She has nothing to do with this,
so let her go!
How can we just send her away?
She's seen all of our faces.
Put Chi Soo deep in the ground tonight.
- And you...
- I said she has nothing to do with this.
She looks very smart with a good memory.
That's not true.
What?
I have a disease, so I forget everything.
My memories will start to disappear
and I won't be able to move my body.
So, you don't need to worry.
What is she saying?
Are you people playing a joke here?
Hey, hey! Kid.
Hey, what's wrong? What's wrong with her?
Hey, wake up.
Hey!
Are you going to kill a child?
Why aren't you following him?
I can't have that happening here.
Put me down.
I said, put me down.
What are you doing? Hurry up and run.
Hey!
I think I can breathe now.
You... you just had a seizure.
Couldn't you tell?
I was faking it.
What could I do?
They were hitting you, Mister.
You really...
It wasn't all a lie though.
What?
They say I will get like that later on.
Once my illness gets worse,
my body will get stiff and I'll shake.
What did you call it before?
A seizure?
I'll get those.
If it gets worse than that,
I won't be able to swallow my food.
Is this a storage space?
You don't live here, do you?
I wouldn't say I live here.
It's so dark and gloomy.
I feel like a ghost might pop out.
If you are sick...
are you taking medicine?
Oh yeah. I have to take it.
By the way, how come you're not
answering the question I asked before?
What?
How did you meet my mom 10 years ago?
I just met her while
I was coming and going.
You're saying the same thing as her.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Thank you.
Please help out the poor.
Please donate to the poor.
Thank you.
I actually called you earlier.
Ah, yes. You came quickly.
Why are you looking for him anyway?
I haven't seen him in about
seven or eight years either.
I have to find him and
have him meet someone.
Please help me.
What are you people doing?
Why are destroying my house?
What are you saying?
This isn't a house.
How can you pitch a tent at a park?
Yes, I know that but...
You just can't take it down now.
Don't be ridiculous.
- Hurry up and take it down.
- Yes, sir.
Hey, seriously!
- You can't do this!
- Don't interrupt our work.
You can't remove it!
Hurry up and remove it.
- What are you doing?
- Hurry it up.
Hold this.
Hurry up and get rid of it.
Little Miss Geum Bi.
Have you still been
kissing Jae Ha lately?
What about Shil La?
Is she still jealous?
Geum Bi.
Your dad is...
Geum Bi?
What's wrong? Say something.
What is it? Are you mad again?
Who are you, Mister?
Dad!
Yeah.
Yes, Geum Bi.
What are you doing here?
Did you follow me?
No, I didn't.
I came because I missed you, Geum Bi.
You're okay, right?
Why? Did something happen?
Oh no.
By any chance, did I not recognize you?
No, that didn't happen.
It did happen.
I told you it didn't.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
No, it's okay.
Can you see Dad?
I see you.
It's okay.
Nothing happened. It's okay.
What happens if I can't recognize you?
It's okay. It doesn't matter.
Whether you recognize me or not,
it doesn't matter.
Even if the sky splits in two
or the world ends...
I am still Geum Bi's dad.
You understand, right?
Should I give you a piggyback ride?
Who are you?
Are you looking for Lawyer Ma?
He emptied his office yesterday.
What do you mean?
He emptied it and left.
He left?
He no longer has an office here.
What am I going to do?
What do I do?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[OH MY GEUM BI]
The man who killed my father
and those 15 years...
No, I was manipulated too.
What will you do if Hwi Chul tries to
get revenge for his dad's death?
Hey. Bring in Mo Hwi Chul too, okay?
If you call the police
or anyone, you're dead.
I'm trying to live properly for once!
You have to give me a chance.
What did Geum Bi ever do wrong?
[DEALING WITH FORGETTING]
Though it may not show on the outside,
I think she's extremely stressed.
Geum Bi!
I don't know where she tried to go.
There may be a
strong desire to return home.
That's how it is.