Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What?
How can you say that, you idiot?
I know I did something stupid,
but I need you to find it for me.
If I don't have that money,
Geum Bi and I are done for.
Do whatever you can to find him.
So, find him!
You have to find him
in order to get your share.
[EPISODE 12]
Wow! How many lights are there?
Why do they put up trees for Christmas?
I don't know.
I'm not really sure.
I think it's to look at pretty things.
Then we can all be happy together,
something like that.
Not fighting with each other.
How come you're always
fighting with Mister Chi Soo?
He's a bad guy.
You two say the same thing.
Why don't you two stop fighting
and get along now?
He keeps picking fights with me.
Can't you apologize first, Dad?
I can't.
It's Christmas, so can't you make
something impossible happen?
I can't make that happen.
I'll make another thing
that seems impossible happen.
I think it would be good to show Geum Bi
her father's face before it's too late.
Can you make it snow on Christmas?
What?
I'll try.
Forget it.
Since the tent is gone,
get me a Christmas tree.
Okay, I can do that much for you.
I'll get you a really big one.
Really?
Of course, I will.
Have you ever seen me lie?
I've seen you lie a lot.
Right, you have.
Anyway, I'll really get you a tree.
I'll get you one that big.
Come this way.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Did you drink?
I did.
Then go to sleep quickly.
Aren't you going to get angry?
I will get angry tomorrow.
I tried my best to be good.
Yes, try your best.
But why are there so many bad people?
Yeah, there are many bad people,
so drink tomorrow and the next day, too.
How many bottles of fish oil
are you going to have to drink?
I'm really sorry...
but can't I eat something else?
The fish oil tastes like tears.
Then eat it mixed with sugar and cream.
I'm sorry.
I really am sorry...
Wait until you wake up tomorrow.
It's 12 bottles of fish oil.
Wow! What is all this?
It's not bad, right?
It's a good tree.
You should have gone all out
if you were going to do it.
What is this? It's a bit rough.
It's because it's been 20 years.
What?
Since I put a Christmas
tree in this house.
I've never gotten one of these before.
Really?
Are these trees expensive?
Why? Are you going to buy one?
No, I was just asking.
Geum Bi would like looking at this.
It would be nice if she could
come for a day, at least.
That wouldn't be possible, right?
We can see her outside.
We can decorate a tree outside.
A tree?
We should let her enjoy her time now.
We don't know what
it will be like next year.
You punk.
You should have told Hwi Chul right away.
Why did you keep it hidden?
You don't know what you're talking about.
What if Hwi Chul had tried
to get revenge for his dad?
That's what Chi Soo wants.
Gosh, damn it.
What are you going to do?
It's been a long time, sir.
What can I do for you?
Lately...
I've been having bad dreams,
so I can't sleep.
I feel like I've wronged
your father twice.
What?
Someone has been digging
into your father's case.
I was fired for being a corrupt cop.
I was in a bad situation.
He offered me money, so I talked.
It was something I should
never have said.
What is it about?
You father, Detective Mo...
he wasn't accidentally killed
by a culprit he was chasing.
This punk...
It was a case that
Detective Mo was working on.
There were corrupt cops involved.
The case started to get bigger.
That gang used Detective Mo's
informant and set him up.
His name is Gong Gil Ho.
He was a fraud who was
Detective Mo's informant.
I think he got something out of it too.
Gong Gil Ho...
Hwi Chul!
Don't even think about revenge.
This won't be resolved by
catching him, that's for sure.
It was a very complicated case.
You'll have to kill and catch
multiple people to avenge him.
Does that make sense?
Please, you have to stay alive, Hwi Chul.
Yes, kill me.
If killing me helps with your grudge,
then go on and do it.
Why didn't you tell me?
I spent 15 years with the person
who helped to kill my dad...
No! They used me.
They gave me false information
and used me as bait.
I didn't even know
and I leaked it to your dad.
I couldn't stay quiet
out of worry for myself.
Would you have stayed put if I told you?
Hwi Chul, please.
Hit me and end it.
You can't do what Chi Soo wants.
Don't go.
What about your daughter?
What will you do about your daughter?
Hwi Chul!
Who are you, Mister?
Dealing with forgetting.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
It's been a long time.
Do you remember me?
Of course, I do.
What brings you by?
I came to help you.
Help me with what?
You're worried about
forgetting these people, right?
I'll remember them all,
so you just need to remember me.
Don't worry about a thing.
It's Christmas. What are your plans?
Things I must do.
What happened?
Okay.
Where are you going?
I have to step out. I'll be back soon.
Did you find him?
It's not happening.
Why not?
That lawyer had a gambling debt
and lost all his own money.
He took your money too.
It's useless to catch him now.
How much of your loan
do you have to pay off?
How much do you have left?
What do I do about Geum Bi's medicine?
You don't even have enough for that?
How much is it?
Why is it like this?
What did I do so wrong?
What did I do so wrong
that this is happening to me?
Yes, I did do a lot wrong.
I know I didn't live a good life.
I should, at least, get a chance.
I'm trying to live a proper life!
I should get one chance!
Don't kid yourself.
Once your life goes wrong
and you fall into the pit
you will spend your
entire life in the dirt.
Don't you realize that by now?
What about Geum Bi?
What did Geum Bi do wrong?
She was unfortunate
to have such terrible parents.
Does that make sense, you punk?
You think the world is fair?
Pull yourself together.
Otherwise, you won't be
able to handle your kid.
Fish oil?
Why are you buying one at a time?
You should buy 12 bottles all at once.
All right. I'll drink it.
All I have to do is drink it, right?
I'll just do one shot of the fish oil...
What is this?
It was under the bed.
You hid it and forgot about it.
What do you think you're doing?
You want to drink right now.
Do I seem like a joke to you?
Are you playing me for a fool?
What right do you have
to raise your voice?
You lost all my money.
- What?
- How did I know?
How could I not know when
you're talking about it so loudly?
The dog in the next neighborhood
must have heard too.
That was my money.
Even the owner of the money is fine,
so why are you throwing a fit, Lady?
It's not even your money.
You...
How much money did you lose?
1.5 billion won.
How many bicycles could I buy with that?
Bicycles?
You could probably buy a plane.
What are you going to do now?
I'm sorry.
Start working hard tomorrow
and pay me back.
You can only drink for today.
Should I pour it for you?
What about this could taste so good?
- Come over here.
- Why?
Just come here.
Why?
What do I do about Geum Bi's medicine?
Tell me about any jobs
I can earn some money doing.
Can you really go back?
You're dead if Jong Won catches you.
Also, you still owe me money. Pay up.
So tell me about any jobs now.
Do you want to put your life on the line?
What do you mean?
Just like you have to answer to Jong Won
Jong Won has to answer
to someone stronger than him.
If you can find Jong Won's
weakness and threaten him
it's not difficult at all to get money.
Tell me the details.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Not like that. Act as you normally do.
Smile naturally.
That'll do.
Will it snow this Christmas?
It's just supposed
to be cloudy this year.
I wish it would snow.
Woo Rim, Ji Hyun!
- I'll take your pictures.
- What for?
- Just smile.
- Why?
I'll Photoshop it for you.
Smile, okay?
Shil La.
- What is it called?
- What?
You know, when you pray for rain.
A rain ritual?
Yes, that.
Is there a ritual for snow?
Is there something like that? Why?
I'm just asking.
- What is she doing?
- Stop that.
I'll make your eyes look big.
She's making an album.
Album?
Is she in grade six or
something? What album?
What are you doing? Don't take it.
One, two, three.
[CHICKEN BREAST AND THIGH]
What is that?
Oh, you're here.
I was wondering if Geum Bi
had her cafeteria lunch.
You can check that online?
Why did you ask to see me?
These are papers and research
on Niemann-Pick disease.
I wouldn't know anything
even if I read them.
I'm not educated enough.
I'm not telling you to read them.
I wanted to tell you there is
a lot to look into and find out.
We can't be sure of anything.
Some people believe a treatment
can be found in approximately 10 years.
Treatment?
They say there's a much better
treatment option than oral drugs.
It's not a false rumor?
They said there are
no drugs or treatments.
Her doctor has said we shouldn't
get our hopes up too high.
But you never know.
There are times a parent makes an effort
and a treatment or drug is found.
Money...
I will need money, right?
You probably will.
We still have time.
I am going to go all the way.
I hope you feel the same way I do.
You never know.
If we do, a miracle could occur.
Then what should I do?
I'm not good at studying.
As for you, Geum Bi's mom...
you are a source of strength
just by being there for Geum Bi.
Geum Bi chose you.
[JOBS HIRING]
Hurry, please!
- Over here, please.
- Yes, okay.
Over there?
Not there. Number three.
- One more bottle, please.
- Okay.
They say there was a witness
when Hwi Chul's dad died.
You should find him and
use him against Jong Won.
A lot of people will be
scared if this gets out.
Even the people above Jong Won.
She was with him,
so we brought her, Boss.
Smile, would you?
You called me to take a
picture when I'm so busy?
Yes.
Can I leave since you're done?
You must be very busy.
What if I'm not?
I'll eat ice cream with you.
What is it?
Nothing.
Is it okay for you to go
around by yourself like this?
Why can't I?
You're sick.
What if you pass out on the street?
Are you worried about me?
Worried? No.
I was just asking.
You are worried about me.
It's written in your eyes.
"I'm worried about Geum Bi."
My friend graduated college and
enrolled in seminary school late in life.
He had mentioned that
he wanted to become a priest.
I didn't really think he'd do it.
If he didn't quit in the middle...
he's probably a priest now.
Mister, you had friends before right?
Comparing then and now,
when were you happier?
I don't know. It's been too long.
You do know.
I heard the whole story.
My dad was wrong.
Very wrong.
What... what's with you?
Mister...
It's been very difficult, hasn't it?
All alone.
Alone with no friends.
You had no one to talk to.
I felt the same way
when I found out I was sick.
But, about my dad...
can't you forgive him just this once?
Just this once.
You're just a little kid.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Have faith in God's mercy and grace.
Lay down the sins you have committed
and confess them truthfully.
There is a man I want to kill.
Will you kill him?
I want to kill him.
I am scared.
What are you scared of?
There's a child.
I'm scared she will hate and resent me.
A grudge is a thing of the past.
Love is about today.
Between your grudge and love,
which feeling is stronger?
The grudge that you hold now and
the regret you will endure in the future.
Which do you think
will be harder to bear?
You already know the answer.
You only need to do
what you already know.
Though I try so hard,
I cannot seem to do what I know.
Does it work that way for you?
You're curious, right?
About what?
You're wondering if
I'm your biological father.
I've also wondered
if you are my daughter.
That's not it.
I didn't wonder about it.
I knew from the start.
I knew you weren't.
I thought very often that it would
be nice if you were my daughter.
Have you ever thought it
would be nice if I were your dad?
No.
I thought so.
Sorry.
Hwi Chul has a bad side to him.
He seems to have changed a lot,
so I think that's good.
By the way, how come you're
always wearing the same clothes?
They're all slightly different.
Here you go.
1.1 million and 3,000 won.
Ah, yes.
What is it? You acted like
you wouldn't see me again.
Did you come to see me on purpose
after my dad died?
Because you felt bad?
Whatever the case,
it happened because I was stupid.
So, you felt bad and
wanted to watch out for me?
I didn't know my own place.
I turned you into a fraud in the end.
If it weren't for you...
I would've turned out worse.
Why don't you act like you normally do?
You're acting out of character.
Give this to Joo Young.
What is this?
Why don't you give it to her?
I'll be curious about
Geum Bi if I see her.
Once I start asking this
and that, I'll miss her.
Give it to her for me.
Are you going somewhere?
Where would I be going? I'm going home.
Bye.
What's this?
Hwi Chul said that
you'd know what it was.
Bye.
[MARIA CHAPEL - PRIEST MICHAEL
GEUM BI'S DAD]
[BACK DOOR]
Between your grudge and love,
which feeling is stronger?
The grudge that you hold now and
the regret you will endure in the future.
Which do you think
will be harder to bear?
Are you going, Boss?
There's a meteor shower this weekend.
Let's go look at it.
Forget it. What kind of cop lies
whenever he opens his mouth?
Don't even think about it.
Let go of me.
This was your plan.
I'll kill them and go to jail
or get killed by them.
Isn't that what you wanted, you punk?
Forget it. Just stop.
Why should I stop?
Don't butt in and get lost.
What about Geum Bi?
Don't you dare say Geum Bi's name.
I'll kill you first.
Joo Young got conned out of
the inheritance and has nothing.
What?
What are you saying?
The lawyer took Geum Bi's
inheritance and ran.
Then, Geum Bi...
Joo Young can barely cover
Geum Bi's medicine costs.
What's with you?
You stuck to me for years like a leech.
What are you doing now?
While I tried to ruin your life,
I just realized I ruined my own.
Stop saying nonsense.
It's because of Geum Bi.
I think you should know
how that could happen.
Do you still have to do this?
Then do it, you punk.
If you want to become like me,
who spent years resenting someone...
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi!
Geum...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi!
Geum Bi, where are you going?
Geum Bi, it's okay. You're okay.
It's cold, right?
Geum Bi.
You'll be okay. You're okay.
It's okay. Get on Mom's back.
Sleepwalking is a symptom.
Sleepwalking...
Though she doesn't show it,
she must be very stressed.
Stressed?
When children feel neglected
or don't feel protected enough
they get very stressed.
Though, I'm sure Geum Bi's illness
has a large part to do with it.
I don't know where she was trying to go.
It seems like the sleepwalking
manifested in an attempt to return home.
Return home?
A strong desire to return home.
That's what it was.
Aren't you going to work today?
No, I'm not.
Is it okay not to?
Hey, how can a person work every day?
They need to play too.
But you play all the time.
I haven't played with you.
Did you find anything?
Is it that hard?
Gosh.
Okay, okay. I'll come with you.
Don't hit me!
- Is he gone?
- Yes.
Hey, do you have anything on him?
Did you look into him back then?
I lost him.
Just go catch Mo Hwi Chul first, okay?
Yes, sir!
This caller is unavailable...
Hwi Chul.
All I want... is for you to
live just like your name.
I got it, okay?
You and your lectures.
Aren't you looking for me?
Call Hwi Chul and tell him to run!
Get him! Get him now!
Stop right there!
Not you again.
Who told you to make that mess?
What a pain this is.
What about that Hwi Chul or Gye Chul?
We have not found him yet.
I've heard the situation.
How did that happen?
[CHA CHI SOO]
This is Mo Hwi Chul, right?
Where are you?
If you call the police or anyone...
you will die.
Hey! Stop!
Are you Hwi Chul? Detective Mo's son?
Gosh, this is so absurd.
Let that guy go.
Stop showing off.
Look, Detective Mo's son.
You're not in a position to
tell me to do this or that.
You killed my father, didn't you?
But I'm here kneeling in front of you.
Let that punk go.
Boss.
If you get to know him, he's not someone
who should be in a place like this.
What are you saying?
If it were not for me,
he'd be in the major leagues.
Major leagues?
Boss, do you have some time?
Why?
If you have some time,
I'll tell you a fun story.
It's kind of long though.
If you're going to leave in
the middle, I won't even start.
Get started, then.
God is love.
Today's mass is a daytime mass in
honor of the birth of Jesus Christ.
As we joyfully greet Jesus who
came to us in the lowest form as a baby
let us start this mass.
Brothers and sisters.
Let us partake in the wonder of
salvation by reflecting on our sins.
Are we not allowed to eat that?
No.
Why are we here anyway?
It's Christmas.
It's a day when the
impossible can happen.
And you know that person there?
The priest?
He looks very much
like your biological father.
The kid... she has Alzheimer's?
Hong Shil La?
That was a lie.
Shil La is a friend
in his daughter's class.
Her dad is the chief prosecutor.
To be precise...
she doesn't have Alzheimer's.
It's called Neimann-Pick.
Well, that's how it is.
I'm in the wrong, so just let him go.
Is he telling the truth?
Stop pretending to be so cool
and go live well with your kid.
I was very late.
What changes if you show up now?
If I had shown up earlier,
neither of us would be in this state.
It's too late for that.
I'm sorry.
Look at these two filming a
romance scene in front of me.
I understand the whole issue.
I have an image to uphold.
I can't just stand by and
let people who mess with me go.
Between the two of you, I need one.
A finger... cut off a finger.
Then I will just overlook everything.
I'll send you both home.
Fine, cut it off. Cut it off.
Which one? This one?
All right. Cut yours off, then.
Hey, how can you say that?
You don't play baseball anymore.
You don't need fingers.
It'll hurt.
Wouldn't it hurt for me?
I'm very sensitive.
You said you would do it.
I was just saying it.
I thought you would volunteer to do it.
Shut up! Man, you are both cowards.
Listen carefully.
I was there when your father died.
It was not me who stabbed him.
As for the person who really did...
the same thing happened to him
and he got stabbed.
He passed away five years ago.
What do you say?
Why don't we call it even with this?
Don't you want to end it?
Hey! You bastards are all dead.
The cops will be here very soon.
You'd better free these two
before they get here.
What are you doing? Let them go now!
What do you mean?
Do they look tied up or something?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hello, Father.
Please pray for us.
Father, please pray for my family.
Yes, I will contact you soon.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Hello.
Merry Christmas.
Would you like a piece of candy?
Yes.
Have a merry Christmas.
Hello.
Why are you following me?
What? I'm only going my way.
Why do you keep standing in front of me?
Why are you following me?
What are you saying?
I didn't think you should go alone
today, so I was coming with you.
What is it?
Why are you following that guy?
[GEUM BI'S]
Someone really has nothing better to do.
They put a tree in an empty lot
but who would even see it?
I'm seeing it.
Oh yeah?
Then we should look together.
It's only fair.
Don't make it hard.
I want to make it hard.
This is a fun one.
This a hard one.
This one's easy.
What is that?
You know how to do this one.
Try it.
Please... please let it snow.
I have a friend named Geum Bi.
She's very sick.
What is this?
There you go.
What are you doing?
It's snowing.
Snow?
Wow! It's snowing a lot.
- I want to see the stars.
- Should we go outside?
I'm back home.
You're late.
[GEUM BI'S]
[MO HWI CHUL, MO GEUM BI]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever