[EPISODE 13]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What's wrong? Do you not like ice cream?
I do. I like ice cream.
What are you planning on
doing from now on?
What do you mean?
You can't just continue making
a living doing manual labor.
You're right.
You don't have to finish it.
Seems like you're not in the mood.
This isn't about you, Hwi Chul.
This is for Geum Bi.
Geum Bi?
If necessary...
I thought you'd consider adopting her.
If I could, it'd be great.
We'd run into problems
even if we tried to adopt her
since we are both single.
Then...
Then what?
So I guess...
Wait. No. No!
Why would you throw that out?
To be honest,
I have a mild stomachache right now.
Then you should've just told me.
This is very expensive.
Was it expensive?
I saw it on sale at the market.
Would you come with me
to this place in a little bit?
Where?
[PEDIATRICIAN PARK WOO HYUN]
While I was reading through
some medical journals
I read that the genetic
neurology treatment
is much more effective than medications.
I get where you're coming from
but I don't think you should
get your hopes up too high.
We don't know how much longer it'll take
before the work is officially published.
Hold on. Is there a way?
Why didn't you tell me about it?
Because it would've been
too risky to tell you about it at all.
How come? Why?
We should try everything we can.
Going forward with
this treatment would mean
we'd be using Geum Bi's brain
as an experimental object.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Geum Bi, aren't you cold?
- I'm getting hot.
While I was on this research team
a patient passed away
during our clinical trial.
For now, they're running basic
clinical trials using mouse brains.
So I'm telling you that treatment
isn't a plausible option.
Please don't chase after something
that lacks scientific evidence.
Dr. Park, thank you.
That's what you need to tell us.
Whether something is an
empty hope or if it's worth trying.
If you keep letting us know
we'll trust your opinion
and keep searching for a solution.
If there is even the slightest chance...
you may even call it a miracle.
If there is any chance at all,
we're going to take it.
Who says miracles can't
happen in our lives? Who knows?
If you acknowledge me
as Geum Bi's primary physician
please trust me and follow my orders.
Whatever it may be,
I'll try my best for Geum Bi.
I'll carefully contemplate the situation
if and whenever there is
even the slightest chance.
Please. We beg you.
Where do I need to poke them?
Is it you?
Ma'am. Over here.
Take a seat and have a drink.
I don't drink.
- Come on.
- I'm sorry.
Enjoy.
Geum Bi!
Geum Bi, where are you going?
If kids are left alone without
receiving the attention they need
they get stressed out by it.
You can't leave right now.
We're short on one person.
So you need to work another hour.
- Didn't you know?
- Ma'am.
Hurry and check on table 10.
All right.
A cute kid goes to the chicken coop.
A goblin's pants are dirty.
They're stinky. For 2,000 years...
Don't get bored when you're by yourself.
With a bulky and beautiful body
he's wearing red clothes.
He has a sweet and sour smell.
A dandy tomato. Tomato.
I'm going to become a cup of juice.
I'm going to become a bottle of ketchup.
Hey pretty lady, do you want
to go have a drink with me?
It seems like you're drunk.
Hold on.
Here.
Here. Don't play hard to get.
I'll ask them to
cut back on your interest.
Pay the principal amount
back as soon as possible.
You know as well as I do
what will happen if you don't.
Is Geum Bi always
by herself at this hour?
Her doctor told me she gets
stressed if she's left alone.
Maybe I should
send her back to Hwi Chul...
If Geum Bi is by herself every day...
could I babysit her one day?
Go ahead.
Tell her I'll stop by her school
when she gets out for her break.
See you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
So it's you.
The girl who will prepare
a funeral service for her mom.
I'll get going then.
- Make sure to give this to your mom.
- How did you two meet?
Your mom lost her wallet
and I found it for her.
Are you sure you didn't steal it
from her on purpose?
I'm not that kind of person.
- I can't trust you. I can't.
- Why not?
Because there are too many bad guys.
- They stole my money too.
- They are really mean guys.
How could they take money from a kid?
So, how much did they take?
- 1.5 billion won.
- What?
1.5 billion won.
I was just going to
drop this off and leave...
- I told him to come in.
- Hey. You.
He doesn't seem like a bad guy.
- Hey.
- Right?
This young lady knows how to read people.
What brings you here?
I just...
I mean, it's been a while
since I've seen you.
And I just had something to give you.
What is this?
It's called jamón.
It's a type of ham from Spain.
Like a sausage.
The thing that
you eat in thin slices, right?
Is that how you're supposed to eat it?
I've never had it before.
Your mom told me she liked it,
so I just bought it as a gift.
Thank you for jamón.
To be honest, I came because
I had something to tell you.
I know this is sudden
but I'm leaving Korea soon.
I'm opening a branch in South America.
So once I leave the country
I probably won't be back
for one or two years.
I guess you weren't lying
when you said you were quite well off.
So anyway, I need someone
who knows how to speak Spanish.
The job won't be easy.
But if you are interested...
I'd like you to come with me.
12 times...
Not bad.
I might not cook often,
but I'm quite amazing at it.
- What has gotten into you?
- What do you mean?
Can't a mother just
cook and feed her daughter?
Who is this?
Patzzi's grandma.
You two look alike. Even if you
had a rough relationship with her.
She and you would've
had a wonderful relationship.
See how she left her inheritance
to you and not to me?
Maybe she did it so that
you could be my wake up call.
Meanness runs in the family.
Do you miss your mom?
A little bit.
A little bit?
A lot.
A lot?
Very much.
This is why people need to
express their love.
If they say things they don't mean
and push others away
other people will act out.
I know she did what she did for me.
You should have listened to your mother.
Hey. I can be sure of this.
As you grow older,
you probably won't listen to me either.
You said it runs in the family.
- I hate you so much.
- What are you doing?
- I don't want to go to work today.
- What?
What do you mean, "What"?
Why are we here?
Hey.
It's pitiful if an adult
doesn't act like an adult.
And it's creepy
if a kid doesn't act like a kid.
What are you saying?
It's freaking cold out.
What a creepy girl.
Who are you calling creepy?
You're the ugly one.
- That's enough.
- What do you mean?
Stop worrying about me
and worry about yourself first.
Live in that house starting today.
What are you saying?
Live with your dad.
- Dad?
- Yeah.
Dad. Your dad.
Forget it.
- I can live by myself now.
- What's wrong?
Are you tired of living with me?
I feel like I won't be
able to survive without you
but I can.
I heard you said...
you felt like I'd die before you
if you just let me be.
Now I can live without dying.
So you can now go back to Dad.
- Without me...
- Geum Bi.
I'm trying to be
an actual adult this time.
To do that, I need to pay my debt back.
And I also need a reputable job.
That's how things are.
So...
I... am going to go
somewhere far away.
Until I come back
live happily with your dad.
You get what I'm saying, right?
Hold on! Let go of me.
Don't follow me.
Don't you take a step closer to me.
Do you never want to see me again?
Mom.
Mom!
Geum Bi!
Please be in here. Please.
My goodness. What am I supposed to do?
Dad.
I'm hearing things now.
What's going on?
Can't you see? I'm home.
What about your mother?
She said she's leaving
to become an adult.
What?
Anyway.
It's you. My Geum Bi.
Include me in this, all right?
Don't exclude me.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
So what do you want to do?
What do you mean? We need to go to bed.
So why does Geum Bi
need to sleep in that room?
Then you want her to sleep here?
Geum Bi, why don't you sleep
with your dad? It's been a while.
That's gross.
Why would I sleep with you?
Gross? I've done so much for you.
I even put up a tree for you.
- I'm going to get pouty.
- Go ahead.
Then we can all sleep together.
How could all three of us...
Fine. Let's do this, then.
Why would we act like homeless people?
This is nothing.
We even simulated boot camp training.
If we had the raining effects,
it'd be perfect.
We're camping out, why would it rain?
- Is this tent waterproof?
- It should be.
It's truly waterproof if it doesn't
let any water out once it pours in.
- We need to spill ramen.
- And barf after eating pork cutlet.
- You made me eat it.
- Be honest.
You secretly ate something
without me, didn't you?
No. That's not true.
I starved all day that day.
- My goodness.
- I can't believe you.
I can't understand a thing.
Try to make some sense.
- What are we going to do tomorrow?
- Tomorrow?
Let's think about that
when tomorrow comes.
- You never plan things ahead of time.
- I know, right?
- You always have no plan.
- That's not true.
I've been living by a plan for years.
I'm a planning man.
- Aren't you the opposite of that?
- You're right.
- He's the opposite of that.
- Unplanned.
You ugly people. Don't even talk.
I'm going to stop by there.
You should stay by our side
if at all possible.
I need to buy gifts for my friends
since we're going on a break.
- I'll come with you.
- Why are you treating me like a fool?
- Are you worried that I'll get lost?
- It's not that.
Geum Bi. Are you sure
you can go by yourself?
Your dad and I will be
waiting for you at that cafe.
Make sure you call us
if anything happens. Okay?
Sure.
It's still...
Hwi Chul. I have something to tell you.
What is this?
In this state, Geum Bi legally
doesn't have any family or relatives.
- You need to adopt her officially.
- Yeah.
I could do it. Adoption.
I guess she's Mo Geum Bi
from now on. Not Yoo Geum Bi.
I'm at a loss for words.
Do you not like Mo Geum Bi?
Then shall we call her Go Geum Bi?
Do you think they'd just
let anyone adopt her?
I'm not just anyone.
I'm Geum Bi's father.
There are adoption laws.
You need to have a certain
amount of assets to adopt someone.
You can't have a criminal
or substance abuse record.
They check to see if you're qualified.
Why would they be so picky?
If a father and his daughter connect,
then they should live together.
That's not all. It'll take numerous
qualification tests and steps.
Also, it's even more difficult
for people who are single.
Why are there so many documents?
An application for adoption.
A credit check.
My goodness.
[CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE]
This...
I told you. It's difficult to
adopt someone when you're single.
You should finish what you can first.
Is this your way of proposing to me?
Proposing? What?
I'm doing this for Geum Bi.
Why would I propose to you?
So why would you
toss your ice cream away?
- What do you mean?
- Never mind.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I don't think Geum Bi can go to
school today. I'll call her teacher.
Her fever is high.
Are you all right?
- Why are you getting up?
- I need to go to school.
You can't go to school.
You have a high fever.
Today is the last day before break.
You won't even have classes then.
Just lie down and rest.
I may not be able to
go back to school next year.
So today would be the last day
I'd get to see my friends.
You should really get some rest.
A break is not given as
your leisure time.
You're just studying the material
you'd be studying in school at home.
Don't be lazy during your break.
Function under a schedule
and be punctual
during your break as well.
This ends the announcements
for our school's winter break.
Since everyone in our class is here
shall we start our party
for the winter break?
Yes!
Since Geum Bi was late,
give her some sort of penalty.
What kind of penalty?
Singing is the penalty
for tardiness, right?
Is it?
Sing for us. Sing!
Sing! Sing!
- Sing!
- So childish.
Fine. I'll do it.
Go, Geum Bi!
An autumn night. A peaceful night.
A night when insects cry.
As an alley behind
a cottage house gets dark.
If you start tearing up
because you miss your mom's hug
sit on...
the floor and...
count the stars.
- Geum Bi!
Geum Bi...
- Wake up, Geum Bi.
- Geum Bi?
Geum Bi?
Geum Bi.
- Geum Bi.
- What's wrong, Geum Bi?
She has Niemann-Pick disease.
- Niemann-Pick?
- Yes.
Since she's having seizures,
give her anti-epileptics.
- And keep checking her vitals.
- Okay. Got it.
Geum Bi!
Oh my. Geum Bi! Geum Bi!
- Are you her guardian?
- What's going on?
- You need to stay back.
- Geum Bi!
We've stabilized her by giving her
anti-epileptics. So she should be okay.
Then can she go home?
She has symptoms of pneumonia.
It'd be best to have her stay here
so that we can monitor her closely.
Pneumonia?
I thought she was just having a seizure.
Her immune system
has been greatly weakened.
Comorbidities complicate this illness.
You need to be aware of it.
Will this keep happening from now on?
I believe her symptoms
will worsen from now on.
Her brain functioning level
will especially decline.
What is going on in Geum Bi's head?
See, this is a picture of
a normal person's cerebrum.
In a human brain, there are
nerve cells called neurons.
Neurons connect at the synapse
and memories are created at the synapse.
Created memories are then
stored in the hippocampus.
In Geum Bi's case, her hippocampus
and cerebrum are shrinking.
This is a current scan of Geum Bi's
brain in comparison to a normal brain.
How quickly does the disease progress?
It differs based on the patient.
Since it developed during her childhood
she may live for about 10 more years.
10 years?
Only if her medications work very well.
However...
Geum Bi's illness is progressing
faster than I had predicted.
You need to emotionally prepare yourself
so that you don't fall apart.
Her seizures will get worse.
It'll be hard for you to bear.
As her awareness decreases
she'll have difficulty
forming words in two years.
Lastly, she'll lose her five senses.
She may even show
symptoms of a split personality.
That's enough. Enough.
Hwi Chul.
You can't just stand here like this.
Get a hold of yourself.
All right. I need to.
What is wrong with you?
You knew what was coming.
We knew what was coming!
I did.
Listen to me carefully, Hwi Chul.
Get a hold of yourself
and listen to me carefully.
From now on, we're going
to see and experience
the things we've been
reading and hearing about.
You told me it was
going to be unbearable.
So then what did I tell you?
What did I tell you?
You said, "It's okay,
because you have someone to..."
"bear it with you."
That's right.
This will be unbearable.
And I'm as scared as you are.
But who are you?
You're Geum Bi's father.
If a father breaks down
things feel even more
unbearable for the child.
If Geum Bi's father breaks down
Geum Bi won't overcome this.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Stay by Geum Bi's side.
I'm going to get her administered
and go home to grab her clothes.
I'll bring other necessities as well.
All right.
[RELATIONSHIP TO THE PATIENT]
- Are you done filling it out?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Where did she go?
No!
No! Soo Yeon! Please! No!
Soo Yeon! No! You can't!
No! You can't! Soo Yeon!
Where the heck were you?
You were brought to
the hospital because you fell.
How could you yell at me?
This happened all because
you made us sleep in a tent.
Be honest. You're faking it, aren't you?
Boot camp training isn't enough.
You need to get trained
in the cold weather too.
Why aren't you at work?
Why are you just fiddling around?
You were going to use me as
an excuse to take the day off, right?
Since you're ugly,
you should at least be nice.
you should at least work hard.
If Kang Hee kicks you out of the house
do you think I'll follow you?
Don't you even think
about coming with me.
I'm going to feed you
cup ramen once a day.
Fine. Whatever. I can't even bring you
pork cutlet anymore since I'm on a break.
- Why is your back so dirty?
- What do you mean?
Sit down.
Clean it off for me.
What are you doing?
Your customer has boarded.
Hurry and get going.
You're so shameless. So shameless.
- Are you cold, Dad?
- No. Not at all.
- It's well-heated in here.
- Then why is your body shaking?
That's because you're tickling my back.
I am?
You give me a piggyback ride
when you're older.
You'll then understand.
- I don't want to. Because you're heavy.
- You're so shameless. Shameless.
Leave! I told you to go!
Why do you keep bothering me?
Where would I go?
I need to take care of you.
Take your hands off of me!
I'm telling you I don't need you.
Get lost!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Geum Bi. You shouldn't befriend her.
I know, right?
[CHA CHI SOO]
Hello?
I was supposed to meet with her today.
- Were you waiting for her?
- Yeah.
I waited by the school until sunset.
Because I knew she wasn't
the type to break her promise.
I wish I could switch
places with Geum Bi.
I guess you really are a father now.
This was probably how my dad
felt too, right? When I was sick.
- What does it feel like?
- What do you mean?
Being a father.
It just...
feels like I'm carrying a large
and warm egg inside of my heart.
I can't describe it in words.
But there's this thing.
I think I somewhat get it.
- You should carry one, too.
- Maybe.
Once I feel like I've earned it.
- What is this?
- It's for Geum Bi.
- You give it to her.
- Take it to her for me.
I'll get going.
Come visit again to see Geum Bi.
Dr. Park.
Please let me meet him.
Who?
I've done some research on
Dr. Huh Byung Soo.
- That man...
- He might be our small hope.
That's right. Where would you go?
Come over here. Here. There you go.
Look at this guy. You just can't.
You've probably looked into
everything for your sick child.
The medications she's taking
can't cure Niemann-Pick disease.
Because of the blood-brain barrier,
her medications can't reach her brain.
When you say the blood-brain barrier...
He's talking about the specialized
structure between the brain and vessels.
Because of it, her medications
have a minimal effect on her brain.
No need to elaborate.
Only we'd understand these concepts.
To tell you the main point,
she needs to keep taking her medications
while we treat her brain separately.
- Through a genetic neurology treatment?
- That's right.
You seem to be well aware of it.
In patients with Niemann-Pick disease
inflammation is severe at the memory
associated region, the cerebral cortex
and the movement
associated region, the cerebellum.
So, if we can save those neurons
through a genetic treatment
I'm saying we could
treat the regions of the brain
that can't be treated
through her medications.
Do you think that'd be possible?
I'm doing this because
I think it'd be possible.
Even if it does work
it may take 10 or 20 years
until it actually reaches the clinic.
If it does work, who cares
about the time frame?
Is there no way to shorten that time?
In order to do so,
he'd need to test it on humans.
It'd be too dangerous.
Also, this person here...
made a mistake during
his past clinical trials.
A patient died.
I can't forgive him.
Dr. Park Woo Hyun.
You may say that now
but it seems like you're
very interested in this research.
What do you think?
Would you like to join my research team?
I think I could shorten the time frame
by five years if you work with me.
If we could reduce it by five years
I could create a treatment
in just five years.
Help me out.
Foxie!
What?
You were having a dream, weren't you?
So?
The thing you've been dreaming about.
Isn't it something like this?
[EPISODE 14 WILL AIR NEXT WEDNESDAY.]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever