(The following program may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 15)
What are you talking about?
We should do everything necessary to save her.
They said she might lose her hearing.
And there might be other side effects, too.
If it goes wrong, it'll be the opposite of saving her.
If it's effective as they say, we should risk it.
She needs more time until the gene therapy can work.
Are you going to look away from a possibility?
Later on, when I'm very sick,
don't operate on me...
or do anything painful to me.
I hope you won't do anything like that.
The spinal injections aren't guaranteed to work.
They said it varies from patient to patient.
Geum Bi might be fine.
She's so normal right now.
How is she normal?
She didn't recognize you and collapsed from a seizure.
Then, we can give her medication and bring her here.
But if she even loses her hearing at her age,
It's like living half a life.
She has less than 10 years to live.
How can you be so ignorant?
Let's wait.
Let's wait it out a little longer.
You look fine,
but I definitely look like I'm sick with my blue lips.
No one would think we're both sick.
It's a long story,
but my body is a bit weird.
It keeps on piling things called lipids...
when it doesn't need them.
That's awful.
So it's not just in your brain,
it piles up in your stomach, too.
Everywhere.
They will paralyze my body.
What's with that?
Apparently, I was born...
with a different gene or something.
Not a lot of people have this disease,
so not many people care about it.
I can't just take medicine,
so I get huge shots in my spinal cord.
It's awful.
Your dad must be worried.
Geum Bi.
Can you dance?
Do you know any dances?
Stop taking pictures.
I didn't even wash my face.
Geum Bi, is there anything you'd like to do?
Should I try on some middle school uniforms?
Are you worried about something?
I'm not worried.
Someone told me this.
Most of your worries don't become a reality.
Who said that?
Someone.
- It's Ms. Kang. - Hey, Geum Bi.
- Hello. - Hello.
Chi Soo.
Geum Bi.
Do you volunteer here, too?
Chi Soo, do you know Ms. Kang?
Geum Bi, do you know him?
Ms. Kang, do you know him?
How?
Eat slowly.
Why? Did it get caught in your throat?
Eat slowly. No one is taking your food.
You're so greedy.
My goodness.
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi, what's wrong?
It looks like she can't breathe.
It's dysphagia.
That means she can't swallow.
It's a side effect from the medicine she's taking.
Then should she quit taking it?
Well, she can quit for a while and restart later.
Shouldn't she take that spinal cord injections?
Oh, well.
Hwi Cheol.
I'll ask Geum Bi.
I'll take the shots.
You might lose your hearing.
I know.
- Cut! - Cut!
Cut!
Chi Soo, that was excellent.
That was good, but can we do it one more time?
Let's make it even more interesting.
Can you do another turn while you're in the air?
- Yes. - Are you hurt?
- I'm fine. - Are you?
Let's do another take.
- Yes. - One more take!
Cut!
One more time.
That's no good.
Okay, that's good. One more time.
One more time. Let's make it even better.
(Baby Box)
My goodness, this is so much money.
Thank you.
And bless you.
What were you so sincerely wish for?
I wasn't wishing for anything.
You just prayed.
I was just...
thinking about something with my eyes closed.
What were you thinking about?
Geum Bi and I both...
I was just...
hoping that there will be a path...
for both of us.
That's what praying is.
I need to fix the windowsill.
Geum Bi got discharged from the hospital.
I'm going to go see her.
Okay.
(Report of Test Results)
The volume of lipids...
decreased than before.
Really?
Are you worried?
They said I got better,
so your test results will be good, too.
We're connected, you know.
We had the same dream.
Geum Bi.
Yes?
Can't you hear me?
Geum Bi.
Are you really okay?
I need you to go somewhere with me.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hee Joon. Take a look at my face.
Can you point at my face with your index finger?
My...
My finger.
Hee Joon.
Can you straighten your finger...
and point at the doctor?
Raise your arm and point forward.
My finger.
There you go. Hold out your finger.
Hee Joon.
There you go.
You can do this, Hee Joon.
Hold it out all the way.
Can you try a bit more?
You can do it.
Hold it out all the way.
Yes, a bit more.
Doctor.
Hold it out.
Hee Joon. You're doing good.
Point at the doctor.
Hold out your arm.
I think Geum Bi's loss of hearing...
is a side effect from cyclodextrin.
Don't blame yourself for it.
You two are trying...
everything the current medical science allows.
You'll have to make more difficult decisions later on.
It could be harder on you than it is for Geum Bi.
If I may say so,
don't give up now...
and protect her to the very end.
I will also try my absolute best...
until the very end.
According to the test results,
her auditory cells haven't been completely impaired.
There's a chance of recovery.
We'll give her hearing-aid and see how it goes.
Hearing-aid?
I want to keep having the injections.
What do you want to eat?
Fried sweet potatoes.
Fried sweet potatoes?
I'll make them for you when we go home.
Come in if you'd like.
Your seat is over there.
Why would there be my seat here?
Zavesca...
Cyclodextrin...
I heard she developed side effects from both.
It must've been extremely painful,
but you're not one to give up there.
I knew you'd come.
I didn't make up my mind yet.
That's what you're here to do.
I came here for assurance.
Do you know why...
I'm so focused on this research?
Would you do it knowing there's no money in it?
I think it was 2 or 3 years ago.
I read a thesis paper on gene therapy...
and a news article on Niemann-Pick disease.
At that moment,
those two created an idea in my mind.
I was destined to do this.
This is not a joint research.
Consider yourself being under surveillance.
The data I've gathered over the years...
are on your desk.
Are you really going to do it?
Do what?
You've been fiddling with that ring for an hour now.
What? What ring?
It won't be easy.
Especially in your case, there's a sick kid involved.
I know that.
Knowing and living are two completely different things.
Gosh, what are you saying?
With a sick kid, you won't be able to do anything.
When everyone else is happy,
you'll feel like it's the end of the world.
When you try to get intimate,
you'll feel like it's not right.
What are you talking about?
Are you talking about marriage?
Why would something like that matter?
It is something that matters.
When your child gets sick,
the marriage will hit rock bottom in a heartbeat.
Do you really think you can put up with it?
By the way, where on earth is Chi Soo?
Should I turn on the lights?
No.
We should've done as you said.
What should we do?
Geum Bi will only suffer more.
She can't even hear now.
I can't turn on the lights even if you want me to.
I'm too embarrassed.
It's not your fault.
I ran away from making hard decisions...
and left them all to you.
I'll do that from now on.
I'm the father.
Leave it to me.
And trust me.
Geum Bi's mom.
The three of us will be together no matter what.
The three of us.
She's so pretty.
Mo Hwi Cheol,
will you never fight with the bride, Go Kang Hee,
never run away,
share delicious food with her,
starve when you don't have any...
Anyway, can you live happily ever after with her?
Yes!
What about the bride?
Yes, I will.
I want my younger sibling to have dimples like me.
I want to see them soon.
Hey.
Okay, then.
Face each other.
It's time...
to kiss.
Kiss, kiss.
- Hurry up and finish. - What are you waiting for?
Just finish it up.
Okay, this is great. You may walk down the aisle.
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi, were you practicing?
Mom.
I walked three more steps than yesterday.
Really? You'll start running next week.
You're sweating.
Let me bring you some water.
Geum Bi.
Do you want a fork?
No. Just these.
Do you want to try using chopsticks?
It worked.
Hello.
Put it over here, please.
Okay.
Here we go.
All right.
Here. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
You're eating so well.
That's my girl.
Look at you go.
Try using your chopsticks again.
You're the best!
- You're so good. - How is it?
Is it good?
Are you leaving already?
Yes. I requested an early leave.
Is it your kid again?
It's not like you're the only one with a kid.
You should just sit at home and raise your kid...
instead of coming here and causing harm.
How many early leaves have you taken, anyway?
I'm sorry.
You're doing so well.
You did so well. Let's do it one more time.
No.
Why not? You're doing great today.
Let's go back and forth just one more time.
I won't.
Just one more time, Geum Bi.
Stand up. What are you doing?
I said no!
She's tired.
Physical therapy is hard.
Get up. Do it one more time.
She said no.
This isn't boot camp.
You're draining her.
Let's call it a day.
I guess she's tired.
Get up.
Geum Bi.
Try again. You can do it.
Here, give me your hand.
Here you go.
Try again. You need to eat.
What is it? Do you not want to eat?
Do you want to use these?
What are you doing?
This isn't child's play.
Try again.
Not like that. That's it.
Geum Bi, even if it's hard,
you need to keep trying.
Push harder.
A little bit harder.
You can do it.
Push into it.
Will you stop it?
She doesn't want to eat.
Hwi Cheol.
She doesn't want to do it.
Why do you keep forcing her?
I want to go.
Hwi Cheol.
What?
Are you trying to turn her into a fool?
A fool?
You keep letting her have her way.
Why do you keep forcing her to do things?
Even I'd get sick of it.
Practice is all good,
but give up after a while. She's tired.
If you keep stopping because she's tired,
what will you do later on?
Stop pushing us both.
I asked you to trust me.
I have an idea and a plan.
What is it?
Do you think coddling her makes you a dad?
As the disease advances, her personality can change.
She can become rough and aggressive...
and repeated disappointments...
can bring upon depression.
Depression?
What should we do then?
Don't ever get angry or berate her.
If you scold her, that's all she'll remember...
and increased instability will worsen her condition.
That becomes a vicious cycle.
Even if she makes mistakes,
try to console her and cheer her on.
Her walking seems to be improving.
If you keep supporting and helping her,
it should be fine.
Yes.
Push the button until it's completely in the hole.
Concentrate.
There you go.
Do it again.
Geum Bi, you have to align the button...
and the hole it goes into.
Try again.
Here.
Don't use your fingers too much.
Do it slowly.
I won't do it.
Do it again.
I won't.
Take your time. There's no need to rush.
Here.
Don't rush it.
Let's try again.
Geum Bi. Geum Bi.
Calm down.
Try again.
No.
Do it again.
Here.
Don't give up and try again.
Why force me when I said no?
You aren't even my real mom.
How dare you.
Get lost.
What are you doing?
First, you corner her...
and now you're hitting her?
Who said I hit her?
Is this what you do when I'm out?
Do you scold and beat her?
Don't talk like that when you don't know anything.
I said nothing because I didn't know.
Had I known you abuse her, I'd have done something.
Who's abusing her?
Are you sick of it?
Have you had enough?
Is this it?
Then say you can't do it anymore!
Don't torture the poor kid.
How could you say that?
Don't you know me?
Would you have done that if she were your child?
Geum Bi.
Did Mom...
actually hit you?
Geum Bi. Geum Bi.
Why force me when I said no?
You aren't even my real mom.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you call ahead?
Geum Bi's asleep.
I guess she didn't tell you.
She hasn't been feeling well.
Can I see her?
Has she gotten that bad?
She'll only get worse.
There's nothing we can do.
You knew this would happen.
Yes. Knowing and not being able to do anything...
is what makes it all worse.
What should I do now?
You must be going through a lot because of Geum Bi.
I'd never be able to do what you're doing.
I'm afraid.
That you might not withstand it?
That I might change.
That I'll end up hating her.
I'm not yet married,
and I've never raised a child,
but I'm a good judge when it comes to moms.
I always have the same thought when I see you.
When I become a wife and a mom,
I would like to become one like you.
Think that we're all like Geum Bi.
What?
Treat other people...
like you treat Geum Bi.
With ease and comfort.
If it's too hard,
you can practice with me.
When you meet...
a type of person you've never met before,
it's natural that you'd be curious.
I can tell what type of person you are...
by the way you treat Geum Bi.
I want you to start anew.
You adore Geum Bi,
and you donate your hard-earned money...
to the orphanage, which is great.
I'm saying you should treasure yourself first.
I think you deserve...
to love yourself a little bit.
Thanks for visiting me.
Eat all you want.
You're wearing a school uniform.
Of course. What else would a student wear?
Do you go to school?
Yes, I do.
It must be nice to wear a school uniform.
You'll wear one when you go to middle school.
Middle school?
I wonder if I'll ever get to go.
Of course you can.
Can I?
Can I wear a uniform?
You bet you can.
If you have to wear one,
go to a school with a pretty uniform.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Why not?
Dad, So Hee's here.
You've met her before.
So Hee, he's my dad.
Don't just stand there.
So Hee said hi.
Geum Bi.
You can stay a little longer.
She wants to leave...
because you're acting all weird.
Oh, sorry, my bad.
Have fun with Geum Bi.
Take your time.
Yes, stay a little longer.
Stay for lunch, too.
Really? Do you do things like that in school?
Do you really? That's awesome.
Geum Bi.
Did you...
have a friend over today?
No. What friend?
Never mind.
Is it frustrating to be indoors all the time?
It's really frustrating.
Do you remember the promise I made on the way back...
from watching the meteor shower?
I told you I'd take you to see the sea.
You did.
Or you have to drink 10 bottles of fish sauce.
You were too sick to go this summer.
Let's go tomorrow.
Can we?
Gosh.
That's it? Keep running.
I'm tired.
You're so shameless.
Are you ready?
Are you cold?
Are you hungry?
Dad.
Geum Bi.
Is it tough?
If I'd known this would happen,
I wouldn't have come to you.
Aren't you glad you came to me?
This is why I brought you.
I...
want to live with you for a long, long time.
I don't think I'll be able to.
You and I...
should travel and see things.
The world is full of things to see.
Someone told me...
that life is like a picnic.
When the picnic's over,
we go back to the sky.
Then we share stories about our picnics.
We should go and see flowers.
When it gets warmer...
let's go and see cherry blossoms,
pear blossoms, azaleas, lilacs,
and see all those things.
Okay?
I had a lot of fun...
since I met you, Dad.
That's why...
once my picnic is over,
I want you to have as much fun as I did.
Don't go...
and have fun without me.
Take me along.
Enjoy your great picnic...
and tell me stories later.
Okay?
We're back.
Dinner's ready.
Where did you both go...
without me?
Here.
Eat up.
Kang Hee.
Who are you here to see?
I missed you.
Kang Hee.
Who are you here to see?
It's a secret.
I missed you.
Kang Hee.
If you go far, far away,
I will go to the seashore every day...
and fly a kite as I wait for you.
If you go far, far away,
I will go to the seashore every day...
and fly a kite as I wait for you.
Geum Bi.
If the strong sea winds make me sick,
I will ask for Hwi Cheol's help before I die.
Don't say things like that.
I'll ask him to bury me by the sea...
and fly a kite by my grave every day.
I'll ask him to tie it to my tombstone.
Geum Bi.
She won't go anywhere, so why don't you eat your food?
Don't you dare try to con her.
I'll report you to the police right away.
Geum Bi.
Can you read my fortune after dinner?
Sure, I will.
What do you want to know?
What about me? Read mine, too.
I don't even have to consult the cards.
Why not?
Just eat your food.
You're so ugly.
You're even uglier.
(My Fair Lady 2016)
Say cheese.
Are you filming me?
Okay, let's go.
One, two, three.
Okay, okay.
No, do it again.
- Does it hurt? - It does.
Hurry up and take the picture.
This is fun.
No. Forget about it.
- Cut, okay! - All right.
Great job.
Tune in next week to watch My Fair Lady 2016.