[FINAL EPISODE]
Geum Bi's mom.
Oh, thank you.
Someone sent a donation to my account.
That person knew that my circumstances
weren't so good at the hospital.
Was that you, by any chance?
No.
How would I be able
to afford such a thing?
Then who?
I don't know who it was,
but I'm grateful to that person.
You can be grateful later.
Take a look at this.
Niemann-Pick causes severe inflammation
in the cerebral cortex
and the cerebellum.
In order to treat the
cerebral cortex and cerebellum
what would you look at?
I would look at the nerve cells attached
to the cerebral cortex and cerebellum.
Thalamus.
The thalamus connects to the
cerebral cortex and the cerebellum.
What is it?
You found something important, right?
I think we have.
Let's split the mice up
into two groups and test this.
You handle the mice that
have been fed the drugs.
I'll handle the mice that have been
treated with the thalamus gene.
Let's get on it quickly.
If this works out...
we could run clinical trials
within five years.
What are you doing, Geum Bi's Mom?
Pardon?
You should split up the mice.
Okay, I will.
Why aren't you asleep?
Dad.
What is it?
I feel like I know all these people.
But I don't remember them at all.
Sometimes...
the memories can come and go.
I really wish I could remember.
I think they were people I liked.
Pick anyone you want.
I'll bring that person to you right away.
What good is that?
I won't know who it is
even if I see the person.
Later, I worry I might not
remember you or Mom.
I get scared and I cry too.
That's how I feel.
Have I already forgotten you before?
No.
Go to sleep.
You'll remember everything
once you wake up.
Dad.
Who is she that she's
been there this whole time?
Who?
Geum Bi's dad!
Geum Bi, I have good news.
Mom.
Who is she?
What's going on?
Geum Bi.
Why are you playing strange pranks?
It's not funny.
What do you mean?
A girl I don't know is in our house.
Geum Bi, take a good look.
You don't know who this is?
Open your eyes properly
and take a good look.
Why are you being like this?
That's enough.
I said I don't know her.
Take another good look.
Come here.
Stop it.
Where am I?
What do you mean, where?
This is your house.
Who are you, Mister?
Who are you, Lady?
Geum Bi, please get it together.
Who is she?
- Geum Bi.
- I said, who is she?
- Who is she?
- Geum Bi.
- Who is she!
Geum Bi!
Calm down, Geum Bi.
Who is she?
- Geum Bi!
- Who are you?
Geum Bi, please focus.
- Geum Bi, Geum Bi.
- Let me go!
Geum Bi, wake up!
Geum Bi, Geum Bi!
Wake up, Geum Bi!
What do we do?
Geum Bi.
If her cognitive level has decreased
so that she doesn't recognize herself...
she is at a critical stage now.
How can she suddenly
be in critical stage now?
Geum Bi will be in a great deal
of physical discomfort.
Rather than focusing on her memories
you need to focus on
her physical well-being.
Then what about Geum Bi?
She doesn't even know who she is
and only her body will be left.
What is that?
We wanted to help Geum Bi
get through this without hardship.
That was our job.
This is the same thing.
How is this the same thing?
Her memories will be gone.
Geum Bi will disappear.
Why would our Geum Bi disappear?
She doesn't even know her own face,
so how is that our Geum Bi?
Whether she has her memories or not,
Geum Bi is still Geum Bi.
We are Geum Bi's mom and dad.
Geum Bi told me that
she wants to remember.
Why doesn't anyone believe me?
She has lost more of her brain matter.
It is getting quite severe.
We need to work quickly.
If things don't work out,
the treatments will all be useless.
Geum Bi, can you close
and open your hand for me?
Can you move your index finger for me?
Now, how about your thumb?
What do I do now?
I can't even recognize myself.
Your trip is coming to an end.
You will live here now and
only watch over them once in a while.
From here? By myself?
You have all your memories
from the trip you took there.
Can't I stay on my trip a little longer?
I can only meet my dad
if I leave this place.
No, you can't.
It's hard for you to even breathe.
You may not realize this
but this place is a protective
shield you've made for yourself.
I'm going to leave.
No... you can't.
I left so many things unsaid to my dad.
I haven't even told him
how much I like him.
You'll die though.
Then I'd rather die.
If I don't know who I am,
I'm not even myself.
I'm going to find a way out and leave.
You'll help me, won't you?
You really shouldn't.
It's dangerous to go any further!
You and I will die if you keep going!
Geum Bi!
Court, prison...
Han River Park.
Hotel buffet.
Campground.
Don't do this.
How many days has it been now?
You already flew a kite at
Han River Park and visited the prison.
Geum Bi's dad.
Wait, wait.
Put this on before going.
[MO GEUM BI]
You like your ramen chewy
and slightly cooked?
Then why do you cook it at all?
Why not eat it raw?
It ought to be cooked just right
with the noodles thick.
The broth needs to be boiled down
for the ramen to taste right.
Why isn't this lighting?
Gosh! Hey, look at this.
Why?
Why didn't the lipid level
decrease in the thalamus group?
The therapy gene did not
affect the inflammation.
Your hypothesis about the
thalamus nerve was incorrect.
No, that can't be possible.
My hypothesis is correct.
A hypothesis can always be wrong.
Did you think this would be so easy?
Let's go over it from the beginning.
[TODAY, I WENT TO A BUFFET WITH MISTER.]
[1. BUY KANG HEE A PRESENT.
2. TAKE PICTURES BEFORE LEAVING...]
[THINGS I HAVE TO DO:
1. TAKE PICTURES OF CLASSMATES...]
Come back, Mo Geum Bi.
I am standing here waiting.
Dad.
I'll come back.
It hurts so much.
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi, why...
Geum Bi, why didn't you wake me up?
Why didn't you wake me up? Geum Bi...
[EXAM RESULTS]
While I was asleep,
Geum Bi regained her senses.
I think she was trying to
communicate something to me.
I'm sorry to say this to you.
Geum Bi's lipids level has gone up.
Geum Bi is no longer
the child you two once knew.
Her memories are all gone.
She will just become a living body
that lives in suffering.
A living body?
Geum Bi is not just some breathing body.
The tests will be done soon.
Please let me know
if you decide to admit her.
Doctor, run the tests once more.
Please? Would you, Doctor?
Can you find that person
from before here?
Dad...
Geum Bi, wait a moment.
My daughter's inside, right?
I thought you had picked her up.
- What?
- You didn't?
Geum Bi!
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi, what are you doing here?
I wanted to see my dad.
Very much.
You can see me, then.
But where is this place, Mister?
This is the place you were looking for.
The place where Mom and Dad met.
I have no strength.
I used it all to get out of the forest.
What forest?
I was trapped in a forest.
I came out to see my dad.
But I don't know where he is.
I miss him so much
that I don't want to eat.
I can't even sleep well.
But I can't find him.
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi, Geum Bi!
It's an emergency patient! Please move!
She's a Niemann-Pick patient.
It's causing her breathing issues.
Get a tube in and check vitals.
You can't come in here.
Doctor, her saturation is dropping.
Intubation.
No.
Not yet, Geum Bi.
It's okay if you don't recognize me.
It's okay if you don't remember anything.
It's okay if you get angry and act mean.
It's not time yet.
It's not time yet, Geum Bi.
You can't leave yet.
Hwi Chul.
Geum Bi's dad, pull yourself together.
We can't act like this too.
It's not time yet though.
I know, and Geum Bi knows too.
Our Geum Bi won't leave like this.
There are still so many things
I haven't told her.
She can't just leave like this.
I'm telling you Geum Bi will be fine.
It's not time yet.
She's going into cardiac arrest.
Get the defibrillator now!
70.
No, Geum Bi. Not yet!
You can just head
towards that bright light.
What happens if I go there?
You will feel at peace.
You don't have to be sick anymore.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Don't think about anything and go.
Your trip is all over now.
Really?
If I leave like this,
my dad will cry a lot.
Geum Bi, you're very sick.
You should just rest now.
Not yet. I need to tell Dad something.
Dad.
Dad?
You're Geum Bi, aren't you?
I'm your aunt, Joon Hui.
Aunt.
Thank you very much for
coming into our home, Geum Bi.
Thanks to you, my sister
was able to laugh again.
Why are you here though?
Oh, you still want to continue
your trip there, don't you?
Yes.
You still want to see your dad
even though you're this sick?
Even though your whole body is in pain
and you feel like it's falling apart?
Yes.
It was brief for me,
but I was in a lot of pain.
I find it comfortable here.
I don't want to be in pain again.
Geum Bi, it will only be for a moment,
but you can see your mom and dad again.
I can really see them again?
In return, deliver a message for me
to my sister, Kang Hee.
What is it?
Tell her I'm doing fine,
so she should live happily.
All right.
You can only stay from the moment
you wake up until you fall asleep.
Once you fall asleep again,
you have to come back.
After that, you won't be able to
recognize your mom and dad again.
Even if you live.
Go straight in that direction.
Her vitals are back.
Check her vitals every hour.
Geum Bi.
Get up.
I was wrong.
Stop wasting your time.
Try another place.
Geum Bi nearly died but
came back three days ago.
She's having trouble breathing
due to muscular deterioration.
She went into cardiac arrest
and barely managed to survive.
They attached a breathing
machine to her small body.
She survived by getting
shocks from a defibrillator.
Why do you think she held on?
It would have been easier for her to go.
Because she wanted to live.
She's telling us she wants to live
with all the strength she has left.
Are you going to ignore that?
There's nothing I can do.
It's not that you want to give up
because you're tired?
You can see right through me.
You scare me.
I'm a mother who just saw my child
nearly die right in front of me.
How could I not be scary?
What should I do then?
Get up.
Get up and keep doing
what you have been doing.
Get up.
Okay.
Yes, I should.
How far did I get yesterday?
- Geum Bi.
Geum Bi.
It's... it's Dad.
Dad...
Geum Bi!
Mom.
It's Mom. Can you recognize me?
You recognize me?
Yes.
I knew you'd come back.
Little Miss Geum Bi,
Mom.
Yes, Geum Bi?
I met my aunt.
Aunt?
Joon Hui?
She wanted me to give you a message.
She says she's doing fine,
so she wants you to live happily.
But... I only have one day here.
One day?
Yes.
Aunt Joon Hui said that
once I fall asleep at night...
I have to go back.
Okay.
Then what should we do first?
Anything...
with Mom and Dad.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Today, I'll do whatever it is you want.
Don't worry.
Geum Bi!
We love you!
What took you so long to come?
We waited for you?
Let's go to the sea
together again, Geum Bi.
Geum Bi, look behind you.
Hi.
Mister.
Where did you go off to?
You didn't say anything before leaving.
You little thing.
How?
How could this be?
Geum Bi, I'm happy to see you again.
Doctors.
You'll fix me, won't you?
Yes, of course.
Of course.
If I can't fix you,
your mom won't let me live.
If I continue to live,
you can use me in clinical trials.
It could be dangerous.
It would take time, too.
Please do it.
I can do it.
All right.
Geum Bi, should we get going now?
Is this what they call a miracle
or something like that?
Still, we are scientists,
so we should look at the evidence.
Let's take a look at the MRI
Geum Bi took when she woke up.
My goodness.
I like it chewy and slightly cooked.
It needs to cooked more.
Dad had me sit here and
he knocked the pot over on purpose.
I saw the whole thing.
It was the only ramen we had.
What a waste that was.
You... that was your fault.
Chewy noodles.
It needs to be cooked and softer.
Chewy!
Stop fighting, you two.
I'll tip this pot over.
- No.
- You can't!
Still, the noodles should be cooked more.
It's all your fault, Dad.
Ramen ought to be cooked well
or it's better to eat it raw.
Dad.
If I were born again
you would be my dad again, right?
Of course.
Why? Were you going to
look for a different dad?
That's good, then.
Geum Bi.
Hwi Chul.
I love you both.
Dad.
I'm sleepy.
Sleep if you're tired.
Mom and Dad will be by your side.
Tell me a story.
What story?
The story of when we first met and
everything that happened until today.
Dad had been going around,
doing some bad things.
It looked like I would
be going to prison.
You showed up out of nowhere.
At first, you were so strange to me.
I thought to myself,
what kind of child is this?
Then your mom and I made
a promise to marry each other.
You officiated the ceremony, Geum Bi.
Suddenly, you told us to kiss.
It was so embarrassing.
Then your mom came at me like a wolf.
And then...
Then you...
you asked us to give you a younger
sibling that would take after you.
Geum Bi.
I can't sleep.
You should sleep now.
I won't be able to recognize
either of you from now on.
No matter where you are...
No matter what you're doing and where...
Whether you are here or not...
To Mom and Dad...
Geum Bi, you are just Geum Bi.
Life or death...
the three of us together.
You know that, right?
Life or death,
the three of us together.
Geum Bi, you're tired now,
so go to sleep.
Dad.
Mom.
Yes?
Even if I'm not here...
you two have to be happy together.
Don't fight with each other.
Also, I have a wish.
Tell us.
Dad will get you the moon and stars
if that's what you want.
I...
Okay.
Dad?
Yes, Geum Bi.
Dad, you are my dad, right?
Of course, I am.
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi?
Our child.
Oh, you're here.
By the way, you've been depositing
the donation to Geum Bi's doctor, right?
Don't worry about such things.
We're even making donations
for the benefit of others now.
Who knew this day would come?
If Geum Bi would get all better
I wouldn't wish for anything more
and it'd be a good world.
Do well with the interview.
Don't ruin this beautiful world.
A person like me doing an interview?
I feel a little shy.
He's here for the interview.
Oh, is that right?
Please sit for a moment.
People will be in line to buy limited
edition sneakers if you go here.
You need to go here and stand in line.
When the client shows up,
give the spot to the client and leave.
Can you do that?
I'll be back.
You can't let people
butt in front of you.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Hello.
What do you do here?
What do you mean?
It's a place of business.
In a legal and law-abiding manner.
Is it a place where you hire people
like that, pay crap, and overwork them?
Why would you say such a thing?
It's suspicious that you only
hire ex-convicts and the disabled.
We are open to hiring
ex-convicts and the disabled.
We do not discriminate.
It's quite obvious to me what this is.
You pretend to care about society on
the surface while sucking people dry.
Right?
If you don't want to work here,
please leave quietly.
Please do not ruin this beautiful day.
I heard that you're con artists.
Hey, you.
I'm sorry you got the wrong idea.
We stopped running scams long ago.
What a joke.
Can a leopard change its spots?
It can.
We can help you do it, too.
Are you insulting me?
You can sit down and listen
or you can leave.
You'll never forget it if you
take a beating in front of this woman.
What should I do, Min Ah?
I'll do what you tell me to.
Why did you let him hit you?
I told you to hit him.
You said to hold myself back.
When did I do that?
You told me to hold back
with your facial expression.
No, that was me telling you to hit him.
Oh, that stings.
That was you telling me to hit him?
You're no match for her.
You should give up on Chi Soo.
Damn it.
Do you have to say that
and make me feel bad about it?
What is it that happened
in Geum Bi's head?
The thing is...
I think I figured something out.
I think I did too.
Should we both say it?
Sounds good.
Inflammation?
What about the inflammation?
We have to treat that first.
And then?
We have to remove that first
and then go after the thalamus.
It's so simple.
Why didn't we think of it before?
Let's start again.
Our Geum Bi didn't leave us.
She looks like a baby in a mother's womb.
She does.
Would we be wronging Geum Bi if
she ended up with a younger sibling?
Geum Bi said she
wanted a younger sibling.
What if I grew apart from Geum Bi
after a baby came?
The Go Kang Hee that I know
is not that kind of woman.
- Hello.
Hi! Jae Ha, Shil La.
Wow, you two!
How did the time go by so fast?
That's what I'm saying.
Are you happy being back with
the wife that you divorced before?
Happy? I'm dying from all her nagging.
Is your husband still not working?
Damn it. What can I do? That's my life.
By the way, that kid grew up so much.
Wow. You can really see his facial
features starting to form now.
Does he look like his mom?
Many people say that.
If you look at him carefully,
he has some of his dad's features.
You don't want him to look like his dad.
Hey.
How does it feel to be a dad?
It's like you said.
Did I say something?
It's warm and feels like
there's a big egg in my heart.
I said something like that?
Never mind. I guess I heard it elsewhere.
I said some good words to you.
Oh! Here she comes.
Oh, it's Geum Bi.
Geum Bi!
[MO GEUM BI]
Have you been doing well, Geum Bi?
You look happy today.
Geum Bi, I brought you a present.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, we were able to
have a 17th birthday party.
I am more thankful.
Thanks to Geum Bi,
we made a lot of progress in research.
All right, I'll take a picture now.
Everyone gather around.
Okay. Let's get together.
Come on.
Hello.
Geum Bi's mom.
Thank you, Geum Bi's dad.
No need to thank me.
Why do you say that every time you come?
It's unnecessary.
Here, I will take the picture.
Go stand there.
If I am still alive
on my 17th birthday...
dress me in pretty clothes.
Make my hair look pretty.
Then I want to take
a picture with you, Dad.
Okay?
Look this way.
One, two...
You ugly thing.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever