Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[EPISODE 2]
I have to speak with my guests,
so go and wait inside, Geum Bi.
Geum Bi.
Oh, these people?
They're here to help me with something.
What, exactly?
Just... something complicated.
- That mister over there is...
- Hey, no, Geum Bi!
Oh!
How did you know to
come here, my Geum Bi?
Do you know Geum Bi?
He's trying to...
Why do you have stuff
all over your mouth?
You're 10 years old.
You should know better.
- Get off me!
- Hey!
What a good girl.
I told you to get off me!
- You know, this mister...
- Hey!
Why are you calling your dad "Mister"?
"Dad"?
Looks like my Geum Bi is
upset about something again.
She calls me "Dad" when she's happy,
but I'm "Mister" otherwise.
Yes.
Since when have you been a dad to me?
Dad will yell at you if you
keep acting this way, Geum Bi.
What are you doing
in front of all these adults?
Oh, this won't do. Come with me!
You need a scolding.
Kang Hee!
- Hey!
- Wait, sir! Wait!
This won't do. Strike.
What did you say?
You know, that thing you're great at.
When I give you the signal, strike.
I'll take care of the rest.
I told you, let go!
I have to talk to her!
That lady and mister over there
planned all this, and...
Child!
What... do you mean by that?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Ms. Kang Hee.
Don't agree to this deal.
What?
Those people seem a bit suspicious to me.
I feel that they may be
trying to scam you.
And this weighed on my conscience,
so I couldn't just sit and watch.
Those terrible con artists.
You bastard!
I knew something
seemed a bit off about you.
You think you'll be safe after
stabbing us in the back like this?
Strike!
You asshole.
That's a nice couch you've got there.
I'm going to end things here
since he's found me out
so don't blow things
out of proportion.
If I hear anything about you telling
people that we're scammers...
I'll make you regret it.
Don't you ever show your
face in front of me again.
If you do, I'll throw you
to the wolves on Jiri Mountain.
Just try me!
Let's go.
Sure. Let's go!
Wait, you...
Are you all right?
No.
Geez! Why did you go all-out?
Were you trying to kill him,
or something?
I can't control myself
once I'm in the air.
You're like a damned bear on a rampage!
He's weird in the head as it is.
What if he has terrible aftereffects?
You'll have to take
responsibility for him!
The hell?
You're the one who told me to do that!
Shut it!
To hell with him.
Are you all right?
Mister!
You should lie down for a bit longer.
Oh... I'm fine now. Yes.
Thanks to you,
I was able to avoid something terrible.
But because of me, you...
Oh, no.
I mean, I am an appraiser, so I can't
stand to see people toying with artwork.
Yeah, that's it.
Are you really all right?
Yes. But...
don't report them please.
If you do, they might try to
do something against you.
So I think it'd be best
to just let the matter drop.
Wait.
So are you telling me that you were
deceived by those people, too, Mister?
Hey, stop calling me "Mister."
It's making your dad upset
to hear such a thing.
I can't believe it.
I really can't.
It seems that I've
stayed here far too long.
Let's go, Geum Bi.
Um, wait.
That's not the way out.
- It's this way.
- Oh, yes.
No, it's not that way.
- It's that way.
- Yes, I see.
- I'll give you a call again!
- Yes, yes.
Don't even dream of it.
What?
You're making it way too obvious.
Hey, squirt.
Be a bit more specific.
Even a puppy would know that
you've fallen hard for Kang Hee.
Your eyes are all over the place
and your mouth has a stupid grin on it.
I thought you were drooling,
for a second there!
What do you know, punk?
I'm telling you,
you'll just end up hurt in the end.
Geez, you ugly little...
What's wrong with you?
You were about to con the woman you like.
Is this supposed to be some
sort of twisted, romantic surprise?
Don't you dare try to con Kang Hee.
If you do, I'll report you
to the cops right away.
You're the con artist, here!
What did I do?
At the buffet restaurant at that hotel.
You told her a fake fortune
and got money off her.
I was just trying to
get money to pay for our meal.
Also, I didn't tell her a fake fortune!
You have no right to say anything
if you have no experience in it.
So what did you say to
Ms. Kang Hee back then, anyway?
I told you. That's not something
to discuss with other people.
Come on, tell me already!
Hey! You ugly little...
You're even uglier, Mister!
What's all this?
Hey, what is this?
They can't do this just because
we're a little behind on rent!
To be honest, letting us off the hook for
six months straight was quite generous.
Let's split up and live alone, for now.
We need to get a new contract
signed as soon as we can.
Oh, what a cutie.
Prepare yourself.
You and I have hit rockbottom.
If we fail this one,
we're done for. You got that?
Are you mad at me because
I unleashed my flying kick on him?
How could you think of
a guy like him as your dad?
Oh, here. Here.
Take this.
Sorry, okay?
Where do we go now?
"We?"
[SKY ORPHANAGE -
ONE KILOMETER AWAY]
Don't go! Don't go!
I told you, I don't want to
go to an orphanage!
Go!
I asked you where we're going.
Yeah, so, isn't there a way I could
send her off to an orphanage?
If I just drop her off,
she'll report me to the cops!
Yeah.
Bye for now.
Hey, peel those eggs later.
Now I want you to give me a
straight answer to all of my questions.
Sincerely, and with gusto.
You got that?
I do, but what part of that makes it
necessary for me to stop peeling eggs?
Fine. You can keep peeling them.
Shoot.
About your mom.
You really don't remember her?
How could I, when I've never seen her?
You've seen her, though, Mister.
You even slept with her.
So why can't you remember?
What did you have for lunch a week ago?
Who would remember
little details like that?
See?
You can't even remember
what you ate a week ago
so how do you expect me to
remember something from 10 years ago?
I've slept with tons of women in my life.
Your aunt really didn't
tell you anything?
Yeah.
You may be a little punk,
but you have a sharp wit
so I'm sure you've realized
the nature of the situation.
- You know, you and I...
- I know.
You got evicted, right?
Because you couldn't
pay your rent, Mister.
But how come you can't
make any money, Mister?
That's why I'm trying to make some now.
But if I'm to take care of you properly,
I can't make money how I usually do.
So, that's why...
Why are you beating around the bush?
What?
You're telling me to go to an orphanage.
Well, um... yeah.
Yeah.
I'm saying this since you
seem to understand, but...
I'm not going.
What?
I said, I'm not going to an orphanage.
You don't know what a dire
situation we're in right now, do you?
This isn't the time for you
to be having a tantrum.
You're saying that because
you don't know this
but I can't afford to waste
any time at a place like that.
What do you mean by that?
I have to hurry and go to sleep
since I have school tomorrow.
Feel free to run away while
I'm asleep, if you want to.
You think I won't be able to?
46-du-1985.
What's that?
You don't even know your
own license plate number?
Want me to recite your
social security number, too?
Why, you little...
Did you look through my wallet?
- Yep.
- When?
Why does that even matter?
Hey, you...
Wow, that little...
Sheesh.
What do I do with her?
Where did he go?
[POLICE]
Hey, don't you dare call that number.
You should've been here on time
if you made a promise!
Do you know how many
bad guys are out there?
They kidnap kids, and things like that.
They have bad hearts, not bad eyes.
Where did you go?
To get us a place to live.
It's supposed to rain today, though.
Do you really believe that?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
We're not supposed
to have an open flame here.
You know, the thing
about the adult world
is that you really can't get by
if you always follow the rules.
You're so lucky.
Why?
Because you're a child.
What if you start a fire?
There's nothing flammable around here.
It's completely desolate.
Turn the stove off.
- It's fine.
- It's not that.
You're overcooking the ramen!
Ramen isn't good unless
you overcook it a little!
What's so great about
disgustingly overcooked noodles?
It only tastes good when
it still has a bit of a bite!
Why would you even
bother cooking it, then?
You might as well eat it raw,
like a biscuit!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Why, you...
You little!
What are you going to do about this?
I knew you'd do this! I knew it!
That was the last packet of ramen we had!
I don't even have money to buy ramen!
See, I told you that it'd rain!
Don't worry. It's a waterproof tent.
Waterproof, huh?
Yeah. It is.
See? The water that's
in here isn't draining.
What is this? Are we going
to sit like this all night?
Hey, squirt.
Elementary schoolers go to boot camps
and the like during vacations, right?
And you even pay to go to those things.
So you should be able to
handle at least this much.
Isn't that right,
Little Miss Geum Bi?
Sure, fine. Let's do it,
then, and try to have fun.
Gee, what a fun-filled
boot camp experience!
I'm starving!
Go to sleep, then! None of that
will matter when you're asleep!
How am I supposed to sleep in here
when it's all flooded?
You're so annoying.
And ugly, to boot!
Stop moving!
You're making the tent shift!
Geez, you...
Go to sleep!
What did you have for dinner
last night, Jae Ha?
I had risotto at a restaurant.
What about you?
I had beef.
I had steak.
Hey, take a shower once in
a while, why don't you?
Do you not even have
running water at home?
Why wouldn't I have water?
My place is practically flooded with it.
You reek!
No, she doesn't.
Take a good whiff.
She smells like a sewer!
How is this a sewer smell?
Ew, get that out of my face!
How disgusting!
Hello, Teacher!
Why, you little...
Shil La.
What are you doing?
Bring all your agenda
books to me, everyone.
Geum Bi. Did something happen at home?
What?
Enjoy.
Enjoy!
Enjoy, or something.
Hey! These are way too small!
Give me one more!
How could I do that?
It's two per person.
You should do it fairly!
Yeah, I did.
I gave you two.
You're so stingy.
How is this fair, when you
gave me small ones on purpose?
What's going on?
What's with the commotion?
Geum Bi wants me to give
just her more katsu.
You shouldn't be like that, Geum Bi.
That's not it!
- Teacher...
- Hurry up and move!
The next person is waiting.
It's fine. You have them.
I don't like pork.
So eat them for me, okay?
Well then, okay.
Are you a bum?
You even look like one.
At least I'm not ugly like you.
What? What did you say?
Um...
[PUBLIC WELFARE OFFICE]
A person I know has a daughter.
But she has no mom, and her
dad is raising her by himself.
But due to his circumstances
he thinks that he may have to
leave his child at an orphanage.
What happens then?
Why aren't you eating it?
You even fought to get another one.
There are a lot more pitiful people
in this world than I thought.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You don't even have money
for a bowl of rice and soup?
I need to make her feel like
we're really in a critical state.
I can't believe you!
You're starving her on purpose?
A child?
I'm not starving her!
She gets lunch at school, anyway.
Well? Have you found a
weakness in her yet?
It's as if she was made
to withstand the outdoors.
It's frightening, really.
Then you have to be tougher on her.
Just look at him! At this rate,
he'll be the one to die first.
Do whatever you have to do
to get her off our backs.
If she sticks around Go Kang Hee,
she'll ruin all our plans!
Okay, I get it, already!
Let me eat in peace.
At first, I was going to take everything
and pass it over to the antiques guy.
But you're on the police's radar now
because of that forged painting thing.
So?
First, we were thinking of getting her
art for cheap, and then making a profit.
But the guys dealing with the money will
take a huge chunk, and we'll get pennies.
So, there's no reason for us to do it
when there's nothing in it for us.
No, that's not right.
We may be lowballing her, but there
will still be a lot of money involved.
And that's what we're after.
And I know one of her weak spots.
Apparently, she once had a daughter.
So?
I heard that she died.
And I don't know the details, but she
seems to shoulder a lot of the blame.
See? You really can't tell with women,
based on their looks alone.
She made her kid die, and yet she's
acting all uppity. How revolting.
What is it that she did
so wrong, exactly?
How would I know?
That doesn't matter, anyway.
So treat her all nice and warm-like
and make her trust you completely.
Oh, stop it!
Don't you dare screw this one up, too!
I'll give you a beating
that you'll never forget.
Where have you been?
Can't we sleep at the sauna tonight?
It's hard, isn't it,
Little Miss Geum Bi?
But if we're going to stay together,
we have no choice but to live like this.
I have no money,
but I still have to look after you.
And I can't even work
because of you.
You can work while I'm at school.
I'm sure you don't know this
but it's really tough to find
a project like that one.
Man. It'll be hard for us to even
have ramen after tomorrow.
What should we do?
Don't worry!
You're hungry, right? Eat this.
What's this?
I got it for lunch today,
but I don't like pork or milk.
It's okay. You eat it.
Why are you being so prideful
when we're in this situation?
Hurry and eat.
It's fine. You eat it.
Did you eat something
without telling me?
What are you talking about?
I've been starving all day.
Exactly, so hurry up and eat.
And stop caring about your pride.
It's fine...
Have some milk, too.
Sure.
Make sure you chew properly!
Are you in a lot of pain?
Don't ask me anything.
Talking makes my head hurt more.
Then we should hurry
and get you to a hospital.
I can't go. No money.
[MS. GO KANG HEE]
You have a call.
I don't want to deal with that.
Just leave it for now.
Hello?
I told you to just leave it.
Mister is in a lot of pain right now.
He didn't really eat anything,
but he started throwing up
and he's so frail
that he can't even move!
Yes, please. Hurry.
Geum Bi, where are you?
Okay. Don't cry, and just wait for me.
Yeah, don't worry.
Hey, it's not like anyone died!
Why are you crying?
Who was it?
Kang Hee.
What?
I thought you said that you were sick!
So stay still, okay?
Why did you overreact like that?
Damn it, this is driving me crazy.
Are you feeling a bit better?
Yes. I'm okay.
You didn't have to come.
How could I not,
when you have a child with you?
It'll be winter soon.
You can't continue living like this.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it myself.
- Can you walk?
- What?
Oh, of course! It's not like
I have a terminal illness.
Let's go, then.
What?
But you know, Kang Hee.
Who did you come to see?
Well, that's a secret.
I wanted to see you.
Well, I rushed over because I
really wanted to see you, Geum Bi.
Really?
This is the room that
my father used to use.
Don't worry about anything,
and get some rest.
I feel like I'm inconveniencing
you quite a bit.
You saved me from getting scammed.
I'd be inhumane if I didn't
do at least this for you.
Get some rest.
You aren't human.
You're divine.
Man, why am I so pathetic?
Wow. It's huge.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
A cute child went to a chicken coop
and tried to catch a hen, but it escaped.
A hungry fox outside said "Yes!"
and scampered away with it in its mouth.
"Cluck," the chicken cried!
A cute child went to a chicken coop
and tried to catch a hen, but it escaped.
Man, this is driving me crazy!
The bathroom is that way.
Make sure the shower head isn't on
when you turn on the water.
If it is, water will get everywhere.
Um, yes. I will.
So your face gets hot when
you take a bath too, huh?
The lady living next door
to us was like that, too.
Huh? Oh.
But still, your face is
way too overheated.
Aren't you tired, Geum Bi?
I am.
Want to get changed
and go to sleep?
We're sleeping together?
Why? You don't want to?
No, I want to!
Yes! Great job, Hwi Chul.
Great, great job.
This means that our sacrifice
wasn't for naught.
Yeah, exactly!
If you've gotten in there,
you're almost done!
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Are you okay, even after
taking Jae Kyung's flying kick?
You're so annoying! Why are
you calling so early in the morning?
My ears are ringing. Bye.
I said all right, already!
Do you have dementia, or something?
How many times do I have to
tell you the same thing?
Yeah!
Okay.
Geez. Oh man.
Come and eat!
Oh, yes!
I got this for lunch today,
but I don't really like pork or milk.
Wow, you sure have a
healthy appetite!
You like milk, don't you?
But still, you need to
have a proper breakfast.
So no more milk, okay?
- Go and get your dad.
- Okay!
Mister!
Yeah.
She wants you to come and eat.
Yeah, sure.
I only got rice for us two.
What is it? Are you mad
that you get no rice?
This is even better than rice.
You don't even know.
Really? Then trade with me.
Stop being ridiculous.
- Come on, let's trade.
- I said no!
- I'll give you 500 won.
- I don't need it!
Then hurry up and eat,
and earn your keep.
The hell are you
going on about, now?
You really don't need to do that.
No, it's fine. You made me porridge,
so I should pay you back somehow.
I thought we were meeting outside.
Well, I had some extra time,
so I came to get you.
And the front door was wide open, too.
- I'll wait inside.
- Um...
Take your time getting ready.
Jae Jin, I'll meet you later.
I'm done fixing your shower.
Who's this guy?
Well, yes. Your situation
does sound grim.
But, still.
I never thought that someone
like an art appraiser
would have to be
living out of their car.
Mr. Jae Jin!
I have a lot of debt, you see...
Oh, debt?
But, you know...
even people who build skyscrapers don't
finance all of that with their money.
They all take on debts to do that.
How old are you?
37.
So you're practically 40 already.
And yet, you have a
10-year-old daughter.
And you live out of your car?
Jae Jin, let's leave now.
What, and leave these people in here?
Do you want to reschedule
our plans for today, then?
Excuse me.
To have a male stranger staying in a home
where a woman lives alone for this long
is not unacceptable,
don't you think?
Yes, and I was actually on my way out.
Why don't you do this, then?
I'll get you a room in our hospital.
You can receive treatment there.
Of course, I'm not quite okay with
letting you stay there for free.
So when you make
a full recovery, you can...
do some odd jobs around the
hospital to pay your bill off.
How about it?
No. I'm fine now.
You don't need to worry
about your pride, here!
It's okay to lean on others a bit
when you're in a bind.
And you disregarded all that by
staying here yesterday, anyway.
Yes, well...
but I'm really okay now.
Little Miss Geum Bi. Let's go.
Um, I'll be in touch with you.
No, don't contact me.
Are you angry?
Angry? I have no right to be angry.
Come over and play again, Geum Bi.
Um, also...
Yes?
Find someone else.
What do you mean by that?
Don't work with the arts dealer
who introduced that con artist to you.
Work with someone else.
Someone more trustworthy.
We've been working with him
since my father was around.
I'm sure this was just an
honest mistake on his part.
Find someone with a conscience
who will give you a fair price
instead of ripping you off!
And when you sell your things, don't
fall for the lies of some scamming thugs!
Make sure you entrust that
money to a trustworthy bank!
And don't make it obvious
that you have a lot of money, got it?
- But...
- Do you understand?
As if I have the right to say anything
about having a conscience.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hey, get back here!
Here it is!
You all have your supplies, right?
Yes!
Take out your oil pastels.
What are you looking for?
My oil pastels. They're gone.
Are you sure you didn't
just leave them at home?
I definitely packed them
when I was in the car last night.
Car?
Well... anyway, where did they go?
Here, want to share mine?
Okay.
Figures.
I knew it wouldn't make it in.
Why are you drinking in broad daylight?
What about it?
I'm breaking stereotypes,
living outside of the box!
You have no sense of creativity.
What kind of drunken nonsense is that?
Here, take this!
What is this?
The thing you asked me
to get for you. What a hassle.
[ORPHANAGE ENTRY APPLICATION]
Damn, why is it that you
do things like this so fast
when you take your sweet time
doing everything else?
How is it that you even complain
when I do you favors?
Speaking of which,
let's take care of this quickly
and put an end to it, already.
No good will come
out of dragging this on.
This punk.
Take him.
So, have you decided
not to sell them, then?
Kang Hee?
Oh. I'm going to ask
around some more.
Sorry. Can I ask you to
wait just a bit longer?
I've never hounded you down
about paying me back.
Why do you keep making me
out to seem so ruthless?
That's not what I meant.
I'll pay you back soon.
And when I start working again...
There you go again.
Sorry.
Have a glass today, won't you?
Let's sleep at the sauna tonight.
Did you get money?
Just eat your food.
What did you do this time?
What are you talking about?
Stop messing around, you little punk!
Kang Hee told me to come
over anytime, though.
Don't ever go there again.
- Why not?
- I said, don't go there!
I'll go if I go. What are
you going to do about it?
If you want to go, then go!
She'll be so happy to see
a con artist's daughter at her door.
But you didn't con her.
I might as well have!
Aw, no!
What? Get away from me, kid.
I'm a formidable match.
Just pick whatever and let's go.
Shush for a second!
These last a really long time.
They're all pretty much the same.
No, they're not!
All right, all right.
Hurry up and pick one.
[PARKING TICKET]
What is this?
Are you serious?
This is why I told you to
hurry and pick one!
So why did you park your car
where you're not supposed to?
I did it because you said you had to
buy those oil pastels no matter what!
What does that have to do with this?
You're the one in the wrong here, Mister.
You said it was cheaper
to buy them there!
Yeah! And we got them
for cheap, like I said!
You call this cheap?
Do you know how expensive
parking tickets are?
I don't!
You don't?
So what do you actually know, then?
You don't know about my situation,
or where your aunt went
or even who your mom is!
How dare you look at me like that?
For a pipsqueak,
you sure are rude.
You think I'll take you in
if you throw a tantrum?
Who's the one actually
throwing a tantrum, here?
What?
Being old doesn't make you an adult.
Why, you little...
You always do bad things
but don't ever take responsibility
and lie all the time!
Then you go around blaming others.
You lost your house,
so you sleep in your car!
You only go to convenience stores
since you don't have money for real food!
Shut your mouth!
Aren't you even ashamed?
What did you say?
Do you really think that Kang Hee
would spare someone like you a glance?
You don't even know your place.
Shut your mouth, now.
How dare you act up like this?
It's not fair that I can't see Kang Hee
because of someone like you.
Go, then! Go and see her!
Go and see her all you want, then!
You said that your scam was exposed
and she wouldn't see a conman's daughter!
Tell her that you're
not my daughter, then!
And who cares if you're my daughter?
Hey.
Hey!
Then, go!
Sheesh...
[LIST OF ARTWORK AND PRICES]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is Kim Mi Ri from the
Traffic Information Center.
That little whelp.
I'll leave her forever if she
doesn't come back in 10 minutes.
[GIL HO]
What a reckless pipsqueak.
And she's ugly, to boot.
[FROM GIL HO:
WHERE ARE YOU?]
Geum Bi.
How hasn't she called me even once?
Man, I'm so pissed!
Goodness...
Oh, damn it all! Why couldn't they
come before I put my face mask on?
What happened to you, Gil Ho?
Hurry and call Hwi Chul.
You came here just to tell me that?
What'd you do with your phone?
It was stolen!
Hurry and call him!
It was stolen? By whom?
[OUTGOING CALL: HWI CHUL]
[ORPHANAGE ENTRY APPLICATION]
What?
All right.
That little girl!
Hey, Geum Bi!
Geum Bi!
Stop right there!
Hey! Stop!
You little pipsqueak...
You.
It's been a while.
Geum Bi!
Stop right there, Geum Bi!
Hey!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[OH MY GEUM BI]
Are you dying, Mister?
Who are you?
Your dad is a much worse
person than I am.
I heard that you're being
sent to an orphanage.
There won't be a problem if I can take
care of her until her father comes back.
She'd be staying in a stranger's home.
Of course that's a problem.
Let's do a biopsy.
The fact that the liver and spleen
are swollen bothers me a bit.
You have to get checked, Geum Bi!
I told you, I'm not going!