(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
(EPISODE 3)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Why are you crying so much in the middle of the night?
Stop crying.
People may think I'm dying.
Will you die?
Of course, I will.
Not now, though.
I'll die in 50 years.
You'll probably be 60 by then.
You'll be an old witch.
What? Do you want me to die soon?
I don't care if you die or live.
You are so ungrateful.
What did the doctor say? Are you hurt?
I didn't ask you to save me.
Oh, you're right.
You never said that.
I should have left you.
You're so ugly.
What are you doing?
Hey, stop. My head hurts.
- Stop it.
- Stop. He has a concussion.
- A concussion?
- Yes.
It's nothing serious, but you'll feel nauseous.
You also sprained your neck. Please don't move.
The doctor will be here soon.
Oh my gosh.
I have a concussion and a sprained neck.
Did you hear that?
I don't think you should get angry right now.
Just you wait until I get better.
I'll tie you from the ceiling and...
Kang Hee.
Are you okay?
Did you call her?
Who else would I call?
I couldn't call those con artists.
Watch your mouth.
What will you do now?
She got me into an accident and now this.
It's getting colder. What will you do with...
How dare you jump in front of a truck?
I didn't jump.
The truck came out from nowhere.
Geum Bi needs a CT scan.
A CT scan?
You don't know, do you?
That really hurts.
I won't do it.
I found this in her stomach area.
Her liver and spleen are swollen up.
There is a possibility that it's a metabolic disease...
or leukemia.
Leukemia?
No, we did a CT scan and a blood test.
She seems to be fine.
You shocked me.
But we should do a biopsy.
I thought she was fine.
That's according to the CT scan and the blood test.
Then why?
I am concerned about her swollen liver and spleen.
I'm not sure about her spleen,
but she already acts like she has a huge liver.
If you sign this consent,
we'll conduct the biopsy right away.
Okay.
- May I use the pen?
- Sure.
I hope you're not ripping us off.
Hey, kid!
Why is she so fast?
- What's her name?
- Yoo Geum Bi.
Geum Bi!
Yoo Geum Bi?
No way.
Geum Bi, you have to do this.
I said, no.
Geum Bi.
You have to get a checkup.
Never.
It won't hurt that much.
They are all lying. I know that.
How do you know?
I just know.
Your dad has some business to take care of.
Why don't you come back to my house with me?
The door is opening.
Don't you want to come along?
I do. But...
Come here.
Okay. I understand.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Is your pride so important...
that you'll make your kid live on the streets?
Pride? I threw that away a long time ago.
Then why are you so persistent?
I want to ask you the same question.
You're being so persistent about having...
two strangers in your house.
Are you Mother Teresa or something?
If you want to help someone,
there are more unfortunate people around.
Look at me.
You're already here. Why?
No.
You haven't looked at me once since yesterday.
Look into my eyes.
I only look at pretty women.
Then why did you draw the ugly woman's face?
My goodness, forget about it.
How do you know her?
I never said you were ugly.
Why did you bring juice?
You should've brought soju.
Did Chi Soo call you again?
Why? Do you feel nauseous?
I'm running away tonight.
Why?
A concussion is a serious medical condition.
I don't think I can live on the streets with a kid.
It looks like she'll take care of her for a while.
I'm sure the kid won't tell the police.
And if she forgets me, it's all for the best.
Who's she?
Kang Hee?
You should go with her. Don't run away.
Are you trying to betray us...
because you're smitten by her?
Did I ever ruin anything because of a woman?
Then just go to her house!
Seize your opportunity while you have a chance.
Darn it. I'm just saying.
I don't want to get involved with her.
- Why?
- I don't know. Just because.
I'm leaving this planet. Don't look for me.
Shut your mouth, you idiot.
Why aren't you asleep?
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm just getting some air.
The nurse told you not to move.
Nonsense. How can I not move around?
Go in and sleep.
If you were going to run away, don't get caught.
What are you talking about?
That is not right. I'm not running away.
I won't run away, so go sleep.
Put your cast back on.
You should worry about yourself.
Don't get caught.
I'll look out for you.
- What?
- Don't worry.
I won't tell the police.
Tell them what?
That you abandoned me.
You have to go back to jail if the judge finds out.
I told you. I'm not running away.
I told you. I won't tell them.
You never trust me.
If I run away,
what will you do?
I looked into it,
and an orphanage doesn't sound so bad.
I will keep my promise.
What promise?
I prayed for you when you were unconscious.
That I'll go to the orphanage if you wake up.
So go.
It'll be embarrassing for me if you get caught.
What are you waiting for?
Didn't you desperately want to send me to an orphanage?
Do you go to church?
No.
What about Catholic church?
Do you go to temples?
Forget it then.
Forget what?
You don't have a religion,
so your prayers don't count.
You don't have to keep your promises.
I'm fine. Stop pretending to be nice.
You should call Kang Hee tomorrow.
Why?
You said you wanted to go there.
I said I'm not going.
You should run away when you have the chance.
Are you sure?
Then don't go. I'll go by myself.
If you don't go to bed early, you won't get tall.
What's so good about being tall?
You don't know anything.
The only short thing people like...
are waiting lines at emergency rooms.
That was a joke.
Gosh, where's your sense of humor?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
You can stay here, Geum Bi.
Do you like it?
I do.
But this is a kid's bed.
A long time ago...
It was your bed once, wasn't it?
Gosh.
I envy you.
- Why?
- For having a sweet daughter like her.
You don't know what you're talking about.
When she doesn't behave, I feel like throwing her away.
Is that why you jumped in front of a truck for her?
That was an impulsive kind of thing.
I don't even remember what happened.
To be honest,
I was suspicious of you, too.
I thought you might be one of the scammers.
But when I saw how you were with her,
I knew.
I knew you were a man of good nature.
Even if you did something wrong,
it was probably inevitable.
You don't know anything about me.
Are you really a con artist then?
Yes.
That's cool, you know?
I'm just a Mother Teresa wannabe.
You hold grudges, don't you?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be.
About being ugly.
Stop it.
Cut it out.
It's just that you won't make eye contact with me.
That's how guilty people are.
They can't look directly into someone else's eyes.
Just how guilty are you?
My crime is that I wasted my life.
Isn't that a line from a movie?
Did you watch it?
I didn't think you'd notice. It's such an old movie.
What's so bad about wasting some of your life?
You can make up for it starting from now.
Are you okay?
Oh, gosh.
- Oh, no.
- I'm fine.
I'll do it.
Am I that hideous?
Do I make you want to throw up?
Why are you being like that?
You hold grudges for way too long.
When one of these sperms meets an egg,
a baby gets made inside a mom's belly.
When Mom and Dad fall in love,
a sperm meets an egg, creating a baby.
When babies grows up,
they'll turn into beautiful children like you.
Do you see now...
how precious every one of you are?
- Yes.
Oh, my head.
(JUN HEE, 6 YEARS OLD)
(JUN HEE, 7 YEARS OLD)
That woman...
used to have a daughter.
(JAE GYUNG)
It's not like she's our only target.
Why are you trying to pull off something gone wrong?
It almost went wrong.
We have to keep trying until it does go wrong.
Where's your humanity?
Are you really willing to become lowly crooks?
Don't make me laugh.
What exactly are we if not crooks?
Do you know how con artists are graded?
What's the point of that?
The best con artists leave the victims unaware...
of the con even after the situation is long over.
Mediocre con artists leave the victims aware...
of the con after the situation is over.
Getting the cover blown before the con is over...
is what makes the worst con artists.
You're the worst then.
You got that right.
My cover was blown...
all thanks to you.
Why is that because of me?
We risked blowing our covers...
so you could continue to work on her.
And this is how you repay me?
You hurt my pride as a con artist.
Are you being like this...
because you fell in love with that woman?
Please come to your senses.
You very well know how much we invested in this.
If we pull this off,
we won't have to live like this anymore.
"Boys, be ambitious."
We need to be more ambitious.
Can we be more ambitious?
I said I got it. I'm trying.
Of course, you are.
Start by replacing this.
What's this?
In that house,
she should have something that looks like this.
So?
Replace that with this one.
I thought we'll be taking everything she owns.
With what happened last time,
we have to find ourselves a new financial.
It takes money to plan our next move.
Fine. I'll replace it when I get the chance.
No.
What?
- Get up.
- What?
You're going right now!
Where are you going?
Do you have to do this?
Yes, I do.
Jae Gyung does have a drive to get things done.
What drive?
What are you waiting for?
Give me that.
Give it to me.
What do we do?
Why are you so scared?
It's not like we did anything wrong.
We did, you idiot.
- Come on. Hide.
- Fine.
- I'm going.
- Hurry.
- Be quiet.
- My goodness.
Duck.
You're home very early.
I came back home right after an errand.
Are you skipping work?
Why?
Can't an ugly person skip work?
Of course, she can.
And I wasn't saying that you were ugly.
What an idiot.
Shut your mouth.
Let's eat dinner once Geum Bi gets home.
Okay.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
That was my dad's birthday gift for me.
It was the spring of my 15th birthday.
I see.
You must've loved these...
since you were a kid.
It was actually for someone else.
Someone else?
I saw a bicycle in the storage...
while cleaning the house.
It's very rusty, isn't it?
It seemed like a child's bicycle.
I think we've grown closer.
Pardon?
Oh, sure.
But we're not close enough...
to share our difficult pasts.
Yes, I agree.
I wonder why you and Geum Bi have different last names.
But I won't ask.
You can tell me...
when the time is right.
If you can't throw it out,
take it out and polish it.
I know I'm over the line here,
but I think that would hurt less.
If you don't, it'll continue to hurt you.
Bye.
- Is it good?
- It is.
Today, I learned...
how babies are formed.
Which grade are you in?
I'm in third grade. Don't you know?
So how are babies formed?
I saw pictures and descriptions,
but I'm not sure if I know.
It's weird, though.
I don't think babies come after holding hands.
How was I made?
Why do you ask?
You were made to look ugly.
I'll explain it to you when we get home.
You will learn in time after you grow up.
What if I don't become an adult?
Quick-tempered kids...
tend to have kids early.
Don't ever do that, okay?
What are you talking about?
(GIL HO)
Hello?
- Is this a fake?
- My gosh.
Why did you steal this?
Darn it. Is he out of his mind?
Let's go.
Goodbye.
The weather is so nice.
What are you doing in school today?
You...
You became a coward.
You weren't like this before.
It's been 15 years. Haven't you had enough?
You know me.
You can't leave me until the day you die.
I don't have anything I can give you.
You are scared.
What's wrong?
You said you didn't care if you died or lived.
Yes. I don't care if I die or live.
Really?
I heard you are onto something with Gil Ho.
Wrap up everything in a week and hand it over.
Give this to Gil Ho.
How can you be confused?
I told you to switch them.
How can you give me the fake one?
You are so stupid.
You're such an idiot.
What? Did Chi Soo...
find you?
You should stay low for a while.
Then what about you?
I'll stay low and see how things turn out.
You can keep it if you'd like.
Really?
I hope you know that we can't stay here...
forever.
I do.
But we can sleep in the car.
We have that waterproof tent, too.
It's going to be winter soon.
You know that we can't do that.
So what? Is this about the orphanage again?
What if...
I find your aunt?
Forget it.
That little brat.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
It's a bicycle.
Whose is it?
Do you want to try?
How are you supposed to fold it?
I don't know.
Sorry. I didn't see it.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
- No.
- Yes, you did.
No, I didn't.
And what if I did?
I'm sorry. I didn't see your foot.
Sil La.
Are you Geum Bi?
How dare you put your hands on my daughter?
You can't be doing that to her.
She was the one to step on my frog first.
What frog? What are you talking about?
Calm down, Ma'am.
Where were you...
when this was going down?
Geum Bi. Tell her you're sorry.
Why should I be? She started it.
Look at her.
She's an uneducated brat.
What are you glaring at?
You're ugly.
What?
(1: WRITE A DIARY, 2: STUDY ENGLISH)
I'll call your dad separately,
but tell him to come see me anyway.
Do you understand?
Where does she live?
I don't know.
Isn't there anyone who knows?
- Gosh.
- Hello.
Hello.
Mo Hwi Cheol. What brings you here?
I'm looking for someone. I've got the name and address.
Why? Did a con go wrong?
Since when do you care?
I don't.
500 dollars up front.
I'll have to make it up with something else.
You're joking, right?
Why don't you join them over there?
You could pay me with your winnings.
Oh, no.
It's a bomb.
I win.
I'll get you next time.
Nice.
Isn't there any other way?
There is.
But are you up for it?
I'll do whatever it takes.
Just find the person I'm looking for.
That aunt you're looking for is Kim Young Ji.
She got a divorce three years ago.
She has a daughter, but they're not blood-related.
What about her birth mother?
I'll have to increase the payment for that information.
Where is this person right now?
By the looks of the credit card history,
she's leaving the country.
She sold her house.
Who's her birth mother?
I tried my best.
Is abandoning a child the best you can do?
What more do you want from me?
I raised someone else's daughter all this time.
You were paid to do that.
Where's your sense of responsibility?
Gosh. Are you lecturing me?
You're the one who wasn't even aware...
of your child's presence until now.
She calls you, "Aunt".
You weren't planning on taking care of her, were you?
You think you did your best?
Do you know what condition she was in when we met?
Was that the best you could do? Answer me!
You're right. I told her to call me her aunt.
And what would happen to me...
when her birth mother shows up asking her back?
How can a dead person come looking for her?
She's alive?
Why would you do that to her, then?
Don't touch me.
Fine.
I don't care why she lied...
or why she abandoned her own child,
but how am I her father?
- Why not?
- Come on!
I can't be the only one she slept with!
No matter how foolish,
she can tell who the real father is.
Did she say that?
Is she sure she's mine?
How can you not recognize your own daughter?
Where is she now?
Where is Joo Young right now?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I heard that...
she fled to Spain five years ago.
Didn't Geum Bi tell you?
Tell me what?
About herself.
Never mind. Forget it.
I don't have anything to say to you anymore.
Don't come looking for me.
Let's go.
Who are you?
Are you Geum Bi's grandfather?
Who's Geum Bi?
What kind of a kid doesn't have a home?
What does her parents do exactly?
This school isn't for children-in-needs.
I can't send my kid here knowing what I know.
What happened, Geum Bi?
I can't seem to reach your father.
You don't live where it says you do.
Tell me.
I'm asking you a question.
Where are you staying right now?
Like I said, she'll have to follow the regulations.
Isn't there any other way?
If a child doesn't have any relatives,
we have to take measures according to the rules.
Can't we find a way if I visit...
the Welfare Center?
I do feel sorry for Geum Bi,
but there are rules so it might not work.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
He isn't picking up.
Maybe he ended up dead somewhere.
Don't say things like that.
Where on earth did he go?
If I find him, I'll kill him myself.
I thought this was waterproof.
Yes. It's waterproof.
See?
Once the rain gets in, it doesn't go out.
- Hey.
- Go away.
I'm in no mood to deal with you.
I heard you're going to an orphanage.
- What?
- Didn't you know?
Your aunt and dad both ran away so now,
you have to go to an orphanage.
Is that true?
Is he not picking up?
Don't worry, Geum Bi.
I'll figure something out.
It's okay. Ever since we were in the hospital,
I was preparing to go to an orphanage.
I won't send you away.
See you later.
It's time to earn your keep.
- How?
- Do you know...
the idiots who sell...
fake goods to the elderly?
Some poor, old lady gave them 8,000 dollars.
Go and get 5,000 from them.
I'll call us even plus a little allowance.
Geum Bi's not here.
That's three days in a row.
Has anyone seen Geum Bi outside of school?
- No.
Have you seen her?
No. Is something wrong?
I'll scream.
What for?
Do you miss your dad?
Are you going to lie and say you're his friend?
We were friends once.
Not anymore.
Who are you?
When you see your dad,
tell him that he can't run away.
That's nonsense.
Once a friend, always a friend.
How can you stop?
(ANTI-AGING)
You scumbags!
(THE MIRACLE ANTI-AGER, X380)
Who do you think you are?
Do you think I'm a bad guy?
I am.
I am a bad guy.
But your dad's much worse than I am.
I knew him...
since we were their age.
He used to lie all the time.
He deceived others and himself.
He even forgot that he'd deceived someone.
He ruined someone else's life...
and can't even remember what he did.
You'll become the same if you stay around him.
Is that what you want?
You're wrong.
He used to go around saying,
"I don't care if I die today."
Would someone like that...
take care of you?
You scumbags.
Stay down.
Are you done?
You look like you want to dance a bit more.
Come at me.
Where were you...
while she was growing up?
I prayed while you were unconscious.
That I'd go to an orphanage if you woke up.
Can't you even recognize your own blood?
Shoot.
That's gross.
I have a loose tooth now.
- You jerks.
- Get out of the way.
Wait, wait!
You idiots.
What is he doing?
Give me a moment.
Okay, okay.
See this?
What's that?
How dare you?
It's too late, you morons.
I sent it out already.
I see you're carrying a weapon.
You'll be arrested for criminal charges.
Criminal or civil? Take your pick.
I'll deal with you whichever way you want.
You're all so bad at this.
That's gross.
Listen, you jerks.
I have a concussion...
and a sprained neck, too.
You're all going down for this.
(I WON'T LET YOU GO UNTIL I DIE.)
Read this.
(CONDITIONS TO BECOME FOSTER PARENTS)
It's what she wants.
Even a great orphanage...
can't be as good as a home.
You're single...
and you aren't related to the girl.
Her father left her with me.
It'll be fine if I take her in...
until her dad returns.
How is it fine?
She'll be with a complete stranger.
I can be a foster parent.
You're single.
It's not applicable to single women.
If you really want her,
send her to an orphanage...
and apply to adopt her.
I'm not sure it'll work, though.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Please leave a message...
after the tone, then press sharp or the asterisk.
Geum Bi's about to go to an orphanage. Where are you?
What kind of a dad are you?
Call as soon as you get this.
Geum Bi.
It's okay.
I knew this would happen.
Have you heard from your dad yet?
Even if he comes back,
I'll go to the orphanage.
I tried living with him...
and I just don't think we'll get along.
Sit down. Let's eat.
Can I eat all this?
You don't have to.
Eat as much as you want and leave the rest.
This spoon's too heavy.
It's for adults. I'll get you something else.
I like it because it's heavy.
When I lived with my aunt,
I always ate microwavable rice.
We used plastic utensils to avoid doing the dishes.
When there's only a few grains of rice left,
you have to scrape the bottom of the bowl.
If you scrape a plastic bowl...
with a plastic spoon, the light weight...
makes it harder to get at the rice.
It just felt weird...
as if the rice would get flung out.
Did you only eat microwavable rice?
I like this sound.
It's heavy and warm.
Geum Bi.
You can visit whenever you want...
as if it's your home.
Whenever you say...
you want to visit me,
I'll wait with the heaviest bowl and cutlery, okay?
Okay.
I should go.
Just a moment!
Stop them!
Get her back.
Go and get her back.
Now!
Hey! Stop the car!
Stop!
Stop the car!
Stop the car! Move.
Out of my way! Stop the car!
Move!
- Stop the car!
- Come back!
He must be crazy.
Is he coming after us?
What's he doing?
Come back!
He fell down.
Is he okay? Is he hurt?
Stop the car!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Where were you?
What took you so long to come back?
What's wrong?
Are you dying again?
Don't die.
Mister.
How can you not recognize your own blood?
Mister...