(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
This time, I'll make it hard for you.
Okay.
Here you go.
I don't think I can do this.
I know, right?
I did it!
Now, you try. This one won't be that easy.
This is how you do it.
I can do that one.
See?
You're a natural, aren't you?
- Let's go again.
- Okay.
Don't move your fingers.
That's not fair.
Here we go.
You go.
How can you not recognize your own blood?
You're good at this.
Do you want to join in?
No way. It's a childish game.
Be a little childish with two childish females.
Why are you playing that?
It's 2016.
You must want to know where I was.
Is this what I'm supposed to do?
Yes, that's right.
I had some urgent business to take care...
It's your turn.
Okay.
So...
stop stalling and join in.
It's all ruined.
You never do anything properly.
Were you going to play all night?
You said this was childish.
Once you start, you have to play to the end.
Start over.
No. You're so childish.
Let's play.
No.
Give it to me.
Geum Bi, Geum Bi.
Shall I tell you a story?
Yes, please.
Once upon a time, on an island at sea...
lived a girl called Yeon Yi...
and a boy called Jang Yi.
The two always flew a kite together.
Whenever the sun set and they had to go home,
they never wanted to part.
Every night, Jang Yi promised Yeon Yi that he'd buy...
a yamyeongju from the far west.
What's a yamyeongju?
It's a large bead that shines in the dark.
What then?
Time passed and Yeon Yi became a young lady,
and Jang Yi became a young man.
Jang Yi left the island saying he'd come back...
with a lot of money.
He also promised to buy a yamyeongju.
He left even though Yeon Yi told him not to...
because she didn't want that yamyeongju.
After that, Yeon Yi flew a kite every day...
by the sea.
She prayed that he would come back safely.
He worked very hard and made...
a lot of money.
Did he buy the yamyeongju?
Be quiet and listen.
When he left the island, Jang Yi had told Yeon Yi...
that he'd come back after the azaleas had bloomed...
and then wilted five times.
The more money he made, the greedier he became...
and he didn't return after the azaleas...
had bloomed over 10 times.
That's bad of him.
Why is that bad?
Things happen when you're trying to make money.
Then one day,
Jang Yi finally bought a yamyeongju from the far west.
He decided it was time to return to Yeon Yi.
Did he go back?
Jang Yi returned on a ship full of gold and jewels...
when he saw a kite flying in the wind.
He was so excited that he'd see Yeon Yi again.
He ran up the slope calling her name...
when he saw the kite was tied to a tombstone.
In the year the azaleas had bloomed...
for the seventh time,
Yeon Yi fell sick from spending too much time...
by the sea and died alone.
Jang Yi was so sad and he cried...
for days and nights by her grave. Then, he threw...
the money, jewels and yamyeongju into the sea.
To this day, that part of the sea glows at night...
as if a full moon is shining under the water...
because of the yamyeongju.
Jang Yi was so stupid.
He didn't know what's really important.
Right?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Don't go.
Let's fly a kite together.
Don't go...
Kang Hee said breakfast is ready.
What's that?
Can't you tell? It's a kite.
Does it fly?
If it doesn't, it's a chicken, not a kite.
(JANG YI)
It flies really high.
It's like a dragon.
Give it to me. I want to try.
Do you know what to do?
I just have to let it loose.
Then it'll crash to earth, silly.
Hold the handle and then this part.
Feel its movement...
and give it room to soar or pull it back.
Don't just release the string, okay?
Watch it carefully. Don't let it crash.
Don't you worry.
Pull on the string.
I envy people who are good at making things.
It's a useless skill.
Kites are cheap to buy.
Why don't you think more highly of yourself?
Me?
I'm a nobody.
Where did you hear that story you told?
The one from last night.
I made it up.
What?
You're a terrific liar.
You could scam people for a living.
Scam people?
You could be a writer.
Novelists and con artists are almost the same.
You don't know, do you?
Know what?
It's not often, but you sometimes shine.
What does?
You.
Mister.
My gosh!
I knew you would do that!
Hey. You don't do anything right, do you?
You should've done something if you saw this coming.
Why didn't you do anything?
Don't you remember what I taught you?
Were you good at everything from the start?
I was. Since the moment I was born.
I guess I'm not like you, then.
I knew I shouldn't have made you that kite.
Whom are you like, Geum Bi?
I don't know.
Maybe my mom.
Goblins wear nice panties
They're tough
They're strong
They're made of tiger skin
They last 2,000 years
What are you singing about?
Mister wears dirty panties
They smell bad
He hasn't washed them for 2,000 years
They're dirty
What a bad song.
A nasty kid sings a nasty song.
Do you want me to keep going? How about a new song?
No, thanks.
Fasten your seatbelt.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
What is this?
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Geum Bi?
Are you hurt?
No.
Gosh.
Someone must've done it on purpose.
They don't just loosen like this.
What do you mean someone did it on purpose?
The bolts are so loose.
They don't loosen this much alone from driving.
What?
Is that your mom?
You're very beautiful.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Have you ever come back here after graduating?
This is my first visit.
You didn't even graduate.
No, I didn't.
Thanks to you.
How is it my fault that you got expelled?
You haven't changed a bit.
All you do is make excuses and run away.
After a while, you even forget what you did wrong.
You do that on purpose, don't you?
It makes you feel better.
Here.
When are we getting back to work?
We can't go back there. Our covers have been blown.
We'll start over again when we find someone else.
We should hurry before Hwi Cheol changes his mind.
There's no need to worry about him.
He's completely in love with that Kang Hee.
Eat your jjajangmyeon.
I am eating. Can't you see?
I hope Cha Chi Soo doesn't mess it up for us.
Gosh.
I'm worried about that, too.
What did Hwi Cheol do so wrong by him?
Why does Chi Soo have the upper hand all the time?
Weren't they best friends in high school?
What good will come out of it...
when the people around get hurt because of you?
I'm in debt to many people in my life,
but they weren't anything I couldn't pay back.
The principal was 5,000 dollars.
Add 7 years of interest and it's 450,000 dollars.
I'm paying back.
Even if it takes selling away my organs.
You can pay back all you want,
but it won't ever be enough to forgive your sin.
I guess I won't have to pay back at all, then.
Nothing will ever be enough.
Chi Soo used to play baseball.
Professional baseball teams wanted to sign him.
If it wasn't for that incident,
he could be playing in the major league for all I know.
What happened?
There was a huge fight in Hwi Cheol's restaurant.
The other guy got hurt real bad.
Chi Soo got blamed for everything.
What about Hwi Cheol?
Hwi Cheol was the one who led the fight,
but he managed to slip out.
If he just went to the school...
and said something to protect Chi Soo,
he'd be living a different life by now.
Hwi Cheol lied low for months...
and didn't show up to school.
In the end, Chi Soo got expelled...
and his baseball career never even began.
After that is...
Oh, you're here. Come over here.
- What's this?
- I told you.
These are the new players.
You don't have to pay me back if you don't want to.
I'll come take what's mine.
Her name is Geum Bi.
And the other one, Kang Hee.
Am I right?
They have nothing to do with me.
No matter what you do,
it's none of my business.
You should answer your phone.
You're late.
I got an appraisal request.
I'm coming for her antiques. Be ready.
You can walk away if you're not up for it.
There are plenty of ways to repay your debt.
I could put that woman and the girl to good use.
Fine.
I take 10 percent.
If you comply with my demands, I'll do as you say.
You can walk away if you're not up for it.
Come take them for yourself.
Next Monday, eleven in the morning.
What was that about 10 percent?
It's commission.
I feel like you're neglecting me.
- What?
- I need to sell mine, too.
Right. Of course.
I can wait until you're finished with the other one.
Are you in a hurry?
I am.
I might not look it, but I'm broke.
What do you mean?
I'm kidding. Get some rest.
Okay...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What are you doing alone?
I'm testing myself.
Do you want to have some tteokbokki?
I have a violin lesson.
What time does it end?
After that... I have Mandarin class.
Is it fun?
It's not, is it?
Why don't you just come with me to eat tteokbokki?
My mom will scold me if I skip my lessons.
Take your pick.
What do you mean?
Is it me or violin lessons?
That's just silly.
I don't have much time, okay?
And I'm willing to spend some time with you.
You don't look too good. Are you sick?
I don't think so.
You must be. Think carefully.
Hold your breath and scrunch up your face.
I feel sick.
What did you want to do the most?
What?
We have some time to kill.
What did you want to do in your free time?
That's what we should do.
(FORTUNE-TELLER)
Here?
They tell us what happens next.
Who does?
You could come back when you're a bit older.
What problems will be in tomorrow's quiz?
You said you don't study.
That's not the kind of thing you ask her.
Shake those bells.
Then the child spirit will come.
What's that?
It's the ghost of a child your age.
Call it.
Don't.
What do you want to know?
I want to know...
if we'll go to a good college when we're older.
If you study hard, you can go to a good college.
That's it? Even I could say something like that.
I don't think that's what you'll do.
And you?
What do you think I want to know?
You want to know when you'll get to kiss him.
Gosh.
Be a bit more sincere. Don't just guess.
Shake those bells a bit, too.
That kiss.
It might happen soon...
or it might never happen.
What do you mean?
Losers who never confess blame their lack of courage...
but it's love they lack, not guts.
People full of love are full of courage, too.
How dare she charge us 50 cents?
She just shook the bells a few times.
She didn't charge us too much.
Why are you here?
Do you have a way out?
- How are things going?
- Why are you asking me that?
Ask the designer.
He's a dimwit.
And you aren't?
They held an audition and found a replacement.
I heard they'll make a move this week at the earliest.
This week?
We'll come for her things, so be packed and ready.
Next Monday, eleven in the morning.
Have the contract signed this weekend...
and take the lot by early next week at least.
There's no point in wasting time.
We're splitting the profits equally.
Why work with a big team?
We're going with a skeleton crew, aren't we?
Let's drop Gil Ho and Jae Gyung.
That doesn't sound bad to me.
- Are you sure?
- Why share the profit?
Drop the replacement...
and tell Gil Ho we have to push things back.
To next Tuesday.
What's your plan?
If you and I work together,
we won't need to replace Gil Ho or Jae Gyung.
The mark's slow, so we'll move fast and distract her...
then get out fast.
There you go.
Are you checking the time again?
What's taking Yong Geun so long?
He's busy.
It's you again.
What do you want?
Can you find someone in another country?
In another country?
Which one?
Spain. The name's Yoo Joo Young.
(MO HWI CHEOL)
You should know whom you're helping out.
Did you look into his past?
That jerk...
is not an antique appraiser.
He's a common con artist.
He has a record.
Don't you get it? Antiques.
He's planning to steal what you inherited...
and sell them for a profit.
Stay out of it.
I'll deal with him.
What can you do?
I'll repay my father's debt, so don't worry.
Do you think I'm doing this for the debt?
The antiques and the house...
is all your father left.
Try to think what'll happen to you...
once you lose all that.
You tell me not to worry about the debt...
because of the inheritance.
You can do whatever you want,
but try to care for me as much as...
you care for charity cases.
That's only fair.
Whatever.
(MO HWI CHEOL)
(UNEMPLOYED)
(GREW UP IN AN ORPHANAGE)
(SENTENCED TO ONE YEAR FOR SELLING FAKE ARTWORK.)
- Hey.
- We found her.
Did you really?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I guess you were meant to find her.
She's in Korea.
She came back a few years ago.
She's doing pretty well as a manager.
She knows how to have fun, though.
She's on the older side but most men can't handle her.
How exactly do you know her again?
It's cold.
Pathetic.
You haven't changed a bit.
You're still the same.
Excuse me.
Go away.
I think you dropped this.
Get away from me, you scumbag.
It's not going to work on me.
- What are you looking at?
- Sorry?
What? What?
Are you trying to hit on me?
I just...
I'm sorry.
Jerk.
What's wrong?
She must be tired from all the talking.
I...
I found someone who might be interested in your things.
Really?
He wants to come by next Monday and take a look.
That's a weekday. What should I do?
If you give me the keys,
I'll show him around and seal the deal for you.
But that would be inappropriate, wouldn't it?
I'll try to adjust the schedule.
You don't have to. I'll give you the keys.
Please make a good deal for me.
I will.
Is the other thing...
going well as planned?
What?
It's an appraisal request. No need for a big plan.
You must come across...
many people who try to deceive you.
There are all kinds of people in this world.
You can't blame the tricksters for doing their jobs.
That's what the scammers say to justify themselves.
They're the ones to blame.
We've gotten close, haven't we?
That's how I feel.
I feel like I can open up to you.
Don't you feel the same?
You have something to say to me, don't you?
Maybe later.
Maybe I will later.
I don't have anything to say at the moment.
If you're going somewhere,
tell me where you're going.
Don't just disappear like last time.
I will.
Gosh. You're so annoying.
I'm busy right now. Go play with your brother.
When people fall in love, they get courageous.
Let's eat.
Here.
Why are you alone?
People get scared of me because I'm mean.
You're lying.
I'm not.
I'm bound to live alone.
Why?
People who don't have a sense of responsibility...
don't have the right to be loved.
You mean like Hwi Cheol?
Why do you think that?
Hwi Cheol is actually...
Never mind.
Geum Bi.
Everyone has their reasons.
There are many sides to someone.
If there's a good side,
there is also a bad side.
If there's a nice side,
there is also a mean side.
And...
That means...
there's room for a change.
Do you want me...
to share a secret?
Yes.
To be honest,
I'm a very bad person.
No way.
It's true.
I won't...
ever hate you...
even if you did very bad things.
I know Hwi Cheol can be strange sometimes,
but don't hate him too much.
He can become someone better.
Here. Try it.
Is it good?
It's good. It really is.
What? What do you mean it's been postponed?
What for?
The faster we do it, the better.
What? What about the new players?
Hey.
He's so rude.
What is it?
He says something came up with the new players.
He wants to postpone it.
I lived off my intuition for all my life.
I told you. Something came up with the new players.
I can't control my flying kick...
once I'm already in the air.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Are you feeling guilty?
Is that why you can't make eye contact with me?
- Stop it.
- Stop what?
What do you want me to stop?
If you're willing...
to stab even me in the back,
it's over between us.
You jerk.
I'm the reason you're even around.
You'd be living in the dumps if it weren't for me.
All you want...
is to score one big deal in life.
You believe you'll get lucky one day.
Did you ever get lucky?
We did this time!
It's my score, not yours!
No, right?
You don't...
mean it, do you?
You wouldn't do that, would you?
I got it all wrong, didn't I?
Quit being a third-rate loser!
Just let it go!
Do you think I'll let it go?
You're wrong.
I won't let you have your way.
I'll take you down with me if I must.
You would.
That's the kind of person you're like.
- What?
- We act like we're close...
but we just use each other. Am I wrong?
How could you...
Do what you want!
I'll die like my dad,
stabbed in the middle of the street.
My life's a waste...
and I wouldn't mind an early exit!
Get lost!
Hwi Cheol!
1400, The Second Revolt of the Princes.
1401, Sinmungo is built.
1405, the Capital is moved to Hanyang.
1418, King Sejong's coronation.
1419, Tsusima is conquered.
Don't you ever knock?
Why are you mumbling?
You're like a monk in the rain.
Do monks mumble when they get wet?
Do you want to drive a subway train when you grow up?
It's something I do.
Why do you do it?
You'll find out later on even if you don't want to.
Later on when?
I don't know.
What do you want to eat?
It's too late to eat anything.
For breakfast tomorrow.
For breakfast?
A healthy meal that's low in cholesterol.
With assorted nuts.
That's it?
Then I'll mix some rice with milk.
You can...
ignore whatever your teacher says at school...
but you must do exactly as Kang Hee says.
Why is your hair such a mess?
Why did you do that?
Go to bed.
What's going on?
It's a special day.
Sit and eat.
I felt bad...
that you did all the cooking.
Take a seat.
Something's off.
Are you about to do something bad?
Shut it and eat before I take your spoon away.
I knew it.
I'm going on a business trip for a few days.
Where are you going?
You don't know what "business trip" means.
I know what it means, but where are you going?
To Jeju Island.
When will you be back?
It takes months just to get there.
That's a lie.
It takes that long if I were to walk there.
I'll be 2 or 3 days.
You don't have to eat if you don't want to.
Do you mean that?
You...
Take this. Before I forget.
In this congenital disease, lipids accumulate.
Only two cases were reported in Korea so far,
making it a very rare genetic disease.
Extraocular muscle paralysis...
and seizures are a few of the main symptoms.
In early stages, patients can't look up or down.
Later on, patients suffer from epileptic seizures...
and the stiffening of muscles.
In serious cases, the whole body suffers muscle loss...
as well as the loss of sight.
It eventually leads to death.
The patient can go into shock...
causing all sorts of problems.
- Hello.
A while ago,
we saw a girl with an enlarged liver and spleen.
Are the biopsy results out yet?
Oh, that little girl.
She refused the biopsy.
Did you say 10 percent?
You need to give me something to live off of...
so you can use me again.
You're still shameless.
Answer after the bell rings three times.
Sorry.
What?
I'm sorry.
A man who doesn't know what he did wouldn't say that.
You scumbag.
Hey, you!
Get him.
Let go! He's the one you need to get!
Stay still!
(INTERROGATION ROOM 1)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
From the year I turned 15...
until he died this year,
my father never said...
more than three sentences to me in a row.
Maybe it was his only joy in life...
or maybe it was his only pastime.
He devoted himself in collecting those antiques.
He spent all his savings.
I'm grateful to you...
for getting rid of those pieces of junk.
But if I don't sell those,
I won't be able to pay the debt my father left behind.
I thought...
we'd gotten close.
Were you just pretending?
To do a job on me?
What about Geum Bi?
Did you keep her by your side for your job?
You used your daughter you first met in 10 years?
Isn't it too late to feel sorry?
Did you do it for the money?
Why did you take them from me among all other things?
Raise your head so I can see your face!
This isn't you.
You jumped in front of a truck to save her life.
You brought her back...
while suffering from concussion.
You cleaned an old, rusty bicycle...
into a shiny, new one!
I..
I wanted to...
What?
I wanted to live.
I...
When I looked at you and Geum Bi,
I wanted...
to have a decent life, too.
Then why did you do that?
I...
I can't live like that.
Why can't you live like that?
I'm sorry.
Please release him.
- What?
- You have to release Hwi Cheol.
He didn't steal anything.
He was caught red-handed.
His other apprentices ran away...
and we caught him right there at the site.
Nothing got stolen.
Nobody stole anything.
What are you talking about?
You said he didn't resist when he got arrested.
Please release him.
You're back early.
You're still the same.
What do you mean?
It's the same ugly you from yesterday.
You're uglier.
Hello?
A hospital?
Yes. That's her name.
Why is a pediatrician asking for her?
He said she was perfectly fine back then.
Okay. Thursday at 2pm?
Okay.
Hey. Are you sick somewhere?
No.
You're ugly.
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm Geum Bi. Yoo Geum Bi.
What?
You called about a biopsy.
But I said I'll see your dad tomorrow.
You came alone in advance?
I need your parents here.
I have something to say to your parents.
I don't have a mom.
Then your dad has to be here.
He's not my dad.
What are you talking about?
He is my dad,
but he isn't my dad yet.
What do you mean by that?
My dad's name is Mo Hwi Cheol...
and mine is Yoo Geum Bi.
Do you have any other relatives?
I did have an aunt,
but she abandoned me.
She found out I have Niemann-Pick disease.
What?
Niemann-Pick disease.
Do you...
know what that is?
It's like dementia, right?
I'll lose my memory gradually...
and I won't even be able to move my body after.
People with the disease die before they turn 20.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU