(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.) SUBTITLES BY VIU N SYNC BY SA143
(Episode 6) SUBTITLES BY VIU N SYNC BY SA143
Jangsan, Jung-dong, Haeundae, Dongbaek, Centum City.
Are you awake or just talking in your sleep?
Mister, have you been to Haeundae?
Of course.
What about Gyeongpodae?
Of course, I've been there.
What about Sokcho?
Why are you listing all the Korean beaches?
You have been there.
Why do you ask all of a sudden?
I've never been to the sea.
Go back to sleep.
When summer comes, I'll salt you in sea water.
When next summer comes?
That's a promise, right?
I'll make you drink fish sauce if you don't keep it.
All right, I promise.
You're one suspicious kid.
Here.
There.
Do it properly.
Gosh, fine.
That ugly kid.
We are pleased to inform you that...
we are offering you a position as a chief researcher.
We'd like you to come to Canada National Institute...
of Forest Science headquarters on December 10...
to sign an employment agreement contract.
I'll bring a blanket.
Geum Bi.
Did you tell Mr. Mo?
Doctor. Is my medicine expensive?
How much is it?
Even with insurance,
it's over 1,000 dollars a month.
I'm not sure exactly,
but I don't think Mister can earn over 1,000 dollars.
He even got kicked out of his house.
Does he...
treat you well? Is he nice to you?
Will it be okay for you...
to leave him for an orphanage?
It's not okay,
but I'll go.
I have to be gone for him to...
I'll go.
(Online translator)
Hey, kid. What did you get on your last English exam?
Pardon?
When are you leaving for Vancouver?
As soon as my replacement gets here.
Good for you.
Hey, if you move to Canada,
you'll break up with that guy you're living with.
It doesn't matter, right?
You should get rid of...
sloppy guys as quickly as you can.
How do you know?
How do you know if he's sloppy or together?
Are you taking his side?
Then what? Are you taking him?
No, right?
Mister.
Where have you been? You should come home early.
What's wrong?
- What? - It's all over your face.
"I am very concerned right now."
- Geum Bi. - Yes?
This is bad.
What is?
She's leaving far, far away.
You don't want her to move far away, right?
Why? Do you want her to go?
We have to live in a tent once she leaves.
Is it really because of this house?
Well, this and that. Everything.
What kind of this and that?
Stop asking.
Just let it go.
Don't cry later saying that you didn't know.
What good would crying do?
If you're that concerned, you should stop her.
What?
My goodness.
This is useless.
This isn't going to stop her from leaving.
Just trust me.
Did you buy a lighter?
Oh, right. I forgot.
(Kang Hee)
My goodness.
I wasn't going to do this because it's so childish.
I love childish things.
Exactly. I knew you'd like it.
Mister has something to say.
No, I don't.
You do.
I know everything.
Tell me.
Well, I didn't mean to pry.
I mean...
Can you not leave...
What is all this?
Who are you?
What are you?
- Her boy toy? - Joon Pil.
Darn it.
Hey.
My gosh.
Sir, you must be mistaken.
We are not involved like that.
See? He definitely looks like a con artist.
You acted like you were so smart,
but you are dating a trash like him.
Mister is no longer a con artist.
See? He's making the kid do the talking.
He probably already knows your background.
They heard about Jun Hee somewhere...
and came to rip you off.
Let's talk later.
What... Stop...
- Stop it. - Geum Bi.
Geum Bi, come here.
Do you feel better being nice to a girl like this?
You must want to make up for the past with her.
Wake up.
They are only using you.
Are you going to blame Jun Hee...
if they take all of your money?
- Excuse me. - Stay out of this.
Sure.
Let's say that you're right.
So what?
What's so bad about getting used?
Life is hard as it is.
What's so bad about...
getting comforted after being used?
Don't worry.
Even if I lose my money,
I'll make sure I leave your portion.
- What are you saying? - Please!
Please get lost.
For today...
Just for today.
Please just get lost!
You must be startled.
I'm sorry.
Your parents must've scolded you often.
What?
Drawing paintings, flying kites,
and doing origami.
They must've scolded you for not studying hard.
Kids with too much time to spend without friends...
are bound to have various hobbies.
You didn't have any friends?
Kids at school went home after sunset...
unless they have shiny marbles to play with.
What about family?
I'm the only son.
My mom passed away when I was young.
My dad was busy.
He also passed away when I was young.
When I was in high-school.
I'm...
going far away.
I know.
Do you have anything to say to me?
I don't.
Really?
Is there really nothing to say?
I'll give you 1,000 dollars.
It'll cover the food costs,
electricity, and other expenses.
I earned a small sum of money.
And I didn't con anyone for it.
Gosh.
- Kang Hee. - Yes?
Kang Hee.
Yes?
You know what?
What?
If you go far away,
I'll wait for you by the seaside...
flying kites every day.
What?
When the sea breeze makes me sick,
I'll ask Mister for a favor before I die.
You shouldn't say things like that.
I'll ask him to bury me by the seaside...
and wait for you flying kites every day.
I'll ask him to tie the string to the tombstone.
- Geum Bi. - When you come back,
you'll be crying filled with regrets, right?
No. I won't do such a thing.
You're not supposed to say that.
I'm Oh In Hye.
Is there a need for a lawyer?
A big deal like this requires one.
You must've studied hard at school.
You even have a beautiful face.
I wasn't good at anything else.
There he comes.
Nice to meet you.
I heard the collection is of the highest quality.
But I also heard that...
you don't own these antiques.
Yes, that's right.
Kang Hee, you little witch.
Kang Hee?
The antiques are at my younger sister's place.
I can take them with me whenever I want.
Will the money be transferred on the day of the deal?
Yes. As long as...
the antiques are genuine.
When this deal is over,
I'd like to make some business propositions.
I'd love that.
Are you out of your mind?
Stop talking nonsense.
How is it nonsense?
It's very clear to me.
That Kang Hee woman blew our cover once.
You're going to con her brother for the same thing?
Gosh. That woman's brother doesn't know who we are.
Besides, he looks easy.
Didn't you see how he was?
He'll do anything to sell his family's fortune.
You're one bold witch.
Come closer if you have something to say or get lost.
He's not eating.
What is it?
Have you seen Hwi Cheol?
Hwi Cheol?
Mo Hwi Cheol?
He's been trying to track you down.
Why would he?
Why do you think?
You two were madly in love once.
It was Hwi Cheol who was madly in love with me.
There must be a reason for a former housemate...
to be looking for you.
Excuse me. Can I get some more radish?
Okay.
The tie between you two isn't broken yet.
- After you abandoned him... - Don't you get tired?
Don't you ever get tired of following Hwi Cheol around?
Aren't you tired of living a life...
trying to take everything from him?
Shut your mouth and listen.
You listen to me.
Why can't you see your own life going down the drain...
trying to ruin Hwi Cheol's?
He's the reason you approached me back then.
You didn't steal me away from Hwi Cheol.
I abandoned you after I had enough fun.
Pay for the bill.
Do you talk to your mom these days?
You haven't seen her for a while, right?
Look who's talking.
Go on your way.
That piece of trash.
(Skynuri Charnel House)
(Yang Yoon Ok)
(Lawyer Ma Sang Soo)
I fully understand what you're trying to say.
There are still a few more questions left.
Did Mo Hwi Cheol take good care of you?
- What? - I mean...
Did he ever forget to feed you...
or hit you?
He's not like that at all.
I...
I see.
Please sit.
Which orphanage will I go to?
I'm not sure. I think you should go somewhere...
not too far from your current school.
No.
I want to go as far as I can from here.
Why?
(Yeoul Orphanage)
When will she get better?
She is getting better. You will see in no time.
When will she get discharged?
She has to be here a little longer.
Hello?
Yes. Yoo Geum Bi. That's right.
Where?
Geum Bi practically begged me...
to keep this a secret from you.
About what?
Are you really her guardian?
Yes. I'm her guardian.
I really don't understand...
why Geum Bi likes you so much.
In medical law,
there is a section on confidentiality.
So what?
I'm telling you despite the risk of punishment.
Listen to me carefully...
and define your position as her guardian.
I won't tell anyone. Tell me what it is.
Geum Bi...
has an illness.
What is it again?
Niemann-Pick disease.
Niemann what?
Then...
What will happen to her?
Well...
There is a gene called NPC1.
It's a disease where that gene malfunctions.
When it does, her cholesterol level rises abnormally.
Since there are no enzymes to metabolize the lipids,
it'll keep on piling up...
in her liver, spleen, and brain.
And what?
When it develops,
she'll have something called a myotonia.
It'll be hard for her to walk.
Her pronunciation will be unclear...
and she will lose her ability to speak.
Then her muscles will weaken rapidly.
She may experience some seizures.
Her intellectual ability will gradually decline...
and display symptoms similar to Alzheimer's.
Alzheimer's...
Isn't that dementia?
What are you talking about?
She's only 10 years old.
She is very bright and has a great memory.
My gosh. You must be mistaken.
Let's say you're right.
What will happen now?
If this breaks out in babies,
they'll die before preschool.
If it breaks out after that, most die during teenage...
Darn it. What are you talking about?
Are you saying that she will die...
before she turns 20?
Yes.
After the onset of this disease and the symptoms...
develop, it will test your limit.
Even if she's your own child,
you'd want to abandon her and run away.
Mr. Mo!
Get a hold of yourself.
And be honest with me.
About what?
Are you capable of managing her?
Geum Bi.
Can you take care of her until the end?
What are you doing?
What's with you?
- What? - Why are you acting weird?
What do you mean?
Tell me the subway stations on line one.
Tell me!
Which direction?
Forget about that.
Where's the place where we first ate?
A buffet at a hotel.
Name...
What's my name?
Mo Hwi Cheol.
Who's the owner of this house? What's her name?
Why? You don't know? Can't you remember?
Can't you?
She's Go Kang Hee.
Why are you cooking a toothbrush?
You need to sterilize it once in a while.
Do you know how many germs are in a toothbrush?
You still can't microwave it. It'll melt.
You're suppose to microwave it for a minute.
You don't even know anything.
Bring your toothbrush, too.
I'm sure your toothbrush is the dirtiest in town.
Do we have ice cream?
What are you making?
I don't know.
There are some things you can only know in the end.
How do you make it?
Teach me.
This?
It's not for stupid kids.
Not to mention ugly kids.
But you can do it.
Kang Hee.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going out to make some money.
Here.
I told you I'd give you 1,000 dollars.
I don't think I'll need this.
Let us stay here for just a little longer.
If I work hard, I might be able to rent a room.
This is good, right? I don't know the details, but...
wouldn't studying abroad benefit you when you return?
It's not exactly like that.
You should go when you have the chance.
Don't regret it later.
I won't.
Speaking of which,
I can't let a stranger look after this house.
I want you to live here and take care of it.
You must pity me.
Homes are bound to break down without people living in.
I'd rather have you and Geum Bi live here,
and look after this house.
You don't need to pay any rent.
Do you not want to?
I'm in no position to refuse.
I'll accept the offer gladly.
It's settled, then.
Turn left.
- Sorry? - Make a left turn.
All right.
Gosh.
Try to get some sleep. You'll be home in no time
Shut it and drive.
How old are you?
- What? - I asked you how old you are.
Okay.
- Here you go. - Good.
I got my keys back.
Good work.
Excuse me. It's 10 dollars short.
What?
- Excuse me. - What?
It's 10 more dollars for the extra distance traveled.
10 dollars, my foot.
Do you think I'm a fool?
How dare you try to con me?
What did you say? I'm not conning you.
Get lost.
Give me my 10 dollars!
Give me that 10 dollars!
Give me that 10 dollars.
- Let go of me. - My goodness.
I know martial arts, you fool.
Geum Bi's dad went to prison once.
Is her dad broke?
- There she is. - She's here.
I heard your dad's been to prison once.
Your dad might end up there, too. Tell him to behave.
Hey!
Hey. Why are you so rude?
You guys must be a bad influence on me.
- Hey! - Hey!
Guys. Don't even bother wasting your breath.
The more you do, the more you'll become like her.
Sil La.
Did you have a good night sleep?
- What? - What did you have for breakfast?
Goodbye, guys.
Eat well and sleep well.
Listen to your teacher.
- Hey! - Hey!
Aren't you going to your after-school lessons?
I'm not going.
Are you sick?
I'm not.
- You don't have to do this. - What?
Sil La might be watching you nearby.
Let her watch.
You should get along with her.
You're going away, aren't you?
I'm going home.
Are you moving?
Where are you moving to?
I don't know for sure yet.
I wish I could go to a place where I can see the ocean.
Why?
I've never seen one before.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
Bye.
(Korea Gene Information Center)
So this is what it looks like.
It's nothing much.
Won't your mom tell you off?
I guess so.
You're brave.
No, I'm not. I'm scared she'll yell at me.
You still brought me here despite that.
That takes bravery.
When are you leaving?
Soon.
Can't you stay?
I have to go.
Don't go.
What?
You have plenty of friends here.
There are many girls who likes you.
I don't need them.
It's a good thing, stupid.
I only need one girl to like me.
You don't know what you're talking about.
So this is what it feels like.
Yes, this is what it feels like.
You didn't use to drink stuff like this.
I'm not in any position to be luxurious.
It's too sweet.
You should've told me sooner.
I have black coffee, too.
If Jun Hee had grown up,
what coffee would she have liked?
You told me not to mention her.
If she were like you, she'd have loved to drink.
What are you up to now?
You can sell the antiques.
Settle the debt...
and give me whatever you want to give me.
If you don't want to,
you can keep everything.
What about the house?
I can't sell it yet.
If I change my mind in the future,
I'll do as you say.
- That scumbag... - He's not like that. Don't worry.
I mean it.
Where will you go?
Far away.
How long will you be gone?
I'll see when I get there.
She'd have liked bitter coffee.
Just like you.
She wouldn't have liked to drink.
Just like Dad.
She would have, right?
It was all my fault.
You were only 15 years old.
I was old enough to look after my six-year-old sister.
That little girl...
Are you caring for her for Jun Hee's sake?
Don't do that.
It's wrong to be nice to a girl...
hoping she'll fill the void of a dead sister.
What if it's not like that?
It's like that.
It may have been in the beginning,
but what if I just want to keep her around...
regardless of the circumstances?
You said you're going far away.
I hadn't seen it in 17 years.
You smiling, I mean.
It had been 17 years.
Don't delude yourself and look closely.
You may be deceived into smiling.
You should learn to smile as well.
Take care.
I won't see you off.
I think we got off at the wrong station.
I don't just think so.
I'm sure of it.
What should we do?
Take another look.
(No signal)
It's not working.
Shouldn't we call home?
You should.
What about you?
Why not?
I need to upset them to make them sick of me.
What?
Call your mom already.
Hello?
Are you with Geum Bi?
Is she not home?
She should be.
She isn't. The house is empty.
Where did that girl go?
Yes.
Yes, she's 10 years old and in 3rd grade.
Yes, Yoo Geum Bi.
Okay. Thank you so much.
Is she back yet?
Not yet.
I'll go to her school.
Geum Bi.
That brat.
You brat. What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Was this deliberate?
Are you doing this on purpose?
Why are you shouting?
Why am I shouting? Don't you know?
What time is it? You didn't call or pick up!
Are you doing this on purpose?
Are you trying to make me angry?
It wasn't that.
You're scaring her.
Is this funny?
Do you think making people upset is funny?
You should listen to her before getting mad.
Geum Bi, where were you?
Do you know how worried we were?
How dare you call me mister?
I'm your dad!
Can I call you that?
What kind of question is that? Of course, you can!
Really?
If you call me mister one more time,
I'll sew your mouth shut!
Who said you can cry?
I'm crying because I'm sorry.
I won't let you off, though.
If you're going to cry, make some noise!
Don't keep it all bottled up!
Go to sleep.
How can I when you're staring at me like that?
Sleep now.
How long are you going to sit there for?
Why? Should I go out?
No.
How long do you want me to stay?
Until I fall asleep.
Okay. Now go to sleep.
I will when I'm sleepy.
Should I stay here all night, then?
Yes.
You're way too selfish.
Give me some time.
I'll fall asleep before the sun comes up.
Gosh. You're so ugly.
You're so ugly.
You see an open road,
but you don't know where it'll take you.
Your heart tells you to go,
but you just can't take the step.
Either you don't want to go...
or something's holding you back.
If you go, you'll lose something precious.
If you stay, you will be able to smile a lot.
(Reply)
Dad.
Hi.
Why are you here?
Isn't it obvious?
Hello.
Hi.
Why did you want to talk?
You know Kang Hee's going away, right?
Can't she stay?
It's best for her that she goes.
Why?
She will learn a lot there.
What's the point of learning a lot?
It's good for her career.
I'll tell her not to go.
Don't do that.
You don't want her to go either.
When we were at the hospital last time,
you said you'd stand guard while I run away.
Why did you say that?
Was it because you didn't want to live with me?
No.
This is something like that.
Give me your hand.
(Korea Gene Information Center)
(To Mr. Mo Hwi Cheol)
What are you doing?
Are you playing with fire now?
I wasn't playing with fire.
What else is this, then?
I can never take my eyes off of you.
It's not what you think. I really need to burn this.
You could have just torn it apart instead.
Is it a secret document? Gosh, it's hot.
I'll clean it up.
I can't trust you with anything.
How can I leave you in charge of the house?
I take it back. I won't leave the house in your care.
Then...
Then what?
I can't find anyone trustworthy to put in charge,
so I just can't leave Korea.
You'll make it a haunted house in less than a year.
What?
I...
I'm not educated properly...
and I'm practically a beggar with no savings.
What a fool.
I know I'm a fool.
I'm a con artist with a record.
Don't you get it?
It's not often, but you do shine.
When?
As Geum Bi's dad.
(Dear Ms. Go Kang Hee)
After her death, all of Yang Yoon Ok's assets...
will belong to her granddaughter, Yoo Geum Bi.
Until Yoo Geum Bi's 18th birthday,
none of the assets can be...
sold or transferred without her guardian's consent.
- "Geum Bi"? - Shortly before her death,
she heard she had a granddaughter and changed her will.
Before the amendment,
was everything left to me?
No, she'd planned to give back to society...
by donating to a few charities.
She didn't even have much.
How much are her assets worth?
Including her savings and securities,
about 1.5 million dollars.
Like I said, without the legal guardian's consent,
the assets cannot be sold or transferred at all.
Who is her legal guardian?
It's me.
How can I make you consent?
I won't consent.
(Yoo Geum Bi)
(My Fair Lady 2016)
What is she to you?
I have a good reason to borrow it.
Even with a government stipend for rare diseases,
her medicine will cost over 1,000 dollars a month.
Are you sure it's 1.5 million?
She left her assets to Yoo Geum Bi, not you.
How dare you come here?
Does a mom need a reason to see her own child?
That's nonsense.
I'm taking her.
What?
Your mom...
Why are you mentioning her?
She isn't dead.
I didn't ask you to find her.
You can't do that.
She won't recognize her if she gets older.
If she dies before seeing her mom,
I'd feel sorry for the girl.