(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Doctor.
What will happen to me later on?
Why? Did something happen to you?
I feel like I should know more about my disease.
What is happening inside my head?
(Episode 8)
In our bodies, there are things called lipids.
They're stored in us to be later used as energy source.
Which means, they're essential to keep our bodies...
alive and moving.
But?
But even the best things in life can be harmful...
when you have too much of them.
When there are too much lipids to be broken down,
they pile up in our brains,
making us hard to remember things...
and unable to move freely.
So it's not because I lack something,
but rather, I have too much of them?
That's right.
Will I not be able to remember anything?
Not even my dad or Kang Hee?
Later on,
you won't be able to recognize yourself...
reflected in the mirror.
How long do I have left...
before that happens?
You've been taking your medicine.
You have a while.
The more lipids I have,
the less I'll remember, right?
Are you...
sick?
I am, but I still have some time.
What are you staring at?
Everything.
- What? - Pretty things.
Buildings.
High heels.
Uniforms.
Dried leaves.
Trees. Streetlamps.
Sky.
Clouds.
Sunlight.
People.
Jae Ha.
- Why you... - Let go of me.
Where's Geum Bi?
Why do you want her?
- Do you want to die? - I'm doing this to live.
I want to save her and myself.
Will she die when she's with me?
Please leave her alone.
I told you to take the inheritance. We don't need it.
Your acting has gotten better.
Do you think you have the rights?
Money will give me the rights, you idiot.
You're really annoying me.
How much do you need?
I'll come back for her, so have her things packed.
If you ever show your disgusting face again...
Never mind.
Throw away those junks.
I'll buy her new things.
Sure! You can try. Bring it on!
Let's see who gets the rights!
Regarding rights,
there is no way you can win against her.
I mean, she calls you dad,
but you two are strangers on papers.
That's exactly where you come in.
I thought you are a legal agent.
Does a legal agent legally give things away?
Well, that's how the law works.
Right of inheritance comes before a written will,
and parental rights win against a good personality.
There is no way you can win this fight.
Why did you look for me, then?
I don't need any of this inheritance.
Just don't let her touch the kid.
What's your use if you can't even do that?
You're nothing more than a counselor.
Please don't say that.
Hey.
The chances are slim to none,
but there is one thing we can do.
What is it?
We can try to take away Ms. Yoo's parental rights.
Do that, then.
That's not up to me.
The prosecutor has to claim for a loss of parent right.
However, they won't make a move...
without a clear evidence.
She abandoned her and ran away.
What's clearer than that?
That's not going to cut it.
What is wrong with these laws?
We need to find something very fatal...
that will make her lose her rights.
You have a wonderful taste.
Is this the best car you have?
When will the new models come out?
This is the latest model.
We have a while until we release a new one.
- Then... - What can you do for her?
You can't live a day without drinking.
It's not just because of money, is it?
It's because you remember when she was born, right?
It was the happiest year of your life.
Go, before it's too late.
Hurry.
Please.
Get lost.
Excuse me, Ma'am.
Hey, Geum Bi.
Hey, we need to talk.
Look at her.
Hey, we're going to a TV station in Busan by subway.
Where do we transfer?
Don't be a bore. Tell us.
You're so pretty.
Where did you get this?
Who are you?
Do you know how kids get cast for TV on the streets?
Are you talking about an acting career?
Exactly.
Never mind. It was your clothes, not your looks.
Sorry.
I really want to be an actor.
Really?
Let's see.
Eyes.
Nose.
Look at your chin.
No. It'll take too much effort.
I'm sorry. Is your dad rich?
Oh, my. You're perfect.
You'll look good on camera right now.
Pretty eyes, nose, and chin.
You look adorable.
I love your freckles.
She's ugly and mean.
Who dressed you today?
They did an awful job.
You look like an old man.
You come so often. I might start to love you.
Did you say you knew something about Joo Young?
Who's that?
Are you already old? Spain.
Oh, Spain.
You must be old, too.
What?
Nothing is free.
Darn it.
- I'll owe you one. - Nonsense.
You can't even do that at a restaurant.
Then what? How much do you want?
Why? Do you have any money?
I know a great organ dealer.
Do you want his number?
I'm willing to do anything right now.
I'll give you everything I got for everything you know.
I have everything you need already.
It's an address. Why don't you go over there?
It's so pretty. Don't you think so?
This color will suit you.
Let's see.
This one looks nice.
It's not your color.
Let's find something else.
There you are.
You look so pretty in it.
It looks warm, too.
Come on.
Enjoy.
I didn't know what you like, so I ordered everything.
You can have whatever you want.
There's probably a misunderstanding between us.
Do you know what that word means? "Misunderstanding".
She said my mom's dead.
What?
That's because I've been abroad for a while.
Young Ji made a mistake.
I even mourned for you.
Because you were dead.
What's your number again?
I'm going to mourn for you next year as well.
Fine.
If you're going to do it,
then you might as well serve the food that I like.
I want pig's feet. From the front legs.
I want cream spaghetti and spicy seafood tteokbokki.
And I also want jamon.
Do you know what that is?
It's Spanish ham.
They're served in very thin slices.
What else? What else do you want to eat?
I'll draw pictures of them and serve you.
That's a small bill.
I'll pay in full.
Is there somewhere you want to go?
I want to go home.
It's way too early for that. The sun is still up.
Do you have a honey jar waiting for you at home?
What honey jar? It's not a bee hive.
Aren't you too broke to be luxurious?
This is nothing.
What do you know about living a luxurious life?
The clothes and jewelry you're wearing look expensive.
What?
Do you have a problem with my fashion?
At what age did you start dressing like that?
Now, I know what you're into.
You want to dress like me, don't you?
Then you should become a grown-up.
What's so good about being a grown-up?
Everything. You can do so many things.
It really is too bad that you're a minor right now.
Wait a minute.
Who says only grown-ups can dress like this?
Let's go.
- Goodbye. - Thank you.
What's this?
Give me your hand.
Is this too old for you?
What do you think?
Maybe pink is your color.
Why are your nails so ugly?
Isn't it pretty?
It's so pretty.
Can you make it wavy?
Let's give her head some more volume.
I'm not sure about parting it to the side.
I want it to look like my hair.
You look pretty.
You look really pretty.
Some makeup can never go wrong.
You look pretty.
Come here.
Surprise.
What is this? I look weird.
Hey. I know you like it.
Don't try to hide your feelings.
I don't like anything about it.
I look like a mean brat.
Exactly. Boys like that.
Don't you know the fairy tales?
Nothing good comes out of living as a good girl.
It's better to be evil and have a fun life.
Then you can be good and have a fun life, too.
Hey, that's like...
That's like saying a wolf only lives on carrots.
It doesn't make sense.
The way I see it, you're definitely evil.
Like me.
You look so evil.
Evil little girl, evil mom.
I'm not evil.
What do you think? Do you notice the difference?
Let's go.
To where?
Anywhere. You're not settling down here, are you?
It was fun being a grown-up, wasn't it?
Boys can't have fun like we did.
What are you doing? Don't take them off.
Why would you do that? You looked so pretty.
I don't look pretty.
And I can't go home looking like this.
Why not?
Do you care about what other people think of you?
I need to get changed.
Just go inside dressed like that.
If I return home like this,
they'll know I met you, lady.
"Lady"?
So what if they know?
Did your dad tell you something about me?
Was it that lady who owns the house?
Geum Bi.
Geum Bi, what happened to you?
Who are you?
Oh, you're Geum Bi's stylist.
No wonder she dresses you so poorly.
Don't be rude. She's like a sister to me.
What did you say?
Just look at her face. She's no sister.
She's an old lady out of date.
You look much older.
What? You...
You're ugly.
Why you little... Come here.
Don't you touch her.
I won't hesitate to start a fight with you.
My goodness.
What if I do touch her?
What will you do then?
Stop being mean to Kang Hee.
Are you serious?
You can't do this to me.
That little brat.
You ruined these expensive clothes.
Are you mad at me?
For meeting that lady?
What do you mean?
I won't see her anymore.
How can you not? She's your mom.
It's okay.
Did you want to wear these kinds of clothes?
I wanted to try for once.
Geum Bi.
Did that lady really look older than me?
- What? - That's what you said back there.
You said she looks older than me.
You said that just now.
Do you like putting on makeup?
Yes.
Come here.
- That tickles. - My goodness.
Wait, it really tickles.
- It really tickles. - If you were going to do this,
you should've done something classy.
- Why? It's pretty. - It's not pretty.
It's really tacky.
My face will change...
over time, right?
Geum Bi, should we do your makeup again?
Let's make you look classy.
Let's do it!
It's been so long.
You two look great together.
Come often.
Welcome.
Here.
Do you know Yoo Joo Young?
- Who? - Yoo Joo Young.
You worked with her in Spain.
Hey, it's not like that.
My goodness.
I'm not a police officer.
I don't know anything.
I just did it a few times with her.
Tell me in detail.
Hey.
What are you doing?
You ran away after getting caught trafficking drugs.
The police takes reports on weekends.
Go ahead and make a report.
Will you say you were threatened?
"I just carried it. I never did drugs."
Police officers would never believe that.
Don't you try your funny tricks on me.
Is this a rumor?
This is my only card.
That's too bad.
You can come and take her, then.
That's 3 and 3 over 7.
- Then one-third... - You're studying, Geum Bi.
Did you get off work early?
Did you cut work?
What are you talking about?
I did something awesome today.
Like what?
You can continue to live here.
This isn't your house.
Exactly. But you can keep living here.
I will even if you try to stop me.
Yes, go ahead.
Be quiet.
Why are you two fighting? I should be speaking.
If you two continue to bicker, I'll kick you both...
I think she'll back down.
- How? - What's going on?
It just happened.
What is it?
- Gosh. - Geum Bi.
Let's all go out together.
Really? Yes. Let's all go out.
Nonsense. All you ever do is play.
Are you mad?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Right.
Remember to put the seat cover down.
You're splashing everywhere.
I did not.
You should go sitting down from now on.
What? That is not happening.
You don't know anything about men.
You take number two sitting down.
Those are not the same.
Also, don't splatter toothpaste on the mirror.
You're the one who does that. Don't blame me.
I'm too small to do that.
You're disgusting.
What an ugly kid.
It's been a while.
What is?
This house...
used to bustle with people.
- Thank you for the food. - You love meat.
- Yes. - Eat meat, Joon Pil.
No way.
- Joon Pil, no. - Kang Hee, have some.
No, eat bean sprouts, Kang Hee.
- Here, Jun Hee. - She eats so well.
You're on a diet. Eat a little.
My goodness. Look at you.
- Give me some, too. - Here.
Here. Not.
It's for Jun Hee.
My gosh. Stop bothering me.
I'm busy. Go play with Joon Pil.
Hey, it's a dog.
You're adorable.
Are you alone?
- Jun Hee! - No!
Dad. Have some.
Joon Pil thinks...
that I think of Geum Bi like she's Jun Hee.
Yes, it was like that at first.
But now,
she's just Geum Bi.
She's not someone else.
She doesn't remind me of anyone.
- She's just our Geum Bi. - I know.
You don't have to say it.
No one can take...
our Geum Bi away.
Do you think I can do this?
She'll lose her words...
and her memory.
She won't be able to walk.
Could I take care of her...
even when those things happen?
What if I get tired of her?
What if I get sick of her?
What do I do?
She's not even my own child.
I'm afraid, too.
I'm scared.
But for now, let's think of this moment.
Just this moment.
I went to the shop.
Then you must know.
I haven't been working.
Will you lend me money?
No.
Then I have no business with you.
I want to be your man.
I do not have any intentions...
of becoming your finance.
I have a daughter.
I have to bring her to get money.
Good for you. You have a daughter.
Of course.
She even mourns for me.
She must be...
with her dad.
Yes.
I didn't know.
How did you meet her dad?
I dated a few guys...
when I was young.
He's one of them.
One of them?
Yes. One of them.
What are you thinking about?
One of them.
What are you doing here?
What's this about?
Where are they?
Who are you talking about?
Where's the couple you helped steal the antiques?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Hello?
Who?
The Central District Prosecutor's Office?
Really?
I'm the President's Chief of Staff.
What?
Are you trying to con me?
I won't fall for it. You called the wrong person.
I wasn't involved.
Right. I'm sure you weren't.
You're on probation...
for dealing fake artifacts.
That was...
This incident had nothing to do with me.
I'm innocent.
Listen.
You're mentioned as an accomplice.
Does being mentioned make you a criminal?
Then you must be an accomplice, too?
Shut your mouth.
What's this?
A kid's involved? Yoo Geum Bi?
Why does she have a different surname?
You got probation so you could care for the kid.
Didn't you?
If you're charged for this crime,
you'll get an additional punishment.
And you'll lose the kid.
Gong Gil Ho...
(Hwi Cheol)
The jerk.
Why did he drag Hwi Cheol into this?
Focus on us getting out of it, not him.
(Hwi Cheol)
Don't answer.
Why not?
Just don't.
What will you tell him anyway?
Get in the car.
These two...
If I get my hands on them, I'll wring their necks.
What now?
Why do you keep coming here?
Get lost.
Look over there.
Gosh...
That evil witch.
What are you doing?
What?
Did you take your medicine?
I will later.
Good, you do that.
Not you again.
This is it.
I have no business with you now.
(Korea Gene Information Center)
Read it and see for yourself.
What?
You won't and feign ignorance later?
Take it out...
and read it with your own eyes.
Read the report, you jerk.
You aren't related.
You and Geum Bi are strangers.
There's no reason for you to keep her.
Live as you always did.
Joo Young.
I can't go back to that life.
I told you before.
People don't change. They can't change.
I said I don't want the inheritance.
Do you love her that much?
Is that why you went...
and dug up my past to threaten me?
I'm the mom of the girl you adore so much.
Is it best for her to put me behind bars?
Do what you want.
Call the police on me.
I can't.
You just don't have the guts.
I can't do anything that'll make her cry.
Can't you leave me alone?
Can't you pretend you don't know...
and let me live as Geum Bi's dad?
I'll do and give you everything you want.
Just Geum Bi...
Leave Geum Bi...
and me alone. Please, Joo Young.
Don't pull that on me.
I'll come for her this weekend.
End it nice and clean.
(Paternity Report, Test Results)
(Test Results)
(11 alleles not identical)
(There is no evidence to suggest that...)
(Mo Hwi Cheol and Yoo Geum Bi...)
(are biologically related.)
What?
I noticed something.
You're really ugly.
That's not news.
You get uglier the more I look at you.
Just eat your food.
We said we'd go on a trip.
Ta-da.
When are we going?
When shall we go?
- Why? - Hurry up.
Smile. Say cheese.
Those frogs
The little froggy's legs
We can have more fun on a full belly.
- This looks so good. - This is for Geum Bi.
- Here. - Thank you.
I want some of that.
Eat your own.
(Hwi Cheol, Kang Hee, Geum Bi)
Give me that.
What? The key?
This symbolizes that we'll be together forever.
We have to throw away the key to seal the deal.
Give it to me.
Let her have it.
It's not worth fighting over.
It's just good fun.
Why would you want something like this?
It's not the key to a safe.
I'll find use for it one day.
You're not getting the point.
This key should never be used.
What if the tree disappears?
We'll have to come and get the lock.
We won't come back here. This is the only visit.
Why is it the only visit? We can come back.
Why would we do that?
Why visit somewhere we've been before?
Give it to me.
Fine, take it.
You can come back alone.
You're so mean.
It's no fun alone. You need company.
There's no time for that.
Be quiet.
We didn't come all the way here to fight.
It's okay. Let's come back here together.
It's clapping.
Hey.
Geum Bi.
Where are you going?
Did you not enjoy that?
No. It was boring.
I was enjoying it.
What's wrong with her?
In the fairy tale...
What are you two doing without me?
We were playing Truth or Dare.
That's such a childish game.
Let's be childish and make him join us.
Come here.
Come over here.
I don't want to join in.
Geum Bi first.
Who owned the pink bicycle?
Don't ask such a thing.
My younger sister.
I'm okay now.
Her name was Jun Hee.
She was sweet and pretty just like you.
She died when she was seven.
How?
I told her I couldn't be bothered to play with her,
so she went out into the streets and got hurt.
My mom and dad...
didn't say anything.
I guess they couldn't forgive me.
For 20 years after that,
no one in this house ever laughed.
Until you moved in.
Is it my turn?
Tell me about your parents.
Be honest.
My mom died...
before I entered middle school.
It was cancer or something.
I don't remember.
I think she was a really sweet woman.
My dad was a police officer.
While chasing a criminal,
he just...
He should've been more careful.
He talked a lot for a guy.
He nagged so much.
I hated listening to him nag.
But now,
I miss the nagging.
I should've recorded his voice.
Now, you tell us.
- What? - What happened earlier?
- When? - During the puppet show.
Why did you run out all of a sudden?
I felt sorry for it.
For what?
The puppet.
Did you feel sorry for the puppet?
Its arms and legs hung limply...
and it couldn't move on its own.
It would be scary if it could.
It would be like "Chucky".
I thought...
that's what I'd end up like.
No.
It won't happen to you.
You won't end up like that.
Wherever you are,
whatever your situation,
if you call me, I'll be there in an hour.
Don't you worry.
Do you understand?
Did your parents have dimples, too?
- What? - I have dimples just like you.
I don't know.
I haven't seen them in years.
What kind of a son doesn't know?
Kang Hee.
Yes?
Can I have the bicycle?
I'll wipe it every day...
and take good care of it for a long time.
You know,
when I'm no longer able to recognize you...
Whether it's now or then,
I'll come whenever you call.
I can't breathe.
Stay still.
Let go.
(Hwi Cheol, Kang Hee, Geum Bi)
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message.
I told you to answer before the third chime.
I have it on vibration.
You jerk.
I won't kick you.
If I break a rib, you'll have to take time off.
Can you see your performance rating?
You are placed...
second from the bottom.
I'm bringing you money regularly.
Our business is nothing...
if we don't make 10 times the banks do.
Who is Mo Hwi Cheol?
You chase him around instead of working.
I hate idiots with too many secrets.
I wondered why someone like you wanted to work for me.
Are you a police informant or something?
Look into my past, then.
Shall I deal with him?
So you can focus on your work.
If you touch him, I'll come for you.
You want to do it yourself?
You remind me of someone I met in prison.
That's so boring.
Work harder.
Break his collarbone before you let him go.
You said it was on vibrate.
Joo Young, please.
Give us some time.
I'll send her to you like you wanted.
Give us more time. Please?
I'm surprised. You never call me first.
I'm surprised.
You never get beaten up.
Don't get funny. Just do as you're told.
Don't get carried away.
Do you think I'm following your orders?
I need my plan to work to ruin Hwi Cheol.
That's how you'll get back at him.
Why did you call me?
I need a loan.
I quit work.
Don't get into something you can't deal with.
Don't be so stingy.
Once things settle down,
I'll pay you back with interest.
Did you get something?
What do you mean?
It seems you got to Hwi Cheol.
What is it?
You viper. You smell it already?
Have you been well?
No.
No?
Me, neither.
Why?
There are too many bad guys.
You're a bad guy, too.
So I'm here to do something bad.
Do that bad thing somewhere else.
I'll do it somewhere else, too.
When you were in school, did you have...
friends other than my dad?
You didn't, right?
Is he not at home?
My dad?
No.
Your friend.
You mean my dad.
No.
Your friend.
Stop playing with words.
No wonder you don't have friends.
Hwi Cheol isn't your dad.
Okay, fine. Call him whatever you want.
Mo Hwi Cheol.
He isn't your dad.
(My Fair Lady 2016)
I'm not Yoo Geum Bi. I'm Mo Geum Bi.
Don't you have a conscience?
Don't you know he barely makes a living?
Why should he put up...
with a kid that isn't his?
Get out of my way.
I can't let someone like you take Geum Bi.
We can't even cancel her parental rights?
It's all my fault.
Considering the way I lived,
even I wouldn't believe me.
You memorized the subway stations.
Have you forgotten them?
Why would I forget?
Geum Bi's very sick.
When her condition worsens,
she won't recognize either of us.
- What? - You can't...
handle her.
Do you really want to live with me?
You're pretty.
My dear daughter.