(The following program may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Hwi Cheol isn't your dad.
- You're lying. - Your mom's alive.
Just like I said.
Hwi Cheol...
isn't related to you at all.
You're a liar. You're not fooling anyone.
Fine.
Being suspicious is a good habit.
You have your mom's number, right?
(Episode 9)
Yoo Joo Young.
Come out if you're in there.
We need to talk.
(Test Result)
I discussed this with Mo Hwi Cheol already.
So keep away from my inheritance.
This isn't some spare change in a piggy bank.
There are procedures for transferring the rights.
Taking away securities requires the court's approval.
You lawyers sure are voluble.
You won't shut your mouth.
What did you say? Shut what?
Let's not waste each other's time.
We're not going to live forever.
Hello?
Hey.
Yes. That man is right.
You and Hwi Cheol are not related.
I used to glare at my mom...
with that look.
I'm not Yoo Geum Bi.
You really need a personal stylist.
You won't have to dress like this if you live with me.
I'm not going to live with you.
Throw away what you don't need when you pack up.
Call me when you're ready.
I'll come and pick you up.
I'm not Yoo Geum Bi. I'm Mo Geum Bi.
Don't you have a conscience?
Don't you know that...
he barely makes a living?
Why should he put up with a kid that isn't his?
Do you want him to suffer?
That judge...
released Hwi Cheol so he could live with his daughter.
But what will happen to him now that you're not his?
If you stay with him,
you'll make him a kidnapper.
- My dad... - He's not your dad.
And do you think he'll keep looking after you...
when he gets busy?
He's not the good man you think he is.
I'm not Yoo Geum Bi. I'm Mo Geum Bi.
Hey.
Call me. Okay?
Can I have that bicycle you have at home?
I'll clean it every day...
and take good care of it.
Are you going to work?
No. I'm going rock climbing.
Be careful doing rock climbing.
I will. I'll be back.
Okay.
Stay inside and play.
I'll go play outside.
Don't go.
What?
It's cold outside today.
It's more on the cool side.
Don't stay up for too long. Go to bed early.
I said don't go.
Come on.
Did you finish your homework?
Don't go.
What is this?
What are you mad about this time?
I don't need to take the medicine. Don't go.
What's with you? What's going on?
Geum Bi.
What's going on?
You don't have to suffer because of me.
This isn't like you at all.
Can you be more like your usual self?
The lady at the mall told me everything.
What if they take you away?
What are you talking about?
Why would I be taken away?
Because I'm not your daughter.
If I stay with you, you'll be a kidnapper.
What?
And you believed her?
Those are all lies.
Geum Bi. What are you talking about?
Hurry up! What are you doing?
You right there.
Stop standing around and get to work!
Get this side, too.
My goodness, you're useless.
Hurry up!
Why did you want to see me so early?
What? Do you want to fight?
You can't take care of her.
- What? - Geum Bi.
Stop minding my business...
and mind your own.
Geum Bi is really sick.
What?
Her short, 10 years of memory will be gone.
She won't even be able to eat.
There is no cure or medicine for this.
Just getting old enough to go to middle school...
is a miracle for her.
Be quiet.
How can you take that? You abandoned her once.
Shut your mouth. I'm her mother.
So what?
- What? - If her condition worsens,
she won't remember either of us.
What difference does being a mother make?
Does Geum Bi need her real mother right now?
- Then... - No.
She needs someone who can be her mom.
If not, someone who can act as her mom.
I know you're after her inheritance with Hwi Cheol.
Is that all you've got?
- What? - What else can you do...
other than accusing people around Geum Bi...
for going after her money?
No matter how hard you try,
you are a stranger, and I'm...
It's a hereditary disease.
What?
Geum Bi's illness is a rare disease...
which occurs when both parents are carriers.
Half of Geum Bi's illness is...
on you.
I can't...
let someone like you have her.
I will annul your petty parental rights.
I only have knowledge about trees,
so let me talk a little bit about them.
Sometimes, two trees are fused by a branch.
We dig them up to see if they have the same roots,
but they each have their own roots.
In human terms, they are strangers...
living together as one.
Hugging trees.
That's what we call these two trees.
Geum Bi and you are like these trees.
You two may not be blood-related,
but you two are a loving dad and a daughter.
That's what you and Geum Bi are.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
"Elizabeth was a beautiful princess."
"Princess Elizabeth lived in a castle."
Go! Yes, I won!
Come to school on time. You are not in college.
I thought you knew all the subway lines.
Did it stop somewhere?
Why? Don't you remember?
Why wouldn't I remember?
Why are you shouting at me? You're the one who's late.
- Hey. - Let go!
Exactly.
Is there any way I can send her to an orphanage?
Yes, Geum Bi. Say hello.
I got this for lunch at school,
but I don't like pork or milk.
I don't care if you're my daughter or not!
Hey!
And one more thing.
Don't call me Mister. I'm your dad!
Live with me.
I don't care if you live or die. Live with me.
Okay?
Who are you?
Oh, right. What's your name again?
Eun Bi?
Geum Bi.
Okay. Geum Bi.
You like your name because it means gold, right?
No, it doesn't mean gold. It means silk.
Oh, yes. Silk.
What about Bi? Does that mean the rain?
It means a crescent moon.
My gosh, why doesn't it stand for a full moon?
A crescent moon is so tiny.
No, a crescent moon is prettier.
A full moon is so fat.
You don't even know anything.
A silky, crescent moon.
That's pretty,
my daughter.
You're so ugly.
Let me tell you a story.
I don't want to hear it if it's not funny.
Just listen.
Sometimes, two trees...
are fused by a branch.
When it's dug up to see if they have the same roots,
they see that the two trees have different roots.
If those trees were people...
These are really rustic to be a girl's shoes.
If we can make Yoo Joo Young...
lose her parental rights, it may be worth a shot.
Then make her lose it.
The prosecutor has to file...
for the loss of parental rights,
but without clear proof that disqualifies her...
as a parent, they won't do anything.
Let go of me!
I need to talk to the prosecutor!
I pay my taxes just like anyone else!
I'm a taxpayer who wants to see a public servant!
Why won't you let me talk to one?
Mr. Prosecutor! It's me!
I really need to talk to you!
Mr. Prosecutor! Please!
Aren't you going to hear me out?
Hey!
Let go of me!
Sir.
- Are you having fun? - What?
After using your daughter for your release,
you start conning people again.
Now, you're after a child's inheritance.
You're leeching off of her, aren't you?
Sir, that's not it. Please hear me out.
Other than breathing,
everything that comes out of your mouth is a lie.
Sir. Please hear me out.
What do you want?
Please tell him something for me.
Tell him what?
Tell the prosecutor that...
I wasn't part of conning Kang Hee's brother.
We didn't con him.
We gave him a good deal. That's not conning.
I'm about to lose my daughter.
What are you talking about?
Your daughter?
Weren't you dying to send her to an orphanage?
Please go tell him that for me.
Do you think you have the right to say that?
What?
Don't you remember what you did to Chi Soo?
What did you do...
when Chi Soo begged you to stick up for him?
What did you say to him then?
Gosh.
What do you want now?
I did as you told me to.
Keep it that way.
If you don't, I'll tell them what you did 15 years ago.
I told you already. I didn't know.
I have nothing to do...
with the death of Hwi Cheol's dad.
Then why do you look so scared?
No matter what you think you did,
you had a part in it.
Am I wrong?
Chi Soo.
(Promissory Note)
You drove me to a corner knowing she's sick, right?
What?
Don't play dumb with me.
You sly snake.
There isn't a cure or a medicine for her sickness.
You knew she'd die before she turns 20, didn't you?
You're trying to take advantage of that, aren't you?
Fine then.
Everyone has their way of living.
But you should draw the line.
Or I'll take you with me when I go down.
The kid is sick?
I told you not to play dumb.
You disgust me.
Do you think you can take care of her?
Did you two come up with that line together?
You're saying the exact same thing.
Will you give her back to Hwi Cheol...
when you can't handle her anymore?
Do you think he will be devastated...
if you split those two apart?
She's not even his real daughter.
After a week,
he'll go back to his normal self.
And you won't?
If she can't even recognize her own mother,
she's better off with someone rich.
32 percent excluding the future interest.
When I get my hands on her inheritance,
that kind of money will be pocket change.
32 percent interest of 50,000 dollars...
isn't anything I can't handle.
It won't take years for the 1.5 million to be mine.
I don't care if I have to pay 100 percent.
What about your alcoholism?
Drinking a few glasses doesn't make me one.
But once you start, you can't contain yourself.
If you quit drinking, you get anxiety attacks...
and your hands start shaking.
Sounds like an alcoholic to me.
Shut it.
(Yoo Joo Young)
We can't even make her lose her parental rights?
Isn't there anything we can do?
It's all my fault.
Considering the way I lived,
even I wouldn't believe myself.
Geum Bi.
Give me your foot.
Come on. Give me your foot.
The other foot.
Do they fit?
They fit.
Do you like them?
I like them.
Okay, then.
What is "a loss of parental rights"?
I'm not well-off.
Do you...
really want to live with me?
That lady at the mall gave birth to you.
So?
That means...
she has the right to live with you.
But she abandoned me.
My goodness. You're harsh.
Anyway.
For you and me to live together,
she has to give up her parental rights.
However, she's never going to do that...
unless she gets herself into a huge trouble.
So I looked for some other ways.
What?
I'm sorry.
Did you have a bad hamburger?
No, I had tteokbokki.
Did you say your dad was a prosecutor?
Why do you want to know?
Just because. I envy you.
Is your dad in a high office?
Of course. He's the chief prosecutor.
He must have a lot of juniors, then.
Of course, he does.
Does he work in a fancy office?
Of course.
Have you been there?
(Public Service Information)
(Chief Prosecutor Hong Yong Goo)
My gosh, I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
So you are Sil La's friend?
Yes. We're in the same class.
Are you good friends with her?
No, we always fight.
Oh, no. Why do you two fight?
There's a boy named Jae Ha in my class.
She likes him.
Oh, really?
But Jae Ha is a better friend with me than Sil La.
Oh, no. So what?
That's why she gives me the smallest pork cutlet...
and steps on my frogs.
I think I know. You're the girl who hit Sil La. Right?
And you told my wife, "You're so ugly."
Is Jae Ha good looking...
like me?
Is that so?
In that case,
can you let Sil La be good friends with Jae Ha?
Then can you do me a favor?
Sure.
I will let her have him.
My goodness. You're a good girl, Geum Bi.
Okay, then. What can I do for you?
I want to live with my dad.
(Lawyer Ma)
What now?
I thought we were done.
Take the procedures for the transfer of the rights.
We're petitioning for your loss of parental rights.
- You should get ready. - What?
She's very smart, just like you.
She persuaded a prosecutor.
What did you say?
(Settlement Room)
Sir.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
- Thank you, Sir. - My goodness.
Stop that.
You're a taxpayer. Don't do that to a public servant.
We should thank you.
(Court of Law)
Yoo Joo Young, is this you?
Yes. It is.
Let us begin.
You can relax.
You can sit back.
We're all parents.
Oh, okay.
I have a question.
How did you bring her up like that?
I beg your pardon?
I envy you.
My daughter is so selfish.
And she's envious and stubborn.
When I buy her presents...
and give her pocket money,
she says she loves me and that I'm the best.
She's like her mom.
I don't think I'm bringing her up.
It's more like she's bringing me up.
I guess I should've been embarrassed...
instead of being envious.
I thought I was a great dad...
by giving her a lot of presents...
and the pocket money she needs.
I haven't done anything for her.
Come on. Geum Bi has another opinion.
Don't expect too much out of this.
I don't expect anything.
I don't expect anything from her.
No, that's not what I meant.
The law...
barely ever allows the loss of parental rights.
Unless her mom has a serious problem,
this won't happen.
The subject, Yoo Joo Young,
abandoned her own child and has not...
fulfilled her duty as a parent for the last nine years.
Excuse me.
I didn't abandon her. I left her with someone.
She said she was psychologically unstable...
and economically incompetent to bring her up.
Even if that is true,
it is unforgivable to abandon a 12-month-old daughter.
I didn't abandon her. I left her with someone.
You've never visited her once over the past nine years.
I was abroad.
Why didn't you look for her when you came back?
That couple had no kids,
so I thought they would register her with them.
You just acknowledged the fact that you abandoned...
her without taking any lawful measures to give her up.
I had nothing back then.
If I didn't leave, we both would've starved to death.
You could've left her with her grandmother.
We were cut off.
She was worse than a stranger.
Ms. Yoo, calm down.
Are you suggesting that I should've died with her?
Is that law?
If you wanted to stay away from her that badly,
why are you after her inheritance?
Why are you accusing me? That's a foul question.
Is that the only thing you can see?
Yes, a prosecutor only sees criminals.
That's a warning.
Yes, Sir.
Let me ask you a non-foul question.
Ms. Yoo.
Why did you give birth to her?
You disappeared after leaving her with strangers.
Why did you give birth to her...
in the first place?
How could I kill her?
You may have offended the prosecutor,
but it's not enough to overturn the verdict.
We need something more critical.
I didn't know. I didn't know those were drugs.
I just did it a few times with Joo Young.
I said no. Why should I see you?
For you and me to live together,
she has to give up her parental rights.
However,
she's never going to do that.
Unless she gets herself into a huge trouble.
I thought you didn't want to see me?
Why do you keep calling? I'm busy.
You know the prosecutor, so go and ask him.
Kids should live with people with the same surname.
I said I'm Mo Geum Bi.
What kind of a name is that?
If you were a Mo, I wouldn't have named you Geum Bi.
Why are you bugging my dad?
Your dad's the one bugging us.
He's tearing us apart.
He's ignoring the law, too.
What kind of law is that?
It won't let me stay with the people I like.
I don't need laws like that.
Even when you and Hwi Cheol aren't related,
you grew to like him by living together.
If you live with me...
You didn't like your mom, either.
When did I say that?
You said you glared at her like I glared at you.
Your memory's way too good.
My eyes hurt.
Are you thirsty?
Stop glaring or your eyeballs will get cramps.
Do you think you can shoot lasers?
You have to live with me whether you live or die.
- Why? - How many times do I have to tell you?
I know, I know.
What right do I have when I abandoned you?
That's what you want to say, right?
I'm sick of hearing that.
I don't need a mom.
I'm sure you don't.
I felt the same once.
But you need a mom until you're at least 20.
I won't live that long.
You're too young to drink coffee.
Do you even like the taste?
I'll find out when I try it.
What do you know?
Is it bitter?
That's what adults drink.
We add tons of sugar and cream...
because it's so bitter.
We keep mixing things in.
In the end,
we forget what it originally tasted like.
What does that taste like?
This?
I don't know how to explain what this is.
Liquor's an adult drink, though.
So what does it taste like?
It tastes bitter like coffee,
but it's a different kind of bitter.
If the coffee is as bitter as it can be,
the more awake you feel.
If it dulls your senses, it's liquor.
Give me some.
I can't.
Why not?
Your life isn't bad enough for you to need this.
Am I wrong?
Even if I am, stick to your coffee for today.
You're drunk already.
You pretend you can drink when you're a lightweight.
Hey. I didn't drink that much.
It's never-ending once I really start drinking.
How much can you drink?
I don't know.
I have to see.
I think you're drunk. You should stop drinking.
I'm just getting started. I can't stop already.
Excuse me. Can I have another bottle of this?
Silly thing.
Geum Bi.
It's great to be going home together.
Walk properly, will you?
I am walking properly.
What's inside that makes people line up?
Why are they wearing short skirts in this cold weather?
Those places are more fun than you think.
It's such a pity I can't show you around.
I can.
Let's go.
Where?
Do you like to dance?
Dance?
I'm sure you do.
Whether you're good or not.
Let's go.
Can I go inside?
Of course. Your mom will take you inside.
If my daughter wants to go inside,
I'll take you with me. Come along.
Move aside.
Can't you see the line?
The line? I'll stand in line.
Then can I go in?
Not with a kid.
Minors under 18 aren't allowed inside.
Age limits are nonsense.
Aren't kids allowed to dance?
Why aren't I allowed?
This place isn't for children.
What a joke.
What?
Anyone can have fun, adults and kids alike.
So what if she's under 18?
The law isn't everything. Step aside.
Stop testing my patience.
Get out of here.
Too bad. We'll have to go.
Did you think I meant that, you idiot?
Move. Get out of the way.
Get out of the way. You're so ugly.
You're so fat.
You witch.
Geum Bi.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
We can try again some other time.
How dare you hurt my daughter, you jerk?
What have you done? Are you out of your mind?
How dare you hurt her?
Did you just push me?
I need to teach you a lesson.
Get up, Geum Bi.
You jerk.
If you want a fight, you've got one.
- Fight me. - What's wrong with you?
What did you just say?
You jerk. Come back here.
(Daddy Hwi Cheol)
Is she not picking up?
The silly thing...
gets into trouble every day.
Shouldn't we go and look for her?
Where would we even start?
Let me...
Hello?
- See you later. - Let go of me.
I said let me go.
I will in a bit.
Gosh. What did I do wrong?
Everyone's pushing me around today.
I've never seen a woman like you before.
Is she your mom?
What did I do wrong?
It hurts.
Hey.
Yoo Geum Bi.
Do you know where you got that name?
Geum means silk...
and Bi means a crescent moon.
I'm embarrassed to say this...
but I don't know the Chinese characters for your name.
But...
I named you.
I paid someone to come up with some names,
but none of them suited you.
My gosh.
You were so pretty when you were a baby.
How dare he come up with such stupid names?
One of them was "Sam Soon".
You had...
long and dark eyelashes.
Just like a crescent moon.
I could stare at you all day...
and not get sick of you.
So I named you Geum Bi.
Hoping that...
you'd have a life as smooth as silk.
And grow up to be as pretty as a crescent moon.
I found out later that...
your name...
isn't a good one at all.
I should have called you Sam Soon.
Then...
maybe you wouldn't have had this horrible illness.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Geum Bi.
What?
What? What did I do wrong?
Can't I dance when I want to?
Shut your mouth.
Your daughter's the reason you aren't in a cell.
Why should I be locked up for going to a club?
That's just nonsense.
That hurt.
Geum Bi, can you get Mom some water?
I'm so thirsty.
You...
Dad.
He isn't your dad.
You're such a mess.
You can go.
Geum Bi.
Where's the water?
Why didn't you pick up?
You should've told me where you'd be.
Let go.
What are you doing?
Where were you? We were so worried.
Why don't you listen?
Why are you shouting? You're so noisy.
What?
Come with me.
Do you think glaring will make you shoot lasers?
What did you say? Why you...
That brat.
Hugging trees.
She wasn't just disorderly. She fought a policeman.
Obstruction of justice.
She slipped up just when we needed her to.
Will she lose her parental rights?
Trying to take a child into a club is no small issue.
If we're lucky...
Excuse me, Sir.
- What? - I have...
something important to do today.
My insides hurt, too.
Can you order me some soup?
What?
Sir.
Based on what we've discussed so far...
and the information that was given,
I have serious doubts as to whether you should...
keep your parental rights.
However,
you, the child's mother, seem to show remorse,
the child is still young,
and...
our society values maternal love and instinct highly.
I will make my decision after speaking with the child.
You have a good taste in fashion.
Try them on.
Why? Don't you like them?
No.
I like them.
Where did you get the money for this?
I earned enough by reading fortunes.
You little...
It's your hard-earned money.
Consider it accepted.
Let's get a refund tomorrow.
Just say you don't like them.
I'll throw them out.
Don't do that. I'll wear them.
Oh, right.
- Did you take your medicine? - What?
Yes. Of course, I did.
Later on,
you won't be able to recognize...
your own reflection.
(Arbitration Room)
Yoo Geum Bi.
Come in.
Go on.
It's cold so let's eat shabu-shabu later.
We'll wait outside.
Okay.
Will it go smoothly?
Gosh. I doubt it.
It's never been smooth sailing with her.
What would've happened if we never met her?
You're right.
Is your name...
Yoo Geum Bi?
Yes.
Do you know why you are here?
You can wait outside, Ms. Yoo.
Pardon? Why?
Go outside so Geum Bi can speak freely.
You, too.
(Arbitration Room)
Now that there's no one in here,
tell me exactly how you feel.
Well...
Yes?
Geum Bi.
The department store...
No.
I want to live with my mom.