(Episode 10)
Hey.
- Yes, you. - Come here.
Come here.
I told you to come over here.
My gosh.
Come over here.
- I'll have the exact same one. - Okay.
Stop right there.
Stop.
Cho Rong.
This phone has been turned off. You'll be directed to voice mail.
Da Rong.
Where did she go?
Go that way.
You.
Stop right there.
Won't she pick up?
No.
She told me she'll come pick us up here.
Cho Rong, let's go find Mum.
- Go away. - You.
Come over here.
- Stop right there. - Go.
Go away.
You annoy me so much.
You.
Wait a minute.
- Why? - Wait.
- I'm going to call the police. - You wench.
- Why did you hit me? - Don't be kidding yourself.
You want to call the police? Go call them.
Do you think I'll let you run off with my money?
It's just money.
I'll pay you back.
You don't even have anything. Look at how you talk.
"It's just money?"
You.
You ran off with my money. Watch how you speak.
Why did you run off when it's just money then?
I heard you ran off with the money you received from another place.
Let go.
Let me go.
I need to go.
Let go of me.
Cho Rong. Do you know Grandmother's house?
Let's go.
Cho Rong. My legs hurt.
I'll carry you.
Cho Rong.
I'm hungry.
Hold on.
Mum will buy us something to eat.
Cho Rong. Are we there yet?
We're nearly there.
Cho Rong, I'm sleepy.
Mum will come find us soon.
This phone has been turned off. You'll be directed to voice mail.
Open the door.
Open it this instant.
You jerks!
Give me back my phone.
I need to pick up the phone.
I need to answer the call.
I need to answer...
Open up.
Cho Rong, I'm scared.
There's nothing to be scared of. I'm here.
Mum will find us soon if we stay here.
Let her go now.
We need to use the room.
Where are you?
Mum.
Cho Rong. Da Rong.
Don't cry.
Are you okay?
This is child abuse.
We need to report it to the police.
Calm down.
How can I be calm?
How could she hit a child?
She has her own child too.
Let's go to the police.
We need to go to the police?
You said you got hit. We need to report her.
Wait.
Cho Rong, where did you get hit?
Tell me honestly.
Yes, your uncle will be a judge one day.
He knows the law well. He studied it for a long time.
But he fails the exam all the time.
Let's go to the police.
Where did you get hit? Your face?
- Your legs? - No.
Did she scratch you? Or did she pinch you?
Not exactly.
Look at her keeping silent.
She's terrified to speak. She must have been abused so much.
Did she starve you or something?
- Did she starve you? - It's obvious.
Why else would she have come all the way here?
Stay out of this.
- Let's go to the police. - Mum, that's not it.
She hit me here.
Like this.
- Once like that? - Yes.
That's still abuse.
Why did she hit you?
- Because of the make-up. - Make-up?
Did you use her cosmetics?
No. I used the cosmetics you bought me.
She told me off for wearing make-up.
She must be crazy.
Who is she to tell you off?
She didn't even buy it for you.
She must be insane.
Let's have a talk.
My goodness.
What?
You're the one who's insane.
How could you buy a kid cosmetics?
She's only in lower school.
Do you want her to turn out like you?
She wanted to buy it.
You shouldn't let her buy everything she wants.
That's why you're like this.
You let Geum Sik use you. You still haven't come to senses.
You're too old-fashioned.
Kids all wear make-up these days.
Honey.
- I... - Say what you need to say.
I just returned from Busan so I'm a bit busy.
I think Cho Rong and Da Rong...
went to see their mum.
What?
What do you think you're doing?
How could you let them go there? You know how much I hate it.
I left the house for a little while and it happened.
Let's talk about the details when you return home.
Please bring the kids home.
Honey.
What are you doing?
Why did you take the kids?
Come out.
You said you'll take good care of them.
Is this taking good care of them?
If you're going to keep like this, let me raise the kids.
- Who do you think you are? - Don't you know?
I'm Cho Rong and Da Rong's mum.
Bring the kids to me.
You have no say in this.
Did you know the woman hit the kids?
- What? - Good going.
I won't send the kids home for a while. That's that.
Hey.
Hey!
- Geum Sik. - A Young.
You know where Cho Rong's grandmother lives, right?
I've been there before. Why?
Go there and bring the kids.
Isn't it tasty?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Grandmother, you're the best. - Grandmother, you're the best.
Eat up, my babies.
Try this too.
Fried shrimps.
It sounds delicious. Crunchy.
Fried sweet potatoes.
I love sweet potatoes.
They're mixing jjajangmyeon.
Stop announcing that. You're killing me.
Ms Nam. Ma'am.
That won't work.
They won't invite us in.
I can't hold back.
We still have 12 tissues left.
You seem dumb.
Then, go to the main building yourself.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Wait.
New toilet paper should be used for new food.
- Good luck! - Good luck!
(Nam Gi Ja)
What is it?
Be quiet.
Is anyone home?
Hello.
Leave it out. I'm going to leave soon.
It's been a long time since we last saw you.
You've gotten so pretty.
- Why are you here? - Let's go. Get up.
Stay a little longer.
It's all right.
- Get up now. - I don't want to.
They're in the middle of eating.
You seem like you just arrived. Why don't you join in?
It's all right. I'll wait outside.
Finish your food and come out quick.
Why don't you stop ignoring me?
We're not enemies, are we?
Hello.
You should address me politely.
Stop.
I'll give you 10 minuets.
That girl is asking for it.
- My gosh. - Mum.
She's out.
What should I do?
- What if I get caught? - That's the end of it.
Wait. She's doesn't know me.
You're going to meet her later.
How is she related to the folks at the main building?
- I'm full. - Are you full?
- Da Rong, are you full? - Yes.
Are you all full?
Then tell the folks at the annex building to come.
They've been waiting for this.
Come over.
Is anyone there?
Don't you want any?
We do.
We're dying to eat some.
Why are you doing this?
What are you doing?
Can't you bring it over here?
For two.
My goodness.
They asked you to bring it?
They have no wits.
Why are you giving them so much?
- There you go. - Oh, my.
Is this for two?
Maybe he thought we wanted two pieces.
Never eat food in a haste.
I know I'd look dumb.
Be honest with me.
Did you...
hit Cho Rong?
- Yes. - Where? How?
I should know.
I just gave her a spanking...
on her back.
It happened in an instant.
I shouldn't have done it. I'm sorry.
Why did you do that?
She was putting on make-up.
Make-up?
Did Cho Rong put on make-up?
She recently started to.
Her mother bought her cosmetics.
I gave her a scolding that she's too young to wear make-up.
I'll make sure it won't happen again.
I'm sorry.
From now on,
I will discipline Cho Rong and Da Rong.
Whatever they do,
just pretend you don't know.
Cho Rong.
I'm so sorry.
Go to your room and hold your hands up.
Right now.
Geum Sik. How could you let this happen?
Cho Rong told me what happened on our way home.
She said Jae Soon hit her.
I can't believe this.
I need to talk to you, Geum Sik.
Geum Sik.
This isn't right.
She shouldn't abuse the kids like this.
I already talked to her about it. Stay out of it.
Are you going to let them go to Da Hae's?
I won't. It will never happen again.
She might start to want something else.
- What do you mean? - You know what I mean.
She only wants to see the kids.
I can't stop her from seeing them.
She made a promise that she won't see them.
Still.
I will take care of it. Don't concern yourself.
Have you forgotten what she did to you?
People don't change.
I saw her in a long time, but she was still rude.
Even the way she dresses and speaks is the same.
What would the kids learn?
When I think about the days you suffered and grew thin,
my heart aches.
You don't still have feelings for her, right?
Of course not.
- You know I... - You don't open up easily,
but once you do, you give them your all.
You knew she was crude,
but you stayed with her because she's your first love.
I...
already married someone.
She's your first love.
You're going to fall for her if she seduces you, right?
Drop some of them at the dry cleaner's,
hand-wash the rest and iron them.
Okay.
Don't you dare lay hands on Cho Rong and Da Rong.
Don't you feel bad for them?
You're not their birth mother. Don't act like you are.
Do you understand?
You told me you got remarried because of the kids.
That was an excuse.
You want to drive them out...
and have fun by yourselves, right?
- Did she tell you to? - She's not like that.
Look at that. You're siding with her.
Let me raise them.
You'll raise them poorly.
I can't let you do that. Never.
You gave up custody.
That's when we got divorced.
- Things are different now. - Nothing is different.
Nothing at all.
You're obligated to respect my visitor's right.
Visitor's right?
It's called visitation right.
What a know-it-all.
Let's follow the law.
Fine.
- Once in a month. - Four times.
Twice.
Only if you don't take them to your place.
The taxi metre is still running, so let's keep it short.
Once a week.
That's 4 times a month, and they get 1 sleep-over.
Bye.
Dad.
Are you here to pick up Ddol Ee?
Yes. How about you?
I wanted to see Ddol Ee.
Why did you pay for Se Gye's medicine?
I'm his sister. Why can't I?
Don't overspend on us.
Stop buying us groceries, too.
Is that credit card...
Geum Sik's?
- Yes. - Then he must get...
the notifications.
It's okay.
Did you know about it?
Of course.
He set it just in case I lose it.
I can use it freely.
It's fine as long as you knew.
From now on, stop spending money on us.
We won't starve. Don't worry.
Also,
about that picture.
Picture? What picture?
What?
Nothing. I'm going to go now.
You said you wanted to see Ddol Ee.
I'm sorry I was so harsh on you.
I'm sorry I punched you.
You and Gab Soon are completely broken up, right?
Both of your families are against it.
You won't make it.
Call me sometimes.
You used to call me often.
Okay.
Let's drink this and go.
Se Gye.
I'm fine with everything.
I'm fine if we broke up,
and I'm fine if we can't get married.
But...
it hurts so badly here.
I kept thinking about how I treated Gab Soon so poorly.
She waited for me to pass the exam for 10 years.
She worked part-time to feed me.
She couldn't buy cosmetics because she wanted to buy me tonkatsu.
She couldn't wear skirts because she wanted to buy me gimbap.
I haven't done anything for her.
I've never...
celebrated our anniversary or her birthday.
I gave her paper cranes on her birthday.
I heard girls hate that.
Gab Soon looked happy,
so I thought she was really happy.
Se Gye.
Why did Gab Soon date someone like me?
I don't know that.
If I pass,
I'll take Gab Soon to an expensive restaurant.
I won't look at the price.
I'll say,
"Order anything you like",
and buy her the most expensive food.
She told me that's her...
long-standing wish.
My dear Gab Soon.
Good.
Remember that feeling and pass the exam.
Think of this as...
one of the memories...
and a shining jewel in life.
All right?
A jewel.
Wait for me, Gab Soon.
I'll buy you a diamond ring that costs 20,000 dollars.
You're drunk. Let's go.
Se Gye.
More than anything,
it's so hard to live without Gab Soon.
I miss her so much,
but I can't call her because it might make her sad.
Gab Soon.
My dear Gab Soon.
Gab Soon!
White shark, blue shark
I play gently because I'm scared
Hello.
Don't greet anyone in our family.
Pretend you don't know us.
Do you understand?
Yes.
It'll be great if you can move.
Did you see Gab Dol?
No, I didn't.
Don't say his name. It brings me bad luck.
But Gab Soon's name sounds similar.
Don't tell her you saw Gab Dol.
Don't stir up her mind.
You're right on time.
Sit down, Mum. You, too, Aunt.
So this is the lunch you prepared. It looks nice.
Come out, Dad.
We were on our way home, and we saw Gab Dol...
Actually, we didn't.
I was saying we didn't see anyone like Gab Dol. It's true.
What's all this? It smells good.
It's pasta.
Gab Soon lightened up the mood.
I can hear her wailing
No, no. I'll be quiet.
Can't I just have rice?
You're so old-fashioned. Just try it.
Just eat what we give you...
without complaining. You talk too much.
I hate men like that.
Gosh. You've been married to him...
all these years and now you hate him?
- I'll get you some rice. - Don't. I can eat this.
Roll it up like this. Haven't you seen it?
Just eat it as you like.
Don't spill.
He hasn't even taken a bite yet.
You always spill on your belly.
- Hold your belly in. - Stop nagging.
If I could control it, I wouldn't live like this.
- It's delicious. - That's good.
Dad, let's have a can of beer, okay?
Okay.
I went out and got them earlier.
She's okay, right?
Can't you tell? She's relieved she broke up with him.
I would feel the same way.
Nobody knows that.
They were together for 10 years. They might get back together.
Stop scaring me.
Ta-da!
Why isn't there soju?
It's cold.
Where is the sauce?
Gosh, you're so old-fashioned.
- I'm sorry. I'm old-fashioned. - Just eat with this.
I've been a wanderer, so I don't know food.
- Cheers. - Joong Nyeon.
- Pour me a glass. - All right.
What about you, Mum?
- He's here! - Is he?
Gosh, he's so cool.
- He's handsome. - Oh, my.
Don't greet anyone in our family.
What if anyone finds out you lived together?
Don't you come anywhere near Gab Soon.
It'll be great if you can move.
Gab Soon.
Goodbye.
Let her be confused.
Let her feel uneasy.
Let her wonder.
Life makes you suffer...
Sausage stew. Underline the word, "sausage stew".
Underlining "sausage stew".
Is the title "Sausage Stew"?
The title was "Men" at first, but I changed it to "Sausage Stew".
I see.
When did you write this poem?
When I was in the army.
In the army, we had football matches between troops,
and we bonded with each other while eating sausage stew.
In the sausage stew restaurant my friend owns,
the whole troop used to have a get-together. On those days,
I'd feel sick to my stomach.
I tell myself I won't have sausage stew ever again,
but looking at that restaurant...
makes me want to have sausage stew again.
I want to eat sausage stew, too.
- Let's eat, then. - I'd like to, but...
You'll get sick if you don't eat things you crave. Let's eat it.
You don't like food like that.
It's embarrassing.
What's wrong with you?
What's embarrassing about enjoying sausage stew?
I'm an ordinary person, too.
I like sausage stew, I want to eat it...
and I miss its taste so badly that it makes me sick.
You're so cute sometimes.
You're only saying that not to embarrass me, right?
Do you have sausage stew ramyeon?
Why is the laundry here?
She took it out here so she can ask...
Gong Joo to do it.
Don't do that. She doesn't know how to do anything.
I already had Jae Soon and did chores at her age.
Kids these days hate to hear things like that.
Be half as good as you are to Gong Joo.
Why isn't she here yet?
Who is this?
Hello? Who is this?
- It's me. - Who?
- Who are you? - I can't believe this girl.
"Who are you?"
Goodness.
Because you're poor,
she didn't even bother to save your number.
Didn't you save your mother-in-law's number?
Mother.
I told you to come and pick up Se Gye's medicine.
Come over now.
Cook rice.
I've never done that.
- That's why I want you to do it. - I can't.
Just try it. I won't scold you.
Frankly, Gab Soon can't cook rice, either.
Of course she can.
She cooked for us.
That's not rice. Those were noodles.
Try it.
I want to eat the rice my daughter-in-law cooked for me.
Stir it and wash it.
Like this?
You should stick your hand in and stir.
Don't just stir water.
Like this?
Drain the water. You should repeat it several times.
Don't spill the rice. Just pour out the water.
Fill it with water again.
Wash it.
Drain.
You're wasting all the rice.
Why can't you do anything?
Stop it. You're going to make her cry.
You've been married to Se Gye for a year now.
You haven't even cooked rice or soup for me.
I'm just unlucky to have you as my daughter-in-law.
Who can I blame?
Leave it.
When are you going to have a baby?
I can't do that.
You can't have a baby?
I've never given birth before.
Listen to that.
Of course you haven't given birth before.
I can't do that.
What do you mean you can't do it?
You always say, "I can't do that."
It must be your favourite thing to say.
How did you get married, then?
My grandpa told me to.
Would you have a baby if your grandpa told you to?
Let me ask my mum.
Oh, dear. You have to ask your mum about that?
Oh, my goodness.
My gosh.
Oh, dear.
Be careful, Ms Nam. You're going to break everything.
Just eat.
Does it suit your appetite?
It's fine.
Is it too salty or bland?
I said it's fine.
What does that mean?
Are you saying it's salty or bland?
- Ms Nam. - Get me some salt.
Why are you being like that?
What do you mean? He asked for salt so I gave it to him.
If you're done cooking, you can leave and rest.
What's the matter, Dad? Why are you not yelling at her?
What are you talking about?
Don't be noisy while I eat.
- Where's Gong Joo? - She's at her in-laws.
I wonder what they're making her do.
It's me.
I just arrived.
Bring Gong Joo back. Don't take too long.
Yes, Ms Yeo.
Eat first. I won't take long.
Se Gye, let's go home.
They almost killed me.
Let's eat first.
Can't we eat at home?
No, we can't.
I'm here.
See you later, Se Gye. Bye, Gong Joo.
Bye, Gab Soon.
Wait, Gab Soon.
Wait for me.
Are you all right?
I am good as you see.
You're brave.
Why? Did you think I was going to cry to death?
If you think about it, women are tougher than men.
What do you mean?
Don't hate Gab Dol too much.
He's thoughtful.
Did you see him?
- We had soju together. - Why would you?
It had nothing to do with you.
I've known him since we were young.
He may look immature and inconsiderate,
but he's not a bad guy.
He was crying over the fact that he wasn't good to you.
Lunatic.
He says he'll come back once he passes the exam.
He wants to take you to an expensive restaurant...
and buy you steak without worrying about the price.
He couldn't buy you proper gifts for your anniversaries...
and made you paper cranes instead.
He was crying because he felt bad about it.
I felt sad for him.
He said he didn't know.
What do you mean he didn't know?
What kind of a guy doesn't know that women like luxury bags?
He just didn't want to buy them.
It's not that he didn't want to. He couldn't afford it.
If he really wanted to, he could have found ways to afford it.
It sounds like you broke up with him because he couldn't get you a bag.
I've just had enough.
After 10 years of dating, there's nothing left.
I'm embarrassed to see my friends.
That's not like you.
It's over already.
Don't detest him or speak ill of him.
Consider this as a good memory.
It's the worst thing to speak ill of your ex-boyfriend.
- I'll get going. - Okay, see you.
He was crying over the fact that he wasn't good to you.
Even if he misses you, he can't call you because he feels bad.
Consider this as a good memory.
What did she say?
She wants me to have a baby.
She told you that?
Of course she did. Would she tell Se Gye to have a baby?
Let's talk about it. Why aren't you having a baby?
What should I do, Mum?
It's not time, yet. You're still young.
She's not young. She's 24.
Dad, I had her at that age and it almost killed me.
You shouldn't have to settle like me. Have fun.
And you didn't have fun? You had as much fun as you wanted.
I didn't have any fun.
You were so busy having fun that you quit high school.
Dad, why? They are watching.
It's time for your medication.
Go inside and have your medication, Dad.
Oh, dear.
Don't do this.
A woman's heart is as fickle as a reed.
You can't.
Don't do this. Don't ask no more.
Your poems make me feel like...
I'm drinking banana-flavoured milk after getting out of the sauna.
Where are you right now?
I'm at bed by this hour.
Same here.
What are you wearing?
I'm wearing pyjamas.
What colour is it?
It's pink.
Professor, can you recite another poem for me?
Joong Nyeon, this one looks good.
It looks good.
You have a good eye.
You should find a man like that.
Forget it. Who looks for a man in the trash?
What happened to you?
You were so clean.
Don't take pity on me. This is fun.
Sure.
You should talk back to your wife.
I feel so bad for you.
I feel worse for you.
What would you do when I'm gone?
I don't know.
I feel sad watching you.
So you should straighten things out.
- The men you used to see... - Stop!
I'll take care of my life.
Is this a married couple going through the garbage together?
Oh, gosh. People say that all the time.
I hate hearing that.
You were always stuck to your brother like glue.
What's wrong?
Do you not like him any more because he's bold and wrinkly?
You can play with these but make sure you put them back.
Have you forgotten, Mal Nyeon?
Even on our first night,
you won't get away from Joong Nyeon so you slept with us.
That's unbelievable.
You did.
Mum!
The daughter of the sauna owner got divorced.
Again?
Was that her third divorce?
It is.
- For what? - Because of the ex-wife.
The ex-wife and the kids would come to the house...
and talk him into things. They kicked her out...
and the husband got back with the ex-wife. She has two daughters.
That's how things are.
You just have to feed boys...
but girls are picky so they're hard to please.
Maybe they're going through puberty.
You should also try your best not to hurt the girls.
Okay.
Don't try so hard to impress them.
Consider them as your own...
and be strict on certain things.
Cho Rong is not easy to handle.
Kids these days don't even listen to their own parents.
You have to talk to them gently when you can.
Does his ex-wife come once in a while?
She doesn't.
He promised me in the beginning and said that won't happen.
You never know. They might be meeting each other in secret.
Daughters are drawn to their mums.
You registered your marriage, right?
They did it when they were getting married.
Is Ddol Ee on your family register as well?
No.
You have to if you want to send him to school next year.
That shouldn't be done so easily.
You can't just change his last name like that.
You have to if the circumstance calls for it. It's just last name.
It doesn't look good if his last name is different from the girls.
They'll be going to the same school.
It's better to add Ddol Ee on the family register as his own.
Changing the last name won't make Ddol Ee his own.
Even if Ddol Ee was to be born again, he won't be their family.
Do you want to change his last name...
and be hypocritical by saying that it's a perfect family?
That's not being hypocritical. Did you have to put it that way?
You don't even know how long Geum Sik and Jae Soon will last.
Are you going to get married again if you find a richer man?
Are you cursing at her?
I know a woman who changed her kid's last name twice.
The kid eventually took the mum's last name.
You should make your sister watch what she says.
What?
I'm just stating a fact.
I'm telling the truth.
That's enough.
You should be prudent. This has to do with Ddol Ee's future.
You didn't see your divorce coming...
and you can never predict what's ahead of you.
Don't think about yourself. Think about Ddol Ee first.
Think about what would happen when he grows up.
It's about his sense of identity.
He's still young and doesn't know anything...
but don't try to hurt him.
He's so inflexible.
Don't you think kids will make fun of him at school...
if his last name is different from the girls?
Ddol Ee has nothing to lose by being registered as Geum Sik's son.
It'll be great if Ddol Ee inherits his estate, too.
Would he?
I see. That's worth doing, then.
You're so clever.
- Don't! - Waive, give me a second.
Stay still.
Try this.
Come here!
You're so pretty.
Come here.
Keep it down.
I'm studying so keep it down.
You were having fun all this time. Why are you studying now?
Why are you studying?
- Here. - Da Hae.
I have to pass this time.
Go ahead. I didn't stop you.
- Go ahead. - You can do it, Uncle!
Be quiet.
- Quiet. - Quiet.
It's not like we stopped him, right?
- Let me see. - He can do it.
He can, right?
Come here.
Say, "Hello, Dad."
You're home.
Hello, Dad.
What were you doing, Ddol Ee?
- I was watching the television. - Were you?
I made some soup. Do you want to take a shower first?
- Sure. - Would you like a drink?
No, I'm fine.
Take a shower, then.
- It's me. - What is it, Geum Sik?
The girls are here.
I know.
We were about to eat dinner.
I'll pick them up by 10pm.
Please have them finish by then.
I was going to have them sleep over.
Is that not possible?
I'll pick them up. I'll call you back.
Is he out of his mind?
I said I was going to have them sleep over.
Watch your mouth.
Do you want Geum Sik to lose his mind?
Send them back. Listen to what he says.
Whose mum are you?
I'm Geum Sik's mum. What do you want?
Where are you going?
I'm going to pick up the girls.
I thought they were sleeping over.
I'm coming home.
Don't yell at me!
I'm hungry, too.
I met up with Do Geum. I'm coming home now.
Yes. Sure.
It's me.
I'm by the street.
I'll come up so please send them this way.
Okay.
- Geum Sik. - Yes. Where are the girls?
- Come in for a bit. - It's all right.
I'll stay here. You can call them.
Come in for a bit.
It's not like you can't.
You're not together any more but what about the girls?
Don't be so cold-hearted.
Have a cup of tea and go.
Come on.
It makes me happy to see the four of you...
lying down like this.
I'm so happy, Dad.
Are you?
Mum, I want us to live together like this.
Aren't you happy, Mum?
It depends on how your dad behaves.
That's what I want to say.
- Mum and Dad, you should kiss. - What?
Let's close our eyes.
- Kiss! Kiss! - Kiss! Kiss!
Well...
You can if you want.
Do you think I can't?
You're more drawn to the woman you had children with.
His ex-wife met the kids in secret...
and now, they're getting back together.
You're back.
You're home, Cho Rong.
You must be tired. It's late.
You told him not to let us sleep with our mum, right?
- Jo Cho Rong! - Don't do that.
Come and eat.
I'm sorry. I forgot to tell you. I have a morning meeting.
Really? You should get going.
See you later.
- Bye, Dad. - Bye, Dad.
Enjoy your food.
Here's sausage for Cho Rong.
Here's ham for Da Rong.
You know the food we brought from our mum's house yesterday?
I want them.
Sure.
It's cooked beans and stir-fried anchovies.
I thought you don't eat them.
I eat them if my grandma makes them.
That's good to hear.
They're good for you so you should eat them.
Da Rong is having a concert at her kindergarten, right?
Can I come?
Mum's coming.
My mum is much prettier.
- It's delicious, right? - Yes, Cho Rong.
Can I try it?
No, don't eat it. It's ours.
Don't go off on your own.
I'll drop you off by the bus.
Mum, I want to go to her kindergarten, too.
They don't have a spot for you, yet. You have to wait a bit longer.
Let's go.
Da Rong.
Let's take a seat.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
Ddol Ee, good morning.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
Ddol Ee, go ahead.
Here.
Don't lose your cool.
Kid. You look smart.
Let me see.
You look charming.
About your mum,
she was pretty, kind and rich.
- She was perfect. - Yes.
She had it all.
- But... - Don't ask.
- Just know that. - Just one question.
Why did she die?
Go ahead. You'll be late. I'm in a hurry.
Dad.
(Geum Soo Jo)
What do you think of this for our wedding ring?
I love it.
He popped the question.
I'm going to be the wife a rich man.
(Number of likes)
What?
What is this?
Once a week?
I thought they weren't seeing each other.
It's natural to see one's mum.
I don't know why I feel this way.
I have a kid of my own.
I know parents and their kids can't be separated.
But I still feel strange.
It feels like...
I'll have to move out if the mum comes back.
Don't say that.
Why are you saying that?
You're right. Why am I like this?
Trust Geum Sik.
He's faithful.
What am I saying? You're not even married.
Jae Soon. Don't worry.
Even if she wants to return, if you stay put, she can't do anything.
- Right? - Of course.
You're lawfully his wife. Okay?
You're right.
Don't tell Mum and Dad.
Of course not.
I need to go to work. Let's go.
Okay.
I'm earning money too.
Jae Soon, don't use your credit card that often.
You didn't need to buy Se Gye's medicine.
He's my brother.
Dad got angry that you used your card. He had a fight with Mum.
They fought?
I think he was worried about you.
- I'll be off. - Okay.
Whose car is that?
I don't know.
It's been there for days. It blocks the way.
Hello? I have a car to report.
The address is...
- Oh, no. - My goodness.
- My goodness. - Oh, my.
- Oh, no. - They can't tow that.
Someone needs to get that.
I reported that.
Gab Soon.
That belongs to the son of the owner of the building.
- What? - The buildings around here...
all belong to them.
I heard he has a temper. What are we going to do?
We're going to get fired.
We might get kicked out.
Stop.
Stop!
Hold on!
Sir!
Stop.
Stop!
(Our Gab Soon)
Are you dumb?
What are we going to live off this month?
Go get it.
Si Nae. Gong Joo.
- Grandfather. - Dad.
You're a thief now?
I asked you to lend me money.
Even if it's a private loan.
Hello, I'm Shin Gab Soon.
Are you free for dinner tonight?
- What is she doing? - She's trying to gain favour.
Kick him out.
If he becomes a police, I'll eat my hat.
I've asked repeatedly.
I told you to be careful that it's an important event for my business.
Help!