- My goodness. - Oh, my.
Should I go and tell him?
I reported that.
That belongs to the son of the owner of the building.
- What? - I heard he has a temper.
What are we going to do?
We're going to get fired.
Stop!
Hold on!
Sir!
Stop!
Look, Gab Soon.
How could you...
be so reckless?
He always parks his car by the entrance,
and customers complained, so...
Whether he parks by the door or not, it does not concern you.
Nobody told you to report it.
What will you do now?
This is a serious matter.
- I know. - Before he finds out,
bring the car back here,
or beg for forgiveness.
Do whatever it takes.
Okay, Sir.
(Towing Invoice)
Give me your driving licence and 2 dollars and 10 cents, please.
Driving licence?
Isn't it your car?
No, it's not mine.
The owner must come himself.
Next, please.
(Tow Company)
We're going to get fired.
Before he finds out, bring the car back here.
(Director's office)
I heard he has a temper.
Excuse me.
Is the landlord's son here?
Do you mean the director?
Yes, I'm here to see him.
Did you make an appointment?
I haven't.
Then you can go there and wait.
Thank you.
- Cho Rong, get in. - Cho Rong.
All right, you can stay with them tonight.
It's not just tonight.
I'm going to do what I want whenever I want to.
Put them to bed early so that they don't wake up late.
Send them off to school on time.
I'll pick them up at 8am.
Make sure they're ready for school.
Don't make them stay up in the night.
Do you hear me?
Hello?
My goodness.
Hello, Sir.
No, nothing's new.
Someone's here to see you. She's been waiting for a while.
I don't know who she is.
I'm Shin Gab Soon.
She says she's Shin Gab Dol.
Not Gab Dol. Gab Soon.
Shin Gab Soon.
She says she's Shin Gab Soon now.
I see.
He's not coming today.
Then I'll come back tomorrow.
He says he has no reason to see you.
He doesn't know who you are.
Are you here to borrow money?
He really hates that.
I'm not here for that.
Anyways, goodbye.
(Director's office)
What's that?
You don't need to know.
Where are you going?
He's asking you.
Why won't you reply?
Why do you keep asking?
- Don't you mind what I do. - You should answer back.
Don't ignore me.
You'd respond to a dog.
She would. It's only because you asked.
You heard her, right?
My goodness. I'm so lonely.
Make a scene.
This is worse than ignoring.
She treats you really bad.
It's not even funny.
I know.
Why are you taking it out on me?
You can't even say a thing in front of her.
Who says so?
You should hold your tongue.
Think first before you say it.
How could you blurt things out?
Whatever you say becomes true.
Plus, don't tag along.
I don't like that.
My gosh.
Oh, my.
It's already done.
It looks delicious.
Here.
It's hot.
There you go.
How is it?
Which one's better? Mine or the restaurant's?
You're the best. It's crunchy and tasty.
It's crunchy and tasty?
Eat up.
I hope Cho Rong doesn't come back.
I'm so happy with just you.
Don't hate Cho Rong.
Cho Rong likes you.
No, she hates me.
She likes you, you just don't know it.
It must be Dad.
You need to say hello to Dad, Okay?
Mum.
What are you doing?
We're eating chicken.
- Where's your husband? - He's not here yet.
Great.
It's for the kids.
I made some tonkatsu and bulgogi.
You didn't need to.
Grandma.
Ddol Ee. Are you eating chicken?
Where are the kids?
They went to their mum's. They're sleeping over.
- What's he saying? - Well...
They went to their mum's to sleep over.
Didn't you say they've cut ties?
This is the first time.
It's not the first time. They went there last time.
They brought food, too.
They didn't let me have any.
- Mum, did you eat dinner? - Since when?
It was recent.
She's their mum. They should be able to see her.
Did you have dinner?
Didn't she remarry?
I don't know. I didn't ask.
Mum, try this.
I made this myself.
It's crunchy on the outside but soft inside. It's delicious.
Is your husband seeing her with them?
No.
They went through a bad breakup. They're not on speaking terms.
It's just the kids. Don't worry.
Who doesn't go through a bad breakup during a divorce?
Are you sleeping?
Mal Nyeon.
- Shin Mal Nyeon. - Why?
Ta-da.
You're so mean.
How could you say that to me?
How could you replay your wife's words to me?
You shouldn't do that. You'll have it coming.
That's why I'm living like this.
You can't even say a thing to her.
I do speak my mind.
You like these.
If you do that again,
I'm going to tell on you.
If she finds it out,
she's going to want a divorce.
You.
If you do, you and I will both die.
So be good to me.
Take pity on me.
All right.
Here.
Eat up.
You're back soon.
They're meeting these days?
That's what I heard.
They're sleeping over every week?
Didn't you hear what she said?
The kids are sleeping over every week at their mum's.
Except the husband.
He shouldn't.
That's what I mean.
Don't make me angry and get out.
You too. The both of you.
This is all because you were greedy.
- Mal Nyeon. - What are you saying?
You made Jae Soon get a divorce because she was having a tough time.
You made Jae Soon marry again because she was having a tough time.
You made her have no choice but to listen to you since she was little.
There's no daughter like Jae Soon in the whole world.
If anything happens to Jae Soon, it's entirely your fault.
Don't blame my brother.
Get out.
- Why? I'm right. - Get out.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
My gosh.
I'm busy working tonight. I won't come home.
Hello.
- What are you doing here? - You know why.
Kids are watching. Talk later.
Later when?
You can't keep doing this.
What's the matter?
Dad, I'm scared.
Cho Rong and Da Rong, goodbye.
- Bye, Mum. - Bye, Mum.
See you next week.
Call me if something happens.
Who are they?
It's none of your business.
- Are they moneylenders? - Why do you ask?
It's not like you're going to pay them back for me.
Why are you living like this?
Have you still not straightened up?
- I'm incurable. - What?
Why are you butting in?
To put it bluntly,
why do you care how I live my life?
Aren't you embarrassed in front of the kids?
Straighten up.
How can I be more straightened up?
You're unbelievable.
Though we're nothing to each other, you're still their mother.
You should be ashamed.
Don't look at me. That's annoying.
Dad, don't be mean to Mum.
I think they're bad people.
Dad, tell them off.
I'm scared.
The landlord's son just came by and made a scene.
He's going to get rid of the café and make a private parking lot.
What are you going to do about this?
He's not in.
When will he be back?
I don't know.
He doesn't meet just anyone.
Why won't this work?
(Private parking lot for Director)
(Do not park here.)
(Thank you for your cooperation.)
Come by now.
Did you lose sleep over that?
How can you smile?
It's nothing I tell you.
You must be worried because of the hot sauna owner's daughter.
Are the kids back?
They went straight to school.
Where's your husband?
He came in early last night.
Isn't he meeting the kids' mum?
- He isn't. - Are you sure?
I'm sure.
They talk sometimes because of the kids.
He doesn't have any good feelings for her.
Who knows?
They had kids.
Ddol Ee's dad and I don't talk.
I don't even know what he's doing.
He did many wrongs.
Mum.
I'm his lawful wife. We've officially married on paper.
What are you worried about?
I thought I could be at ease.
Why is she like that all of a sudden?
The kids want their mum.
Mum.
Don't worry. I'm doing great.
You should.
You were kind-hearted since you were little.
I don't know why but you make me feel sad.
I think Gab Soon will manage anything.
I don't feel at ease when I think of you.
I'm worried you won't be treated well.
I'm treated well.
You're destined...
to live without trouble, under the care of your husband.
I am living like that.
Add Ddol Ee to the family register...
before he enters lower school.
So your husband can think of him as his son.
Dad doesn't want that.
You don't need to listen to him.
He's a stubborn man.
He didn't agree to this marriage, but look how well you live.
If he finds out...
I'll take care of that. Go with it.
You need to send him to school next year.
They will go to the same school. If they have different surnames,
they'll be hurt.
Ddol Ee and his daughters.
Then you won't have to worry about that.
Both the biological parents need to agree to...
the adoption of their biological kid.
Which means that the kid's father needs to agree.
Is that necessary?
Yes.
Are there people who don't agree?
Of course. You can't do it as you please.
He's studying today.
Wavering, wavering.
Oh, my.
Do you have good news?
Why are you acting so frivolous?
Why do you care?
Excuse me,
what's wrong with you these days?
What did she do?
She keeps talking back to you. She's just a maid.
Don't be like that.
The person before you was kicked out for that.
My father hates that.
I see.
Relief Patch didn't talk back to me.
If you let her be like this, she'll get worse.
I can't even dare.
Excuse me.
Is the director in?
You can go in.
Thank you.
Hello, I'm Shin Gab Soon.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was your car.
This isn't much,
but I brought something.
Director, can't you please take back what you said about the café?
Everyone's worried.
I cleaned the place up...
and made a spot for your own private parking lot.
Couldn't you please overlook this once?
I'm really sorry.
This song is great.
See you later.
Who are you?
I'm Shin Gab Soon.
I'm here about your car.
I see.
You can go.
Okay.
Here.
Take it with you.
Please take it.
Listen to me when I tell you once. I don't drink that.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Are you free for dinner tonight?
Me?
Yes.
You're not my type,
but I'll give you time to apologise.
What's up?
What's wrong?
Dad, my mind's set.
We'll go to see you soon.
Take that in mind.
My family.
It must be tiring, Sir.
Your family is quite ahead of times.
Don't talk to me.
Yes, Sir.
Money.
You must be tired. Let's take my car.
All right.
Waiter.
Get the change ready next time.
I'll be going.
Goodbye.
Welcome.
It's me, Gab Soon.
- I'll have the usual. - Okay, Sir.
You know what you did, right?
Yes.
- Do you work at the café? - Yes.
- How old are you? - I'm 29.
You're quite old.
- I can talk to you casually, right? - Excuse me?
If you don't like it, I'll get rid of the café.
No. Please don't get rid of the café.
All part-time workers will lose their job.
You don't have a boyfriend, do you?
No.
I recently broke up.
Was it because of money?
I guess you can't come to places like this often.
It's my first time.
Can I take a picture?
Stop. It's tacky.
Okay.
Get in.
Not the front seat.
Excuse me.
Please drop me off at the nearest subway station.
(Jamwon Station)
Get off.
Thank you so much for forgiving me,
and also for the delicious...
Just get off. There is a car behind us.
Okay.
Get in.
Go to sleep. You seem so distracted.
Aren't you going to study?
Not today.
Gosh.
(Pass)
- Why are you up? - I'll help you with the delivery.
You don't have to. Get some sleep.
- You stayed up all night studying. - I'm fine.
I can use some exercise.
What's wrong? Did you sprain your knee?
- I think so. - What should we do?
Gosh, you little...
Are you messing with me?
Are you asking me to go?
I will go crazy if I see her face on a day like this.
You should go this time.
I shouldn't be with Ms Yeo alone.
That's not a problem.
Change to something neat.
Aren't you going to clean up this room?
I'm going to throw away all of these someday.
Don't you dare.
I hate you more and more.
You always have.
Hello, Ms Yeo.
It's you today, Mister.
You should call me by my name.
My wife doesn't feel well today.
It's because she stays home all day and never exercises.
Mr Shin. I heard you told Gong Joo to have a baby.
Yes, I did.
They've been married for a year. I wanted to hear about their plans.
They have no plans for a baby yet.
Isn't that something they should decide on their own?
My dear Gong Joo is too young to do anything.
I should decide it for her.
Who will raise the baby?
If you can't,
we're willing to help them raise the baby.
I just want them to have one.
We're looking forward to have a grandchild very much.
If you'll raise the baby, I'll think about it.
Okay.
It's boring and dull without your wife.
I'll be going then.
Are you leaving?
Of course.
We don't have anything to do.
Goodbye, Mr Shin.
Wait.
Are you a moron?
You went there to get money. Why didn't you say something?
I couldn't bring myself to say it.
Do you know how I feel now?
Do you know how it feels to ask for money to the in-laws now?
Go and get it.
We need money for this month.
Joong Nyeon. Lead the way.
I'm sorry.
You should've told me before.
You must've been so anxious.
I'm sure you didn't do it on purpose.
Of course not. I just forgot.
Sure.
You'd never do that on purpose.
You just forgot.
It's a sign of dementia, you know.
Dementia?
It's nothing.
- She's just joking. - No, I'm not.
Thank you for your kindness.
We wouldn't be doing this if hadn't blown my pension.
I'm sorry.
I guess that's fine.
Since they're married, don't you think Gong Joo should manage...
the money Se Gye earns?
- Of course she should. - No, she shouldn't.
You're the one who worked hard to make him a doctor.
You spent so much money on his education.
It's not just any school. He went to a medical school.
Gosh. It would be even more expensive than this house.
Who is getting the benefit now?
Ms Yeo. Don't you think so?
I don't know. I haven't thought about it.
Goodbye.
What a rude woman.
Why can't you just keep your mouth shut?
I shouldn't have brought you.
You can face Nae Shim now thanks to me.
Joong Nyeon. I think...
that woman and I are alike.
What do you mean?
I'm not telling you.
I cross a bridge...
in the starlight.
I pass by a breezy reed field.
It was always there.
Your apartment waiting for me.
Please be quiet. You're making me confused.
Dad. I got ramyeon.
Maybe it's because we don't own an apartment,
this is harder to memorise than others.
What should I make for dinner? It's so hard to decide it every day.
Please make sausage stew. It's so delicious.
Sausage stew?
Maybe I should.
She's making sausage stew.
Should I put the noodles in?
Wait.
Can't you smell it?
No.
Let's wait.
You'll smell the sausage stew soon.
I'm starving. Let's just eat ramyeon.
Gosh.
Be on standby, and come in when I call you.
It won't work.
Aren't you going to eat?
You're here again.
I have an upset stomach today.
Mum. Shouldn't we raise the toilet fee?
He's so shameless.
Aren't you going to eat today?
I'm asking because...
I don't want to bother you when you're eating again.
They don't have an appetite.
They don't have an appetite?
I don't know what that means.
It's my wish to be able to overeat.
Did you make the sausage stew?
No.
She didn't make the stew.
Why did she ask me then?
She asked me what she should make for dinner.
- Gosh. Cook ramyeon. - I already am.
Si Nae.
Your grandpa is asleep, right?
Yes. He was sleeping when I checked.
It's delicious.
It's more delicious to eat secretly.
He'd flip out if he knew.
"Stop eating already."
"Look at the fat. What are you going to do with all that?"
- "Lose the fat." - "Lose the fat."
Because of my family,
I can't even consider doing it.
Don't make a hasty decision. You might regret it later.
I don't think I'll regret it.
It will just be hard.
If it's too hard, why don't you transfer to a different department?
You're fine if you don't operate.
Se Gye. That's how people live their lives.
Not a lot of people have a job that they actually like.
They just do it to earn a living.
You're better off than me.
I didn't...
even have time to think about it. I only tried to move forward.
I have to make money...
to support my family.
I'm jealous of you.
Are you upset that I don't understand you?
Your own wound hurts the most.
Si Nae.
Gong Joo.
Si Nae...
Mum!
Grandpa!
Oh, dear. Dad!
Dad.
(Ms Yeo)
- Hello? - Hurry home.
(Emergency Room)
We should've called the ambulance sooner.
What if Grandpa dies?
This wouldn't have happened if you hadn't ordered food.
Se Gye. How is he?
He has acute indigestion.
This wouldn't have happened if you had come home early.
You're not around when we need you.
Good afternoon.
How could you cook so poorly?
- Excuse me? - My dad almost died last night.
What are you talking about?
Grandpa was taken to a hospital in an ambulance.
He stayed in the emergency room all night and just got home.
- So? Did he live? - Of course he did.
Ms Nam. Be more careful from now on.
Goodness.
What happened? What's wrong?
It's acute indigestion.
You should've eaten slowly.
Why do you always inhale your food?
You scare me every time you eat your meal.
You'll say goodbye to this world if you're not careful.
Not yet.
It's not just your look, but your organs get old too.
No one is going to take your food. Please eat slowly.
Chew it well and drink water often.
Stop nagging.
They'll blame me if something goes wrong.
Let me see.
Is it here? It hurt here, didn't it?
Yes.
I felt heavy in the chest and had fever.
My hands and feet were cold, and I felt nauseous...
and dizzy.
It's acute indigestion.
You should apply acupuncture right here.
It would hurt.
Still, you should.
You might die otherwise. You have to endure the pain.
What was your daughter doing?
She was eating food.
They're always eating something.
She only talks like she cares about you.
They didn't call the ambulance fast.
I really almost died.
It'll be so hard for you to go leaving behind all this money.
You should've called me.
I don't have your number.
Save your number on my phone.
Children are useless,
so you shouldn't just hold on to your money.
Get yourself a wife who will take care of you when you're sick.
You should eat porridge today.
Just stay in bed.
You look cute today.
Stop looking around.
I'll take them.
Make a written promise.
Are you crazy? I'm not going to do that.
You still don't get it.
Fine.
I'll do it. It's just money.
Stop saying it's just money.
You don't even have a dollar.
- What should I write? - I, Heo Da Hae,
will pay back...
5,000 dollars for the principal,
and 5,000 dollars for the interest...
5,000 dollars for the interest?
Gosh.
Fine!
Just come down a little.
Let's not waste our energy.
Just write it if you want to get out of here alive.
- Stop threatening me. - Do you think it's a threat?
You better pay me back.
You can't run away from me.
I know your home and your family.
If you...
ever lay hands on my family,
I won't just watch it.
What are you going to do?
I will kill you.
I'm not your friend, you witch.
Stop being so rude.
Mum.
Gosh, you crazy girl.
Are you stealing from me now?
I asked you to lend me some money.
Get a private loan or something.
If you don't,
they will sell me.
I can't believe I celebrated after giving birth to you.
What are you going to do now?
You should think first. Aren't you worried about your future?
Aren't you worried about your children?
I can't fall asleep at night because of you.
Aren't you embarrassed of yourself in front of your kids?
How could you call yourself a mum? You're a thief.
You should leave.
I'd rather not have you as my child.
It's not like I want to live like this.
I want to be a proud mum in front of my girls.
But I can't be one so what am I supposed to do?
When I was fooling around at school,
you should have beaten me up and set me up straight.
You lunatic.
I beat you up and you still snuck out of the house.
I'm upset too.
I don't want to live like this,
but this is the only thing I know how to do. That's all I've got.
It's not like I'm educated or skilled in something.
This is the only thing I know how to do.
I want to do something for Cho Rong and Da Rong.
I am their mum so I should feed them delicious food...
and buy them clothes.
But I...
don't have anything.
If I don't pay off my debt, I'll get sold off.
Then, I won't be able to see the girls.
What am I supposed to do?
You don't understand me!
You don't even know.
You call yourself a mum?
You lunatic.
Oh, dear.
I've never been to such a party.
It's a dinner party with a business partner I got acquainted with...
so they don't have to know this is our second marriage.
There are foreigners too,
so don't make any mistake. Please, watch yourself.
Okay.
Are you leaving?
A Young, I'll leave the kids to you. I made dinner already.
Let's go.
Business is good.
- Hello. - Hello.
Thank you.
Your tie looks great, Sir.
Thank you. Did your wife pick it out for you?
That's right.
Mr Jo! Over here!
Hey.
- Good to see you. - Yes.
Really?
You have a beautiful wife. Nice to meet you.
Excuse me, but who are you?
I'm Mr Jo's wife.
Mr Jo?
You're not the wife I saw before.
I could be mistaken.
Excuse me.
My goodness.
Help!
Excuse me.
Help.
- Oh, dear. - Excuse me!
Excuse me!
Rea! Rea! Are you okay?
Rea! Rea!
Rea. Rea.
I'm sorry.
Jae Soon.
Do you know how to swim?
I'm not good at it.
Why would you jump in the water if you can't swim?
I was too shocked.
I had to save her.
You should have thought it through.
What if both of you fell into danger?
I didn't know the water was that deep.
I thought I could save her.
I didn't think it through. I'm sorry.
I ruined the party. What are you going to do now?
I warned you before we left.
It was an important corporate event. I told you to watch yourself.
All the contracts got cancelled. What are you going to do about it?
What should I do if a rich man asks me out?
It's time to take your medication.
You've been watching too many dramas.
They're right. I should take some medication.
Good night.
I forgot what to do in a relationship.
Teach me how to seduce a man.
First of all, the woman has to be pretty.
The best woman is one that's pretty and obedient.
Relate to him and smile along.
(Economy of the Ancient Era)
Are you up?
Yes.
Do you want to talk?
Hello?
Are you working today?
Yes.
Then, leave early and clean my car.
Okay!
What are you looking for?
See you later.
Don't you think your skirt is too short?
I wore underpants. It's okay.
Leave her alone. That's how girls dress these days.
It looks pretty on her.
You should have dressed like this before.
You have to be pretty above all.
You should start dressing up.
- Do I look pretty? - You do.
I'll be back. See you later.
She's cheating.
What do you mean? She's a single woman. She's going for a date.
She's meeting somebody else than Gab Dol. That's cheating.
Mal Nyeon.
Gab Dol and Gab Soon.
Cut it out.
What is she doing?
She wants to impress the landlord's son.
It's not going to work.
She's wasting her time.
"It must be reported"...
"on a regular basis"...
That's incorrect.
"Taxes must be reported"...
Are you studying hard?
Watch this. It'll make you laugh.
Forget about the woman who left you.
(My make-up looks so awkward. It's not pretty at all.)
She's pretty.
My Gab Soon.
I cleaned your car.
Come to the café within five minutes.
Excuse me. May I sit in the front?
Stay at the back.
Where are we going?
I don't like people asking questions.
Okay.
Welcome. Long time no see.
Change into this.
Me?
Look at your clothes.
Come this way, please.
Come.
($1,800)
- He wants you to put these on. - Okay.
- I don't have much time. - Okay!
You don't have to get these for me.
I don't want to lower my standards.
Turn around.
That should do.
Let's go.
Okay.
Thank you.
Lawyer.
Let's go now.
Geum Sik.
What brings you here?
- I have to head out. - It won't take long.
Don't be shocked.
- Somebody proposed to me. - How old is he?
He's the director of Golden Foundation.
His father is the director. They're well-off.
I asked how old he is.
Try to guess.
If he's a director, he should be older.
That's what you thought, right?
Ta-da. Don't let this shock you.
He's five years younger than me.
- He's five years younger? - Aren't I great?
- This is how good I am. - That's enough.
Geum Sik.
I don't need to hear any more. You only care about a guy's age.
($10,000)
(Promissory note)
(I, Heo Da Hae, promise to pay the principal of $5,000 and interest.)
Welcome, Sir.
Welcome.
You can't go in.
Why not?
Why can't I go in?
You should have dressed better.
Look at you. You're wearing slippers.
Let me in.
Don't look down on me.
Let's just go.
Look what you did on my birthday.
Let go.
Why can't you let us in?
I'll pay.
Let me in!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Today's for Gab Dol, okay?
If we get the prettiest girl, she's for Gab Dol, okay?
Hey, it's my birthday!
Gab Dol is lonely these days.
I'm lonely, too.
It'll be your turn next time.
Let's drink up.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Is your wife okay?
Thank you. Thank you so much for saving my wife.
She wanted to be here personally to thank you but she couldn't.
To be honest, she lost her voice so she can't speak.
Really?
If she didn't scream for help at the top of her lungs,
I don't know what would have happened to her.
Hey.
It's okay.
Tell President Jo...
that I intend to change my flight schedule to repay his favour.
And that we're to meet immediately...
to sign the papers today.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
- No problem. - Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'm home.
You're home early. Dinner's not ready, yet.
These flowers looked pretty.
Take your time making dinner.
Mummy. Mummy.
Mummy.
(Geum Sik)
- What is it? - Live your life properly.
Please.
What? Wait.
You...
What a crazy jerk? Who does he think he is?
I won't let him be.
What is it?
Okay.
I told you I can't work today.
Who's that rich man?
I don't think he's a regular here.
You're lucky.
I don't know why you can't figure your life out.
What are you saying?
(Third-party debtor: Jo Geum Sik)
Jerk.