(Episode 19)
You haven't been eating or sleeping for several days. What's wrong?
Are you afraid that you won't pass?
No, that's not it.
Don't worry. You'll get it this time for sure.
I even prayed to your father.
I prayed that you would pass this time.
If he doesn't make it happen, he's not good enough to be your father.
What can a dead person do for me?
I can't bare to watch you worry so much.
Get some sleep now that you've taken medicine.
Turn off your mobile phone.
It keeps beeping unnecessarily.
Gab Dol. It's me, Gab Soon.
I'm in front of your house. Please come out.
I wonder if the pharmacy is closed.
Gab Dol, please.
If you're inside, please come out for a minute.
Hi, Ms Nam.
What are you doing here so late?
I want to see Gab Dol.
Why do you want to see him?
I have to tell him something.
He's sleeping.
Please let me see him just this once.
I must tell him something.
What's wrong with you?
What could you possibly say to him?
You're unbelievable.
Why can't you let him go?
I've said it again and again. You and Gab Dol are on different paths.
If you have something to tell him, just tell me. I will tell him.
Please let me just see him for a minute.
I'm not trying to get back together.
I really have something to tell him. Let me just tell him that.
What is it that you want to say?
I am not pleased about you being like this.
Why don't you listen when elders talk to you?
Why are you so stubborn and talking back to me?
Dad, I feel bad for Gab Soon.
I am mending my underwear.
Do you feel worse about her than me?
- Just this one time, please. - What's wrong with you?
Go back now. I'm have things to do.
I don't know why you're here,
but don't ruin my son's future.
He's just waiting for the good news.
How dare you show your face here so late at night?
What if this causes bad luck?
Go back now.
Okay.
Go away.
Evil spirits, go away.
Please make Gab Dol pass his exam.
What can I do for you, Ma'am?
Do not tell what you just saw and heard to Gab Dol.
I will neither relay nor deliver.
I'm not a delivery boy nor am I a loud mouth.
Isn't that right, Soo Jo?
That's right. We are not loud mouths.
We didn't hear anything because we were busy mending our underwear.
I think I know why Gab Dol's father passed away so early.
Me, too.
Hear me out before you go.
No, I won't.
I don't want to hear what a liar says.
(Sauna Entrance)
- Hi. - Hi.
I'm about to close. What do you need?
I left my purse at home.
Please give me some fruit. I will pay you tomorrow.
No problem.
Dad's late.
Do you have something to say to him?
I just wanted to see him before leaving.
Let's talk since you're here.
I've wanted to ask you about this for a while.
The money for our living expenses.
We always get it from your mother-in-law.
Can she just make a bank transfer from now on?
I feel like she's meeting me just to rub it in.
"You should go out more often."
"Were you making kimchi?"
She always shows off.
My pride doesn't allow me to listen to that.
I made you a doctor, not her.
Why must I get your hard earned money through her?
I will talk to her.
It should have been like that from the beginning.
It's all your father's fault.
He doesn't think through things.
He insists that a wife needs to manage husband's salary.
You were like that, too.
How are your wife and I alike?
He's here.
- Jae Soon. - When did you get here?
What are you doing here at this hour?
I couldn't sleep, so I came after kids went to bed.
I bought some fruit.
What are you doing here?
No reason.
Does he need a reason to be here?
He's here to see me.
We ate dinner.
Is Dad sleeping?
He went to look for Se Bang. He hasn't returned.
He went to the homeless yesterday.
Today, he's meeting some of his business associates.
I don't know what's going on. What if he's completely bankrupt?
Man should always have backup plans.
He was overspending his money.
Are you sad because he was once your husband?
I am not happy. I wish he was doing well.
That'd would be nice.
If he is completely bankrupt, that would have been something.
You would have been out on the streets with Ddol Ee.
Nothing is certain. Don't say such things.
I'm leaving. I'll see you later.
Eat this before you go.
I got rid of your dad's stuff before he found out.
Without his permission?
Why do I need his permission?
I gave it all to the salvage and cleaned everything out.
I feel so great.
He will be so angry.
I don't care if he's angry. It's better to hear him complain.
I don't want to live with that junk.
I will be able sleep well from now on.
You should have gotten his permission first.
He will be very upset.
We should deliver the news, right?
- Yes. - Let's betray her one time.
He's suffering so much.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Gab Dol.
Wake up.
Gab Dol, Gab Soon was here.
I think she came to beg for your forgiveness, Gab Dol.
Turn on the light.
He's completely out.
(Heo Gab Dol)
Maybe...
- He's alive. - He is?
Gab Dol.
- Heo Gab Dol. - Gab Dol.
The medicine is effective. I wonder what it is.
I wish I could sleep like him.
Me, too. I guess when you're wealthy, you can sleep like that.
Should we spray water on him?
No, let him be. This is his fate.
My goodness.
Hello.
- Hi. - Dad, you must be tired.
Why are you all here? Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong. It just happened.
Se Gye had dinner already.
Jae Soon couldn't sleep so she brought some fruit.
Are you banding together?
To kick us out?
You're quick-witted. Did you find him?
No, I need to go again tomorrow.
You should go. It's late.
- Okay, good night. - Okay, good night.
Good night.
- I'll go, Mum. - Okay. See you.
I cleaned the room.
What a surprise.
What's this? Where is everything?
Come here.
What happened?
She's gone and done it.
Can't you hear me?
What? Why?
Come here now.
There's no need. A thank you will be fine.
In Nae Shim.
- Dad. - Dad.
Who told you to clear that?
- Who told you to? - Don't get angry.
How could you not even ask me? You know what that means to me.
Why are you like this?
You did wrong.
Tell him you're sorry.
- I haven't done anything wrong. - What?
She must have put it away since it bothered her.
It's already done.
Why are you like this as well?
What do you know?
Even my children aren't on my side.
How could you do as you wish? Who do you think you are?
I'm nothing.
Look at you talk.
Stop. The kids are watching.
Why would you put that in the house? It looks haunted.
- I put it away as I had bad dreams. - You...
- Dad. - Dad.
Leave him. Let's see what he does.
Do you think that little of me?
Do you think I'm a pushover?
- Oh. my. - How could you not ask me?
If you had 3 children with me and lived with me for 40 years,
isn't it time that you took interest in how I feel,
what I think and why I'm like this?
Are you even interested?
Your only interest is money.
Say that after you've given some money.
Have I not earned money?
Have I not given you 10 dollars or 50 dollars?
From a dollar to pennies, I brought home all the money there is.
What have I not brought home?
You brought home all your wage.
As if that was much.
It's not even funny.
Just because I put away some garbage.
Does that look like garbage to you?
Yes. Then what is it?
Right, junk.
They don't even pay much for that.
Here. Here's the money.
Are you like this because of this?
You...
Do you even understand me?
Did I live with you for 40 years?
How could you be worse than a stranger?
How could you not understand me?
Do you understand me then?
How I felt every time I picked those...
out from the trash can.
Look at him lost for words.
He's such a brilliant talker.
He must be so frustrated that he can't even talk.
When he was young,
he used to compete in speech contests.
You used to scold me for crying.
Now you're the one crying.
You cry so often now that you've aged. What's gotten into you?
If you have nothing to do, clean the house.
What use is garbage?
Why are you angry?
I can't walk around the streets because I'm embarrassed.
Who cares if our children live well or not?
You shame the kids.
Gab Soon's future husband will come by tomorrow. You should be ashamed.
Do I embarrass you?
Yes, you embarrass me so much.
Is that all you have to say?
I feel so alone.
Don't regret this.
- Dad. - Dad.
Don't follow me.
What do we do?
You went too far. You have no regard for him.
You should have asked him first.
He collected it for years.
Don't point the finger at me.
Gab Soon needs to marry this year.
We have no money saved up and I felt frustrated so I sold it off.
Mum. He won't come. We won't get married.
My goodness.
Is it because of the money? Don't worry.
I'll apply a mortgage and get the money ready.
Don't be discouraged and go with it.
It's not that. I'm not getting married.
I don't want to.
Be quiet.
I'm frustrated already. Just do as I say.
Stop it.
I won't get married. I can't.
What's wrong?
- Did he find out? - What?
A historical night.
Mum, I'm sorry.
He didn't go out with me because he liked me.
He was just playing with me.
What?
How could you meet him without knowing that?
Let me get my hands on him.
It's not his fault. It's mine.
I'm the crazy one.
I thought I got lucky when I met him when working at the cafe.
There's nothing to see in me.
Even Gab Dol's mum looks down on me.
I didn't know myself.
I thought my Prince Charming had finally come.
My goodness. A Prince Charming.
What did you do all this time not knowing that?
You're so smart.
Didn't you realise whether he was joking with you or not?
And you come home crying, annoyed that a man broke up with you?
- Mum. - Mum.
Gab Soon's the most hurt. Stop, Mum.
How could all the guys you meet have nothing good about them...
or just play with you?
Why are you crying?
I'm not crying because he broke up with me.
It's because I'm disappointed in myself. I'm angry at myself.
Being so poor is the problem.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Have you ever taken my side?
If we met after a divorce, we should try harder to make it work.
Are you happy to make me that woman that looks through your phone?
I thought you hated liars. You're the liar.
I'm sorry.
If I could explain myself,
I lied because I didn't want you to worry.
Nothing that you're worried about ever happened.
Trust me.
I won't make you worry about that ever again.
Thank you...
for putting up with this...
and waiting for me.
This phone is turned off. You will be directed to voicemail.
- Oh, my. - Can you sleep?
How could you sleep after kicking him out?
- I didn't sleep. - Look at you lie.
He went out because of you.
What if something happens to him?
Don't even say that.
Where is he till this hour?
He has nowhere to go.
What if he had stupid thoughts?
Joong Nyeon.
This phone is turned off.
Mum, why?
Your dad hasn't come home yet. What should I do?
Not yet?
He still hasn't come back?
Why would he go about and make people worried?
What if he got into an accident?
If that happened, we would have been contacted.
I'll find out.
Don't worry. Nothing's wrong.
This phone is turned off. You will be directed to voicemail.
Please speak after the beep.
Where are you?
Even if you don't call Mum, at least call me.
I'll be waiting.
Does it work?
It doesn't? Are you sure?
Okay.
You haven't gone to work yet.
I will in a moment. You can use the toilet.
I didn't come to use the toilet.
- I came because of this. - What's that?
As you can see, it's mandarin.
One wouldn't be enough, so I bought 2 for each 6 in total.
Since you have 3 people, it's 6, right?
Are you asking for an extension on your monthly rent?
No. It has nothing to do with my rent.
- I'll have to see. - What?
You're asking me to stay quiet when we go to the Yeo house.
I'm moved.
You are incredible,
instantly understanding what I mean.
I told you to stop with the scam.
I'll come clean soon. Please give me some time before then.
I'm terrified that you might tell the truth.
I spent big money.
You did.
Am I allowed to receive that?
What's the name of the law again?
I heard that it's strong. So everyone's cautious.
Kim Young Ran Act.
Kim Young Ran. My first lover's name is Kim Young Ran.
I thought it was Baek Suk.
Take it with you. I don't want to get caught.
This is all right.
I asked Sam Sik just now. He knows everything.
Is that so?
I will eat it as you brought it.
I can't make promises as I can't keep things to myself.
I'll have to ask my mouth.
That's why I brought mandarins. To please your mouth.
Or else I have no other choice but to tell Gab Dol about what I saw...
- last night about Gab Soon. - Are you threatening me?
Of course not.
I'm just saying, but I was surprised when I went to their house.
It felt like the house belonged to you.
Do you know the halo that shines behind you?
I heard from when I was little that I looked elegant.
Even when I worked at restaurants, people thought I was the owner.
I'll try to keep my mouth shut.
Madam. Thank you. Bless you.
When Gab Dol wakes up, give him some porridge that I made.
Give him his medicine.
Today's unlucky again.
If you have time for that, go meet your ex-husband.
No, thank you.
Use your brains.
What brains do I have?
Can't you realise that he has feelings for you?
Right.
He doesn't even eat it,
but he sat in front of you till you finished your rice soup.
Who would wait for that?
What are you trying to say, Mother?
You know. Why are you pretending to be clueless...
when you have the brains for this?
It's not possible.
He's married and living well. What is there for me to do?
Mum!
Quickly. Do it once.
It feels awkward. I've never done it.
Copy me.
Honey.
I will, in due time.
Let's use the familiar form.
I think we should stop using the honorific. It makes us feel distant.
Once I started using the familiar form,
I began to talk bluntly and swear.
That won't happen to us.
Then I'll use the familiar form first.
I thought you said I can have one wish.
I want us to use familiar form and call each other "Honey".
- All right. - You're using it again.
Okay.
Will you come home late?
I'll come home early.
Honey.
Okay.
I have to talk with A Young about...
the wedding gifts so I'll have dinner at home.
- At home. - What do you want to eat?
I like everything you cook.
- How about spicy seafood stew? - That sounds great.
Spicy seafood stew and soju.
My goodness. I've never done that before.
You can do that?
I'm embarrassed.
I've never done this either.
I'll be off.
Mum. What's the matter?
What?
This phone is turned off. You will be directed to voicemail.
Please speak after the beep.
He won't pick up.
What should we do?
What if something happened to him?
Wait till he comes back.
I don't understand him? Does he understand me?
He's not a kid. Why would he make us worry like this?
He said he'll go looking for your ex-husband.
Then he needs to find him soon to help you out.
Is that important now?
We don't even know if Joong Nyeon is alive.
This phone is turned off. You will be directed to voicemail.
Please speak after the beep.
Come home. Stop making your children worried. Come home.
Come home and let's talk.
He would be fine.
I'll look into it. Don't worry.
All right, Mum.
What will you do?
I'll tell the chief and go out to find him.
Do you know where he might be?
I bet you didn't have time to talk about yourself.
He took a day off?
Why?
(Gong Joo)
Yes?
Where are you? I heard you took a day off.
Yes. Something came up. Did you come by the hospital?
To pick up Grandpa's medicine.
Mum wants to speak to you.
No...
What do you mean "no"?
How could you go on a vacation without asking for my permission?
- It's not vacation. - Didn't you go on a trip?
I'm on my way to a wedding of my teacher's son.
I'm sorry that I couldn't mention it earlier.
I just received the invitation.
You must be out of your mind.
What about my father?
I'll call him and tell him.
Gosh.
Your face and body are all wrinkly.
Did you think clothes would make you younger?
You're going to break your bone.
What?
Do you think it can smooth out your wrinkles?
Give it a rest.
You can't even do it.
You'll see. I'll become muscular in a month.
Easier said than done.
- Do you want to make a bet? - Whatever.
How about 100 dollars?
I guess I'll get some easy money. You can pay me in advance.
That's...
If you say I'm wrinkly one more time, I won't stand it.
What are you going to do? Can you survive without my food?
Ms Nam. The professor will come, so prepare some fruits.
I know. I'm doing it already.
How did you know?
I just took a guess.
Call me "ma'am".
- Sure, Ma'am. - Why would she call you "ma'am"?
Of course she should.
Ignore her.
How can I ignore her?
She keeps telling me to call her "ma'am".
Just listen to what I say.
Flowers.
I didn't prepare any.
Wasn't it just for the first day?
You still don't get it.
You have to be consistent.
Don't forget to get it next time.
Get off and give me a bow. She's watching us.
Call me if anything comes up.
I already took care of it. It cost me a lot of money.
Keep your head down.
Welcome, Professor.
My lecture ran late, so I couldn't buy the flowers.
You don't have to do that every time.
My father is taking a bath after working out.
Taking a bath?
My family often take baths.
- Let me show you my room. - Your room?
- Come this way. - Don't do this.
- Don't you want to see my room? - No, I don't.
It won't take long.
Those are the words that scare me the most.
What are you going to do? Please don't do this.
Please spare me. Ma'am!
Why don't you give it a rest?
Hello, Professor.
Hello, Ma'am. It's good to see you.
Is it? You saw me this morning.
What do you mean?
Just ignore me.
You're here, Professor.
- Hello, Sir. - Have a seat.
Please have a seat, Professor.
Si Nae.
What happened to the renter who looks like him?
He came back, begged for my forgiveness.
I couldn't do anything, so I just let him stay.
Oh, my.
- Ms Nam. - All right.
He creeps and crawls everyday now,
but who knows he won't run away again?
He bought some mandarins for us. He could've bought a box,
but he only bought 6, so each of us can have 2.
He still says it cost him a lot.
That's why he's just a renter.
He must look so petty.
He doesn't. He looks quite neat.
Professor. You look very neat today.
- "Oh, my. Don't do this to me." - Goodness.
"A girl's heart is like a reed."
"No. Why are you doing this?"
"You shouldn't do this."
Oh my, don't do this to me
A girl's heart is like a reed
"I'm not a great heroine of a novel or a movie,"
"but I'll give my all to you."
Thank you.
You must know a lot about women.
He knows everything, Dad.
I should learn from him.
Professor. Have you dated a lot of women?
- Excuse me? - You shouldn't ask him that.
Geum Sik has feelings for you, silly.
Can't you take the hint?
Display them well so women can easily buy them.
Sir. Did you come to inspect us?
I came here to buy you a treat.
If you have any problems, report to me right away.
- Yes, Sir. - Yes, Sir.
It's me.
Let's have dinner tonight.
How about the seafood stew restaurant we used to go?
That place is shabby, but the food is good.
What do you think?
Hey. Go easy.
I should go home early, and I'm also busy.
- If you want to talk, talk now. - Are you playing hard to get?
I don't want to talk. Bye.
Stop making noises.
It's so annoying.
Mum. Don't worry.
It won't be anything serious.
You haven't eaten, right?
Geum Sik will be home early today.
I'll come over after dinner.
I'll see you later, Mum.
Ms Shin. What is this?
What did you do?
I forgot to tell you.
I was washing it, and other clothes left a stain.
I'll buy you a new dress.
Why would you ruin my dress?
You did it on purpose because my mum bought me this, right?
That's not true.
- I'll buy you... - Forget it.
Can't you wash clothes properly?
I haven't even worn it yet.
All you do is cringe to my dad.
What are you doing?
How dare you speak to her that way?
Apologise to her.
No. I didn't do anything wrong. Why should I apologise?
She ruined my dress.
That's enough!
Don't. I made a mistake when I was washing it.
It's her favourite dress. I understand.
I'm putting up with this because of her.
If you do it again, I won't let it slide.
You're betraying us.
- Cho Rong, please... - Let me go!
- Cho Rong! - I'm fine.
She didn't do it on purpose. Go to your room.
I'll go to Mum.
Come here.
No!
- I should teach you a lesson. - No!
Stay in there.
What's going on?
Be quiet. Stop crying.
How much do you need?
Should I ask him?
It may be impolite to ask how much they want.
Maybe we should just offer them a proper amount.
Still, we should have an estimate.
The more, the better.
He's from a rich family.
For A Young's sake, we should offer them as much as we can.
It will help her be more confident.
Of course. You're smarter than I thought, Jae Soon.
Since I was little, people often told me that...
I'm smarter than I look.
(Dad)
The person you're trying to reach is not available.
Come out and eat.
I don't want to eat. I have no appetite.
Don't make me feel worse.
I haven't eaten yet. Let's eat together.
He's not answering my calls.
He's mad at all of us. Of course he wouldn't answer.
He doesn't have anywhere to go.
He will come home if he runs out of money.
What about Aunt?
She had lunch and went out to look for your dad.
I should pour some water so I can swallow.
I'm sorry, Mum.
It's all my fault.
You should've checked before you date him.
There's no one to blame. It's all because we're poor.
If we were well-off,
you wouldn't have fallen for someone like him.
We're so poor...
that you were blinded by greed.
Just consider yourself unlucky and move on.
I can't believe this.
How can you be eating?
Joong Nyeon might be...
starving or even dead.
How can you be eating in peace right now?
That's right. We are eating in peace.
I have such a good appetite today. This is my second helping.
You'll be punished.
You threw out your husband. How could you have an appetite?
Yes. I strangely have an appetite as if this is the last food we have.
Aunt. Mum hasn't eaten anything all day until now.
How could you do this?
If your dad has gone missing, you should be out looking for him.
I can't believe you're eating at home right now.
Children are useless.
You're useless.
Jae Soon and Se Gye are the same.
He worked so hard to raise you, but you all side with your mum.
Who made all the money...
to get you food, clothes and education?
Who did?
Nae Shim. What's so great about you?
Do you think you can look down on Joong Nyeon?
You should've gotten his permission to get rid of his stuff.
You can't do that as you please.
Stop it, Aunt.
You couldn't say anything to him when he worked and got you money.
Do you realise that you've changed?
You shouldn't do that.
Your children will become just like you.
It will all come back to you someday.
It will bring you great pain.
All right. Go on and take it all out on me.
It has brought me pain a long time ago.
I've been through enough pain already.
No one knows how I feel.
(Mansunho)
Here is the next news.
A body was found in Han River.
- In Mapo-gu, Seoul... - Oh, dear. What should I do?
Oh, my. Joong Nyeon.
Gosh, Joong Nyeon.
(A body was found around 10am at the southern end of Seongsan Bridge.)
What is it?
The news says they found a body.
(It's a body of a woman probably in her 40s.)
It's not Joong Nyeon.
It's a woman in her 40s.
Mum.
Turn that off,
and clean the broken dish in the kitchen.
Okay.
Gosh, I can't believe him.
The person you're trying to reach is not available.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Don't cause any more trouble and come home.
How could you get so upset over something like this?
Don't you dare do anything silly.
I will follow you until the end and give you a good beating.
What are you doing? You can't lift heavy things.
Of course I can.
Why did you come? You're all useless.
I took a day off because of you.
- Let's go. - Forget it.
If you're so busy,
- don't mind me and just go. - Dad.
Do you think I'm weak and incompetent?
Did you think I'll just follow you if you told me to?
I'm still strong.
I'm only 63 years old. Don't look down on me.
I've never looked down on you.
Aren't you worried about our family?
Let's go home with me.
I won't. I don't want to see your mum.
You can't not see her forever.
Maybe I can.
Many elderly couples get divorced. Why can't I do the same?
Dad.
Go home.
Really?
He found Dad. He's in Sokcho.
Is he okay? Is he having meals?
He gets upset when he misses a meal. Don't worry about that.
Okay, Se Gye.
He says he will bring Dad home later in the evening.
I'm so relieved.
Why would he worry his children like this?
Grandpa wouldn't wake up, right?
We'll be fine for at least two hours.
I feel the happiest when I'm sitting in front of food.
Is Se Gye coming?
He texted me and said he can't come home today.
He can't come home? Has he forgotten that he's married?
I emphasised it so many times.
I think Se Gye doesn't feel like he's married, just like me.
I shouldn't have let you marry him so young.
Grandpa made a fuss about how my husband has to be smart...
since you have no son.
Why would you need a son? Grandpa is so old-fashioned.
Mum. Is having a son that important?
(Inn)
(Man Joo)
It's a good thing that you found your dad.
You should try and make him feel better.
Don't worry about the hospital.
Gosh, they look good.
I'll drop off Da Rong.
- I have to drop her off. - I can do it, too.
Move!
- Hey! - Jeon Ddol Ee.
Don't talk back to Da Rong ever again.
I don't like you or your mum. You're so annoying.
Try some tangsuyuk.
I took it when my boss wasn't looking.
How do you eat it?
Do you dip the sauce or pour it?
I pour it.
Hasn't Gab Soon called?
I bumped into her while I was on delivery and I told her everything.
What?
I told her about you going to the police station and what he said.
Don't talk about her and don't talk to her about me.
I'm not going to say hi to her any more.
You should forget about her, too. She's high maintenance.
- Eat. - Can you set me up a blind date?
You're serious, right? I got it.
I have one.
She's from a rich family and is the only child. She drives a luxury car.
Let's do it before it's too late.
Why would she date me?
She has a peculiar taste.
Hey, it's Dal Tong.
You can leave your wallet.
It's empty anyway.
I don't eat steak any more.
You've been studying ever since you graduated from college?
When I study, I get game withdrawal symptoms...
and when I play games, I get studying withdrawal...
I guess I had no studying withdrawal symptoms.
So you took the examination to be a public servant?
Do you think you'll pass?
It's 3,000 percent. I have false hope.
You're so funny.
I don't see anything else in men.
I don't care about your family, education or occupation.
I just want you to be mentally stable and humorous.
I look at their faces, too.
I like small faces.
That's my complaint.
You're my ideal type.
I have a good feeling about this.
- Eat. - Sure.
My ultimate goal is to come to restaurant like this...
and order without looking at the prices.
You're so funny.
I can pay for these every day.
Sure.
Cheers.
He's waiting for you.
Give me a minute.
Your mum might kick me out for this but I have to say it.
What is it?
Gab Soon came over.
It was the day you were sick. She was crying.
Have you been well?
(Choi Ha Soo)
Come out. I can't wait for too long.
- Hello. - Hi.
Your mum's right.
I should have saved my severance pay...
for my later years.
Businesses are not for everybody. You can't just start a new business.
I can't die even if I wanted to.
What am I going to do until I'm 100?
I'm anxious and restless.
There's no joy of living.
After I stopped working,
there was nowhere for me to go once I stepped outside.
All day, I'd be sitting at one place...
or sit by the river.
I don't know why the day is so long.
It was so short when I used to work.
Your mum thinks it's all trash...
but that's what saved me.
When I go through the trash, time flies by.
I am not dexterous but when I play with them,
I feel less lonely and empty.
When I used to earn money, I wasn't afraid of going home.
Your mum used to listen to me.
But guess what happened after I retired?
I feel bad when I ask her to make me food...
and my heart sinks whenever the bowls clank on the table.
I get uncomfortable in our bedroom...
so I sleep on the sofa saying that I'm watching the television.
It's my house but there's nowhere for me to sleep comfortably.
After I filled my room with trash, it felt more like mine.
It felt like my own space.
Maybe I wanted to check for myself that I was still alive.
It's like checking to see if I still have a place in this household.
Children don't help.
You always take your mum's side.
I'm the outsider.
When I lost all my severance pay,
I went to the Han River a few times.
I couldn't jump off because I was reminded of you guys.
You doctors...
say golden time is when the patient has a chance of survival, right?
Men are done when they lose their business card.
I'm just...
trash in the trashcan.
I can't even be recycled. I'll end up in the incinerator.
That's what I am.
You would say...
my golden time is over, right?
Dad.
Father!
Dad!
(Our Gab Soon)
Don't do this. You can't do this.
Stay still, Professor.
If something happens to your dad, I won't be able to live.
Look for him. Hurry.
If you two break up again, we won't be your friends any more.
Let's go out.