Dad!
Father!
Hello?
Mum, why is your phone turned off?
I didn't turn it off. What's going on?
Dad disappeared.
- What? - I woke up and Dad is gone.
He's not at the beach nor at the dock.
What do I do?
Where could he be?
What were you doing?
How could you not know where your dad went?
How could you fall asleep when you are supposed to look for your dad?
How could you sleep?
Find him quick.
I can't live if something happens to him.
Find him now.
Don't regret this.
Gab Soon! Mal Nyeon!
Dad!
Why aren't they open yet?
Hello. We want to buy tickets.
It's not time yet.
Jae Soon, we're at the bus terminal.
I'll set off in a minute.
After I send the kids off to school.
Gab Soon, look after Mum.
Call me if something happens.
Dad.
You were here.
You startled me.
Why? Did you think I might have killed myself?
My dad...
never let me near the ocean.
He was scared I might sail off.
My dad...
always looked down on himself for being a fisherman.
He never let me play near the dock.
Nor would he let me on the boat.
Thanks to him, I was able to leave the ocean early.
I used to come here often when I was young.
I had big dreams and was never looked down on.
I never knew...
I would stand here so shabby...
like this 50 years later.
I thought I would age into an impressive old man.
I struggled my whole life to make ends meet.
I keep thinking how it would have been if I had become a fisherman.
I wouldn't have become...
this useless retired man looking for junk.
You lived a great life no matter what others say.
You did everything you could for us.
You did your best.
We all know what you went through.
Your golden time has not yet begun.
You're only 63 years old.
You're still young.
I'm saying this as a doctor.
Do you think...
I can start something at this age?
Of course.
You're still young.
Thank you for saying that.
It's nice to hear.
(From Seoul to Sokcho)
When are you going to leave? I'm in a hurry.
We'll set off when it's time.
There are times when men want to cry.
Though people say men shouldn't show their weakness.
Are men supposed to be good...
at everything and scared of nothing?
There are times when I want to quit everything and run away.
Cry if you want to cry.
Don't hold it back just because you're a man.
Did I ever tell you about my dream?
Fisherman?
Being a doctor is quite...
a valuable and rewarding occupation.
You can both help others out while making a living.
Think of the lives you saved.
There are lives that I couldn't save.
The lives that I couldn't hold back.
That's the way of Nature.
You're still great.
I wanted to become a doctor.
Your grandfather told me to become a doctor instead of a fisherman.
If I was good in school like you, I might have become a doctor.
Did you worry about me?
Of course.
Oh, right. Mum.
Leave it.
She'll be glad. She might be looking for the insurance policy.
She won't.
She told me that she'll be coming right away in tears.
What happened?
Did you find him? Is he alive?
All right. That's fine. It's enough that he's alive.
I'll hand the phone over.
- Don't. - There's no need.
I'll go back home. Let's talk later.
Stop. Stop the bus.
Please stop the bus.
Too bad for you that my brother's alive.
I thought you said that you're most envious of a woman that lives...
alone without a husband that you need to make food for.
I have no pension.
Don't you have life insurance?
My goodness. She was terrified that she would become a widow.
Make sure to eat well and don't do anything dangerous.
If you do that all of a sudden, you might hurt yourself.
Promise me.
Set off now. Drive safe.
My golden time is over.
I'm a piece of rubbish waiting to be incinerated.
What will I do until I become 100?
There are times when I want to quit everything and run away.
Se Gye, cry if you want to cry.
Don't hold it back just because you're a man.
Se Gye.
- Where's Dad? - Didn't he come with you?
Thanks, Se Gye.
He never thinks of others.
He's so selfish.
You must be hungry. Have you eaten yet?
How's Dad?
Won't he come back?
Mum.
When Dad comes back, apologise for throwing out his stuff first.
- What? - It's not just rubbish.
Have you thought about how he must have felt after he retired?
He had nowhere to go.
He didn't lay it out around the house. It was only that one room.
You could have let him have that.
It's true. What he says is all true.
It's not only Mum. It includes us all.
He always said he had nowhere to go every morning,
but none of us listened to him.
Of all occasion, when he wasn't at home...
Don't you see what's more important?
Did your dad say that?
He doesn't remember everything good I did for him.
He's upset that I threw away his junk?
You were hard on him.
About what?
After he retired, you kept saying how he should be careful of himself.
When he asked for food, you said you couldn't be bothered to.
You would clank the dishes on the table.
You told him off for dropping food even before he started eating.
Even though this is his home,
he didn't feel comfortable so he stayed in the playground many times.
Why would he have slept on the sofa and not in the bedroom?
He said he couldn't stand my snoring.
Dad said he wanted to die.
He's worried about what to do until he turns 100 years old.
He regrets about his severance pay.
He wants to die because he can't act as the breadwinner.
He went to Han River a few times,
but he couldn't jump because of us.
My goodness.
Dad's lonely.
Don't be too hard on him, Mum.
He's right, Mum.
Let Dad do what he wants.
He went through a hard time.
We were wrong.
We made him lonely.
Why are you all like this?
Can't you see that I'm having a hard time as well?
Is he the only lonely person?
I don't need you kids.
How could you all be on his side?
Do you know how I feel?
I'm always the one to blame.
Water.
I don't need the handkerchief.
Didn't you spill any?
I'm not a baby.
Buy two of that.
Why would you want to eat that?
I hate eating those kind of things on the streets.
It's so childish.
I told you I want it.
I said I don't eat this.
- Relief Patch. - Yes?
I thought you didn't want to eat it?
Mr Yeo!
It is tasty, though.
I'm home.
Why did you come home so late? Mum's angry.
What did you do till this time?
It's not like you became a doctor by fooling around.
Is it all right to take days off like this?
I got permission from the hospital.
Since it was the wedding of my professor's son.
What kind of a wedding takes three days?
Didn't you go on a trip?
Do you think I'm joking?
- No. - Did that woman doctor go with you?
She must have. She went to the same school.
She didn't.
It's obvious. She must have.
You're back.
Yes, I'm back.
Be careful what you do.
Don't you do everything at your whim.
Don't forget whose son-in-law you are.
All right.
- Where are you going? - Where are you headed?
To the hospital.
I'll be going then.
My goodness. That was unnecessary.
Excuse me.
Why do you always get irritated at what Relief Patch says?
Dad. I need to scold her.
Don't tell me off in front of others.
That's why she looks down on me and behaves like that.
You're the mighty person that pays my salary. I don't look down on you.
I felt as if it could happen to me as I'm a mother of a son.
Don't you worry.
How can you dream of marrying your son off to a rich family like us?
Dream on.
Even if I'm penniless,
I won't marry off my son to a mother-in-law like you.
- Excuse me! - All right.
Call me ma'am.
Dad, say something. She won't listen to me.
What you're saying is nonsense.
I don't like her nor Se Gye.
There's nothing you can do.
He's like a son.
If you don't have a son, be quiet.
You must have felt sad.
I didn't know.
Dad was going through such a tough time.
It never occurred to me.
I see why people say that sons are always on their dad's side.
My mum was upset about that.
What can we do?
I guess you can't mention your worries for now.
How about you put up a little longer for your dad?
He relies on you so much.
Se Gye.
I'm on your side on everything else,
but I can't about your job.
I'll be off.
No!
- I should teach you a lesson. - No!
Stay in there.
(Kitchen staff wanted)
This is boring.
They're looking for kitchen staff.
(Cho Rong's Mum)
Pick up.
You cannot reach this phone. You'll be directed to voicemail.
My goodness.
Did I ask him to get me a job or give me money?
Why won't he pick up?
Why don't you just break down the door?
Where are you going? I thought you quit working at the cafe?
I'm going out to meet someone.
Who? Gab Dol?
I broke up with him ages ago.
Your destiny went wrong since lower school.
If you didn't meet Gab Dol, you would have met a decent guy...
and married him.
That's the same for Gab Dol.
If he didn't meet me, he might have married off to a decent girl.
You're suspicious.
What?
The way you talk.
Before, you would have been full of malice and said,
"Don't even mention Gab Dol in front of me."
"It's annoying."
You have no malice in your words any more.
Tell me now.
Don't you go crying later.
Aren't you seeing Gab Dol?
I told you I'm not.
Stop making your dad worry.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
You're playing with her?
Welcome.
I quit eating snack.
This is on me. I got money from my moneybox.
Don't think about the price and order as much as you want.
I told you not to look at the price.
I can't help it.
What do you want to eat? What should we have?
- Let's slice. - Really?
Can I have pork cutlet?
Please give us pork cutlet.
What else do you want? Would that be enough?
Tteokbokki.
And we'd like to have a generous dish of tteokbokki.
- Okay. - Any drinks?
- I'll just drink water. - It's fine.
Excuse me. Can we have a coke, please?
My aunt is so peculiar.
I think she knows that we're back together.
Really? She has such a sharp instinct.
Did she learn it from someone?
She's good enough to teach someone.
Did you forget about me? You can text me first now.
- What is it? - Just a spam text message.
We should start saving money for our dates again.
- How about 100 dollars per month? - Okay.
How did you do on the exam?
A beat-up car wouldn't have done well.
- A beat-up car? - You called me a beat-up car.
No, I didn't.
I always didn't make the cut-off score,
but I was confident this time.
If you hadn't called me that, I would've easily passed.
I'm worried about one question.
You'll pass. I'll pray for it.
Give me your hand.
You have another one at home, right?
What? Yes.
They're not expensive, but they looked so pretty on you.
Earrings are no good if it's not a pair. Just like us.
It looks delicious.
You had it yesterday. You ate it instead of your brother.
You know Joong Nyeon and I are crazy about raw fish.
We often had raw fish when we were little,
but we couldn't eat it after we moved. We've missed it so much.
You should've bought some more.
You shouldn't be so petty.
I had been so generous since I was young.
People told me that I shouldn't be so generous...
when I have no money.
Everyone knew how generous I was.
But thanks to your incompetent brother,
I became so petty and narrow-minded.
To sum up, girls should marry a competent man.
No one can beat you in arguments.
Did you also win a speech contest when you were young?
What are these?
I picked them up myself.
He's being a baby about it. I should calm him down with these.
Why is he becoming so weak as he gets old?
It's not charming at all.
You think he's not charming after all these years?
The things I picked up were much more than that.
That's not enough to make him happy.
"Now that your husband is not picking up the trash, you are."
That's what someone else would say.
- Dad! - Joong Nyeon! Gosh.
- Gosh, Joong Nyeon. - What's the matter?
Goodness. I feel like our late father came back to life.
I've been watching the news all day.
I was afraid that you'd be on the news.
You wouldn't know how anxious I was.
Dad.
My goodness.
How silly.
Do you feel better now that you made everyone worry?
They were all so upset.
I prepared your meal. Go and eat.
You should eat. She got you raw fish.
If you don't want to eat it, forget it.
I don't know why I was so worried about him.
I was crazy to spend money...
to prepare all this. He doesn't even care.
I resent that this is my life. No one understands me.
Husbands and children are all useless.
- Se Gye. - Did Dad call you, too?
Yes. He called Jae Soon as well.
What can it be? Why did he want to meet us outside?
I'm not sure. Let's go in.
Tell me about the things you want.
The things I can do for you. I don't have any assets to leave you,
so don't ask for money.
Jae Soon.
You'd feel better if you register Ddol Ee as Geum Sik's son, right?
Yes.
What about you, Se Gye?
Why are you suddenly asking us this?
Dad. Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
I realised I haven't done much for you. I just want to do what I can.
Tell me.
There is nothing I want.
Gab Soon.
You want to get married this year, right?
No, Dad.
You said your boyfriend will visit us soon.
He's a jerk.
He just played with Gab Soon for sport.
What is she talking about?
You're a smart kid.
You must've fallen for him because of the money.
If we were well-off,
he wouldn't have treated you that way.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I didn't know I had such a bad taste in men.
I admit it.
I know I broke you and Mum's heart.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Don't be hard on yourself.
You've never dated anyone who drives an imported car,
and buys you nice meals like him.
It can make you go crazy.
I understand that.
- I'm sorry. - Don't say that.
I feel bad that we couldn't raise you in a better environment.
I'm just a snob. It's not your fault.
You didn't raise me, Jae Soon or Se Gye poorly.
Just forget about him.
You'll meet someone better.
Dad. I'm sorry I didn't try to understand how you feel.
When Se Gye told me, I felt so terrible.
Jae Soon felt bad, too.
Dad.
Rely on us.
We have your back.
Don't ever say that you want to die.
Don't feel lonely.
Okay. I won't.
I shouldn't.
I heard you and the kids had a talk.
You may be thinking about leaving after doing nice things for them.
What about me? What would I do without you?
What's the thing that you want?
Tell me one thing.
If I can do it for you, I will.
Don't cry.
I can't be apart from you.
I'll follow you anywhere you go.
Why are you doing this?
Are you thinking about dying?
Even if I want to die, that's not up to me.
Joong Nyeon.
I'll behave, so please don't leave me.
Is Se Bang here?
The girls are coming over today, right?
Yes. They'll come later.
Ask Geum Sik what he wants to eat.
- Why? - Do you have to ask?
I want to cook for him when he comes.
It's your day off. Just take a rest.
We'll order in Chinese food.
That's not good enough.
Call him and tell him to come.
If you miss him that much, call him yourself.
Look at you talk.
It's Mother. I mean Da Hae's mother. Should I not answer it?
You should answer.
- Hello? - Geum Sik.
You remember that the girls are coming over today, right?
They're getting a piano lesson, so I'll drop them off later.
I'll make spicy crab soup, your favourite. I'll see you soon.
I should go grocery shopping.
Change into something less revealing.
What's with that makeup?
- What? - Don't wear that lipstick.
You know Geum Sik hates it.
Don't wear glitter clothes like this.
Why do you have to buy such short skirts?
Buy something better.
This is good enough.
A Young.
- What is it? - Come out.
You're free today, right?
Drop Cho Rong and Da Rong off at Da Hae's.
I don't want to. You should do it.
I guess you don't need wedding gifts.
I can keep my money then.
Geum Sik.
If you want the wedding gifts, do as I say.
They're taking a piano lesson. Go and pick them up.
Hey.
Hey! Stop.
- Don't. - Gosh, A Young.
Turn the water off.
Stop it already.
- Hey! - A Young.
How do I look?
That's only a tracksuit.
This is the only neat clothes I have.
Call in sick today.
You should spend some time together with Geum Sik and the girls.
I have other people to spend time with.
You're lucky I'm busy right now.
Do it before I spank you on the back.
I can't come to work today.
My house is on fire.
Would that make you happy?
Grow up, please.
Don't look at me. That's annoying.
I ignored her.
We ran out of ramyeon.
I don't want to buy it by the piece.
Let's just buy a box.
Really?
We're finally buying it by the box.
Not everyone can buy ramyeon by the box.
We're getting into the high society step by step.
Maybe someday we'll have food waste.
People who take out food waste every day...
must be so happy.
They are blessed people.
- Grandma! - Grandma!
Gosh, my little ones. You're here.
A Young, you came instead.
- Where is your dad? - He's cleaning the house...
and the front yard.
I didn't know Geum Sik cleaned.
I thought his wife is a full-time housewife.
Why would she ask him to clean the house?
What a selfish woman.
Hello, my daughters.
What time should I pick them up?
You don't have to.
I'll drop them off myself. Just go.
Thank you.
What does that mean?
What?
They're my kids. Why would you thank me...
for dropping them off?
Stop nit-picking.
I don't want to come here, and I don't want to see you.
I just came because Geum Sik asked me to.
Aunt. Don't talk to Mum like that.
Be quiet.
Please drop them off later.
Goodbye.
A Young. I made spicy crab soup. Why don't you stay and have some?
That witch. I should teach her a lesson.
What's wrong with you? You didn't do anything wrong.
Why do you crawl to her?
- What was that for? - I'm just frustrated.
I shouldn't have bought the crab.
Hey!
What?
My mum worked hard to make you spicy crab soup.
You should've at least called.
Is sending A Young the best you could do?
Tell her to watch her tongue. I won't stand it.
I don't care. Do as you please.
Your mother just assumed I'd come.
- I never told her I would go. - Are you kidding me?
That's enough.
Tell her I'm sorry. I'm hanging up.
Her mother made spicy crab soup. She's mad that I didn't come.
Do you want to eat spicy crab soup?
I do like it, but I don't need to eat it.
Let's go grocery shopping.
I was going to go to the market anyway. Let's go.
What are you doing here with a box of ramyeon?
I thought you were someone else.
Did your brother tell you?
A child we support lives near here.
I'm here to deliver ramyeon.
I want them to feel comfortable,
so I don't wear luxury clothes when I go to see them.
That's the basic etiquette.
I see. You could've ordered your subordinates to do it.
This makes me feel good. I want to do it.
What brings you here?
I just met some people that are bad for my family.
Seeing them puts me in a bad mood.
I'm sure people who live here don't try hard to live better.
You can't say that. They may have their own reasons.
They may have tried, but failed.
The people I just saw aren't like that.
She's incompetent, but she only wears designer clothes...
and takes deluxe taxis.
She must have certain circumstances, too.
You said you'd like me even if I was a poor renter who only eats ramyeon.
That's different. I can't even compare her to you.
Eat it on your own. I have a date.
What is it?
Nothing.
You're not sick, are you?
Poor people shouldn't get sick.
I'm not sick.
Only my heart aches.
It's spicy crab soup.
- Here you go, Da Rong. - Look at you.
You haven't tried this, right?
Put some rice in it,
and mix it well.
Here you go.
Professor.
Today is the last day of October.
I somehow feel empty and lonely.
I thought only poor people feel that way.
I don't know how you see me,
but I'm a very lonely woman.
Everyone in this world is lonely.
- I got it. - What do you mean?
I got inspiration. For the poem, I mean.
"I still remember"...
"the last night of October."
"Leaving puzzling words behind,"
"we said farewell to each other."
"Was that lonely face a reflection of how you felt?"
"Do I have to be forgotten without a word?"
Why?
What's wrong?
Have you heard of this poem before?
No. I love the poem so much...
that I can't walk.
"Leaving puzzling words behind,"
"we said farewell to each other."
Where should I underline?
It has a title.
Underline "The last night of October".
Professor, it's the last night of October...
so let's go for a movie.
Your salon is in a good location so you must have a lot of customers.
Come and perm your hair. I'll give you a special price.
Sure.
Here.
Do you watch movies here?
It's for couples. You can lie down and watch the movie.
- Here? - These are our seats.
Lie down, Professor.
I can't do this.
What do you mean? Lie down. It's comfortable.
I'm getting scared.
Let me leave.
Don't do this. Let go.
Stay still, Professor.
I'm scared.
It's not scary. Stay still.
I'll take care of it.
Take care of what? Don't do this. You can't do this.
Soo Jo, save me! I'm dying!
Save me!
My gosh.
Darn it.
Cho Rong, wait for us.
Cho Rong.
- Do you have something to say? - I don't.
Why are you acting like that, then?
Mum.
Can't you live with us?
Live with Dad.
It'll be better for you guys to live with him.
You can use as much money as you want and buy whatever you want.
You can live with Dad again.
It's too late already.
- You have Jae Soon. - They might break up.
I'm okay,
but I want Da Rong to live with you.
Da Rong is still young so I feel bad for her.
I told you already.
Even if you were to live with me, I can't do anything for you.
Other kids are shrewd and they stick by the parent with more money.
What's up with you?
Let's go.
It's me. You said you'll be at the playground. Where are you?
I'm almost here.
I see you.
Cho Rong and Da Rong, I'm leaving.
- Bye, Mum. - Bye.
Did you eat good food?
I don't know.
Don't worry about her.
This is our neighbourhood.
Nobody is looking.
I almost died of withdrawal symptoms when I didn't see you.
- Do you feel better now? - Yes.
You can go.
- I don't want to leave you. - Should I drop you off?
We'll be up all night. This is the third time.
I know. I should leave.
Once we save enough money, should we go somewhere overnight?
I'll save up as fast as I can.
My heart is pounding already.
Only my heart.
Hey.
I'll see you in my dream.
I'll text you.
- See you. - You, too.
- What are you doing? - What?
Nothing.
You were dumped by a guy so you should be crying your eyes out.
Why are you dancing around?
I didn't get dumped. I dumped him.
How's Gab Dol doing?
I don't know. You don't know what you're talking about.
Good luck trying to fool me. I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Hey, Soo Jo.
You're in a good mood.
Thanks to you. Thank you, Soo Jo.
- Are things going well? - Yes.
- I'll go in first. - Hold on, Gab Dol.
What's love?
Love?
You know better than me.
As you know,
I've only dated Gab Soon seriously.
Answer my question.
It's hard to sum it up.
Let's make this simple, then.
What would you switch it with?
- 10 portions of rib eye? - No.
- A pair of luxury dress shoes? - No.
A luxury car?
I don't know what you can switch it with,
but one thing is for certain.
If that person doesn't exist in this world, everything is useless.
Imagine this. It's a beautiful park.
The cherry blossoms have bloomed...
and the background is green.
Flowers, butterflies, balloons and children.
You can hear them giggle.
Then, everything stops like a scene from a black-and-white movie.
The giggle stops and the screen turns black and white.
That's how it is.
That's what happens when that person disappears from your life.
You don't want to eat. You have no joy.
The world only shines when that person is around.
Once you stop loving,
it feels like the world is going to end with you.
It's not like you've never been in love, right?
You're getting married.
- A bottle of soju, please. - Okay.
Are you worried about something?
I'll give you advice. Spill it.
Hey.
How rude.
Move out!
Hey, wait for me.
Soo Jo. Geum Soo Jo!
Come out, Soo Jo.
What is it?
What happened to these?
Who did this? We don't have dogs in this house.
Hey, why are you going there?
I'm done with the bathroom.
Buy me a new pair.
- Hey! - What is it?
Soo Jo's shoes were soaking in water.
Did you do that?
I don't know.
It sounds like she did.
Why did you soak his shoes in water?
He was acting up.
He gave me a piggyback ride so I was going to be nice.
Who gave you a piggyback ride?
When I had to go to the hospital, he gave me a piggyback ride and ran.
If you act up again, I won't let it go.
I never acted up.
Soo Jo never acts up.
As I said, he's been trained at a young age to marry a rich girl.
Whatever. I'll pay for your shoes!
Get me the same pair today.
Why does she have to get a new pair?
You can dry these and wear them.
It's leather so you can't.
It's been soaked in water all night so you can't turn it back.
So he can't wear them.
How much are they?
The original price is 1,000 dollars...
What kind of shoes cost 1,000 dollars?
They're luxury shoes.
He wears luxury shoes when he can't afford them.
They were posted on the internet as used for 700 dollars...
so we met up with the person and begged.
My dad talked to him nicely and convinced him...
to sell them for 450 dollars. They were difficult to get.
He's right. I can attest to that.
He was adamant against giving me a discount...
so I lied down on the ground...
and did everything to get them. We poured in all our savings.
Because of what happened that day,
my body aches on gloomy days.
Just tell me what you need.
Buy me the exact same pair.
Let's go, Dad.
1,000 dollars?
My goodness.
Why are you all like this?
Can't you see that I'm having a hard time as well?
Is he the only lonely person?
I don't need you kids.
How could you all be on his side?
Do you know how I feel?
I must be the bad person to you.
- You're up. - What is it?
It's about sending money to my family.
Can't you transfer it to their bank account instead of meeting my mum?
Did your mum say anything to you?
She doesn't feel comfortable. It must be uncomfortable for you, too.
It's totally fine with me.
We should see each other at least once a month. We're a family.
I'm going to see her next week.
Get to work. Don't worry about that.
Doctors shouldn't be worried about something so trivial.
Get going.
You need to get your money.
Saturday at noon. Golden Hotel Lounge.
Dress up nicely.
This woman.
I told Se Gye to talk to her.
Get on.
You got prettier.
Thanks to you, I took care of all the other girls.
You're pretty good.
I couldn't sleep...
the past few nights because of you.
I've never been hit by a woman.
I think of you when I see flowers.
Let's...
go out.
Pick up my calls.
Text back right away.
Dal Tong put this together.
Don't say anything to him.
He's the reason we're together again.
Here comes the couple!
See? You two look good together.
We're even numbers now.
If you break up again, we won't be your friends any more.
Swear in front of us.
I swear.
That's not enough.
- I swear! - I swear!
We're witnesses.
Don't you ever say anything about getting divorced again.
I'm going to take you to the family court next time.
Gab Dol
- And Gab Soon lived in one village - And Gab Soon lived in one village
The two of them loved each other
Congratulations!
- What is it, Honey? - Should we watch a movie tonight?
We can't leave the kids here and go to the theatre.
We can watch it at home.
I'm going to take a break.
Sure. I'll make good food.
Yes, Miss. What is it?
Sorry?
I'm sorry.
Why did you do that?
Are you a bully?
Why did you hit your friend?
Ddol Ee.
- Mum. - You're here.
Are you his mum?
Look at my daughter's face.
He scratched her. What are you going to do about it?
What if it leaves a mark on her face?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Ddol Ee, say sorry.
I'm sorry.
My gosh. That looks painful.
I'll scold Ddol Ee. I'm sorry.
I'll pay you for the treatment.
That's not the problem right now.
What did you teach your child?
Maybe you set a bad example for him.
If he doesn't have a dad, you should have taken better care of him.
My goodness.
I'm so upset.
Counselling?
I think that would be a good idea.
He pushes girls and attacks them.
He only does that to girls his age.
I've been his teacher for three years but it started this year.
You should get counselling for him.
Sure.
Okay, Miss.
- Follow me. - Sure.
Is that right?
When was that?
It's been a while.
I heard you came by a few days ago.
Unfortunately, I was on a business trip at the time.
(Me, Mummy)
How is Ddol Ee's condition?
He received a psychological test.
He has a lot of anger inside.
He does?
He's releasing the anger caused by torment of his step-sisters...
through violence on the girls his age at the nursery.
He doesn't have a good relationship with his step-sisters, right?
They argue sometimes,
but they get along fairly well.
That's only when you watch them.
Well, I thought that it's normal for kids to argue when they grow up.
Do not take this lightly.
Even kids from same parents have issues.
This problem is not an ordinary issue.
Ddol Ee is pretending to be good and peaceful.
He's holding everything inside.
He doesn't want to make you sad.
You didn't know, did you?
To Ddol Ee, you are his everything.
He worries about you and loves you so much that...
he doesn't show how he feels and is holding everything in.
It's too great of a burden for a seven-year-old to bear.
I can't believe it's gone on for so long.
He needs treatments.
Come quickly. I found a very funny movie.
Can we watch it some other time?
Why?
Ddol Ee is not feeling well, so I want to sleep in his room.
I think he has a fever.
Why does he have a fever? Did he catch a cold?
It's not a cold, but I want to monitor him.
A second marriage is tough even for adults.
A seven-year-old would have had a tough time dealing with it.
He hid the stress he was getting from step-father and step-sisters...
from you because he didn't want you to worry.
He really needed mum's support.
Those who get remarried must put their children's needs first.
My son.
(Our Gab Soon will air back-to-back from next Saturday.)