(Episode 21)
In order to send Ddol Ee to elementary school next year,
he has to be registered under Geum Sik soon. I'm worried.
Mum, did I wet the bed?
I'm sorry.
I was dreaming...
It's okay. It's no shame.
Who cares? You have nothing to be sorry for.
I wet my bed when I was little, too.
You don't have to worry.
You'll have to wash the sheets.
I don't mind.
Let's get changed and get back to sleep.
Did Ddol Ee wet his bed?
No, why would he?
He perspired a lot because of fever.
How is he feeling?
He's feeling better now.
Where are you going?
Aren't you going to eat?
Where are you going? Take me with you.
Stay home. I have to go somewhere.
Where are you going? Why aren't you taking me?
I'm asking where you are going.
What's wrong with him?
Why doesn't he speak to me? Why is he upset?
He's mad at you. Can't you tell?
That's odd.
- I wonder if he's seeing a woman. - What?
Who is kind and understanding here?
If a young woman is nice to him,
wouldn't he be tempted?
That's how men are.
I've been through it all. I sure have.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Why would a young woman approach him? He has no money.
I've seen several women who approach men who don't have money.
My brother used to be very popular among ladies.
You know all about it.
I was the popular one, not him.
(Mum)
Hi, Mum.
What's wrong with your father?
- Why do you say that? - He hasn't been talking to me.
I don't know why he's so upset.
He goes in and out without saying a word.
I don't know if he's found Se Bang or not.
I'm sure he'll take care of it.
Is Ddol Ee at kindergarten?
What? Yes.
Then stop by.
I need to talk to someone. It's so frustrating.
Mum, I have an appointment.
What appointment? Whom could you possibly meet?
You don't even see your friends any more.
I do have an appointment.
I'm hanging up now, Mum.
Has he wet the bed before?
No, this is the first time.
He was potty trained at an early age.
Both his mind and body are frail, and his anxiety level is very high.
Make sure he's relaxed and...
actively show him that you're on his side.
You mean the world to him.
You need to be supportive.
I understand.
Will he get better then?
We'll have to be patient.
Adults are the cause of every child's problem.
Mum's attitude and his relationship with the family is crucial.
Mr Shin.
Se Bang.
What happened?
Why are you in here?
How did you find me?
Now that I'm here, people stopped contacting me.
Still, I knew you would come to see me. Please have a seat.
You look better.
They have a strict schedule here.
I quit smoking and drinking and I exercise often.
Isn't it too uncomfortable?
Thanks to human rights movement,
even the meals are not bad here.
I deposited some money for commissary. It's not much.
How did it happen?
So that's how it happened.
Anyway, take care of yourself.
I will.
Is everyone doing well?
How is Ms In?
We're all okay.
How is Ddol Ee?
He's starting elementary school next year.
He must have grown up a lot.
Does the step-father treat him well?
He does.
He may be a step-father, but he is good to him.
That's good.
I just want Ddol Ee to be happy.
How is Jae Soon doing?
Well...
She's not entirely happy.
She suffered so much because of me.
She deserves to be happy now.
Se Bang,
you have to do this one thing.
Have you heard about step-children adoption?
It's a way to register under step-father...
to give a child the same privilege as his own child.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying that you want to add Ddol Ee to his family register?
Is that it?
Since you're here.
It's not easy to raise a kid.
You need a lot of money to raise a kid.
Do you think I'm out of my mind to give up my child?
Ddol Ee is my child. I won't let that happen.
He is of course your child,
but be realistic.
How will you support him?
You know Jae Soon was having trouble and that's why she married.
He'll be attending school next year.
He'll be hurt if he has a different surname.
It's better to add him to the family register if you think of him...
going to university with his step-father's support.
Does she want to live with that man by changing my child's surname?
She didn't want to. I made her.
For Ddol Ee.
Whatever happens, I'll support Ddol Ee.
I won't let that happen.
Even if I'm lacking, I'm still his dad.
If it were you, would you have allowed that?
Don't even talk of the impossible.
You didn't help out financially at all after the divorce.
She cut all connections.
Then she hurriedly got married after a year.
Don't talk about the past.
I came to see you to ask for permission,
rather than using the law and making things difficult.
Please understand me.
We were like son and father.
That's what hurts me more.
I never imagined you'd be like this.
It doesn't mean that you're not his dad.
Changing his surname won't change his blood.
I can't permit it.
Tell Jae Soon...
not to live like that.
I'll see how happily she lives by changing her own child's surname.
I'll be released next month.
My company is doing well too.
Don't think of me as a dead person.
Se Bang.
- Doesn't it look delicious? - Yes.
It's so good.
I'm going to have it all to myself.
I want some.
One spoonful for you.
And your response?
Wake up, Prince Ddol Ee.
- Shall I feed you? - Yes.
There.
- Does it taste good? - You're the best.
You're the best.
Chew slowly.
- I love you more than anything. - Me too.
I love you more than anything in the whole world.
Da Rong, you're home.
I'm sorry, I forgot to pick you up.
Did you come by yourself?
I can come home by myself.
- I need to talk to you. - She needs to talk to you.
She seems anxious.
Have you decided not to speak to me?
What have I done so wrong that you're all sulky like this?
You should be sorry to have made...
the whole family worry and go through all that trouble.
Are you going to live like this?
I have nothing to say to you.
I do. Just one question.
Why do you burst into tears so often?
You're a man. You should be manly.
Why do you cry and get sulky?
I hate to see that.
Also,
why did you talk gibberish to Se Gye?
About me being cruel to you. That you're scared to enter the bedroom.
Every single detail. Aren't you embarrassed to tell the kids that?
Lastly, why won't you talk to me?
What's the reason? What did I do?
- Are you done? - Fourth,
until when are you going to ignore me? Do you want to live like this?
Do you want a divorce or what?
- Can I answer? - Go on.
First,
not only women go through menopause.
Don't you even watch television?
Everyone knows except you.
Now that I've aged, I don't know why but I get teary.
Because I'm upset and anxious.
Because I'm angry and resentful.
About what?
I'm not done speaking.
Second,
what's wrong about being honest to my kids?
Don't you think I would be embarrassed to say that?
There was no choice.
Third, why won't I speak to you?
You know best.
Fourth, until when will I not talk to you?
Do I want a divorce?
I don't know. Are you satisfied?
From now on, only talk to me about our kids.
I'll put up with this.
Since I'm the better person.
Even my name means patience, I'll live up to my name.
What happened to Se Bang, did you find him?
- I did. - Where is he?
What's he doing? Will he agree?
Don't ask any further and get out.
Don't make me upset and get out.
Get out.
What's wrong with you?
Did you get kicked out?
My goodness. What happened to you?
Are you happy?
Of course I'm happy that my brother's winning.
Joong Nyeon.
You wait and see.
That looks awesome.
What's so good about that?
All men love cars.
How did you feel when you rode one?
What did you think? Was it great?
It's all right. It's not all that great.
I'd love to ride in a luxury car with the top down.
You've been in one.
Tell me how you felt.
We'll now hear Gab Soon's thoughts on her experience in a luxury car.
Your hair gets messy and you get dirt on your face.
I'm hungry.
Even if your hair gets messy, it must have felt awesome.
Who cares? Stop talking about that.
What's wrong?
- Your stomach must get upset. - Why?
It's used to eating cuisines but now you eat junk food.
It must be startled.
I used to eat it before.
What's wrong with you today?
- What? - Are you doing that on purpose?
It's because I'm sorry.
I want to be successful to take you to great places,
but I drag you to places like this.
- Are you being sarcastic? - No, I'm sincere.
You deserve that.
You deserve to ride in luxury cars...
and go to restaurants to eat steaks.
You met the wrong guy and always have to walk around instead.
And eat these kind of food at snack bars.
I feel bad.
All women dream of meeting guys like that.
All men...
dream of doing that for one's girl.
It's just that we can't afford that.
Who's that?
Se Gye called an engineer to fix his computer upstairs.
Hello.
Hello. Where's the computer?
Please follow me.
I could never understand that.
Would you like a glass of juice?
Yes, thank you.
Why are you so busy?
- Relief Patch. - Oh, my. You startled me.
Why?
What are you doing stuck right next to him?
I'm helping out.
Wasn't it difficult to learn this?
- Are you married? - Yes.
Since you're an expert, you must have no worries on making a living.
Why are you asking that?
Finish it quick and go.
I left the stove on. Please go and turn it off.
Isn't it over yet?
What's taking you so long?
Haven't you seen those people who were humiliated...
for being bossy?
He's already having a tough time. Don't make it worse.
Look at him sweating.
You should take your jacket off.
Thank you.
- I'll be going. - Okay. Goodbye.
If something goes wrong, please contact me.
I'll be on stand by day or night.
Okay.
Goodbye.
His name is...
What's gotten into you?
Are you going to call him?
When there's something wrong.
You're a player.
If I were, I wouldn't live like this.
He's young to be your son.
He's not that young.
At most, he's 24 years younger than me.
I'm only 12 years older than you.
You're older. I'm talking about younger men.
You and your younger men.
Who doesn't like young men?
Look at the young men who appear on television. Everyone loves them.
Is money power? Youth is power.
What?
People are great judge of character.
I don't know why people look at me like that.
The service engineer thought that...
I lived here and you were my father.
Bring him to me!
I'm home.
Mother wants me to call every day.
What do I say? I have nothing to say.
Even if it's not everyday, it's your duty to call once in a while.
I hope you can do at least that.
Hearing her voice just makes me nervous.
Come here.
Gong Joo,
when you order Chinese food, don't they give you coupons?
- Yes. - Each time you call Mum,
I'll give you a coupon.
What do you get when you collect 10 coupons?
A small dish of tangsuyuk.
If you collect 10 coupons,
I'll buy you what you want.
Really?
How's Ddol Ee?
I'm going to let him rest for a while.
Did you take him to the hospital?
It's not that serious. I think he must have been tired.
I received a text message from a counselling centre.
Why did you go there?
All the kids went to a psychology consultant.
- Everyone did it. - I see.
Ddol Ee, look here.
Let's make friends.
To the dinosaur...
(Heart and Empathy, Child Counselling Centre)
- I'll pay in cash. - Okay.
What are you up to?
As you can see.
I have nothing to do. I feel bored.
Maybe a snack would help.
Do you want some pancakes?
I never thought I'd hear that come out from your mouth.
Do you have a favour to ask?
Aren't you glad that I'm taking you out like this once a month?
Have you finished making kimchi today?
We're going to make pancakes later.
I have a housekeeper so I don't do those things.
You could enter a pancake competition, right?
How did you know?
She entered a competition and won third place.
I'm not that great, but not too bad either.
People who say that are always great.
Nae Shim,
I was wondering who Gong Joo took after. I see it's her mother.
Isn't she beautiful like me?
You two will win in a competition to drive people crazy.
Since it's not every day that you come out,
you should take a look around the hotel.
Check the restroom.
These places have great restrooms.
What's so great about where you release your excrement?
My goodness.
Please enjoy the coffee.
I'm not sure you know, but this is expensive.
The smell is different.
Who cares about the smell? Tea house coffees are the best.
Tea house coffee?
If you haven't tried it, be still.
There are two imbeciles who don't know anything about coffee.
First are those who go crazy over...
anything that's expensive.
Second are those who stake out at the town's tea house...
the whole day to catch a glimpse of the girls who work there.
Haven't you heard that before?
You must be the same as me.
Which university did you go to?
Tea House University, Coffee major.
I think...
your amount of schooling is the same as me.
Let's be honest.
Weren't you a delinquent in school?
I didn't.
Then a bully?
With a pretty face,
you must have hung out with them like me.
Ms Nam, give me water.
It's me.
Why are you so loose-tongued?
Excuse me?
Did you tell others that I didn't graduate from high school?
I don't understand what you mean.
You told them that I was a delinquent and a bully.
I didn't even know about that.
Whether you were a delinquent or a bully.
Did you even tell them that my tooth broke?
What do you mean you didn't?
Who else could have told that?
Ms Nam!
All right.
What's wrong?
I'll take a pass.
Did you see her face?
How could you think up those words?
Tea House University Coffee major?
It makes me laugh.
I nearly entered a speech contest.
- My goodness. - You're so funny.
I just got out of the library.
All right. See you there.
What's that?
A passing car honked at me.
See you.
Hello.
You didn't reply.
- Will you go out with me? - You must be insane.
You're cute.
I'm letting you off like this because I'm also responsible.
I must have lost my mind.
Don't show your face to me again.
I want to work at a high-paying part time job.
I live off part time jobs.
I'm craving for tteokbokki. Do you have any money?
Let's eat at home.
When will they post the results?
I think this week.
Don't forget our promise.
Our promise?
That you'll propose to me when you pass the exam.
With 100 roses.
You said that 10 years ago.
Let's forget that.
I have nothing. I don't even have money to rent a room.
I want to take that back.
Hey.
It's Mum.
Hello.
I told you not to greet me.
I told you to pretend you don't know me.
He bumped into you. He can't not say hello.
You would've said he's rude if he hadn't.
Why are you in this neighbourhood looking blank?
Why are you going through the trash?
I wasn't going through the trash.
Don't be so hard on him.
What are you going to do if he becomes your son-in-law?
Mal Nyeon. Watch your tongue.
This is what drives me away from you.
Drive? You don't even have a car.
How can you be driven away?
You're the one who sold our car.
I should watch my words.
- Goodbye. - I said don't greet me.
Don't greet her.
Come out.
What's wrong with your mum?
What is she going to do if I pass the exam?
I know.
I don't look blank.
I'll pass no matter what. I'm 3,000 percent sure.
Is it you, Gab Soon?
- Come here. - What is it?
Does Gab Dol still call you?
No.
Then why is he hovering around our neighbourhood?
I saw him going through the trash earlier.
I hate to see people going through the trash.
This isn't just our neighbourhood. It's also his neighbourhood.
We went to the same school.
Isn't he hovering around here to see you?
Of course not. I'm sure he came for something else.
Why would he go through the trash?
I don't know. Was he going through the trash?
That's enough, Nae Shim.
They're already talking to each other.
Don't just assume things.
Mal Nyeon is always right.
I don't like how he dresses, either.
He always goes around dragging his flip-flops.
Look at his eyes. He's a squit.
The eyes of successful people always sparkle.
His eyes are totally blank as if he's lying in a warm room.
No. His eyes sparkle, too.
He did well on the exam. He's waiting for the good news.
He won't date me even if I asked him to.
His mum wants him to marry a teacher.
- Is he going to pass? - He did well on the exam.
You don't know that until he really passes.
It's not like he already passed.
Don't you dare see him before he does.
She will. Joong Nyeon will have to stop you from killing her.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
She spoils everything.
Ddol Ee is a bedwetter
He is a bedwetter
No. I'm not a bedwetter.
Aren't you too old to wet your bed?
Da Rong. Don't make fun of him.
Apologise to him now.
What are you doing? Why are you scolding Da Rong?
Because she did something wrong. Ddol Ee didn't wet his bed.
We're family now. Don't make fun of each other.
Da Rong, it's wrong. Apologise to Ddol Ee.
Don't scold Da Rong.
I told you. From now on, I'll say what I want to say,
and I'll scold you when I have to.
Eat some snacks and go to the piano lesson.
I don't need it.
Da Rong, let's go.
She scolded Da Rong?
I wanted to tell you when we were at your house,
but I didn't because it would worry you and Mum.
These days, she only cares about Ddol Ee.
Dad has changed as well.
He only takes her side and scolds us.
Why would he scold you?
I don't know.
He yelled at me,
and told me to apologise to her.
She's scary. I try to be tough with her so she wouldn't...
look down on us, but it's not working any more.
Are your dad and Ms Shin on good terms?
Don't they fight?
I haven't seen them fight.
Never?
Mum often lashes out at Dad,
but Ms Shin always curries favour with Dad.
When Dad goes to work, she comes and adjusts...
his clothes and gives him a kiss.
She sounds like someone as cunning as a fox.
I wonder what she has done to him. He's a blunt guy.
Giving his wife kisses every day doesn't sound like him.
It looks like she's fawning upon him.
Any men would fall for that.
- Doesn't that upset you? - It doesn't.
Geum Sik never carried shopping bags for you.
He never cleaned the yard.
He was always out saying he's busy.
He's so crazy about her that he doesn't even care about the kids.
Stop it.
Thanks to my great daughter,
I can't let a young worker pass by.
I keep thinking if he would earn enough money to feed you.
I even asked the computer repairman...
if he earns enough money.
Then the old codger misunderstood me.
Cho Rong tries to be tough with her,
so she won't look down on them, but it's not working any more.
She treated the kids carefully at first, but she doesn't any more.
Geum Sik said he married her for the kids' sake. What an excuse.
He just fell for her.
Geum Sik is married and happy. Don't cling on to him.
- You look desperate. - They have kids together.
Even so, they're already divorced.
You're doing this because he's rich, right?
Don't encourage her. Don't you have any pride?
Why is everyone so crazy about rich men?
You shouldn't be.
Ddol Ee. You can play with it after dinner.
Dad. Scold him.
You can't play with toys when you're eating, right?
Da Rong. Telling tales is bad.
Don't do that to your friends at school.
Ddol Ee. Let's eat first, and play with it later.
Ms Shin. Give me some water.
Why don't you get it yourself?
You're old enough to do that.
Also, Cho Rong and Da Rong,
put your dishes in the sink after you finish eating from now on.
Can you do that for me?
I'm sorry. I'll sleep with Ddol Ee for a few days.
"The three pig brothers were walking on a street."
"The eldest pig sank down on the ground."
"Gosh, I'm too lazy. I'll just build my house with straws."
"The lazy eldest pig started"...
"to weave the straws."
"I'm too tired. I'll just build my house with the tree branches."
Da Rong. You're awake.
- I want to pee. - Okay.
"The second pig brother made a sloppy house, and took a rest."
"The hard-working youngest pig"...
What?
I feel like I'm the one who raised you poorly.
There is no one to blame.
It's all my fault.
That woman is nice and gentle.
She also knows how to please Geum Sik.
I guess it's because she has been well-loved by her parents.
What's wrong?
After your father died,
I've done all kinds of things so I can feed you.
I worked at restaurants and other people's houses.
I sold all sorts of things on the street.
Because of that, I couldn't raise you right.
I didn't make you starve,
but I didn't give you enough affection.
Come to think of it,
that's when you were going through puberty.
You had to take care of Gab Dol and do the house chores.
I didn't buy you...
anything good or pretty.
I could've used words,
but I yelled at you and hit you instead.
It's because you were having a hard time.
Frankly, I often took out my anger on you.
I never hit Gab Dol,
but I hit you a lot.
I deserved it.
I hung out with delinquent girls,
never listened to you,
abandoned Gab Dol and stayed out late.
I deserved a beating.
You didn't want any guys to make passes at you,
so you started yelling at men not to look at you.
I should've comforted you well.
It's all my fault that...
I gave you such an ill fate.
Hello?
This is Shin Joong Nyeon.
Excuse me?
A prison officer?
Really?
Okay.
Didn't you do the laundry? I put them out a long time ago.
If you need it, wash it yourself.
Why aren't you cleaning my room?
Ddol Ee. It's time to go to school.
I don't want to.
Let's not go, then.
Shall we go out and have fun?
Let's go to an amusement park. Da Rong said she went there.
Sure. We can go there, too.
Let's go to an amusement park, okay?
I'm so excited!
Today is your day off, right?
I'm going out in the evening.
I'll be back before then.
Please pick up Da Rong when she gets back from school.
I prepared some snacks.
Give them to Cho Rong and Da Rong, and send them to their lessons.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
- I have some errands... - To an amusement park.
An amusement park?
Are you two going to an amusement park?
Yes. Why?
How can you go there...
without Cho Rong and Da Rong?
Why can't I?
Giving the girls some food isn't so hard.
They're your nieces.
I'll see you later. Let's go, Ddol Ee.
What are you doing?
I'm free.
I got rid of all the girls.
I'm lonely.
(Private Tutoring)
They won't be able to remove it now.
Get in.
What are you going to do after Soo Jo gets married?
Do Geum. Isn't it time to tell him the truth?
What truth?
I'll take it to my grave.
Okay. I'll be right there.
See you later.
What is this?
She told me to open it at home.
It's money.
This is the pay for yesterday.
These are the flyers for today.
You're hard-working.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
I normally don't believe in coincidence.
Anyway, aren't you happy to see me?
Don't get cute with me.
Hey, Gab Soon.
Stop it already.
Do you think I'll go out with you?
If you do this again, I won't stand it.
You dropped this.
Should I eat it?
Mum. I can marry Gab Dol if he passes the exam, right?
Are you sure he'll pass?
You can feel it after the exam.
He thinks he will pass.
If he passes, you can.
Really?
Thank you, Mum.
She can't marry anyone else.
They dated for 10 years and even lived together.
If he passes, beg him to take her. You should.
I don't need to beg,
but I'm worried about his mother.
I'm also worried about Jae Soon. Can she really marry him?
People even become in-laws with the same person twice.
You'll be a bit uncomfortable, but it won't be a problem.
But...
she has the final say. Would she let them get married?
Even if she approves it because of Gab Dol,
what if she abuses Gab Soon?
Gab Soon may be miserable.
They can move out, then.
They'll see her only a few times in a year. Look at me.
After Se Gye got married, I hardly see Gong Joo.
Gosh. I guess being a public official is a big deal.
It changed your mind completely.
Kids don't listen to their parents any more.
If they like each other, I can't do anything about it.
It's not like I'm happy about it.
Don't worry, Mum. I'll be good.
You can see him if he passes.
If he fails, don't even think about it.
Of course.
Do you really believe that?
You know so little about your kids.
I guess it makes you carefree.
Who would it be?
- Who is it? - Delivery service.
Are you Ms Shin Gab Soon?
- Yes. - Please sign here.
- Goodbye. - Thank you.
They're apples.
We just ran out of apples. Who sent you these?
As an apology,
I sent you a box of apples.
I hope you like them.
- Hey, Gab Soon! - Gab Soon!
I don't need apples. Tell him not to act up.
Make sure you do.
It's warm.
Mum says we can get married once you pass the exam.
She says we can get married once I pass?
Yes. It's making my heart flutter.
It'd be great for us to live together.
We've done it before.
That's before we got married. Our parents almost killed us.
I'm not going to do it again.
I think we should get married with everybody congratulating us.
Where should our wedding be?
It's up to you.
We can't do it at a hotel.
A nice Catholic church? An outdoor wedding?
- It's up to you. - What about our honeymoon?
Let's have a small wedding and go on a nice honeymoon.
We've never gone abroad.
Passports. We should get passports first.
Where do you want to go?
It's up to you.
- What's wrong? - What?
Do whatever you want.
- Aren't you going to take the exam? - What?
I didn't study much this time so I don't think I'm taking it.
There are not too many dates left. I'll take it next year.
What are you planning to do?
I thought you wanted to be a teacher.
You can't keep doing this.
There are not too many dates left so you should be pulling all-nighters.
We can't make a living with just me making money.
We can't have just one person working per household nowadays.
We both come from poor families so we should both be making money.
You have no sense of conscience. You're planning to live off of me.
What do you mean I have no sense of conscience?
I take that back.
I'm not going to mooch you off. I'm going to take it next year.
I'll start studying again once we get married.
Aren't we going to have babies?
Should I have a baby first and then study?
You've already made up your mind. You're going to mooch off of me.
You said you loved me.
This has nothing to do with that.
Women are funny.
You try to make excuses over love.
If I pick up your call late, you say, "Do you love me?"
If I forget about your birthday, you say, "Do you even love me?"
Then, did you want both of us to work?
You probably won't marry me if I don't make money.
I see. That's what it is.
I'll leave. Good luck finding a working woman.
I said that because I don't want you to abandon your dream.
You can't throw away your education.
If you pull a few all-nighters, you might remember what you studied.
You've been studying for a few years.
I forgot it all.
What were you doing all this time? You should have studied.
You were busy fooling around that you didn't have time to study.
You're not supposed to study when you have time leftover.
You can cut out all men in your life and that might still not be enough.
That hurts.
Must you criticise me like this?
You said you won't bring it up again.
Don't overthink. I'm talking about studying.
You said the exact same to me.
- Should we take a picture? - Yes.
Say cheese.
Mum, what if you get scolded?
For coming to an amusement park.
Who will scold me? I'll scold all of them.
I'm strong.
What should we go on? Let's try all the rides you like.
Really? You're the best!
- Yes, Mum. - Where are you?
I have some kimchi for you. I wanted to talk as well.
An amusement park?
With Geum Sik and the kids?
Just the two of you?
What about the girls?
What if Geum Sik says something?
He can't say anything. It's my choice.
I don't care if I'm out of favour with him.
My child is suffering so why would that matter?
Hey, Jae Soon.
Se Bang, you asked me to come see you.
What does Ddol Ee's...
step-father do?
He's a businessman.
He has a good company and some asset.
How is his personality?
Is he good to Ddol Ee?
He is. You don't have to worry.
Does he have kids of his own?
He does. He has two daughters.
Ddol Ee will be the youngest child on his family register.
I'll leave Ddol Ee...
to you.
A father like me won't be good for his future.
He's 100 times better than a bad father like me.
It's for Ddol Ee.
Don't worry.
Don't worry about anything.
Please, tell Jae Soon this.
Tell her not worry and...
raise Ddol Ee well. Tell her I hope she's happy.
She deserves to be happy because I couldn't make her happy.
Se Bang.
I'll be there...
for Ddol Ee...
until he grows up.
I'll take good care of myself and I'll take care of him...
You'll be released next month?
Call me once you get released. All right?
I'll come back when I have time.
Don't come back.
Stay healthy.
Eat well.
Hold on.
Can I see Ddol Ee just once?
Do you have a picture of him?
A picture?
I should be carrying one.
I might have lost it.
Here. Here it is.
It's my background.
I took it recently.
Hasn't he grown a lot?
I'm home.
Geum Sik.
Why are you here? Where's Jae Soon?
You don't know what's going on in this house.
- Do you know where Jae Soon is? - Isn't she home?
She must have gone to the market.
She went to the amusement park with Ddol Ee.
- Does this make any sense? - An amusement park?
I'm so upset. She wanted me to make Cho Rong and Da Rong's snacks.
She didn't even pick up Da Rong.
She only takes care of Ddol Ee. She doesn't care about the girls.
She doesn't give them snacks or get them school supplies.
She mistreats them and she scolds them if they don't listen.
She even threatens them.
Stop making up stories.
I'm not making this up.
She only took Ddol Ee to the amusement park.
She leaves the house in a mess and doesn't clean or do the laundry.
She's starting to show her true self.
I met Se Bang today.
You met him?
Where is he? What does he do?
He was doing well before,
but he's not in the best situation right now.
I knew it.
He should have focused on his business.
He always bluffed and acted with pretentious.
Good thing you divorced him.
We still got a lot from him.
He was much better than Geum Sik. It's true.
He agreed to give Ddol Ee up for adoption.
He was probably happy about it.
Someone else will be raising his child for him.
It takes over a few hundred million dollars to raise a child.
Se Bang is a lucky man.
He never paid a cent for child support after the divorce.
And now, somebody else will be raising his child for him.
Don't put it that way.
I'm right.
Se Bang agreed to it...
so just be thankful.
It's not easy for a man to agree to it.
He was crying.
He wanted me to tell you to raise Ddol Ee well.
And he wants you to be happy.
He's at least thoughtful.
Of course he is.
I feel bad for Se Bang.
He got divorced...
and on top of that,
he gets his child taken away.
What?
Can I think about it?
Think about what?
Geum Sik didn't agree to it?
It's not about Geum Sik agreeing to it.
I have to agree, too.
I can't worry about Geum Sik all the time.
I'll do it when I'm up for it.
Even Se Bang agreed to it.
Do it when he says yes.
What if he changes his mind later?
She has something else in mind.
Like what?
I don't want to gossip so ask her yourself.
I want to think about it.
I don't think I should do it now just for convenience.
I have to think about Ddol Ee once he grows up.
What if I regret it?
Why would you regret it?
Oh, dear.
She's too slow.
You're like a light bulb.
Light bulbs turn on instantly these days,
but you're an outdated light bulb.
She's going to get a divorce.
That's not what I meant.
I want to think about it from Ddol Ee's point of view, Mum.
Let me do that, Dad.
I must be thoughtless.
I don't know what you mean by Ddol Ee's point of view.
Where have you been?
I went to the amusement park.
What time is it? How...
You'll wake Ddol Ee up. Let's talk later.
Ms Shin.
I have to take this to school. I need you to do it now.
Now?
I can't do it right now.
You can go to school. I'll drop it off.
Don't come to school.
Do it now.
You should have told me earlier.
You can't ask me to do it right now.
If you don't tell me ahead of time, I won't do it for you.
Do you want me to get punished at school?
Cho Rong.
If you did something wrong, you need to get punished for it.
If you don't want that to happen, tell me earlier from now on.
I'm not a robot. I can't do everything in a second.
Jo Cho Rong! Come here.
What is it?
She won't help me prepare my school supply.
You have to tell the truth.
I can't prepare it when you're leaving for school now.
You're in the fifth grade. You should know by now.
You should prepare your own school supplies.
Why are you asking her for it?
You're in the fifth grade so you should be able to do it!
And did you and Da Rong bully Ddol Ee?
I didn't!
I told you to take care of him like your own brother!
You're a kid but you should know how things work in this household!
Why are you yelling at me?
Work stresses me out enough.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
I don't care if you get punished at school!
Why are you acting this way, Jae Soon?
Tell me why you've been doing this since yesterday.
You went out without picking up Da Rong from kindergarten...
and you didn't do any housekeeping or take care of the girls.
What's going on?
I went to the amusement park. Is that such a big problem?
"Why did you two go alone?"
"Let's go together next time." Can't you say something like that?
He was envious of Cho Rong and Da Rong...
so I took Ddol Ee to the amusement park.
This is not about the amusement park.
Ddol Ee is not happy these days.
You don't know how Cho Rong treats him, right?
She teams up with Da Rong and bullies him.
She steals his toys, too.
She does this every day.
- He even... - I took your side.
I scolded Cho Rong.
You pretended like you were on my side.
I pretended?
I'm trying my best, too.
From now on,
let's not take our own kids' sides.
It's good for nothing if I side with my girls and you side with Ddol Ee.
I'll watch myself from now on. I expect the same from you.
Jae Soon, let me ask you a favour.
Don't keep things inside and explode all at once.
Tell me right away.
If you don't say anything and explode, I can't handle it.
You're...
speaking formally to me again.
Regardless of how much I try,
I can't tear down the wall between us.
What do you think the problem is?
- Do Geon Ho? - Here.
- Jang Da Rae. - Here.
Jo Cho Rong.
Cho Rong.