(Episode 23)
Did you pass?
How did it go?
Is the result out?
- Mum. - What is it?
He must have failed.
What is it? Did you fail?
Mum. Thank you.
You passed.
I passed for 3,000 percent.
My baby.
My dear son.
You finally did it.
I'm so proud of you.
You're not lying, are you?
How could this happen? You brat.
Mum.
You did a great job. You really did.
It's all good now. All the hard time is over now.
This is the best news. It's 3,000 percent the best news.
Gab Dol, you're the best!
My goodness.
- Gosh. - Oh, dear.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Do you want to eat meat that badly?
Tell me about it.
We just got nice and cheap pork.
I don't want cheap pork. Give me the finest rib eye you have.
If you have something better, that'd be good, too.
Rib eye?
You don't even eat pork that often.
I would buy enough beef for the whole neighbourhood if I could.
My dear Gab Dol passed his exam.
My goodness. He finally did it.
I'm so happy for you.
You've been working so hard to raise your children without a husband.
It finally pays off.
You should eat anything you want to eat from now on,
and get your knee treated.
After I found out Gab Dol passed,
I ran all the way here without feeling any pain in my knee.
I guess this is what you raise your kids for.
Of course.
Chinese food delivery, Ma'am.
These dumplings are on the house.
Does everyone get free dumplings?
Gab Dol passed his exam.
Gab Dol's mum is here to buy rib eye because he passed.
It's not like he became a minister. It's just a public official.
Just a public official?
He should get a good scolding.
You should go and ask Gab Dol to teach you.
You said it's only a part-time job. Are you going to do that forever?
You've been a delivery man for years now.
When is the last time you studied?
Quit your job and study!
I already quit studying.
That brat.
- Just give me the rib eye. - Okay.
You said you'd propose to me with 100 roses on the day you pass.
Keep your word like a man.
Welcome.
How much are 100 roses?
- 100 roses? - Yes.
Is it going to be a present?
It's a newly opened gym. You can get a discount with this.
It's a newly opened gym. You can get...
- Hello. - Don't greet me.
You said you'd become a teacher. Do you give out flyers now?
Don't come near my house ever again.
My son passed his exam after he broke up with you.
Really? Did Gab Dol pass?
Why does that make you happy?
Gab Dol and you are on different paths now.
Don't even greet him on streets.
If it makes an unsavoury rumour, it'll be a problem for his marriage.
Why don't you move?
I don't want to live in the same neighbourhood as you.
Goodbye.
Let me go. I said let me go!
I'm working.
(Nam Gi Ja)
You should treat us big.
You finally did it.
- Congratulations. - Are you going to get married?
Your friends are making a big fuss, right? Are they jealous?
Eat first. Your sister will eat it all.
I haven't even eaten any.
Gab Dol. You finally hit a home run.
It's not just a home run.
It's like passing a state exam.
In the old days, he'd be a royal inspector.
Go on and eat. Eat before Da Hae eats it all.
You're mean like a stepmother.
I even saved your name as "stepmother" in my phone.
Gab Dol.
Thank you for being a good son.
Look how happy Mum is.
I told you. You're like the pillar of our family.
You saved us.
Of course he did.
I knew a day like this would come.
If your father was alive, he would be so happy.
We should pay him a visit later.
Why are you crying on a happy day like this?
Hey. Give her a piggyback ride.
That's right.
- Get on. - You'll hurt your back.
Go on. If he gets married, he will have to carry his mother-in-law.
Hurry.
Right. I should get on his back while I can.
You're strong.
- Are you happy? - Of course, I am.
I can't believe such a great thing happened in my life.
Goodness.
Be careful.
Let me down. You may hurt your back.
What do you think you're doing? Take me back.
Why do you see him when you have to hear that?
I'm showing the bottom of myself to you.
I'm not even ashamed because you've seen so many terrible things.
Just don't be with him, then.
Do you know love requires loyalty, too?
I don't know that.
Although I don't know,
I just know that one should not let his mum...
say something horrible like that to his girlfriend.
If you're his girl,
he should not let you hear those words.
A woman's love lies in the time she spent together.
That's how women are.
Though you dated a guy for 10 years, you can fall in love just in a day.
Please go out with me.
You're so sweet.
I want to be swayed.
Then, be swayed.
No, I won't.
I know you don't belong to me no matter how sweet you are.
I'm not too young to believe what you say.
I'm almost 30 years old now.
If you're tired of your toy, you're going to leave, aren't you?
I thought you were smart but I don't think you really are.
I already have a lot of toys.
I don't need to play with you.
I must be a different toy.
A strange toy that you've never seen so far.
Give me a ride. Otherwise, I'll take a bus.
Stay there.
Ddol Ee, block me. I'll play offense.
All right.
- Take it. - I will.
Take the ball from me.
Gosh.
I scored.
- You play offense now. - Offense.
Try to score.
You played very well.
Gong Joo, please take this.
What's up?
If it's not about our children, don't talk to me.
What did you want to say when you asked me to come out?
I'll talk later.
What is it?
Is it about money? Did you make trouble?
What do you have to say outside the house?
It's not something like that. Don't worry.
Let's talk about it later.
You ask me to come out only when you make a trouble.
Just like when you lost your retirement pay.
Is it something about our house?
If you do something with this house, you'll be dead.
How are you doing?
Is your family doing okay since you don't have Ddol Ee?
You'll be punished.
I am.
- Where is Mum? - She is sick in bed.
We're getting sick since we have to play with Ddol Ee.
Ddol Ee doesn't have time to put his feet on the ground.
Everyone takes turns to hold him and to give him a piggy back ride.
He's enjoying a wonderful life.
Thank you.
Mum.
I'm okay with other kids. But I get so upset...
when you say something like that.
What's wrong?
Did you come to let out your anger again?
I'm sorry, Mum.
You must have let it out to your own mum since you were suffering a lot.
Speak frankly.
When did I mistreat you?
Did I mistreat you and make you feel uncomfortable because you were here?
Frankly, you did a little bit.
I felt uncomfortable while eating, too.
When I took out some fruits, you said...
"The fridge gets empty as soon as I fill it."
And when Ddol Ee cried, you said...
"Why do you make him cry? It'll drive good luck away."
It's no use to be nice to daughters.
You guys are happy only when I treat you well.
I was upset back then but now, I understand how you'd feel.
When I got divorced and came back with my child,
you must have felt ashamed to your friends and had a hard time.
It was as if the whole world collapsed.
I thought, "What did I do wrong to experience this?"
"She must be suffering more with her child."
I was hopeless.
You'll never understand how miserable I was.
What did Geum Sik say about Ddol Ee staying here?
He told me to bring him back right away.
He said so even though he doesn't mean it.
He must've thought a lot about this.
I also have a lot to fix.
I tried to think of the girls as my own children, but it wasn't easy.
If they were mean, I got annoyed and hated them.
I had doubts about living like that.
Your own children get hateful often.
If they're not your own, it's even worse.
You can hang in there because it's you.
Moreover,
the girls are extremely difficult to deal with.
Above all, their mum is the problem.
She was divorced because of her fault, wasn't she?
Since she has nowhere to go...
and Geum Sik has a lot of money,
she must be wanting to come back with the help of her kids.
Watch out for her.
- We're back. - Ddol Ee must be back.
Ddol Ee.
- Mum. - My dear child.
Did you have a good time?
You're tanned.
I played basketball with Uncle.
He had so much fun.
He was very good at basketball. He could make a professional player.
Are you a good basketball player?
Ddol Ee, did you have a great time?
Where is Gong Joo?
She went home to wash up.
Gong Joo said she called you yesterday.
My goodness. Tell her never to call me.
Why?
Does she trade stocks?
Stocks? No.
All of a sudden, she talked about some DAQ...
and a lot of thing regarding stocks.
I had a hard time listening to all the words I don't understand.
She must have read newspaper because she didn't have anything to say.
Here you go.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof.
What?
Hey, Shin Mal Nyeon.
I didn't teach him. He learned on his own.
Ddol Ee is a genius.
I'll get going, Mum.
Can we talk for a minute?
There is nothing special.
Didn't he say anything when you went to Sokcho?
Like he made trouble or something.
- No, he didn't. - Then, what's wrong?
I think there is something for sure...
but he doesn't tell me.
He doesn't talk to me.
I don't know what's going on as he gets older.
He gets upset easily and cries a lot.
He used to be annoyed when I cried,
but he's the one who cries everyday now.
He also gets teary while watching a TV show.
Men change like that as they get older.
It's a fact medically proven.
Other men look still young at the age of 63.
He's the only one who's like that.
People don't believe that we're of the same age.
That's because you look so young and pretty.
It's true.
Some think I'm in my early 50s.
Mum.
Dad is severely sick.
Where?
His heart.
Who is not?
All my body and heart are sick.
I'm like a general hospital.
Think of Dad as a patient.
I'm a patient, too.
I wish I could stay in your hospital for a few months.
In my opinion as a doctor, you're healthy.
You talk about your feelings and have friends to meet.
Since you've taken good care of your heart, you're okay.
But Dad has never done that before.
Please understand Dad.
You've been living with him for 40 years.
Nobody asked him to live like that.
He stays at home all the time after he retired.
He said he didn't meet his friends because he didn't have enough money.
He wanted to save money.
You're having fun, too.
I'm having more fun than Ddol Ee.
Gab Dol has passed the test.
Really? Has he really passed the test?
Yes.
He must have tried hard.
After trying for about 10 years, he finally succeeded.
Bring him over sometime.
How can you change your attitude so easily?
You used to tell her to dump him because he's unlucky.
The situation has changed.
Don't count your chickens before they're hatched.
Their daughter-in-law has to be a teacher, right?
Give him up already.
If he finds another girl, you'll be miserable.
I've been through it all. I sure have.
I'm living proof.
It's true.
That's right. You know what I'm saying.
Dad.
Your son, Gab Dol, is here.
I passed the civil service exam.
I did a good job, right?
Dad.
Thank you.
I'll be a better son for Mum.
I'll do better for you, too.
Watch me how I'm doing.
I'll try my best to live well.
Thank you, Dad.
(Gab Soon)
Gab Soon, I passed...
Congratulations, Gab Dol.
I thought you would tell me first.
I heard it from your mum.
Are you still mad at me?
Let's not argue any more because of our family stuff.
You know how hard we've been trying to keep our love.
Come out. Let's celebrate with a drink.
I don't feel like going out tonight.
- It's me, Gab Soon. - Hi.
Congratulations. I'm really happy for you.
Your family and friends must be very happy, right?
Yes.
Can't you come out tonight?
Can we meet up just for a while later?
- Where are you right now? - I'm at home.
Did you not work today?
I came home from work a while ago. What time can we meet?
I think I have an upset stomach from eating meat.
You should've eaten slowly.
I'm not feeling well right now. Let me call you back later.
Okay. Let's meet up later then.
Call me back, okay?
I don't think he has a feeling for you any more.
Stop begging him for his love.
You better make up your mind before you get dumped.
Now that he passed the exam, he wouldn't care about you any more.
If you devote yourself, you'll get abandoned like an old shoe.
I've seen many girls getting dumped after they devote themselves to men.
Gab Dol wouldn't do that. You don't know anything about it.
What do I not know?
I've been through it all. I sure have.
I'm living proof. It's true.
My good boy.
You're such a good son.
I'm sure this is what children do for their parents.
Honey, thank you...
for grating my wish after all.
Please bless him...
and send him a good wife soon.
I'll call you back later.
He's playing hard to get already.
He passed the exam. Why would he want someone like you with no job?
Like the whisky slopping
In a glass
You look so excited. Do you need a microphone or something?
Do you think I would stop singing?
I can even dance in front of the big crowd as well.
I'm not jealous of you being rich at all today.
Your son should know about it.
He could pass the exam because of your great devotion.
I just want him to live well and happily. That's all.
That's not all.
You may feel bad sometimes like other parents do.
Take this and...
buy your son a nice suit.
I think he'll need a suit for work.
Take it.
I'm not sure if I can take this.
I'd better listen to you while I'm working for you.
Thank you, Sir. No, Mr Yeo.
If he failed again,
I was going to offer him a security job at my company.
What do you take him for?
He had studied for the bar exam before.
If things had gone well,
he would have become a judge or prosecutor. And what?
I don't need it.
Don't be so hard on me. You scared me.
My bad. Please take it.
Ms Nam.
Why? What's the matter?
Why don't you keep your voice down?
People may think that you're the boss in this house.
You always speak so loud.
Dad, why do you stay in the kitchen so often these days?
You never came around the kitchen before.
What are you talking about?
What's up with your lips?
What about it?
I asked her, but why are you answering me?
Her lips look too much. It's not like she works in the kitchen.
Wipe it off right away.
What the...
Do you want me to scold her?
Don't get scolded by her.
Shall I wipe it off?
Please don't. You look pretty with it.
Geum Soo Jo.
Thief. Get the thief!
- Stop! - Get the thief!
(Orthopedics)
What's wrong with your leg?
What happened? How did you get hurt?
I fell over and sprained my ankle.
Why did you wear that kind of shoes then?
By the way, why do you tag along with him?
It's about business.
What business are you talking about?
Soo Jo, can we talk?
Why do you follow around?
If Geum Sik sees you two hang out,
she'll be mistaken.
He took me home since my leg was sprained.
Why are you giving him a hard time like that?
Do you want something else from her?
Sorry?
I mean you're sticking to her because you need money, right?
That's not right.
I'll be careful next time.
I rented a room to wrong ones.
What's wrong with you? I said it's not like that.
Don't get along with him.
You better hang out with a rich one,
not a loser.
Gosh, it's really hard to make money.
You know, he got sent to his grandmother's.
Cho Rong called.
So what? Is that a big deal?
She couldn't stand it, so she sent him away.
That's how she gets a divorce.
- When will you see Geum Sik? - Tomorrow.
I'm not seeing him.
We're just going to school because of Cho Rong.
The kids don't look like they know,
but they sense everything.
I should've stopped you from getting a divorce.
It doesn't matter what other people say.
I just want you to get back together with Geum Sik...
and live happily with your kids.
Was she lying?
She didn't marry a rich guy.
She was putting on a show.
Thank you. I'm glad I listened to you.
My nephew really liked it.
I'm never wrong, you know.
I follow your advice too much.
I broke up following your advice.
How can you joke about that?
I'm sorry.
So what did you do?
We played basketball.
I was having more fun than my nephew.
It felt like my mind was being healed.
Playing with kids can heal you.
Won't you have kids?
Isn't it about time to have one?
I'm home.
Let's go to your room. It's time for a check up.
I'm totally fine.
Your patient is over there. Go check.
I felt like my blood pressure was rising.
Don't get worked up.
Mum hasn't had anything to eat all day.
Does your stomach hurt?
Her stomach is fine. She just doesn't have any appetite.
Do you want to get an IV?
Mum hates needles.
Leave me.
She never starved like that before.
Did you read news articles to my mum?
What?
- I did. - Did you thought she'd get angry...
and say "Don't call again."
- Did your mum tell you to do that? - Yes.
I'm scared of Mother.
My mother isn't scary. She's really nice.
Gong Joo.
I want you to be nice to my mother, like you want me to be nice...
to your mother and grandpa.
You don't need to call her if you don't want to.
What about the sticker?
Call her if you want a sticker.
Call her when you want to.
But no more newspapers.
Okay.
Wouldn't it be nice if we had a baby?
What is it?
Sit down.
What's wrong?
I just don't have any appetite.
I have no strength because I'm starved.
You'll lose all the weight you gained.
Don't think anything stupid.
I've observed him for over a year. He's a good guy.
He has no other interests.
You don't know that.
I won't pass it on to him right away. I'm not that easy.
He's your son-in-law. Think of him as your son.
That's how he'll become your family. Will you leave Gong Joo on her own?
She has me.
I have a long life ahead of me. I don't need to rely on him.
It's me. Are you looking into it?
I know it's difficult, but you have to find it...
as fast as possible.
I'll pay any price if you find it.
You can't think of it as just an absence.
Cho Rong is sending a sign that she's having a hard time.
A sign?
She might end up running away from home, right?
Some kids do that.
I told you. This is a start.
You have to pay closer attention because she's an adolescent.
To be honest,
kids with divorced parents go through a tough time.
Cho Rong was mad at us for that.
Give her more love...
and don't let her see you two fight.
You're right.
She remembered us fighting when she was little.
We bought her toys whenever she saw us fight.
She remembered that, too.
What shall we do now?
When parents get a divorce, kids resent them...
or feel guilty thinking it was their fault.
It sounded like her relationship with her step mum wasn't great.
You will have to solve this problem wisely.
I knew it.
It's all because of her step mum.
How can you interpret it that way?
Why did you have to rush?
You should've asked the kids for permission first.
- Be quiet. - I won't argue with you.
The teacher told us not to fight.
- Get in. I'll drive you. - I'll call a taxi.
Get in.
What brings you here?
I just wanted to drop by and say hi.
I bought this for you.
Thank you.
- Do you want some tea? - No, I just had some.
- Sit down. - Okay.
I want to buy you lunch,
but I've been so busy.
I know you're busy.
I have a favour to ask you.
Go ahead.
I think my sister's feeling a little unsettled.
Ddol Ee is home.
I think you and my sister are similar.
You don't say what's on your mind.
Even though she doesn't express her feelings,
my sister...
likes you a lot.
I believe she's trying very hard.
I want you to know that.
I always feel sorry because I should take care of her.
It's hard to do that with my personality.
I hope you're not upset because I told you this.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I want to be good friends with you.
I didn't know you came in.
Take a shower and come out for dinner.
Da Rong's kindergarten is...
doing an annual family camping. Let's go together.
- With me? - The whole family.
Let's take Cho Rong and Ddol Ee, too.
Can I go?
Cho Rong and Da Rong won't like it.
You can't walk on eggshells forever.
We have to go through it...
so let's not avoid it.
Then, let's not take Ddol Ee.
Here.
Your son is almost dying.
I'm almost dying, too.
I feel like I will die early.
Meet my son and persuade him, please.
How can I stay put when I know he'll ruin his life?
Please tell him to marry.
He said he'll return if you marry.
There's no other way.
That's the only way you two will live.
What will you do to make a living?
Listen to your dad.
You should follow your dad's orders.
Don't you know how he raised you?
Your dad has gotten so old.
He's aged so much.
Hi, Mum. What is it?
- Mum. - Ddol Ee!
Mum, why aren't you coming?
I've been busy today.
Ddol Ee, did you miss me?
Yes. I've been waiting for you all day.
It's only been a day, but he misses you so much.
I can't raise him without you.
He asks for his mum only.
Okay. I'll be right there.
Ddol Ee.
- Mum! - Goodness.
Ddol Ee, were you playing nice?
Did you miss me?
You're being so dramatic.
He was looking for you all day.
He woke up from his sleep several times.
He never left your side when he was little.
I'm going camping with Geum Sik and his kids. I want to take him.
Leave him.
He's finally getting better. He shouldn't see them again.
How did you decide to go camping?
They go from Da Rong's kindergarten every year.
Did they say they'll go with you instead of their mum?
Geum Sik said so.
That's good. That's how things are supposed to be.
What should I do about Ddol Ee? I'll be gone overnight.
You can take care of him once you get back.
That's nonsense. Why would you do that?
- Let's do that. - No, I'm not going.
I thought we were going with Mum for sure.
I don't want to go either. I want to go with Mum.
Mum hurt her leg. She can't come.
Don't be a rebel. We're going with Ms Shin tomorrow.
Mum, did you hurt your leg?
Yes, I pulled some muscles.
You hurt your leg so we're going camping with Ms Shin.
What?
It doesn't matter if your leg or back hurts. You have to go.
They're going overnight.
Call Geum Sik and tell him you're coming.
The girls dislike her. What is he trying to do?
I don't understand Geum Sik sometimes.
He heard what the teacher said but he would never change.
He has to think of the kids first.
You don't have to come. You hurt your leg so get some rest.
All right. Go by yourself.
I'll go on my own.
I don't want to argue with you so I'm hanging up.
Hey. Da Hae.
What is it? Do you need anything?
No.
I packed some fruits.
We have snacks to eat in the car, too.
You didn't have to.
It's more than an hour away. We might get bored.
Did I forget anything?
Your running shoes. You need running shoes.
Wash up and go to bed. We have to wake up early tomorrow.
Jae Soon.
I'm sorry. I offered and now I have to take it up.
Can you forgive me just this one time?
Da Hae is going to follow us.
Knowing her, she'll come for sure.
I don't know what will happen.
Okay.
I'll say hi to everybody and get back home right away.
I won't lie.
I promise.
- We're leaving. - These are snacks for the girls.
These are clothes. This is yours and that's for the kids.
I don't need extra clothes. I'll be back before dinner.
I look forward to good food.
Let's spend some time alone.
Choose a movie.
- The bird sings in the forest - The bird sings in the forest
- You want one? - Yes.
That house is still there.
That was so long ago.
I think we finish with dinner. I'll go back tonight.
I'll come in the morning to pick you up.
That's not fair.
It's okay. Let him leave.
We'll have fun on our own.
Everybody!
- Yes! - Yes!
We have a barbecue party planned for dinner..
but the grill is not ready, yet.
I'm hungry.
So before dinner is ready,
we'll play a game for an hour.
There are a lot of prizes you can win.
Let's start with a three-legged race.
Parents, come forward with your child.
If it wasn't for my injury, I would have won all the prizes.
We have Dad.
You can do it, Da Rong!
- You can do it! - You can do it!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - One, two.
- You can do it! - Hurry. Stand up.
- Let's go! - One, two. One, two. Good job.
- Let's go! - One, two.
- One, two. - Hurry!
We won!
How would I know?
We're siblings...
but I don't know what Joong Nyeon has in mind.
What if he got himself in trouble?
You would know.
I can't say even if I know and I won't even if I know.
Tell me what you know.
You're good at predicting other things. What about your brother?
It's one or the other.
It's either money or women problem.
He's not tall and ugly.
He's short and good looking.
Forget it.
Nae Shim, you should watch yourself. You might be wailing soon.
You know you have to take good care of your husband, right?
It's not a one way route. He has to take good care of me, too.
You still have to be good to him. Don't mistreat him because he's old.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Do you have time for dinner?
I'm on my way to meet up with my high school friends.
Can we meet some other time?
I'll call you.
Okay. Have fun.
It's been a week since we started dating.
You can use me for a day. You can do whatever you want.
- Can you get out of the way? - You have me all day.
I don't usually do this.
Why are you doing this, too? Don't bother me and leave.
Stop mocking me.
I'm not mocking you.
I'll get you flowers. Hit him with it.
Let me use you.
Any time.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
I'm jealous, Gab Dol.
You'll pass, too. Watch me.
I persevered through it all.
Let's drink until we die. It's on me!
Wait for me.
Can you go by yourself?
I'm heavyweight.
I'll be back. Order more sides.
Let's go home.
I'm sure you have met many girls like me.
Girls who would go crazy about your money.
Did you get rid of all the girls?
I showed you a proof already.
Do you like me?
Fine. It's not a big deal. Let's go out.
Da Rong and I ran a three-legged race.
We won the first place.
Dinner will be a barbecue party,
but I'll skip it and go home.
Please enjoy.
- Ouch. - Oh, my.
- Are you okay? - Mum!
Are you all right?
- I'm fine. - Really?
Try to get up.
Dad!
What is it, Cho Rong?
What's going on?
Da Hae hurt her leg, so I stayed for the dinner.
I'm still here with the girls.
I'll text you when I head out.
I just put the kids to bed. I'm coming home now.
I'm sorry I had to stay longer. Please wait for me.
The girls are asleep.
I'll come back in the morning to pick them up.
What are you doing?
Being here reminds me of the old days.
I saw...
the resort that we spent our first night together...
on the way here.
It was our 100th days anniversary.
I invited you to a trip because I wanted to spend a night with you.
That day,
I hid your car key on purpose.
I wanted to be with you.
I knew.
I didn't know you did.
After I gave birth to Da Rong, I had such a hard time.
I found out later that...
it was postpartum depression.
Why did you make me feel so lonely?
You said you loved me.
Did you really love me?
I had never met a girl like you.
My parents passed away, and I was left with my baby sister.
I just tried to move forward without a break.
I worked so hard, so people wouldn't look down on us.
I always tried to do the right thing. To me, you were...
a shock.
A model student and a delinquent girl.
I fell for you instantly.
I really did.
I let you lead me as you like.
Why didn't you say you were sick?
You didn't give me a chance to say it.
I didn't even get to see you.
You were always working late or on business trips.
My company was starting off, so I was busy and tired.
I thought making a lot of money was what I could do for you.
It was my dream...
to make a lot of money and buy you everything you wanted.
That's not what I really wanted.
When you came home, you didn't even look at me.
You only looked down on me and got your dander up.
That made me act perverse.
Taking pills for depression didn't help, too.
After a while,
I started not to care about anything, even the girls.
That doesn't justify your betrayal.
I could put up with it...
when you abandoned the kids,
spent all the money I gave you...
and fell into debt. I could put up with all of that.
Do you know how hard I tried to forget about it?
Do you?
You were...
the first woman I loved.
It was nothing. I don't even remember the guy.
I don't remember his name or face.
I just...
met him a few times because I was lonely and bored.
It's true.
Frankly,
I still had feelings about you.
I was jealous.
Then why did you get married so fast?
It was for the kids.
I was so busy with my work.
I was always working late that I couldn't take care of them.
- You could hire a nanny. - I did.
I tried hiring different nannies.
That didn't help. It only made things worse for the girls.
I couldn't even work any more.
Still, you should've put your children first.
I got married because I put them first!
It's not an excuse.
I wouldn't have gotten married if it hadn't been for the girls.
I was sick of women.
You traumatised me. I couldn't trust women.
People told me to marry an unmarried person,
but I chose someone with a kid on purpose.
I thought someone with a kid would be better for Cho Rong and Da Rong.
But after we started to live together...
I didn't think it would be this hard.
Are you going home?
- I should. - It's past 3am already.
Will you come back?
If you are, then why?
It's not as if it's urgent.
The kids are both here as well.
I think it's best if I sleep before we set off.
Go back in.
Sleep comfortably indoors.
If that feels strange,
let's have some beer.
I need to drive. I can't drink. Go back in.
(Jae Soon)
Why?
Dad, Mum disappeared.
- What? - She left her phone.
Did you have a fight again?
Wait here. I'll go find her.
Da Rong.
Da Hae.
I brought jjamppong. Eat up.
What did Gab Soon say? Didn't she love it?
I didn't see her. I was busy.
What? Did you change your mind already?
- What? - I'm disappointed in you.
You shouldn't be like that.
Now that you've become a civil servant, did you change your mind?
You shouldn't breakup with someone you've been going out for 10 years,
It's nothing like that.
Beware.
- What? - Girls change their minds easily.
If you're like this, Gab Soon will change her mind.
She still has feelings for you.
Why didn't you see her after you knew you passed the exam?
She should have been the first person you saw.
Be quiet, if you don't know anything.
Goodness me.
Hey! Bae Dal Tong!
She was with us till last night. Then she went inside to sleep.
When the kids woke up in the morning...
- Mum! - Mum!
I apologise. She's here. I'm really sorry for this.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
Sorry again.
(Service area)
(Insert cash)
Is this right?
Let's do this.
What took you so long? Why didn't you answer your phone? Get in!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Who are you rushing off to see?
Be quiet, the kids will hear.
If you want to go home, go by yourself.
We'll take a taxi.
If you won't come, go by yourself.
You're impossible to talk to.
Stop it, the kids are here.
- We were told not to fight. - You're picking a fight.
You made me annoyed.
Stop it.
Da Rong, don't cry.
You made everyone worried.
If you're that old, you should be predictable.
How could you be like that?
Were you scared that I might have died?
It's not like I have life insurance. Why would you want that?
Why are you like that?
Are you trying to make Da Rong like me?
Mum and Dad, grow up!
Why did you call the police?
The kids want to go shopping.
They don't like the clothes the woman buys for them.
Drop me off at the department store and give me a credit card.
You said your legs hurt. Go next time.
It's fine.
I can do anything to go shopping.
Buy only the kids' clothes.
Don't even think of buying yours.
Don't make a scene.
Let's go.
Mum.
All right.
It's been a while since I've been here. I can't resist it.
I have no excuse.
I wanted to put the kids to sleep and come home straight away.
Stop it.
Let's...
stop this here.