(Episode 25)
- Do it after eating some bread. - Let me just finish this.
What a nice young girl. How did you decide to do this job?
People only like easy jobs these days.
Don't your parents say something about your decision?
Of course they're not happy about it.
Since there are a lot of cleaning services, we can't take it easy.
We have to get many regulars and good reputations.
We can get regulars only if we don't spare ourselves.
The customers want everything to be sparkly clean...
but cleaners want to earn money without doing hard work.
Since our legs and backs are aching,
we want to avoid difficult work.
Wait a moment. I'll write them down.
There's no secret know-how.
- Please tell me. - There's not much to say.
Everyone cleans about the same way.
We use the same cleaning products, too.
There's no special technique.
Still, if you say nice things to people who hire you and...
don't slack off, they'll like you.
Also, if you pay attention to hidden spots like window or...
the back of the toilet bowl,
they'll appreciate you.
It's a hard labour, but if you work hard, you'll make a living.
After a while, you can open an office and...
hire some people.
Then you will be the boss.
I'm home, Mum.
I said I'm home.
Your mum won't respond. She's mad.
No matter what you say, nothing will change my mind.
I should just leave this house.
When are you leaving?
You should leave when the weather is warmer.
Did you have a good day?
Yes.
Your mother says she'll leave the house.
Just don't say anything.
I've been through it all. I sure have.
I'm living proof. It's true.
I didn't do cleaning, though.
The best cleaning tip is not to slack off.
Clean behind the toilet bowl.
(Cleaning Journal)
To obtain regular customers, you must clean hidden spots.
Mum, where is the pain relieving patch?
I don't know.
I didn't buy them for you.
Do I have to see my 29 years old daughter...
putting on pain relieving patch?
Sit down.
How long will you do this?
- Until I accomplish my goal. - What?
Don't expect me to quit after few days.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want to see me die?
I was so embarrassed when your father collected garbage.
Why are you doing this to me, too?
It would be better...
if you just do nothing while pretending to study.
You won't be able to get married.
How can a college graduate clean other people's houses?
Everyone should look for a job that fits the educational background.
Times have changed.
These days,
poor people become entrepreneurs and become rich.
Do you remember my junior high friend, Man Jung?
She came over to our house few times.
Her parents have sold pajun at the marketplace.
So what?
Don't underestimate pajun business.
Once it becomes famous,
people from everywhere line up to eat.
You can be filthy rich.
I'm not envious of that.
When she was young, she never went near the marketplace.
Now, everyone's envious of her.
She was unemployed after college.
Now, she works at her parents' shop cooking and serving.
Are you envious of that?
Her parents want that for her?
Your mother doesn't know what's going on in this world.
She goes shopping in Hong Kong every month.
She wears outfits that cost several thousand dollars.
I'm sure she does.
My friend became successful selling hangover soup.
She wears big diamond rings.
They have opened a second store.
All my friends are so envious of her.
No one thinks what she's doing is humiliating.
I'm sorry that I don't have a pajun restaurant for you.
I wouldn't have started it if I was going to fold so easily.
Now, all my friends will know what I do.
I will probably meet people I know while I'm cleaning.
Still, I will continue.
I'm holding on.
I'm holding on as if I'm dead.
Can you encourage me by saying, "It's all right"?
Yes, keep holding on.
No one cares if you fall.
Hold on and rise up.
I wouldn't mind starting a franchise business.
But I don't have any money.
Out of all the people, couldn't you be more supportive?
I can't stand how you look at me...
as if I'm a big failure.
Did you hear how she talks to me?
- Let her be. - I hate you more.
She is like that because of you.
Why are you blaming my brother?
It's so hard to be a parent.
I would like to resign as a parent.
To whom do you tell when you resign as a parent?
Do you tell the president?
What's wrong with her?
It's so obvious.
Whenever Gab Soon gets dumped by a guy,
she goes crazy.
Would she be like that if Gab Dol asked her to marry him?
Why did you bring a briefcase?
And why are we meeting at the police station?
From now on, forget about me.
What are you talking about?
Everything I've done is fraud.
My father isn't a chairman nor do I have an aeroplane.
I am unemployed and penniless.
I rent a 200-dollar room in the ghetto and...
I eat ramyeon every meal.
I am nobody.
Are you testing me?
This is a lie, right?
From the beginning until now,
only this moment is the real truth.
This can't be true.
I posted everywhere about you on the internet.
How am I going to live? I am so ashamed.
I will gladly pay for my crime.
Hey, you!
That would only bring embarrassment for both of us.
Disappear quietly.
And keep silence.
You will pay for it if you speak to anyone.
Get out of here. Don't ever show your face again.
Dad, I'm turning myself in.
By the time you read this, I'll be at the police station.
Be healthy.
It's embarrassing to say this because it's my first time.
I love you, Dad.
Soo Jo, why would you go to the police?
I should be the one to go.
What happened?
What did the police say?
Don't worry.
It's over now.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Aren't you going to work?
I can't go. I'm sick.
Why are you sick so suddenly?
You delivered milk just fine this morning.
Go to the hospital if you're sick.
Cho Rong!
You left your jump rope behind.
Thank you.
Come home early. I will make delicious food for you.
Is Ms Nam still not here?
I wonder if something happened.
What's wrong with her?
- Ms Nam. - I'm sorry.
I wanted to go to work,
but I have severe body ache.
I don't think I can work today. I'm sorry.
If you can't work, you need to tell us in advance.
How can you just tell us now?
Can't she come today?
I'm so annoyed. She has body ache.
We have guests coming. What am I going to do?
How can you get sick without any notice?
Who plans to get sick?
Let's see when you get old. Also, why are you inviting guests?
Don't ever invite anyone from now on.
Why shove around someone that's already struggling to look after me?
She doesn't do anything. You don't even go to the hospital.
Don't you know how much we pay for her?
What? Stop meddling.
It's my money, not yours.
Listen to me while you live in this house!
See you later.
- Don't drink too much. - Okay.
If you're ill, get up and go to the hospital.
- Hello. - Can you walk or not?
- Why? - Just answer me.
Can you walk or not?
- I can walk. - Then come out.
What brings you here?
Follow me.
Eat.
- Well... - Don't say anything and eat now.
Let's talk after this.
It's hot. Blow it before you eat.
Cheer up with this food. Don't get sick.
Why, did I do something wrong?
Why are you crying, then?
I'm touched.
Up until now,
I wondered who'd care about me this much...
since my husband died.
There was nobody that took care of me like you did.
Even though I have two children,
neither of them cooked for me even if I was ill.
No one touched me, either.
All they do is to tell me to go see a doctor.
Children are...
all the same.
In the last 20 years,
no guy has ever treated me to a meal.
I'm all old.
Nobody would care this much about me.
You care about my meals,
and you care about my illness.
I'm all old. Nobody would care about me like you do.
Relief Patch,
look at me.
Let me just say...
one thing only.
I don't know how long I will live,
but until the day I'm intact,
I'll look after you.
I promise.
I've never heard of such thing since I was born.
I only thought I'd need to look after others.
I never considered myself...
as someone who needs to be taken care of.
I didn't say that to make you cry.
Thank you...
for making me realise that I'm still alive.
Thank you for coming to my life.
Besides,
don't tell me that I'm old.
You're just like a kid to me, so stop acting up.
Eat with rice.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
Have some.
Chungcheong Province?
Go there for a couple of days. You have many friends there.
I was actually planning to go there.
How did you read my mind?
No need to party.
Here's some money for your ride. Go eat something with your friends.
I'll be all dignified thanks to you.
Joong Nyeon, you seem fishy.
No need for suspicion. It's to make you not feel so lonely.
I was getting lonely with the cold weather.
- Go back home. - I'll see you get on the bus.
All right.
- Mal Nyeon, - Yes?
- Don't get sick. - I won't.
- You do the same. - Yes, hopefully.
- Be safe. - Okay.
Goodbye. Don't argue with Nae Shim.
If she nags, avoid her. I'll teach her a big lesson once I'm back.
All right, please do.
- Go. - Goodbye.
Let's talk.
- Did Mal Nyeon go? - She did.
Turn that off.
Why? Would it take long?
You been dying to talk to me for quite a while. Go on.
There's nobody home, so proceed.
What's this?
(Divorce Application Form)
I've already filled out everything.
Just sign the papers.
Are you kidding me?
I wish I was.
Let's get a divorce.
How could you suggest a divorce to me?
You are so brazen.
I should be the one to demand a divorce.
Did you suggest it because you were afraid I'd do so?
- Pretend you suggested it, then. - What's the reason?
I'd like to hear it.
I'd like to hear why I should let you divorce me.
There are hundreds of reasons why I should divorce you,
but how dare you suggest one to me?
Ask others on the street.
You're right. Everything you say is right.
You should be the one to divorce me.
I'm sorry if I hurt your pride by giving you the papers first.
I can no longer live with you.
What?
It's not because you did something wrong.
We just don't get along.
Since when did you think about this?
Since when did you prepare to get a divorce?
- I've never prepared one. - Then what's wrong?
When you threw away my stuff,
I made up my mind.
That's how you look at me.
That's how you treat your husband with whom you lived for 40 years.
You're unbelievable.
Are you suggesting a divorce because of that?
You must be out of your mind! It's just trash!
Exactly.
You consider me as garbage.
That's why we don't work.
Stop with your nonsense!
Call the kids and ask if this makes any sense.
It's a problem between us. Leave the kids out of this.
Let's stop arguing.
I'm not confident enough to live with you until 100 years old.
Do you think I want to live with you?
I was going to suggest it anyway. Let's get a divorce!
Our current assets,
a number of insurances...
and this house are the only things that's worthy.
The one we saved for our retirement.
Thanks to you, we have this house.
We even asked our son for living expenses.
Still we kept this place.
I was the breadwinner,
but you protected the house.
So let's divide the money in half.
I'll be down in Sokcho.
I'll tell the kids about it.
You don't have anything to say, do you?
What is it? Do you have something to say?
You realised you went overboard, right?
Tell me the truth. For how long have you been planning for this?
Since when did you decide to divorce me?
I told you when.
I don't believe it!
That can't be a reason to get a divorce.
You planned this behind my back.
You should have at least given me a hint.
How can you drop a bomb like this?
I'm sorry.
Divide our assets in half?
That's nonsense!
What is nonsense?
Why don't you count your severance pay?
You lost that money,
so we can't divide this house in half.
We have to count the money you lost.
So I'll take 70 percent.
That's not right.
Let's go by the law.
The law? Did you say, "Let's go by the law"?
Let's not fight.
Let's have a nice divorce.
Getting angry will only give you more wrinkles.
Go to your room.
You got a mistress?
You should know better.
You wouldn't do this if you don't have one!
Of course I would.
I have to pack.
Hey! Shin Joong Nyeon! Open the door!
Hey!
Open the door! Are you going to be like this?
Don't stab me in the back like this!
Hey!
Please sell it as soon as you can.
I'm willing to go down in price if there's a suitable buyer.
Okay.
- Hello. - Hi, Gab Dol.
Congratulations. I heard the news.
Great job.
Thank you.
Wait a minute. Shall we...
get some tea?
Did you break up with Gab Soon?
- No. - Did you have a fight?
We didn't. We had a misunderstanding.
You two seem a little distant.
You don't have plans to get married, do you?
Well, you just passed the exam.
It'll take you some time to get settled.
You also have your mother.
Marrying Gab Soon will be hard, won't it?
She gave up on the teacher employment exam.
She's trying to start a cleaning business.
I put this house up for sale.
I asked the realtor to sell it as fast as he could.
I cooked this rice. You cook your own.
(Cleaning Report)
I'm here to work.
Why are you so late?
I got some groceries.
Hurry up and cook. Dad is hungry.
I'm not hungry.
Why are you being so rude to her?
She's much older than you.
This is why she doesn't respect me.
She doesn't even call me "Ma'am".
What?
Why are you demanding respect?
I'm sorry, Ma'am. I won't be late next time.
I'm already so upset. Why does she have to make it worse?
What does she have to do with you being upset?
Dad, why are you doing this to me?
Don't take it to heart.
I'll scold her one day.
Don't be so obvious.
I'm really nervous.
What if I'm obvious? What are they going to do?
You shouldn't.
Go to Cho Rong and beg.
You should apologise if you did something wrong.
You put her through so much. Don't you feel sorry for her?
How can you call yourself her mum?
I didn't forget anything.
I know what you did to us.
We are like this because of you.
I raised Da Rong.
Don't show up again.
Kids, snack time.
- Okay. - Okay.
Here.
How's A Young? She isn't coming home these days.
Didn't I tell you?
She flew to Europe. She'll be back next week.
- This is delicious. - I envy her.
She goes overseas all the time.
It's no fun if it's for business.
Let's go together once I take care of some work.
- Really? - Sure.
Are you crazy for attention?
I know your face. You're dead meat.
You'll never get married to the rich.
Don't lie.
Do you still have that bad habit from high school?
You're a serious liar!
I just fell for you at first sight.
- Can I join you? - No need.
Allow me, all right?
It's annoying. I'll just get married to you.
If you act like this, I'll really marry you.
Who's that guy? Do you want me to take care of him?
Don't get beaten instead.
- Where did you come from? - I was at work.
I always rush like a loyal dog whenever you call me.
I can't go back home.
What's that?
Don't mind.
Do you have any rich friends...
or someone like that around you?
I sometimes meet the rich people because of work.
Did you get dumped by a rich guy?
Goodness.
I'm sorry, Dal Po.
If you were from the rich family,
I would have married you long ago.
Do you like me?
Let me tell you something.
Don't like someone like me.
As you know, my life isn't that good so far.
I got divorced and have two kids.
And I can't even take care of my kids.
You said you're not interested in girls without money.
Just forget about me.
I'm sure you'll end up getting hurt.
You're stupid. You picked the wrong one.
Think about your father and wake up.
I'm saying this as your friend. Just keep that in mind.
Let's be friends like before.
(Dal Po)
The phone is turned off...
Geum Soo Jo. Soo Jo!
Why didn't you come in?
Today's breakfast looks great.
It's beef soup with radish.
We often have it after Gab Dol passed the exam.
You go eat alone. Don't tell me to come over any more.
Why?
- Are you going somewhere? - I'm going to find a job.
- Do you want to get a job? - Yes. I have to.
See you later.
Soo Jo is looking for a job these days.
I should have sent him to college.
Whenever I think of it,
it breaks my heart.
Can you find me a job?
Why don't you go out with her?
I don't call her any more.
I don't want to fool someone nice like her.
I'm so worried about what to do for a living.
I don't want my kid to take all the responsibility.
He's not a kid any more. He's 32 already.
I wasn't a good father for him.
You did all you can do for him.
You've spent your life only for him, right?
You've been through such a hard time.
It wasn't hard at all, but I was just happy.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Where did the patient go?
He just left the hospital.
Mr Na!
You're scheduled to get surgery in the afternoon. You can't leave.
I can't get the surgery.
I can't afford to pay for the surgery.
And I can't leave all the debts to my wife.
- It's too much for her already. - Please just get the surgery first.
What else could be more important?
You need to save your life first,
and then you can take care of your kids.
Please let me go, Sir.
I know I can't live long, even if I get the surgery.
Dr Shin.
Thank you for taking good care of me...
with your heart.
I won't forget this, Sir.
Did you tell the patient in room 804 to leave the hospital?
He was supposed to get the surgery in the afternoon.
You know...
what's going to happen if he doesn't get the surgery, don't you?
You need to be stronger if you want to be a doctor,
or else you should work as a volunteer.
How can a hospital make a profit if you act like that?
(Letter of Resignation)
Stop it.
He went to the seminar, so he's not in the office now.
Don't do this and think it over.
Se Gye. Dr Shin!
What about your parents?
You can't just throw your licence out like this.
You got it after putting so much effort,
so you have to use it for the patients.
Dr Shin.
(Chorok University Hospital)
I made up my mind.
Don't bother.
What about the living expenses?
How are you going to make money for your parents?
You look great, my son.
Why do you buy me a suit when you don't have enough money?
I can wear the one that I wore when I graduated.
I have money.
Someone gave me money to buy you a suit.
- Who? - Someone you don't know.
Don't worry and buy two so that you can change.
You can't wear the same suit every day.
(Making a blog)
What are you doing?
I'm making a blog.
Did you decide the name?
I named it "Sparkly Clean Gab Soon".
You told me to.
I think the name is catchy.
I'll treat you if I succeed.
Don't you miss me?
I can go to your house right now.
Forget it. I'm busy. I have to go.
Congratulations on your first day at work tomorrow.
I couldn't buy something big because I don't have money,
but I bought your shoes on credit.
They're not luxurious shoes, though.
Thank you, Da Hae.
Gab Soon, what are you doing?
Tomorrow is my first day at work.
Congratulations.
(Congratulations)
Get inside. It's not a big deal.
It is a big deal.
You're a public official everybody admires.
I couldn't even get a sleep.
Since you are going to work for the first time,
I was too nervous to get some sleep.
Greet them politely,
pay attention to what your seniors say...
and get along with your colleagues.
All right.
If you want to be a good son,
just take good care of your business. Go quickly.
- Bye, Mum. - Go, my dear Gab Dol.
- Hello. - Hello.
Sit down, please.
You're assigned to our office.
Congratulations.
Please don't forget the self-esteem...
and the pride as public officials.
Today, we'll have an orientation course about...
serving citizens and mental training.
We'll skip on the welcome dinner.
I am Officer Kim Young Ran,
who will guide you as a three-year senior to you.
Kim Young Ran is a famous name these days, right?
Follow me.
Administrative Support Team is...
in charge of major events of Dongsan-gu office.
They also take care of the general parts of...
welfare and education of the employees, too.
So you'll need a lot of help from Administrative Support Team.
(Dongsan Tax Office)
(Business Licence)
Did you need me?
Don't forget I'm three years senior to you.
You'll get a lot of benefits if you're obedient to your seniors.
But you know you'll violate the law if you get free benefits, don't you?
Yes, I do.
- Don't get relaxed. - Okay.
From tomorrow, we'll make a pair and work outside.
I got it.
How tall are you?
My height? I'm 180cm tall.
I asked you to see if you can take out things high up on the shelves.
Get going.
- Clean them up. - Okay.
I have something to tell you. Spare me a minute.
I'll wait outside.
Clean that spot.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time.
Did you come to see Gab Soon?
You didn't have lunch, did you?
I bought plenty of them.
Eat some if you want.
No, thanks.
Sushi delivery.
He brought sushi.
Gab Soon's boyfriend is nice.
What brings you here?
I don't need a special excuse to see you.
I came to visit you because you're busy.
Last time, it was definitely Da Hae's fault.
I even beat her up.
Though she's my child, I get upset about her. No wonder you do.
Can't you forgive her just for once?
It's not me but our kids. They don't want to see her.
- Geum Sik. - Mother.
I'm sorry to say this but please don't come here any more.
I feel uncomfortable to see you.
How could you say that?
I know you are angry but you have to think of your children.
I do think of my children.
She hurt their feelings and they don't want to see her now.
I'm also heartbroken.
Even so, how could you...
sever all the ties like this? This is too harsh.
Even if Da Hae made a terrible mistake, this is not right.
How can you break the family relationship?
Cho Rong is upset now...
but I bet she'll get back to her mum later.
Adults should keep the door open.
You can't shut it like this.
Did your wife lure you to do that?
She is such a nice and kind woman.
Don't get involved in my family matter.
Wait.
Did you add her son to your family register?
You idiot, why on earth did you do such a thing?
What do you mean?
Geum Sik says he added her son to his family register.
You should've known better.
You made your children and Geum Sik turn away from you.
What are you going to do?
Did he get her son registered?
He said he'd take care of his own family and told me not to come.
I should have left earlier.
Don't hurry and be careful when you're driving.
I'll go on a business trip.
- When are you coming back? - Tomorrow.
Take care of your sister and brother.
Da Rong, take care.
Daddy, what about presents?
Presents?
Okay.
Ddol Ee, you take care, too.
- Honey, you might be late. - I'll call you.
- Bye, Dad. - Bye.
Bye.
Get inside now.
Aren't you going to hug me?
You only hugged the kids.
I'll get going.
Drive safely.
Goodbye.
He's not here.
He left for a business trip a while ago.
Where did he go?
They'll all burn out.
I called the kids to come over.
- What for? - We need to tell them.
I told you...
to come over because...
we are...
We will be separated for a while.
- Why? - Why?
- Is there something wrong? - Is there something wrong?
Your dad wanted to go to Sokcho, so I told him to do so.
There's nothing he can do at home anyway.
She's right.
I have nothing to do in Seoul.
It was nice when I visited there last time.
The air is fresh, and I can sometimes go on a boat.
It's better than Seoul.
Good.
I agree. Mum goes to gatherings with her friends,
but you always stay at home. I'm glad to hear that.
Good. He'll catch some fish once in a while.
That's right.
I'll come back about twice a month,
so keep that in mind.
No need to waste money. You can come back twice a year.
I also have something to show you.
Surprise! Dad, look.
What is it?
Envelopes scare me.
(Business Licence)
It's a business licence.
Have you already registered it?
Yes. I'm a president of my company now.
I almost cried.
Mum, take a look.
Forget it. It's just a cleaning company.
It's true.
Shin Gab Soon, the president.
You're the first president of our family.
Congratulations.
You're successful now.
Sparkly Clean Gab Soon.
I like the name.
You've now registered your company.
You're the first president of our family.
Do your best.
I will.
Don't show this kind of stuff to Mum.
She won't be happy.
Thanks to all of you, the company has grown this much.
We are now exporting more not only to China and Russia,
but also to all over the world.
Let's work on developing our offline sales on top of online marketing.
Let's work hard to increase the rate of repurchase.
For the ones that posted reviews on our website,
let's hold events to show our appreciation.
The profits we have made thanks to your effort...
will be used for the product development...
and for your benefits.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
- Good luck. - Thank you.
Thank you.
What brings you here?
Should I say it here or should we go somewhere else?
Shall we go somewhere where I can make a big fuss?
If you have something to say, do it quickly. I'm busy.
I heard you added the woman's son to your family register.
- I warned you. - You have nothing to do with me.
Stop caring about my family register.
The assets I'll give to my kids...
are about to be rewarded to some other kid.
As you said, you've done everything to save your company.
I'm not going to let him take it.
That has got nothing to do with you.
Let me say this clearly.
He is...
my child.
I'll treat him the same way I do to Cho Rong and Da Rong.
He'll get as much asset, too.
You must be out of your mind.
You're the one that's insane.
How could you follow me all the way to my business trip?
Sometimes,
I regretted having divorced you...
because I took the kids' mum away from them.
Honestly, I had lingering feelings for you, too.
I wasn't sure if it was a good idea to marry the second time.
I even thought about that.
However,
I now think that having divorced you is one of the best things...
I've done in my life.
Don't ever show up in front of my kids.
Reflect deeply on what you did at the mall,
what you have done so far...
and how much you have hurt your kids.
You should reflect deeply on all of that.
I beg you.
I can no longer live with you.
I'm going there right now.
I can be on time for the meeting.
You're aware that the company's future lies on this project, right?
It's already been approved, so he'll sign the contract today.
I've already sent my lawyer there, so have the papers ready and wait.
- What are you doing? - Your employees are watching. Go.
- Get off. - I won't.
Call a deluxe taxi.
I won't get off unless you take your words back.
I don't have time for this.
I said I have the most important task ahead of me today.
To me, this is more important.
- I need to hear your answer. - Do you want to see me go crazy?
Nullify having added him to your family register.
I can already see what she's going to do.
I can already see what will happen to my kids, too. How can I get off?
- What is it that you can see? - You already know what it is!
You can't even make a sound decision because you're all over her.
I wasn't a good mum for my kids,
so my last duty is to at least do this for them.
You're now saying that you'll take care of Cho Rong and Da Rong,
but I can tell how you'll push your kids aside because of that wench.
Since that kid is a boy, you'll hand over the company to him for sure.
Think whatever you want. Don't speak a word from now.
Otherwise, I'll drop you off on the street.
You married a woman that has a child and hurt...
Cho Rong and Da Rong. Do you think you've done a good job?
- Be quiet. - He's now on your family register.
She'll abuse them in their faces.
Shut your mouth.
Ask everyone on the street if you're in your right mind.
Can't you tell that she approached you because of your fortune?
If you had no fortune, she would not have married you.
She wouldn't even have added her son to your family register.
I said, be quiet!
(Jae Soon)
Don't pick it up.
Da Hae!
Let go!
Hey!
I said let go!
- What's wrong with you? - I said, don't pick up the call!
Do you really have to pick up her call?
Let go!
- Jae Soon. - I said, don't pick up the phone!
Hey!
Come on out and eat.
I think I should feed you before you leave.
- Where's Gab Soon? - She went out for night cleaning.
When did you make all this?
I thought there would not be...
a divorce in my life.
When people talk about a midlife crisis divorce,
I didn't think it'd be something that would happen to me.
It all happened because of me.
Men are like this.
Even though they got treated like a loser outside,
they want to lead their family...
at home at least.
I no longer work and became incompetent.
That made me do something like a loser.
I'm sorry...
and thank you.
You got married to a poor family,
took care of my parents,
and married off all my siblings.
You also gave me birth to my precious three kids.
I'm sure I could keep this house,
all thanks to you
Thank you.
I really want to...
give you all this but,
please understand me.
Let's just hang in and go through.
I guess...
we expected too much each other.
I thought you would know how I feel...
and give it back to me what I gave you.
We should have tried to bear with each other...
and care about each other's thoughts.
We didn't know what to do about that.
We worried when our kids cried...
and looked for what would be good for them,
but we got annoyed when one of us cried.
I'm so sorry about that.
I realised that...
we can't be one or feel the same...
even though we got married.
That's why people say life is lonely.
You were lonely, too. Right?
I'm sorry about that as well.
Let me ask you a favour.
I'm sure...
our kids will take care of themselves well.
But please...
let Mal Nyeon stay here until I get settled in Sokcho.
I'll take her with me as soon as I'm settled.
Do you have any place to stay?
I'm not sure yet. I'll get on a fishing boat.
I already asked for that job.
They told me to come as soon as possible,
but it was delayed for taking care of all this.
I don't think you can get on the boat.
You'll get seasick right away.
It's like "Do or die," I think.
Don't worry. I won't die anyway.
I'm not worried about you.
You're so selfish. You must have set aside some money for yourself.
You look old now.
You weren't like this when you got married me at 24.
When I look at all the wrinkles on your face,
I feel sad because I think I gave you all of them.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for living with me.
I'm glad we'll get divorced without any bad happenings.
Thank you for your understanding.
I'll go there first and come back around next week.
After that, you can file the divorce papers.
It's very simple...
to be strangers each other.
(Divorce Application Form)
(Our Gab Soon)
Do you really want to do this?
My mum may not like you even if you become a teacher.
Why would you do this then?
I won't get married to you.
I will stay here for a while.
Tell me what happened.
Are you thinking of getting a divorce again?
Now are you happy there...
after leaving me with all your troublesome kids?
How dare you come here?
You're such a rude old lady.
Dad, we're in trouble.
I'm sorry, but I already turned in my resignation.
How could you quit that job without any words?
This is obviously a fake marriage.
Take your son back, please.