(Episode 26)
The person you are trying to reach is not available.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. He's coming soon.
I'm sorry, but we can't be business partners...
with someone who can't even show up on time for an appointment.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. It can't happen.
He's coming soon.
You should have done whatever it takes to make them stay.
I will get a cast and go right away.
Make them stay no matter what.
You know what I am saying, right?
Yes.
Thank you. Can you finish this quickly?
Please be patient.
You're lucky that you're not injured seriously.
Thank you, Geum Sik.
I heard that you turned the steering wheel...
to keep Da Hae from getting injured.
Please don't move.
Geum Sik.
Are you okay?
I wonder what time it is.
It's nice being alone.
I don't have to cook for anyone else. This is so convenient.
I forgot.
I need to make rice.
Is anything good on TV?
Sometimes, things happen.
In a few days, I have to vacate my house.
After vacating your house, have some fun for a while.
(Squeaking)
It's similar.
What are you doing? Can you come out?
Let's get some fresh air.
You're going to babysit your grand child with your husband?
You do everything with him.
Don't you get sick of him?
You feel lonely when he's not around?
You're so weird.
Okay. Bye.
Doesn't she ever get sick of her husband?
How is the weather? I wonder if it's cold.
I guess I'll just take out the trash.
Is that you, Joong Nyeon?
It's me.
Joong Nyeon.
He's not here.
Where did he go?
- He went to Sokcho. - Sokcho?
Did you kick him out while I was gone?
I didn't kick him out.
He probably left because you badger him and make him feel lonely.
How do I make him feel miserable?
My brother worked all his life to earn a living.
You should treat him like a head of the household.
You've been mean to him since his retirement.
You had to get rid of his pile of junk.
How could he live comfortably here?
You must've said something to make him go to Sokcho. It's true.
Why are you getting on my case, too?
You have no idea about what's going on between us.
I have a very good idea about what's going on.
I've watched you guys since the day you got married.
Honestly, my brother is really a good person.
If there's another one like him, I would propose to him just like that.
Don't say that unless you've lived with him.
Did I not live with him?
Living as a sibling is not the same as living as a couple.
Look around.
Do you know how bad other husbands are?
Does he gamble, cheat on you, or beat you?
Other women would be glad to have someone like my brother.
My goodness.
Don't you know that he's the type that causes grief quietly?
People say that I'm the evil one because I scream and yell.
He's so selfish and cold.
He only thinks about himself and do things without telling me.
He's so devious.
I found that out the hard way.
I can't believe I've lived with him for 40 years.
If you say that someone like my brother is devious,
you're not a human being.
You should keep loyal to your husband.
You disrespect him because he doesn't work.
You'll be punished.
I'm being punished right now.
You should go, too. I don't want to see you.
I'd love to.
You threw out your husband and now his sister, too.
I hope you have a nice life without us.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
My goodness.
- Don't ever come back. - Fine.
(Now Hiring)
(Resume)
(No work experience)
We're looking for experienced employee.
You're quite old,
and you only went to high school.
Do you want to work at the restaurant as my assistant?
He wants to get a permanent job, not a temporary one.
You're old, and you have no work experience...
or a university degree. It won't be easy.
If you're not qualified, you should take any job you can get.
I'm not going to do that...
no matter what I do.
It's... That brat.
You punk.
- What? - Did you have to say that?
Do you think he doesn't know he's old and undereducated?
Gosh.
Goodness.
Come in.
Hello.
- Hi. What brings you here? - Have you been well?
She's just like me.
What is it? I'm a little busy right now.
I'm here on Nae Shim's behalf. Give me the monthly pay.
- Monthly pay? - Was it living expenses?
It's not the date yet.
I'll contact you through my secretary later.
Gosh. You got a nice office here.
It looks so much different from outside.
What do you mean?
I mean it looks great.
It looks really great.
Looking at you work here like this, I'm starting to admire you.
I'm sure you've entered beauty pageants before.
Not exactly,
but everybody told me that I was pretty.
I was sick of it.
Don't ask for money in advance again.
Of course. Bless you.
You're just like me.
You keep saying that. What do you mean by that?
It's a secret.
Why did you come back? I told you not to.
Go to your brother.
- Mum, it's me. - Is it you, Jae Soon?
Hello, Ddol Ee.
Grandma.
Are you going on a trip?
Ddol Ee. Go to Grandma's room.
What is it? Where are you going?
I'm sorry, but please don't ask me anything.
What's going on? Did you have a fight with Geum Sik?
Dad is not here, so I'll stay in his room for a while.
Tell me what happened.
Please let me stay here for a while.
I want to think about what I'm going to do from now on.
I'll take my time to think about my life and Ddol Ee's life, and decide.
I wanted to stay at some place else,
but I had nowhere to go.
I didn't want to come here with Ddol Ee and a suitcase again.
I'm sorry, Mum.
I know it's embarrassing and upsetting, but help me this once.
I won't stay for long.
Is it about the girls' birth mother?
- Did Geum Sik tell you to leave? - It's not that.
You should tell me what it is.
Just give me a few days.
The doctor told you not to move.
Geum Sik.
I should call the doctor.
Don't.
I have to go.
They said you should stay here for a few more days.
I don't know what's so urgent, but please stay.
I can take care of myself.
You ruined my life.
You're a hopeless woman.
Don't ever show your face again.
Please.
What is it? Why is he being so cold?
Did you cause the accident?
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
You should've called us. You didn't even have a big surgery.
It was just a broken bone. This is ridiculous.
We stalled them for three hours, but you didn't come or call.
What are you going to do? That deal was the reason for my investment.
How will you take the responsibility?
I'll take care of it no matter what.
I won't let the stockholders suffer any loss.
All you needed to do was make a call.
How could you lose your phone at a time like that?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Dad! - Dad!
Cho Rong, Da Rong.
What is it?
Don't cry. I'm fine.
- Have you eaten? - No.
- Does it hurt a lot? - It doesn't hurt at all.
I'll be fine after I remove the cast.
Shall we order some Chinese food?
I'll do it. You should rest.
Okay.
Why are you going in and out?
I thought you were asleep.
Is it because of the job hunting?
Don't worry.
There will be a way for us to make a living.
I'll make money no matter what.
Come in.
Tell me.
What made Geum Sik so angry?
I've never seen him so scary like that.
He turned the wheel to save you. Why is he so upset?
How did you get into the accident? Tell me.
- Don't answer it. - Let go of me!
Hey!
Gab Soon.
- What brings you here? - I was visiting my aunt.
What's that?
I'm running an errand for my mum.
We're doing a big house cleaning tomorrow. I got this from my sister.
I see.
I saw your blog. You're starting a cleaning business.
Did you give up becoming a teacher?
Gab Dol passed his exam. Aren't you two getting married?
What if Gab Dol's mother finds out about your business?
I'll be going now.
I'll see you at the reunion.
Okay.
You're here, Jae Soon.
- You must be tired. Have you eaten? - I have.
Why do you ask for trouble?
You should just study.
Don't be like that. Where is Mum?
She went in to her room to sleep.
Did you stay to see me?
No. I'll be staying here for a while.
What? Did something happen?
Do me a favour, and don't ask me anything.
Just for a while. Don't tell Dad.
Mum was so upset,
but I told her to give me time to think.
I don't know what it is,
but I don't want you to hold yourself back any more.
Jae Soon. Don't think about anything else.
Just focus on yourself. It's your life, not anyone else's.
Your words mean the world to me.
Thank you, Gab Soon.
Gosh.
Thank you.
Where is Ms Shin?
She went to take care of some urgent business.
She'll be back in a few days.
I wish she were here.
Did she leave because of us?
No. She'll be back.
Cho Rong. You should help me for a while.
I'll be busy with important work at the company.
Take good care of Da Rong,
and order food with this. Can you do it for me?
Se Gye. You're leaving early.
- Yes. - Get in.
-It's okay. - I'll give you a ride. Get in.
There's no need to use two cars.
Do you remember my friends you met before?
Make appointments for them for next week.
They can call the hospital and do it themselves.
I know that.
Pull some strings and get your chief treat them.
That's illegal.
I'm just saying.
That's illegal, too.
(Cho Rok National University Hospital)
Get off. Talking to you makes me so frustrated.
- Drive safely. - I'm not driving yet.
I knew you'd come.
I came because of my mother-in-law.
You're not answering the chief's calls.
He wants to talk to you in person.
I sent him an email and told him I have nothing to say...
regarding that matter.
I'll pay him a visit later.
Bye.
Se Gye. Dr Shin!
Joong Nyeon!
Mal Nyeon.
How could you do this to me?
Were you planning to leave without me?
I went through so much to find you during the Korean War.
I wasn't even born then.
- Why did you come here? - Be honest with me.
Did Nae Shim tell you to leave? Did she kick you out?
I came here myself. It was too lonely to stay in Seoul.
I'll buy you a meal. Eat and go home.
I don't need you to buy me a meal. I'll stay here, too.
I can barely take care of myself.
Just go home. I can't look after you.
Don't worry. I can take care of myself.
Here. Take this. It's a little pocket money for you.
- Where did you get it? - I'm not telling you.
It's not bad money. You can take it.
Take it.
It's my first time to receive money from you.
Be a good brother, and I'll often give you money.
My gosh.
As I see you here, you look like a bumpkin.
I am a bumpkin, you know.
Goodness.
Here.
We, public officials, exist for this country and the citizens.
Don't forget to be loyal to your country.
Don't forget to be loyal to your senior officer, either.
(Public Official Heo Gab Dol)
There's finally someone successful in our family.
Look at his business card.
Now, my only wish is for you to get a good wife.
I set you up on a blind date again.
I told you I don't want blind dates.
I want to meet a woman in a natural way. Stop setting me up.
How about your fellow public officials?
Is there any nice and pretty girl?
- No. - Think before you answer.
There's no need to think.
- I'm going out. - Where?
- To see my friends. - You little...
Listen.
You said some of your colleagues are women.
What I want is a teacher, but a public official isn't so bad.
She'd get a lot of pension later, right?
What's with Da Hae? Is she okay?
What is it?
It's been a while since you cleaned my house.
Come in this week.
Okay, Sir. Thank you.
We have another work.
We've been doing great since Gab Soon joined us.
It's good to have a young person.
You should be proud of yourself.
Young people these days don't do this kind of work.
If you're done eating, I should go. I have to clean up some things.
Don't be late tomorrow.
- Okay. Goodbye. - All right.
- I'll be going, too. - Okay.
Men who carry women's bag aren't charming.
Can I invest in your business?
- Invest? - I'll invest the foundation fund.
You should get an office and a car,
and hire two employees.
Do you have a driving licence?
I got one with my mum before. I haven't been driving, though.
You should have some mobility to work faster.
That'd be good.
- Why would you invest? - Because I believe in you.
I think you can pull this off.
- I don't make investments easily. - You're just saying it, but thanks.
I mean it.
It'd be great if I let you invest and start my business...
with an office and employees.
But I'm not confident yet.
I'm not sure I can handle the debt.
When I'm confident and hopeful enough,
I'll ask you to invest.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Please give it.
I want to.
I'm being harassed with phone calls everyday.
My goodness!
Stop crying! Be quiet!
Don't be like that.
- Don't cry. - Mum.
It doesn't have to be much. Please consider my situation.
Please be generous and think of how I came to work everyday.
I don't expect much.
I told you I don't have any!
What's this?
Come out!
What happened?
- Where's Ms Shin? - She isn't here.
Where's she? Is she at the amusement park again?
No.
- Dad got in an accident. - What?
You'll be directed to voicemail. Please speak after the beep.
Jae Soon, I need to see you. Let's talk.
I know what you're thinking. It's a misunderstanding.
I'll explain myself.
Honey.
I had so much fun.
- She thinks it's a business trip? - Yes.
Here you go.
(Jae Soon)
Don't answer that.
Why is she calling?
She'll get suspicious.
Who cares?
I told you not to answer.
I need to.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for a job.
Until when will you stay here?
I'll pay my share. I won't be a burden like last time.
Tell me what's going on.
Are you going to get a divorce?
Are you?
What should we do?
We need to find him and make the deal.
Let's go.
It's not difficult. Look, Grandfather.
Do you see the icon that looks like an envelope?
- Press that. - I see.
Then the keyboard appears.
When you press it, it becomes a word.
Grandfather, what do you want to write?
Relief Patch.
What?
Never mind. Tell me again.
- I need to press this? - Yes.
(Relief)
What does that mean?
Relief?
Relief Patch. What are you doing?
I get it.
If you're going to send a message, send it right.
What do you want to eat?
Darn it!
Why is he cursing?
That was a mistake.
I meant to say doenjang.
I meant to type doenjang stew.
I'll cook that for you.
I don't have time to reply. Don't text me.
Okay.
On a sanitary inspection, we need to be meticulous.
It's directly related to the citizen's health.
- I see. - Gab Dol, let's eat.
Of course we'll pay for our own meal.
Gab Dol.
- Hello. - My goodness.
I nearly didn't recognise you.
- Where are you headed? - I'm working.
I see.
Who's this?
She's a colleague of mine.
I see.
Have you seen Gab Soon these days?
Gab Soon must be busy these days.
She couldn't find the time for me so we couldn't meet.
I see. Okay.
- You should drop by the house. - Okay.
Did you meet Gab Soon's mum?
- Did you see us? - I wanted to say something,
but I didn't because of your colleague.
What does she have to say to you?
She just said hello.
Get out. I need to get changed.
Your colleague looks nice.
Think of the pension you both would receive.
- Stop it. She's my senior. - How old is she?
- Get out! - My goodness.
(Sparkly Clean Gab Soon has opened! We have a promotion just for you!)
Why aren't you seeing him?
I heard you said you didn't have time for Gab Dol.
Mum, I'm working.
I met him today. He looks handsome.
Any girl would die to meet him.
- He's a public official. - Mum.
His mum wouldn't be able to do anything if her son likes you.
You only need to see her once or twice a year.
The couple is the most important. Who cares about the parents?
- Get out. - You're just a cleaner.
Don't play hard to get.
You need to hang onto Gab Dol!
You should come to your senses!
Get out, Mum.
Se Gye.
- How's everything? - What's the matter?
- Is something wrong? - Nothing's wrong.
I had a few drinks.
Do you have good news?
I had a few drinks with my colleagues.
How is it there?
Isn't it cold? Have you eaten?
I'll make time and go see you soon.
There's no need. I know you're busy.
I'm not busy.
Is there something wrong?
You've never called late at night.
I'm sorry to call you in the middle of the night.
I'm sorry I wasn't a good son.
I'll be a good son from now on.
Dad. Don't do dangerous work.
You might hurt yourself.
All right. Don't worry about me and go home.
Your wife would be worried.
Don't drink too much.
All right. Go home.
This is it, right?
This is a big house. We won't be able to finish it in four hours.
I'm here.
- Right. - Gab Soon, you're the best.
Let's go!
I was going to text you.
But it was too long so I called.
I called a cleaning company.
So don't do anything. Just boss them around.
Don't lift a finger.
- Don't use your knee. - Okay.
It must be them.
I won't lift a finger nor will I use my knee.
Hello.
- Hello. - We're here to clean.
- Hello. - Be careful.
Hello.
Mr Yeo told us to take orders from you.
Is that so?
Ma'am, where should we focus on?
Is there such a thing in cleaning?
You need to do it well.
Every nook and cranny.
Behind the toilet and the light switch.
Don't forget the entrance floor or the slime and dirt.
I see. You heard what she said, right?
- Take good care of the toilet. - Okay.
Get a move on it.
Ma'am, please tell us what do to.
All right. Get a start on it.
- Yes, Ma'am. - Yes, Ma'am.
Let's get a move on it.
We don't have much time.
Follow me.
Toilet!
Start with the bedroom toilet.
What are you doing?
I can't believe this. I thought you were going to be a teacher.
You're an undergraduate. What are you doing here?
Are you working part time here?
I'm only a part time now, but I'll found my own cleaning service.
What?
That's the end of you.
Do your parents know what you're up to?
I'm saying this because I feel sorry for you.
Don't even think about getting close with my son.
I have advice for you. Study.
Who'd want you to be a daughter-in-law?
Think of your mum.
How could you be so thoughtless?
Scrub this clean.
The slime and dirt here.
Yes, Ma'am.
- Mum, enjoy. - Okay.
Se Gye wanted to apologise,
so he specially made time for us.
Please enjoy yourself.
How kind of you.
- Ms Yeo. - Yes?
What is it? Tell me.
Se Gye, why are you like that?
Do you have something to say?
Eat up.
Did you pack everything?
- Yes. - Yes.
I have everything here.
It's quite all right.
Toilet. You did well.
Thank you.
Ma'am.
If you're dissatisfied, please call us.
All right.
You all did well today.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye, Ma'am.
Let's go.
Be careful.
I thought you had something to say.
- It's nothing. - Be careful.
Grandfather must have called the cleaning service.
Gab Soon!
Hello.
- Who is she? - She's my sister-in-law.
You saw her at the wedding.
She's my sister.
Your sister?
She's a cleaner?
I don't know when he'll be back.
Why are you looking for my son-in-law?
I have my reasons.
He's not in.
I don't understand why I run into you so often.
As a mother of a daughter, I believe that...
you'd understand so I'll say just one thing.
Don't be upset.
Geum Sik and your daughter got a divorce.
He got a divorce and now he has a family.
You shouldn't disturb that.
If you got a divorce, you should leave it.
They have two daughters. How can they become strangers?
You shouldn't go trying to tempt an ex husband.
What are you talking about?
Who do you think you are?
What?
That's why my daughter's at home.
If it was some other woman, she wouldn't have let you be.
My daughter's too nice.
She's at home?
She's being patient.
I hope we never meet.
Wait.
I have one favour to ask.
Do you know Gab Dol became a public official?
Yes.
I've raised my kids all by myself for over 20 years.
Those who raised their kids as a couple wouldn't understand me.
I hope my son never has any business with your family.
I know they broke up but just to make sure.
I'm nothing much so I work at another's home,
but your daughter came to clean...
today at the house.
- Pardon? - To be honest,
if she was a teacher, since they love each other so much,
I'd give my blessing.
But I can't let this happen. Wouldn't you agree?
I'll think that you'll do me a favour. I'll be going now.
(Dongsan District Office)
- Are you here for a delivery? - Yes.
Gab Dol, you know Gab Soon is cleaning these days, right?
The guys are all talking bad about you.
We thought you'd get married as soon as you pass the exam,
but you're making her go through a hard time.
Be good to her.
You'll be punished if you breakup with her.
The noodles will get soggy.
I'm home.
Did you know Gab Soon is cleaning?
Goodness.
She came to clean the house I work for.
You didn't know, did you?
Don't even say hello to her.
I'm scared she'll latch on now that you're a public official.
What is she thinking?
How can her parents let her live like that?
I feel sorry for her.
Gab Dol!
Must you do this?
I get you want to start a business.
Why does it have to be cleaning? You can do something else.
What else? Something splendid?
Should I open a franchise? Will you pay for that?
What will the guys think?
They're all blaming me.
Do you need to leave me in a difficult spot?
I'm sorry for that.
Don't be sarcastic.
Think if you were me.
I heard you ran into my mum today.
If you want to marry me, you should make an effort.
She might not let us even if you become a teacher.
Do you need to start on the wrong foot like this?
Would it seem normal for the elderly?
Do you know how I feel?
How could you not be understanding?
I advised you to study because I want to marry you.
Are you going to get married or not?
You only think of yourself.
Do I need to satisfy your mum about my livelihood?
I let my parents down when I started this.
Nobody lives my life.
You?
You want me to think myself in your shoes?
Have you thought of my situation?
That's how people are. We can never think ourselves in another's shoes.
Was that a marriage proposal?
I'm sorry. I won't marry you.
Where have you been?
- Mum. - I don't want to see you like this.
Tell me what happened between you and Geum Sik.
She must have come because she knew something.
What are you talking about?
I went to see Geum Sik but he was away.
Why did you do that for? I said I'd think about it.
I couldn't just watch so I went.
You packed up and came back home.
You have to tell me what's going on.
Don't make things worse than it is.
Nothing ever works out when you get in the way.
What did you just way?
I never told you to do dishes.
Who told you to vacuum?
Do you think I want to do dishes and vacuum?
I'm doing it so that I can forget about everything.
Don't nag me. This is what you did last time, too.
If you left me alone, I would have taken my time.
That goes for both the divorce and the remarriage.
Fine. You can blame me.
Let's say it's all my fault. Tell me what's wrong now.
Please, Mum. Leave me alone.
Don't go around looking for Geum Sik.
My life is not up to Geum Sik. I'll decide for myself.
Are you going to get divorced again?
Great job.
Everything's working out perfectly.
You want me to watch my daughter getting divorced twice?
You told me to get divorced if I can't stand it.
I didn't mean it.
Are you getting divorced so that you can obey me?
Mum, I'm the one who's suffering the most.
I even registered Ddol Ee on his register to live with him.
Do you know what it took for me to come here without a penny?
If I had at least 1,000 dollars, I wouldn't have come here.
It's been over a year since you got married and you don't have that?
For goodness' sake. You fool!
You should have saved some up for yourself.
I am a fool.
I thought I'd be okay if I was loyal and frugal.
I don't want to live like that any more.
So leave me alone for a few days.
Look at my daughters.
Are you happy going around like this?
Get out. I don't want to see your face so get out!
Mum.
One of our ancestors must be a ghost who loves to clean.
Why are you both doing this today?
You need to set yourself straight.
You know how humiliating that was?
I have a bad daughter...
so I deserve to hear advices from that woman?
She was bragging so much about how her son became a public official.
I couldn't bear to watch her.
He wanted to be a public official and you wanted to be a teacher.
You two started studying at the same time so why can't you make it?
You carry this junk around.
Do you two want to see me die?
Stop it, Mum.
- That's your ego. - What?
I know because I have a kid of my own.
You can't always make your kids do what you want.
Don't judge us because of how we are now.
One of my friends failed to get into a college so she was going to die,
but she ended up becoming a hair stylist.
We used to pity her,
but she owns a popular hair salon in Gangnam now.
She has over 20 people working for her.
That's her and not you.
You're this way so your sister takes after you.
If your younger sister takes the wrong path in life,
you're supposed to lead her to the right path. And what do you say?
If you showed good example, she wouldn't have turned out this way.
Don't scold Jae Soon. It's all my doing.
Mum.
I'm sorry for not being a good example.
This is all I'm capable of.
Jae Soon!
I'm embarrassed as the older one of the family.
You didn't do it on purpose.
There are things...
that you can't control in life.
Even if I try to escape it, I can't...
and even if I try my best, I can't do anything.
There are things you just have to struggle...
and endure.
By the way, what were you talking about earlier?
Did you bump into Gab Dol's mum at your workplace?
Yes.
It must have hurt Mum's pride.
I wanted Mum to look proud...
in front of Gab Dol's mum.
I went cleaning at Se Gye's house.
Se Gye's house?
You didn't know it was his place?
I knew it was the same neighbourhood but I've never been to his place.
I feel so sorry for Se Gye.
What would his in-laws think about us?
I know.
What did Gab Dol's mum say to you?
I don't even need to ask.
Gab Soon, can't you stop working as a cleaner?
- Jae Soon. - I agree with Mum.
I can't stop you if you insist,
but you know Mum.
We're her source of pride.
It's like I'm standing alone in a windy field.
It looks like Geum Sik kicked his wife out.
She's at her parents' place.
I went to see Geum Sik today and her mum was there.
She must have gotten worried because her daughter came home.
What's wrong with you? Why aren't you saying anything?
Where have you been?
What's wrong with him?
I have only two kids...
and they are worse than having 12 kids.
Goodness.
I'm leaving, Jae Soon.
What's that?
I don't think Mum's feeling well.
I won't budge, Mum.
I've experienced it all. I've already been humiliated.
I won't give up.
Don't get sick. I'm leaving.
What's wrong with this door?
That was the wind.
I made your favourite soup.
It's not that I don't understand you.
Gab Soon and I are grown ups.
We'll take care of ourselves.
We talked about it yesterday.
We understand you're an older person,
but we don't want you to worry about us any more.
Don't be so attached to us. You should live for yourself.
What did you just say?
We have grown up.
Whether we sink or swim is up to us.
You can live happily with Dad. Don't be attached to us.
Attached?
I'm attached to you so I must be bothering you.
You're saying I should give you some room?
I've done my job so I should step out of your life?
That's not what I meant.
Take this away.
I don't want to see your face so get out!
This is why they say kids are good for nothing.
I shouldn't be attached to my children and live my life?
That's not what I meant, Mum. I'm sorry.
I'll prepare your food again.
Forget it. I don't want to eat your food.
Who is it?
It's me. It's Geum Sik.
- It's Geum Sik, right? - Don't open the door.
Geum Sik.
What's wrong with your arm? What happened?
I got into an accident.
When? How bad is it?
Did you just hurt your arm?
I broke a few ribs too.
They were hairline fractures.
For goodness' sake.
If you have nothing to say, leave.
Jae Soon.
Mother, I'll explain later.
Let me talk with her first.
Sure. Come in.
Let me start.
I'll listen to what you have to say after.
That day, Da Hae followed me to my work trip.
She didn't want me to adopt Ddol Ee as my son.
She was against it from the beginning.
I didn't think she would follow me there.
There were other people watching so I couldn't argue with her.
And as you know,
I was getting back for an important contract...
and she got in the car.
I told her to get off,
but she said she won't unless I told her that I won't be adopting him.
She was being persistent so I couldn't kick her out.
That's when you called.
I was going to take the call...
and she was trying to stop me.
That's when I got into the accident.
My throat is burning.
I guess I was mistaken.
When you ran to the emergency...
and saw us lying down side by side,
I could only imagine what ran through your head.
I would have thought the same.
I can't forget...
what I saw on your face.
It was as if your world collapsed.
I'm sorry.
I was mistaken,
but I don't want to live like this.
As long as the girls are with you, you can't cut off their mum...
and it'll continue being this way.
You'll keep letting her do this...
and I'll have to cope with it.
You won't be able to handle me for it.
Our problem doesn't end here.
- We can't solve it. - We can.
- It's already over. - What concerns me...
What concerns me more than this...
is that you were in the same car...
with your ex-wife.
You could have told her to get off.
It's not that you are not strong enough.
If you wanted to, you could have dragged her out of the car.
I was running out of time so I couldn't.
That's an excuse.
You say, "I couldn't do anything,"
"I can't do anything about her,"
and you let her push you around.
You will let her...
push you around forever.
You told her to get off,
but you never dragged her out yourself.
You felt bad about leaving her on the street.
I can't do this any more.
I don't want to.
I have reached my limit.
I thought about it for the past few days while my mum was pestering me.
I came to the conclusion...
that I was very naive.
We both have children...
so I should have been more prudent.
It didn't occur to me...
that they have their own mum.
I didn't realise that...
your ex-wife could...
do what she wants...
with my life.
Mother, I'll get going.
You must be thirsty. Have some water.
Thank you.
Are you leaving?
You should take her back home. You can't just leave.
You should drag her with you if you plan to live with her.
You can't leave her here for long.
- I'll be back. - When?
Mother.
Please help her feel better for the next few days.
She probably doesn't have a penny on her.
Here.
How did you know she didn't have money on her?
She hates to see her parents hurt.
Imagine what it took for her to be here.
Please take this to cover your living expenses.
All right. Take care of yourself.
Who's taking care of your household? What about the girls?
There's probably nobody to cook.
I'm ordering deliveries. There's my sister too.
I have to do what I can.
So Geum Sik didn't do anything wrong.
You're so cruel.
He came all the way here and left you money.
He said he's sorry...
so you should have followed him back home. Why are you being stubborn?
Didn't it occur to you when you got remarried?
It's not like his ex-wife died.
You know she's alive and well.
Didn't you think that she'll come back for the girls?
It's okay as long as Geum Sik is certain.
It's not like you're educated or rich.
What are you doing?
You didn't eat since yesterday. You need to eat.
I didn't ask you to make me food.
I'm not going to rely on a man to feed me any more.
I knew how embarrassing that was,
but I felt it even more this time.
Women need to be self-sufficient.
I rely on my husband to feed myself...
so he looks down on me. Even you and my siblings do as well.
Even when I'm struggling, you only worry about what people say.
It's not for me.
I don't care about what people say.
It's for you.
Where would you meet another man like Geum Sik?
That's why his ex-wife is clinging on to him.
Are you going to let a good man like him leave?
What if his ex-wife moves in while you're here?
Let her be. I don't care.
It's not like you're young or unmarried.
Nobody's going to take you in.
I don't need anyone to take me in.
Mum, eat. You'll faint.
How are you going to make money?
You don't even know what you're putting yourself into.
What's wrong with my daughters? Both you and the younger one.
Is this how I raised you guys?
Fine. Eat first.
I don't need to eat!
Why are you not listening to me?
Do you even know how I feel?