[Episode 27]
I'm sorry, Se Gye. I didn't
know it was your house.
I made you feel embarrassed
to see your in-laws.
And to your wife, too.
I'm okay with that.
I just didn't know...
that our housekeeper was Gab Dol's mother.
It is such a complicated relationship.
Don't mention it. You'll
only feel uncomfortable.
I won't feel uncomfortable,
but I'll pretend that I don't know.
You must feel discouraged.
In fact, when I was cleaning for work...
and even when I write about it on my blog,
I've been afraid that someone
I know might recognise me.
I've been pretending to be
confident, but that act was a lie.
That was the only way for me to cope.
I think I've made a breakthrough
after meeting Gab Dol's mum.
I'm confident that I won't be
embarrassed like I was before.
I think I will be fine even if I
meet a friend while I am cleaning.
Hello, customer. Where should I clean?
Please tell everyone about our service.
If you use us 10 times, the
next service will be free.
That's not easy to do.
Koreans can't be true to themselves...
because they're so conscious
of how others view them.
I'm proud of you.
I will do this.
I must do this.
At least, our family has you.
"What's wrong with my daughters?"
"What would I have done without Se Gye?"
"Se Gye is our only hope."
Mum always says that.
Jae Soon and I agree.
You are the representative of our family.
You're the only one we can be proud of.
Why did you cancel? You should
just postpone it until next year.
No, I told him that I don't want to.
He tried to talk me out of it. I felt bad.
I can't say anything right now
since I'm not doing well.
I wanted to send you off
in the best possible way.
I'm sorry.
Did you get the money back?
- Money?
- Perhaps, I should...
meet him and talk to him directly.
I will also apologise to him.
I will do it. I heard that Mr
Geum is out of the country.
I will ask for the money
when he comes back.
Can I have more kimchi?
Yes.
Give me just a little bit.
I'm in a real bind.
I served all day long.
Please give me a little bit.
I have nothing to give to you.
Look. There's hardly any customer.
Still, give me just a little bit.
Can I have some water?
Give him some water.
Hello? So how much is the hospital bill?
Get the surgery no matter what.
Get the surgery. I'll get the money
even if I have to sell my body.
You can't let a human being die.
I got 300 dollars for now.
We called it even for that place,
so don't go asking for more there.
This is not enough to call it even.
Do you want to die?
Turn yourself in to me
before I call the police.
(Hiring)
You're too old and have no experience.
You don't have a college degree.
I can't hire you.
(Blog, Sparkly Clean Gab Soon)
(Hello, I'm Shin Gab Soon
of Sparkly Clean Gab Soon.)
Get your act together.
Why are you doing this?
- Didn't Gab Dol propose?
- Gab Dol that horrible jerk.
Gab Dol, you know that you have
to work late tonight, right?
Yes, I do.
What? I'm busy.
When are you getting off work?
I have to work late. Don't
call me at work. Bye.
You have time this Sunday, right?
Someone set up a blind date.
Meet her just this one time.
I don't have time to meet anyone.
She's a Korean teacher. She's
pretty and her family...
Hang up. I hate Korean teachers.
Gab Dol.
(Dongsan District Office)
You did poorly in Korean
at school, didn't you?
I guess I know why you don't
like Korean teachers.
What do you mean?
You have typos and punctuation errors.
Here, here and here.
There are run-on sentences. You
need to separate them here.
The readers of this report
will run out of breath.
- Revise it.
- Okay.
Who is Gab Soon?
Pardon?
Gab Dol and Gab Soon.
I accidentally overheard it that day.
It doesn't sound like siblings. Who is she?
She's my girlfriend.
You have a girlfriend?
Gab Dol.
Why are you here? How did you get in?
The guard let me in when I told
him I'm Heo Gab Dol's mum.
This is my mother.
Mum, this is my co-worker.
Please, take good care of Gab Dol.
Hello, my name is Kim Young Ran.
Gab Dol is doing well.
He writes very good reports.
He's a bit slow at first,
but he does well on everything.
Eat this with Gab Dol.
I made some fried tofu sushi.
I can't. It's a violation
of Anti-bribery Act.
You can't share meals together?
Take it back with you.
- How old is she?
- Don't even think about it.
- I came to pick up the dishes.
- I left them at the entrance.
Gab Soon, I need to talk to you later.
- Who is he?
- He was my classmate.
You have classmates everywhere.
I grew up here. That's why.
Do you want to go for a drink?
Tell me your worries. I will listen.
I'm having doubts about my work.
I'm wondering if I'm on the right path.
Do you regret it?
I've disappointed my parents.
My friends think less of me. I
wonder if this work is worth it.
I change my mind several times a day.
No one wants to hire me
for the cleaning service.
I would work so hard, if someone
would give me a chance.
It's deflating.
It's not easy to pick up new clients.
Even big companies have to
advertise to sell products.
Spend some money on ads.
You have to advertise to gain customers.
I don't have money for ads.
You have to invest money to make money.
If you are tired, you should
rest and re-energise.
I'm in no situation to do that.
Take some time off and think.
Go on a trip.
Leave. You're annoying me.
What do you mean?
At times like this, I feel like
we live in different worlds.
We think differently because
we grew up so differently.
Go on a trip? I have no car and no money.
Take some time off?
If it weren't for my parents,
I would starve to death.
Don't give me advice based
on your living standards.
I feel so inadequate.
Do you have to do this?
If you want to get married to me,
you should try to win my mum over.
What are you doing?
All my friends blame me.
I'm so embarrassed.
You're only concerned about yourself.
No one helps me with my life.
Get married?
I'm sorry, but I refuse to marry you.
Buy ramyeon and pay for the rent with this.
I'll save money tenaciously
and buy a truck.
Once I manage to find
customers, we won't starve.
Do you feel better...
now that you're out of Seoul?
I don't necessarily feel better,
but I do forget about it a while.
Joong Nyeon,
you know what?
Wherever I go,
I feel lonely.
Do you at least keep in touch?
You don't even know where he is, do you?
I'm home.
Se Gye, you're home early nowadays.
My work is quite smooth these days.
- Mr Yeo.
- No need for a checkup.
I'm all normal.
I'll go upstairs, then.
Se Gye, sit here for a second.
What's wrong with your sister?
Right, why is Gab Soon cleaning around?
- Cleaning?
- You didn't see her, did you?
The one that was following the
cleaning ladies last time...
is Se Gye's little sister.
I thought she was preparing to
become a teacher. Was that a lie?
I didn't lie. She studied to
become a teacher for a few years,
but things didn't go smoothly, so
she's trying to start her business.
A cleaning business?
Stop her. Man has got to do the
right thing for his class.
There must be a reason.
She's all grown up. She won't
listen to her brother.
You said she performed well in school, too.
Was that a lie, too?
That's not a lie.
There were a lot of awards
she earned at home.
Everyone can win those awards.
Who did she take after?
Aren't you two biological siblings?
You went overboard.
How could there be a doctor and
a cleaner from the same family?
Cut it.
How others earn their living
is none of your business.
It's because I'm embarrassed.
When people ask what she does for a living,
should I say that she's a cleaner?
Why would anyone ask you about her?
It could happen.
Don't you think so?
Don't judge people by their occupation.
Then how could I judge people otherwise?
Go outside and ask others.
Everyone introduces himself by
his name and his occupation.
Her brother is a doctor,
yet she lacks insight.
Don't your parents say anything?
Me being a doctor has nothing to
do with my sister being a cleaner.
What is wrong with cleaning?
Is it that great to be a doctor?
I...
What is it?
Never mind. I'll go upstairs.
Ms Yeo.
Yes?
What is it?
Tell me.
Dad. It's an emergency. This is urgent!
Dad.
Go get him.
- Hello?
- It's me. Where are you?
- I'm at the hospital.
- Hospital?
I know you're not there.
Come home right now.
Tell me the truth.
Mum found out after she
went to the hospital.
Did you really quit working?
Answer.
I'm sorry.
I submitted my letter of resignation.
I should have told you earlier.
I'm really sorry that
you found out this way.
Do you think this makes any sense?
How could you quit on your own?
- I'm sorry.
- Apologising isn't enough.
Nobody would have found
out if it wasn't for me.
Every morning, you pretended to go to work.
How could you be so cunning?
How could you do this to my family?
Did your parents make you do that?
My parents had nothing to do
with my decision. My parents...
don't deserve your criticism.
What? Then you should've
behaved appropriately.
Follow me.
Sit.
I'm sorry.
Why did you do that?
What were you thinking?
How could you make such decision
without a single discussion?
Were you always like this?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you earlier.
What did your parents say? Did they
tell you to submit your resignation?
I haven't told them yet.
You little brat!
Get out. Get out of my sight...
because seeing you makes me upset.
It must be Geum Sik.
What brings you here? Did
you come here by yourself?
Yes, I came here by myself
to quibble over something.
Quibble over something?
What's the matter?
- Hello.
- I'm not fine.
Are you aware that your son
quit working at the hospital?
Excuse me?
He resigned because he no
longer wants to be a doctor.
He quit without a word.
He resigned without our permission.
Mum, Mum.
There may be a misunderstanding.
There's no way Se Gye would've done that.
He just confirmed it with
me before I came here.
I was so shocked that I even
went to another building.
This is a fraud.
I approved of my daughter's wedding
because your son was a doctor.
I didn't approve of it to some jobless guy.
How on earth did you raise your child?
He must have looked down
upon his in-laws...
to make such decision without a discussion.
Let's nullify their marriage.
Nullify?
Take your son back.
I'm done talking, so I'll go.
Mum, Mum, hold yourself together.
Call him. Call him now.
Your call has been forwarded to an
automated voice message system.
- This call may be charged...
- His phone is off.
Call your dad.
What is he doing right now? Call him now!
All my three kids are torturing me,
and what is he doing now?
I might die from anger.
Tell him to come now!
Dad.
What, what's the matter?
You should come home.
He's having ramyeon right now.
How could you be eating
ramyeon at this situation?
You left all your troublesome kids to me.
How could you possibly
enjoy your life there?
Why? What's the matter?
Tell me what it is.
Se Gye no longer wants to work as a doctor.
He even quit working at the hospital.
The in-laws want us to take him back
because their marriage was a fraud.
Jae Soon brought Ddol Ee home
because she wants to get a divorce.
Gab Soon's marriage isn't going
to happen no matter what.
What do you want me to do?
I'll be right there.
Joong Nyeon!
This is wrong.
My parents are expecting a lot from you.
You can't make a decision
like this on your own.
Answer your phone. Mother and
Grandfather are furious.
Why did you make it come to this far?
It's not like you.
(Voice Mail)
First message.
It's me. Let's meet.
I won't scold you or say anything.
Let me just see you.
Do you have something to say?
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to say?
I'll make sure to send you money...
You don't have to do this.
You don't have to.
Don't come in.
I don't know what to say.
I apologise.
I am sorry.
Saying sorry won't cut it.
You need to settle this situation.
I don't care about your
son quitting his job,
but it becomes a problem because
he's married to my daughter.
You understand what I mean, right?
I do.
You must've been so shocked.
He's my son,
but I'm very disappointed in him.
I don't know what happened,
but I believe...
he was going through a hard time.
He couldn't talk to you about it.
He was probably agonising
over it on his own.
Quitting his job without
discussing with you was...
a wrong thing to do.
He should've at least...
talked to you, if not to us.
We never knew what Se Gye was thinking.
He lied to us every morning and
said he was going to work.
This is different than handing
in a resignation letter.
How could he do that
without telling anyone?
I was really shocked.
How could he deceive us like that?
I had a feeling he would do that.
Smart people are the scarier kind.
Look how he deceived us.
You never know what he's going to do later.
I raised him wrong.
He's still young,
so please forgive him.
I'll talk to him and make him
return to the hospital...
You can return the clothes you bought.
Why not a person?
They didn't register their marriage anyway.
We can end this quietly.
Didn't they...
register their marriage?
No, they didn't.
We were going to when they have a baby.
Your call has been forwarded to...
What will you do?
It's my kid's problem,
so I'll take the responsibility.
How?
The reason you married your
daughter to my son was...
because...
of his job as a doctor.
Now he wants to quit being a doctor.
I'll leave it up to you to decide.
You should go home and take this back.
There's nobody who'd drink this.
- What did they say?
- They probably want a divorce.
He brought back the
liquor, so it's obvious.
You know how mean they are.
They must've shamed him. Poor Joong Nyeon.
I told them I'd leave it up to them.
I have no power.
We sent my son off to a rich family
so we can get some benefits.
We have no choice to
wait for their decision.
Where is Se Gye?
How can he take off after
doing such a thing?
I don't think he can work
up the courage to show up.
He's probably going
through a terrible time.
You know how he is.
He should've told us at least.
Whether it's quitting the
hospital or quit being a doctor,
he should've told his parents about it.
He's a smart guy. Why didn't
he know what would happen?
Did he become a doctor on his own?
Doesn't he know how hard his
parents worked to support him?
He's a really bad son.
- You should just kill him.
- What did he say?
You met him. Why didn't you beat him up?
I had no energy.
He'll tell us when he figures things out.
Jae Soon, I need to talk to you.
What happened?
I heard Geum Sik was here.
Why didn't you go?
I think I need to divorce him.
Did you take Ddol Ee into consideration?
If that's what you decided,
do what you want.
What are you doing?
You should scold her or something.
What do you mean, "do what you want"?
Geum Sik came here and begged.
Why is she being so stubborn?
It sounded like she misunderstood.
Leave her be. It happened before.
Will you let it happen again?
She blamed us for not stopping her.
She said she married him because of us.
Our children are adults now.
Just leave them be.
You should live your life.
He's right.
Your family doesn't need you any more.
Your children aren't yours.
Once they turn 20, they don't
listen to their parents any more.
Your 40-year-old daughter
won't listen to you.
Your smart doctor son won't listen to you.
Even that stubborn Gab Soon
doesn't listen to you.
Joong Nyeon now lives alone
because you're bothersome.
You're done now.
- Mal Nyeon!
- You'll wake Ddol Ee.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof.
The president is not in at the moment.
I raised my son wrong.
I'll leave it up to you to decide.
He didn't do anything right.
Why doesn't he even come home?
He hasn't even begged for forgiveness yet.
His family is all in on this.
They knew about it.
How couldn't they?
He quit because he thought
he didn't have to work.
He won't just live idly. He'll
have something else in mind.
How dare he!
He's so sly.
It's hot ginger tea.
He must've suffered so much
to quit such a good job.
I would've wanted to quit, too.
He sees patients all day in the hospital.
He comes home and does
his duty as a doctor.
She always says to him, "Don't
forget whose son-in-law you are."
He always talks to me very politely.
He seems to be raised properly.
I'm sure that's why he
became part of this family.
Talk to him carefully...
so that you can understand what happened.
- A divorce?
- Yes. You should be prepared.
Why do you always be like this?
Are you okay when he does
things without telling you?
There must be a reason for that.
He's not a bad person.
Be quiet. Our family needs a good person...
who can take care of all our possessions.
I didn't like him from the beginning.
Keep in mind what I just said.
Se Gye, where are you now?
Even though you don't see others,
you have to at least meet me.
We're a married couple, aren't we?
(Gong Joo)
(Answer your phone.)
- Gong Joo.
- Se Gye!
Where are you?
Come back home.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry to you.
I should have told you earlier.
I'm so sorry about that.
Just come home.
I'll protect you from whatever
Mum and Grandfather say.
Don't worry and come back home.
Have you eaten?
Where are you now? I'll go there.
No. Don't come.
And I ate something, so don't worry.
I'll go home when I feel okay.
Se Gye.
I miss you.
I'm hanging up, Gong Joo.
My family is all upset.
They're extremely mad.
What should you do?
My parents and in-laws are both shocked.
The shock is bigger than I expected.
I think so, too.
I didn't expect this,
but I feel sorry the most to Gong Joo.
Although we've been married for a year,
I never thought she's my life companion.
She was crying when we talked on the phone.
It hurt.
Of course that hurts and makes
you feel sorry for her.
This is all I have.
There're my house deed,
savings and shares in it.
I'll take all the
responsibility and step down.
I'll make sure there's
no harm to the company.
(President Jo Geum Sik)
Wait.
I'll let you go...
for my kids.
I guess I'm bad luck to you.
As I look back, nothing went
well for you since you met me.
This company got better
after you divorced me.
Now, you almost died because of me.
If anything wrong happens to you,
who will take care of my kids?
I don't think I can afford...
to send them to college and marry them off.
You should be with them.
You tried to save me even at
the moment of the accident.
I know you tried hard to save...
such a bad mother like me.
If I hadn't gotten in that car...
If we hadn't had a fight...
I'm sorry for all the trouble I caused.
Don't hire any random helper for the kids.
Tell her to come home.
I promise I'll never see my kids.
When they grow up and look for me,
I'll see them then.
Goodbye.
Cho Rong, Da Rong.
Don't you think this is too much?
How dare you come here?
Look who's talking!
I brought some side dishes for my kids.
Why did you come here when
Jae Soon stays at your home?
But it's still my son-in-law's house.
I'm the present mother-in-law...
who should take care of them.
- You're such a rude old lady!
- What?
You shouldn't see him
once he got remarried.
Why are you lingering around?
Is your daughter dumb?
What in the world are you talking about?
Who's dumb?
That's why even after she got divorced,
she's clinging to her remarried ex-husband.
If she loses her mind, you should
be in your right mind at least.
What on earth are you doing here?
Right! I'm not in my right mind. So what?
You remarried her off because he's rich.
What? Do you want me to teach you a lesson?
Bring it on!
It's here. It looks nice, doesn't it?
- Yes, it does.
- Please go in.
- Excuse me.
- Who are you?
I'm a real estate agent.
We came to see this house.
People live here, though.
What's going on?
- They moved out.
- Moved out?
- Where?
You can stop here.
Se Gye, what happened to you?
Have you eaten?
Be quite. That's not the problem here.
- Do you know what you've done?
- Be quiet.
I should scold him since he did wrong.
You should listen to me
while you live with me.
Follow me!
You quit the job because you didn't
like it, so I won't say anything.
But let me ask you one thing.
What are you going to do from now on?
You're smart. I'm sure you have a plan.
What do you want to do?
You probably didn't quit
to just hang around.
I just want to hang around.
What did you say? Did you say
you wanted to hang around?
- Did I hear it wrong?
- No, you heard it correctly.
I did say I just want to hang around.
Ever since I was young,
I've never enjoyed my life.
I'm not that smart.
In order to be a doctor
to please my parents,
I tried my best only to study.
I had to struggle to keep up with my study,
but I also had to work part-time.
So I've never played a video game...
nor have I been on a trip with my friends.
Because I didn't have enough money,
and I was busy with my work as well,
the trip to Jeju Island for
two days for my honeymoon...
was the first and the only trip I went on.
Have you not played any video games...
and not been on a trip?
Was the honeymoon really
the only trip you went on?
Change your clothes and wait
for me in front of the gate.
Follow me.
This is the wrong address.
- Take it back.
- All right.
Haven't you found him yet?
I don't have time. Please find him quickly.
You can't just hang around.
I don't acknowledge someone
who can't earn his own bread.
You must work in the morning.
This is our store that is
the closest to our house.
Start with cleaning,
organising the goods...
and managing employees.
Go to the clothing factory
to work once in a few days.
Start doing the basics including
from packaging to inventory control.
After that, you may do whatever
you want in the afternoon.
Try doing that for the time being.
Okay, Sir.
But I have a favour to ask of you.
I have to give living
expenses to my parents.
Make sure your work is worthy of that.
Thank you, Mr Yeo.
Where have you been?
Why?
Geum Sik has moved out.
Did you know that?
No, I didn't.
Why did you go there?
I went there to give some food to
the kids, but Gi Ja was there, too.
She's so thoughtless.
How could he move out without a word?
She went there without knowing that.
I think he moved out without
telling them, either.
I guess something bad happened to Geum Sik.
He even had an accident already.
He's getting so unlucky.
I should've been the one who got hurt.
Since I'm useless, I should've got hurt.
For my kids,
Geum Sik has to live long.
Did you finally grow up?
Anyway, where did he go
with the young girls?
I can't reach him.
He may have his reasons.
What kind of reasons?
Can't you tell what it means
that he suddenly moved out?
It's either he wanted to leave her...
or he went bankrupt.
I get scared when you say something.
Things pan out exactly as you say.
You may become a shaman at this rate.
Why don't you meet with him?
We should at least know what happened.
Please don't meet him. You don't have to.
He seems to have moved
out to break up with me.
So we don't need to meet him.
Is there anything wrong?
If you can't take care of our kids,
bring them to me.
I'm frustrated.
I can't take a shower because
the bathroom is too small.
You should've at least order Chinese food.
You should know better.
We should save even a penny.
This is for you. I poured water for you.
Geum Sik, did we have to
move into a place like this?
Please be quiet, Aunt.
I don't like this place, either.
I want to go home.
We have no other choice.
I used up all our money
to save the company.
Please endure even if it's uncomfortable.
I'll try my best to earn again.
A Young,
take care of my kids for the time being.
I have a packed schedule for my flight.
I should have a secure job at least.
Dad, don't worry and just work.
I'll take care of Da Rong.
Even when she was young, I changed
her diapers and fed her formula.
I technically raised her.
It's much easier now
since she grew up a lot.
Cho Rong, you're cheering me up.
- What about the money?
- What?
That money will be a big relief to us now.
Stop pestering me. Do you think
I'll not get it back to you?
- Aunt, eat ramyeon.
- I won't eat it.
Go ahead and eat.
Thank you, Cho Rong.
Take care of yourself and
don't worry about us.
I appreciate it.
- Go, Dad.
- Go.
This is our main item made
with ostrich leather.
The customer response is very good.
I see.
We're home.
Father, let's talk.
- Do you have something to say?
- Where have you been?
Why are you curious?
I've been to the shops and...
the factory with Se Gye.
You're not handing over our
company to him, are you?
He made the cut.
I'm 70 years old. I need
to decide the heir now.
What about me?
I've worked so hard under
your supervision...
for more than 20 years so far.
Though I didn't study much, I did
most of the work for the company.
I know the best about the company.
I can't give it up.
I tried hard to build my assets.
A smart person should take care of them.
I know much better about
how hard you tried.
You can't do as you like.
You're mean.
It's none of your business.
I was on your side so far,
but I can't be in this matter.
You're wrong this time.
You should know better.
I'm doing this for you...
so that you won't be left out.
In order to hand it over to you,
I need to take it over first.
If Se Gye starts to run this
company as your grandpa says,
you can't take the money.
You already know about the
financial situation of his family.
Both of his sisters are not doing well.
The whole family will rush
in to take the money.
You're taking his side
since he's your husband,
but we can only rely on each other.
We have to count on each other.
How much do you think
you can make with this?
If my eyesight were good, I
could string them quickly.
I did it.
It can ruin your eyes.
Drop it.
My son is delivering
water during the day...
and alcohol at night.
I have to earn even a little for him.
Are you quitting this for good?
Did you find a sponsor or something?
The sponsor of my life is me.
I want to change my field.
From entertainment to labour.
Are you going to do labour? I bet
you won't even last a month.
Just wait and see if I'll survive.
You told me about a chicken
restaurant a while ago.
You said your acquaintance
wants to sell it fast.
- Did he sell it?
- I'll call him.
The food is ready. Please enjoy it.
Hi. You're here.
- Hello.
You're not cut out for business.
I visited there, and it was so crowded.
Why would they sell a popular restaurant?
They have to go to the Philippines
to take care of their kids.
The decoration is nice, and I think
I could make quite a lot of money.
Mum,
can I please run that restaurant?
Do it if you have the money.
I want you to open it for me.
I don't have any money. Besides,
not everyone can do business.
You have to sacrifice
everything to run a business.
You can't do it because you
have a horrible personality.
You'll even drive your own customers away.
- I can do it.
- You'll go bankrupt in three days.
You said you're too weak to work.
How will you run your business?
If you won't help me, forget it.
I'll start it no matter what.
I know you're penniless. Why the big talk?
Besides, stop asking me for
money because I'm broke.
I know you have money.
I don't have it!
I know you hid money somewhere.
Even if everyone is broke, you'll never be.
You're so fierce.
I know you won't even share a penny.
I'm glad you're aware of that.
Enjoy your life alone.
You think your business will
flourish once the store is open,
but that's just your dream.
You can't even pour a cup
of water for yourself.
You'll only run into a
fight with your customer.
I'll be relieved if you don't
get locked up behind bars.
Stop cursing me!
What if I do well?
What are you doing?
I'm looking at today's sales report.
I'm also checking popular products.
Stop caring about such things
and clean up the boxes outside.
I already did.
Arrange the inventory, then.
I will.
I'm sorry.
Do you deliver water?
Yes.
Will you deliver it to my office as well?
How did it go?
Please find him as soon as you can.
I said I'm willing to pay
as much as it takes.
Do it as soon as you can.
You answered right away.
What are you doing?
I'm just hanging around.
I was worried about what I'd do,
but time passes so quickly.
Are you happy?
If you're happy, I'm happy, too.
Don't you miss me?
I'm sorry, I should've
mentioned that first.
Enjoy your freedom while you can.
Why didn't you tell me that you
hadn't registered your marriage?
I had already guessed,
but I learned how your in-laws
treat you after this incident.
I thought all my kids' matters
were resolved, but I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
I was at least going to tell you,
but I couldn't do it.
Since you already fell on the ground,
take a bit of rest and think.
Your aunt gave me this.
She got her living expenses
before all this happened.
She gave it to me in astonishment.
Give it back to her.
No, I'll still take care
of the living expenses.
Take it.
I told you there's no need
for the living expenses.
- Don't do this.
- Take it now.
Do you feel better now?
It breaks my heart that you suffered...
every time you went inside the OR.
I had no idea that you didn't
want to work as a doctor.
People have lingering feelings for
what they could not accomplish.
Since you only thought about
pursuing one career path,
look around for other options...
so that you won't regret it.
Do it while you're still young.
If I could live my life again, I
would've made the same decision.
I would've done everything I wanted to do.
Did your mother-in-law
want to give this to me?
Yes.
It feels like I earned
this by selling my son.
I didn't realise it when you were a
doctor, but now it feels like it.
Don't think like that.
From now on, I'll give
you the money myself.
No matter what I do,
I'll take care of your living
expenses, so don't worry.
This is what sons do.
Se Gye.
Can't you work as a doctor again?
People struggle so much
to become one, but you...
Take a break for a few days,
and go back to the hospital.
If you don't want to work for
that hospital, find another one.
Your dad didn't want me to say anything,
and I wasn't planning to say anything,
but I end up saying this...
because I feel so bad for you.
You struggled so much to
earn your medical licence.
I'm sorry I couldn't treat
you to a better place.
Don't worry.
I'm old-fashioned, so I
like places like here.
My favourite food is a home-cooked meal.
I'm sure it is.
I'm sorry my son...
upset you.
Besides, thank you...
for accepting him nonetheless
with a broad mind.
I'll have to wait and see,
but Se Gye is a smart guy,
so he will be good at anything.
Se Gye is now a member of my family.
Thank you.
There's no man in my family,
so he has to be the son.
You have daughters...
and a son-in-law as well.
You don't mind giving us your son, do you?
What are you doing?
I'm checking my blog.
Do you have any customers?
- No.
- Not even one customer?
No.
Do you really want to continue this?
Even you have to be so unsupportive?
At least, you should be
the son of our family!
You need to bring a smart son-in-law...
so that I can rely on him.
Seriously, I feel so lonely.
(Hope Loan Service)
I can't work full-time because
my son is still young.
Can I work only in the morning?
The supermarket is busier in the afternoon.
We need someone who can work all day long.
Should I?
Yes. You expanded the company,
so you should run the company.
I'm not in the right position to do so,
and I feel too bad to do that.
I'm reflecting on it as well.
I tried to expand it recklessly,
and that was the problem.
The company lost nothing from it.
You saved the company from going
bankrupt with your own assets,
so us, the shareholders, lost nothing.
We can't overlook how you
expanded the company this big.
You need to recover from
your loss last time.
If that's really what you want,
I'll start over from the sales position.
I'll start over from the bottom.
Let's decide over a general
shareholders' meeting.
Long time no see.
Are you leaving for a delivery?
Let's be comfortable with each other.
You make me feel awkward.
- Can we move out?
- No way.
There isn't any place like this...
that's so cheap and offers
some food sometimes.
Let's move to a nice place after saving up.
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
Never mind. See you later.
Don't work too hard.
If you get hurt, it'll cost
more than you earn. Got it?
That darn money!
Who on earth owns all the money?
Gosh, it's crazy.
I heard you had an accident.
Are you feeling all right?
The bone was fractured, so
it'll be okay as time goes by.
I'll take off the cast next week.
Thank goodness you're okay.
I heard you moved out. Where is it?
It's around the old place
because of my kids' school.
It's smaller than before, though.
Are you not doing well at all?
I had to use all my money...
and barely took care of it.
I didn't want to damage the
company I've been all in.
So did you quit?
I work as a sales manager.
I'll start over from scratch.
I wanted to see you...
to talk about my current situation.
Jae Soon didn't want to see me.
Actually, I'm in trouble.
I had to use all my savings
and sell the house.
I'm like this now,
so I can't even ask Jae Soon to come back.
If you had a child with him,
I would say you have to
support him by his side.
But since you decided to get a divorce,
I can't tell you to stay with him...
nor break up.
She can't go back because she came here...
before bad things happened.
No one will blame Jae Soon anyway.
I guess that's all the
luck Jae Soon's got...
since whoever she marries
would become broke.
- Mal Nyeon!
So do you live like that because
you only had that much luck?
Tell her to watch out her mouth already!
Before you talk,
just think it over at least once.
How could you spit it out
like a high-speed train?
Her words are even faster
than a high-speed train.
What's in your mind?
I wouldn't go back.
I didn't ask you.
What are you going to do?
I'll get a divorce.
(Seoul Prison)
What are you doing, Dad?
Nothing. Just go back to sleep.
Dad.
Why did you come out? Sleep more.
Dad, don't cry.
I'm not crying. Why would I cry?
I'm not crying.