(Episode 28)
Sit.
Excuse me?
There's no one here. Let's eat together.
What if somebody comes?
Nobody will come.
Listen to me while you work in this house.
Get yourself a bowl of rice and sit down.
Eat.
Nobody has ever boned a fish for me.
It's your first time?
Your husband never did this for you?
No.
My dad boned fish for me.
He raised me as a precious child.
But I guess I'm just unfortunate.
My husband was neither considerate nor was he a man of heart.
From now on, do everything with me if it's your first time.
Eat.
What are you doing?
When... When did you come home?
Ms Nam, what are you doing?
Why are you having a meal together with my dad?
When did you sit there?
I told you to bone my fish, not sit.
- From now on, be careful. - See?
You were too easy on her. That's why she sat to eat with you.
Be careful from now on.
I will.
Say, "Ma'am".
I will, Ma'am.
What a sight, really.
Bring a glass of juice to my room.
- Relief Patch. - Forget it.
"When did you sit there?"
I only sat down because you begged me to.
Who would have known that she'd come right at that moment?
I'll teach her a lesson.
Forget it!
Hello.
You must be Mr Yeo.
And you are?
Our sales is going up day after day. Thank you.
Can I ask you a favour?
Please conduct a survey for those who buy our product.
I'll use this information to produce a better product.
Leave it here.
- Thank you. - No problem.
- Da Rong. - Cho Rong!
I just washed Da Rong and gave her ramyeon.
Thank you, Cho Rong.
I'll be home as soon as I'm done.
I'd like to make an appointment tomorrow. Are you available?
Dad!
- Dad! - What's wrong?
- What's going on? - I finally have my first customer!
What happened?
Finally, someone wants my service. He wants me to clean tomorrow.
Good job.
Everyone, go back to sleep.
I thought you passed to be a teacher.
Ddol Ee almost woke up.
My goodness.
- It's clean. - Thank you.
In case there's something you're not satisfied with,
contact me within three days. I'll provide a follow-up service.
Here's your coupon.
If you use our cleaning service 10 times, the next one is free.
I'd really appreciate it if you spread the word.
It's my first income. I'd better post it on the wall.
Are you that happy?
Of course. When he texted me last night,
it felt like the door to paradise was opening.
I'm sorry I vented at you.
I'm okay with your venting any time.
You said that to help me, but I was all twisted.
Now, I'll save money, get an office and buy a car.
I could teach you how to drive.
Really?
Hold on.
Jae Soon.
Right, I totally forgot.
Hey.
Thank you.
If you ask for her service once a week, I'll buy you a nice meal.
You liked her service, right?
I told you she's good.
I better hang up now. Bye.
It looks delicious.
What's the matter?
I'm going to Sokcho.
I'll leave you with the kids and go relax.
How could none of our kids not know about how we feel?
Gab Soon was always stubborn, so she did as she pleased.
However, Jae Soon never defied me.
All of a sudden, she looked straight at me...
and said all the things to defy me.
It feels like I got my back, front and side stabbed.
I really want to resign from parenting.
I don't know where to set my mind.
Don't try to find a spot to set your mind. Just take care of yourself.
Leave your kids alone.
No kid follows their parents' wish.
We all used to be like that as kids, too.
- Are you leaving now? - There's someone I have to see.
I'll be back next week.
Let's go to court then.
Dad, can't you go to Sokcho tomorrow?
I called everyone over. Have dinner with us.
Did something happen?
What are you doing? Why aren't you coming?
Ta-da.
Is it someone's birthday?
It's no one in the family.
- I'm getting married. - Forget it.
Today's Mum and Dad's wedding anniversary.
Why bother remembering a day like this? It's bothersome.
It's not bothersome.
We all exist because you two got married, so it's a precious day.
That's right.
They went through thick and thin, but you were born thanks to them.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have seen the world.
I also forgot about it, but I knew because Jae Soon called.
She's s good at remembering these things including our birthdays.
She didn't even perform well at school.
She remembers all the useless stuff.
She wasn't all that bad. She was just average.
Thanks to Jae Soon, I remembered my wedding anniversary every year...
since she was in elementary school.
I never got a single card from my husband,
but she gave me cards congratulating my wedding anniversary...
for 30 years.
Blow the candle together.
Blow.
- Congratulations, congratulations - Congratulations, congratulations
- Happy wedding anniversary - Happy wedding anniversary
It isn't something grand enough to congratulate.
Thank you.
There are many parents who keep talking about getting a divorce,
but you two have always been great with each other.
Thank you.
Same here. Thank you, Mum and Dad.
My friend's parents got divorced when she was in high school.
She struggled a lot. She even ran away from home.
That's better than getting divorced later on.
There are many silly people who get divorced when they're old.
- Why is that silly? - Why is that silly?
You two always come at me together these days.
How sad that I don't have a husband.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Even if you're old, you can still get divorced.
If living with your spouse is too hard, you'd be better off alone.
I think Mum and Dad don't fight as much as other parents.
- You're right. - That's right.
They do fight.
After your dad retired, your mum always...
nags him and yells at him.
I have a present for you.
Surprise! It's matching t-shirts for you guys.
My goodness. Hey. Let me see that.
If he wears this,
he'll look 10 years younger.
Nae Shim. Why don't you hold it up to yourself?
Mum. What do you think?
- It looks good on you. - It's pretty. Yours, too, Dad.
You look like a happy couple.
Stop it. It's tacky.
I don't like people wearing matching clothes.
If you don't want to wear it, forget it.
- Hey. How do I look? - Yes?
I always follow your dad around,
so I should wear it instead.
Gosh. It's Mum's.
You little...
Here.
We bought this together. We thought you'd enjoy a trip to a hot spring.
They're tickets for a trip to a hot spring.
You can wear those matching t-shirts.
A trip may be too much. I'd prefer cash.
I don't need all that. I don't want to go on a trip with him.
What's wrong with you?
She must be drunk.
When did you drink so much?
She's been sipping on that for a while now.
I don't need any of you.
I've been holding myself back for you. Is this all I get?
- Go in. You're drunk. - Let go of me. I'm not drunk.
I'm just so upset and angry.
How can you do this to me?
- I don't need any of you. - Stop. This is a happy occasion.
Happy occasion, my foot.
Tell me. What on earth did I do wrong?
I just wanted you to succeed. Do you hate it that much?
You told me not to care about you.
You told me to live my life and not cling onto you.
- Stop it. - Listen, Shin Joong Nyeon.
- Mum. - Mum.
Goodness.
I don't need you all. Just go.
This is my house. I don't want any of you to come.
I'll live by myself. You should all just go.
Why on earth should I give you 50 percent of it?
Nae Shim. Let's go in.
Don't. I'll do it.
Don't mind us. You can go if you want to.
Come here.
We had an anniversary party when we're divorced.
Are you happy now?
It'd be great if we go to a hot spring in those matching t-shirts.
I need to talk to you.
- Keep your voice down. - Shin Joong Nyeon.
You can tell me now.
What on earth did I do wrong?
Is this what I get after...
taking care of all of you for 40 years?
I've always fed you even if I had to starve.
All I have now is this broken body.
Why are you all doing this to me?
Don't you need me any more?
I couldn't even say anything when I was sick because you'd worry.
I'm not made of iron.
I get sick, too.
I'm left with nothing.
I feel so empty and so dejected.
Goodness.
Did they go home?
After Nae Shim got so upset,
they went out to have a drink by themselves.
They didn't hear her cry. Don't worry.
I made them leave right away.
Go to sleep. We should go back to Sokcho tomorrow.
Joong Nyeon.
You divorced her, didn't you?
What's wrong with Mum?
Did something happen?
I don't know.
Maybe she didn't like our present.
We should've given them cash.
Mum likes money.
Maybe Mum and Dad had a fight.
I hardly stay home these days, so I don't know what's going on.
I didn't see them fight.
I've never seen Mum so angry.
I guess you haven't seen it,
but we've seen it a few times.
Mum is acting strange these days.
It's because of me.
I upset her, too.
I guess it's because of us.
Mum. You seemed drunk last night. Are you okay?
I made bean sprouts soup. Do you want to eat it now?
No.
Dad went to Sokcho with Aunt this morning.
I'm not getting enough customers as it is.
Did you have to come today?
I know.
Your business is going badly, but we come and try to find faults.
It's terrible, isn't it?
I'll come in this Sunday and help you clean.
Actually, I can't. I have a blind date that day. I'm sorry.
Gosh. You're so sly.
I called a cleaning company already.
We don't want to do this,
but it's directly connected to people's health. We have no choice.
There she is.
Hello. I'm here to clean.
Are you here to clean?
You must do a thorough job.
You should satisfy her.
Okay.
Let's go. Ma'am. I hope your business goes well.
You two look good together. Is he a new employee?
Why bother going on blind dates?
If you say so, I'll think about it.
Goodbye.
- Let's go. - Have a good day.
Ma'am. Where should I start?
Gab Dol. Can I talk to you for a minute?
All of our friends are saying bad things about you.
You know that, right?
Are you going to leave Gab Soon like that?
You're a man. You should take care of her.
I know your mum doesn't like her,
but be a man about it.
You said you'd marry Gab Soon once you become a public official.
We're all witnesses.
Did you change your mind?
It's not that. You know it.
You're always with your female senior officer these days.
- Are you two together? - We're not.
I just work with her.
You're with a public official. Gab Soon is with a rich playboy.
What is this? This isn't what I wanted to see.
What are you going to do?
Is she always with that guy?
People think they're together.
Gab Soon. Are you busy? Can I see you later?
I'm busy today. I have a cleaning job at night.
We can't keep doing this.
Let's meet. I have something to say to you.
You can't make personal calls during work hours.
I'll see you later.
Ma'am. I know we have a to clean at night,
but something urgent came up at home. Can I come back later?
We need to finish it by tomorrow morning, right?
We should finish it by tonight.
They're going to move in here early in the morning tomorrow.
I know. I'll finish it later tonight.
Get in. I found a great restaurant. They make spicy stir-fried octopus.
I can't. I already have plans.
- What plans? - Don't ask questions.
Do you need a ride?
Gab Dol. We've got urgent work.
The chief needs it by tomorrow morning.
- I have plans. - Ms Kim. Hurry up.
Yes, Sir. Let's go.
The person you're trying to reach is not available.
(Dongsan District Office)
- Can I use the restroom? - Make it quick.
I'm working late because of urgent work.
Public officials work overtime, too.
It's hard to keep up with everyone.
I'm so sorry.
I've been so busy that I couldn't even go to the restroom.
What did you order?
I ordered one pork rib soup for each.
You worked hard today, so let me pay the bill.
No. We should pay the bill separately.
I didn't order one. I should head home.
Okay, then. Great work today.
Thank you. Bye.
Are you done already?
- With what? - Pork rib soup.
I left without eating. How did you know?
I saw you.
I'm sorry for earlier.
You could've texted me that you'll be working late.
Don't you even have time to go to the restroom?
I shivered in the cold on the street for two hours.
I hate that we always have to meet up outside.
Let's meet at warm cafes from now on.
I was just so used to meeting you outside.
I couldn't clean, and I had to work hard alone because of you.
I rejected someone who wanted to take me to a great restaurant...
just so I could see you.
A great restaurant?
What's wrong with that guy? I can take you there, too.
I spared my valuable time.
Time isn't only valuable to public officials like you.
It's also valuable to cleaners like me.
Also, I'm disappointed in you.
Do I embarrass you?
When I went to the restaurant to clean, you ignored me.
I just thought you'd be embarrassed.
You didn't say anything, so I kept quiet, too.
You kept quiet because you thought I'd be embarrassed?
You just assumed that I'd be embarrassed of myself.
I'm not.
After seeing your mother, I've changed.
I won't be embarrassed any more.
Now that you're a public official, do you think the world is yours?
Let me ask you one thing.
Are you in a relationship with her?
What's wrong with everyone?
It's not like that.
You saw it. We were just working.
Your mum would like her.
She's a public official who will get pensions.
Do you work with her at night, too?
You were alone with her at the restaurant.
We weren't alone. We were with other employees, too.
You don't have to explain.
I heard guys have changed.
You used to judge girls by their looks, but now it's their jobs.
I'm sorry, but I still judge girls by their looks.
I love pretty girls.
And to me, you're the prettiest girl.
You may not know, but you've changed.
I haven't changed. I'm the same person!
Why does everyone say that I've changed?
You said you had something to say to me.
There isn't anything to say, right?
I want to break up with you, too.
But we've been together for 10 years.
I hate myself for being like this.
I think about breaking up with you dozens of times a day,
but I can't bring myself to do it. I hate myself for that.
Do you have any idea how I feel?
You deny it,
but it's sad to watch you change.
Ddol Ee is getting much better and stabler.
Thank you.
He should continue with the treatment.
You should stay strong for him as well.
Okay. I will.
Does that mean I can work morning shifts?
Yes. If we're busy, you can work during the afternoon as well.
- I can do that. - You can start from tomorrow.
Thank you.
Mum.
This phone is turned off. You'll be directed to voice mail.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Gab Soon.
Mum isn't home?
Where did she go?
Her coat and handbag are gone, too. She's not answering her phone.
She has never done anything like this before.
Mum has been strange these days. I'm so worried.
There should be a notepad in Mum's drawer.
Her friends' numbers are in there. Call them. I'll be right there.
Okay.
(Divorce Application Form)
I don't need any of you.
I've been holding myself back for you. Is this all I get?
Listen, Shin Joong Nyeon. I don't need you all. Just go.
Get out. I don't want to see you. Get out!
I don't want any food.
Do you know how I feel?
Jae Soon. What happened?
Where is Mum? She won't answer my calls, either.
I'm scared that she might do something terrible at this rate.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
What's wrong with Mum these days?
- Mum. - Mum.
Why are you so happy to see me?
Where have you been?
I came home in the middle of cleaning because you went missing.
Where have you been? Why is your phone off?
You're making a big fuss.
Why do you care where I go?
Is everything okay? Are you all right?
You should've told us. Where have you been?
Do I have to report every place I go to you?
I didn't even do that to your dad.
What's wrong?
Can't I go around outside?
- It's not that. - Tell us where you've been.
I went out to get some fresh air.
I heard that my friends who have money and time...
go to art museums or galleries from time to time.
I went there to take a look.
I didn't know you go to art museums.
Can't I go? Am I too crude to go to places like that?
I didn't mean that.
You look classy when you dress up.
She's right. My friends asked me if you were a teacher.
Did you have fun? What did you see?
I don't get what's so great about it.
Maybe I'm too ignorant. I didn't understand what it meant.
I guess someone like me wouldn't understand art.
I've never been to an art museum.
I had no time for that.
I don't really get it, either.
It's fine as long as it's good to look at.
You don't have to interpret its meaning.
Maybe you should've gone to a theatre.
She's right. There are so many good movies these days.
That place is no different. How can I go alone?
Many people go alone.
It would be nice to have Dad around.
Dad's been in Sokcho for too long. Should I tell him to come?
- Leave him be. - Leave it.
He's already there. Why bother?
Mum, let's go together next time.
Gab Soon, you should go back to cleaning.
All right.
Don't do this again, Mum.
Tell us if you're going somewhere.
You make me nervous these days.
- Have you eaten yet? - I'm not hungry.
Do you have something to say?
- No. - I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry.
Hey!
You!
Stop there!
A Young, wait!
I'll give it back. I will.
You didn't use the money, right?
- I haven't. Well, not much. - "Not much"?
Give it to me.
I kept it because it would be dangerous for you to have it.
Don't misunderstand me.
Look.
- Where did it go? - You!
Wait!
It was here a minute ago. I'm not lying.
It was right here when I walked into the office.
I'm sorry.
What will we do?
My goodness.
Hello.
Jae Soon, you're in charge of the special offer products.
Pardon?
The special offer eggs over here are three dollars.
The other products over there are over four dollars.
You need to sell these in an hour.
Could you tell me how?
Buy some eggs.
Eggs are on sale for three dollars.
Eggs are sale for three dollars.
Buy some eggs.
How could you not sell even one until now?
You need to sell all of the special offer products in an hour.
Excuse me.
My goodness.
Everyone! Eggs are here!
Come and see the delicious looking eggs.
They're only 3 dollars. Only 3 dollars!
- I'll take one. - Give it to her.
- Okay. - I'll have two trays.
Here you go.
- I'll take one. - Here it is.
- I'll have that one. - Here.
I can't eat.
I'm worried about them.
I don't even know where they moved.
I'm worried sick.
Just ask them like you always do.
Ask them where they moved and if they've eaten.
Don't.
Geum Sik, it's me.
What happened? I heard you moved.
Yes.
I didn't have the time, so I couldn't tell you.
Where did you move to?
You didn't move far because of the kids' school?
Of course. Are the kids all right?
What happened to the company?
Hello?
I guess he isn't doing so well. He hung up.
Maybe he went bankrupt.
Let me give you a piece of advice. Mind your own business.
Don't call him again.
Hello?
Now?
I'll be right there.
Where are you going? I thought you were taking a rest.
My client wants me. You should go to bed.
Take care of your health.
It's ready.
Thank you.
Please call me again whenever you're out of water.
I'll get going now.
It's important to set it at the right temperature.
You'll know it by the sound.
- A glass of beer, please. - Okay.
I'll go get it for them.
Geum Soo Jo.
It's nice to see you here.
- Are you in charge of this place? - Yes.
I'm taking over this place.
- Are you starting a business? - Yes. Isn't it a great idea?
Don't you think I'll do a good job?
It's better than working at karaoke.
Say hello when you stop by.
- A bottle of soju, please. - Okay.
Where have you been?
I went to train for the job.
It's not easy to fry chicken.
There isn't anything that can be done easily.
- Are you really going to do that? - I will.
I'm going to earn money and bring the kids here.
Dream on.
Don't worry about others. Worry about yourself first.
I've attracted investors.
What kind of lunatic would invest in you?
It's a secret.
He must be filthy rich to waste money like that.
What does he see in you?
You wait and see! I'll surprise you.
Mum.
What is it?
I made some kimchi pancakes. You haven't eaten dinner yet.
Why? Do you feel sorry...
after making me worry all this time?
I am sorry.
- Where's Gab Soon? - She's at her cleaning job.
Mum.
I saw the papers.
Your divorce papers.
I found it in your drawers.
Why did you look through my drawers?
Why did you have to do that?
It's a shock that you and Dad are getting a divorce.
I'm a divorcee myself, but I never imagined this.
Can I ask why?
Did Dad do something wrong?
Of course, only the two people involved would know.
You must have had your reasons for wanting a divorce.
But there's no good in getting a divorce now.
Mum. Cancel it now when you can.
I don't want you to live alone.
I don't want people to see you as a divorcee.
You must not know reality.
It's amazing that you're with the man you married for the first time.
You came this far already.
That's only what you kids think.
My friends' parents also got a divorce at an old age.
The kids are having a hard time.
They only meet on family events.
Others call them a "family event couple".
The kids are also living all apart. They don't even meet often.
They make two trips to see each parent.
They feel like they're not a family any more.
Parents are the ones who hold the family together.
I don't want our family living like that.
You're all being selfish.
Look. Even until now, you're trying to...
stop us from living our lives just for your own sake.
It's not because of that.
What good will come of getting a divorce now?
Dad must have been shocked.
What did he say?
Did he agree to the divorce?
It's just like what your aunt says.
I tried to keep my husband under control,
but I've been betrayed.
He's the one who wants a divorce.
Dad is the one who wants a divorce?
Yes.
I always thought that if we do get a divorce,
it would be me giving him the papers.
Your dad is one scary man.
He got everything ready then gave me the papers.
He filled in everything himself.
That's the kind of person your dad is.
He fooled me for 40 years.
He'll be here next week to file it.
If we're going to get a divorce, we should get it over with.
Until then, don't tell your brother and sister.
We should go to Seoul.
- Aren't you going? - No.
- Does she want a divorce? - What?
Yes.
Even if she says she wants a divorce, you should have said no.
What will you do at this age?
If our parents were alive, they would be shocked.
She's one cold-hearted woman.
If you lived together for 40 years, she should keep living with you.
What good is she trying to get from kicking you out?
She'll be punished.
Don't say that.
She put up with me for a long time.
Put up with what?
And why are you giving her half your wealth?
What did she do to deserve that?
That's enough.
Don't try to meddle in others people's business.
Maybe she has a man.
Look at him. He looks anxious.
Excuse me. Are you here alone?
Would you like some?
No thanks.
You're beautiful.
You must have been very popular in your younger days.
Se Gye, what are you up to?
You're free for dinner these days, right? Do you want to have dinner?
I have dinner plans.
Let's take a rain check.
Or should I reschedule?
There's no need. If you have plans, we can eat another time.
Okay, bye.
- I'm back home. - Hey.
Do you want to eat out tonight? It's on me.
Ddol Ee got invited to a friend's birthday party.
- I see. - Let's wear something nice.
- Gab Soon. - Yes?
Let's have dinner tonight.
I'm on a night shift tonight. I'll be home late.
All right. Get back to work.
I don't know if I made the right decision.
I'm trying not to think about it. I'm enjoying my time these days.
I work in the morning.
Where have you been?
I don't make plans. I just get in the car and drive around.
If I find a nice place,
I get out, take photos, and enjoy the view.
Then I have a local meal...
like sundae-gukbap and jjinppang.
You're living your dream. I'm jealous.
You're jealous, right?
You don't think of me, do you?
I'm not used to not seeing you everyday.
It's hard.
Since I could see you everyday,
the fact that you were married didn't hit me hard.
It was the same for me.
What's gotten into me?
Let's drink up.
Don't bother doing that. You have poor eyesight.
You'll hurt your back if you sit down for so long.
I'll earn more money.
It's fine.
When I think of you moving water bottles and beer barrels,
I feel the need to earn more.
This work brings in good income.
The small one is worth 50 cents and the big one is worth 70 cents.
It's fun. Time flies when I'm stringing these beads.
- How many have you done? - Two.
That makes 1 dollar and 20 cents already.
I can make money for instant noodles.
Finish this and don't ever do this again.
Speed up. The chairman will come for inspection.
My goodness.
I didn't want to run into you like this.
You still didn't no need to break off all contact.
I'll take any punishment you decide to give me.
How do you want to be punished?
Whatever you decide is fine.
You know I'm a bad man, right?
I do.
You made me believe a song was your poem.
Do you know I'm penniless?
I do.
Do also you know that I've never went out with a woman?
I should highlight that.
Have you really never gone out with a woman before?
That explains it.
The man that ran away without paying the rent...
is me.
I'm that scrooge.
You are unbelievable.
Can I sleep over for the night?
Half of this house is my brother's.
How did you come? What about Dad?
I have something to say. Have a seat.
- What's the matter? - Sit down if you did nothing wrong.
I sat. What do you want?
Do you have a man?
- Aunt. - Leave her. Let's hear her out.
My brother never cheated on you, beat you, or gambled.
How could you ask for a divorce?
Jae Soon, what do you think?
Since your the oldest, you must have an opinion about this.
Do you think it's right for your dad to get asked for a divorce?
Aunt, you should stay out of this. It's their business.
I see.
So I guess you're all on your mum's side.
Don't be like that. You'll be punished.
You should be thankful that my brother's a kind man.
What has your mum done to receive half of his wealth?
Have you lost your conscience?
Aunt. It's normal to split the wealth in half these days.
You should think twice.
What do you mean Mum did nothing?
She did more than she ever had to.
She supported Dad and raised us three kids.
She did good to your parents and Uncle as well as you.
She even took care of Grandma and Grandpa when they were sick.
What do you think would have happened without her?
Can that be counted with money?
You shouldn't say that as a woman. That's being ignorant.
What did you say? Ignorant?
Dad went through a lot, but Mum did as well.
I understand why she wants a divorce.
Don't butt in.
If you're going to be like this, don't come here.
My goodness.
Your kids are on your side.
It's a great thing that you're wanting a divorce.
If you let my brother go earlier,
he would have lost less hair. I'm sure of that.
Yes, don't you worry.
I'll cut off clean.
Mum.
My gosh.
Didn't you go to bed?
I came out for a glass of water.
You had a glass of water earlier.
Why did you come all the way here?
I didn't think I should tell you this over the phone.
I want to speak to you in person.
Is it urgent?
I saw your divorce papers.
I heard you asked Mum for a divorce.
Why did you do that?
It's between me and your mum, so don't worry about it.
Do your siblings know?
Only I saw it.
I'm still in shock.
I don't think they'll be able to handle it.
It's not exactly the same,
but I know how shocking it must have been for you when I got divorced.
Mum doesn't know that I am here.
I always thought Mum would be the one to ask for a divorce.
She had to hold back so much.
Grandma treated her poorly when she married you,
and she took care of Grandpa when he was hospitalised.
She raised your younger siblings...
and married them off.
Why did you do that?
You at least had your time outside when you worked,
but she never got recognised for what she did.
She dedicated her life to being our mum and your wife.
I've been living as a housewife,
so I know how she feels.
It's tiring to be a working mum,
but you still keep your identity.
I thought you'd understand.
How do you think...
Mum would have felt when you asked her for a divorce?
I respect you,
but I don't think this is right.
It makes a difference whether you initiated the divorce or not.
Couldn't you have let Mum...
keep her pride?
I think I would be sad and furious.
She sacrificed her whole life for the family,
but all she gets is divorce papers from her own husband.
Mum can't even sleep without alcohol.
It's been a while since you've been outside, right?
I hope you're more at ease now.
It must have been hard for you.
I feel bad for your husband,
but it worked out for the best.
They say the dead are the ones who are at loss. I guess it's right.
Life still goes on for the ones who are still alive.
Even after my husband died, I was able to eat and sleep.
Your children are all just useless.
Your husband is the best.
It's not like we were the happiest couple,
but it feels like one of my arms fell off.
I'm...
really all alone now.
When he was bedridden, we argued so much.
I told him to die...
instead of...
making me suffer.
You did everything you can.
Anybody would have said that after doing that for seven years.
It's difficult to take care of someone for a long time.
Even a year or two is difficult.
We all think you're incredible.
Do you know...
what I regret the most?
I've never told him...
how sorry or thankful I was.
He worked all his life to support the family and raise the kids.
I never thanked him for it.
I regret that the most. It pains me deeply.
I should have told him.
You should be thankful that your husband is healthy.
If you have something to say, tell him when it's not too late.
He'll never know if you don't say it.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
Do you know what I regret the most?
I've never told him how sorry...
or thankful I was.
Nae Shim, don't be like that.
Do Geum, where were you?
Look, it's a baby.
Please raise him well.
His birthday is December 3.
What are you going to do? You can't even feed yourself.
As soon as I looked at him,
I had the urge to live.
Look at him. Isn't he cute?
Ms Nam.
Can you make me seaweed soup for breakfast tomorrow?
Is it somebody's birthday?
It's my precious son's birthday.
Please make it with beef.
Here you go.
Don't bother. I'll make seaweed soup.
Thank you, Ms Nam.
Can you make some side dishes with meat, too?
Bulgogi would be good.
Hurry. Hurry up.
Don't rush me.
Soo Jo has to leave for work. I have to feed him now.
Eat before you go. It's warm seaweed soup.
Ms Nam made bulgogi as well.
I can just get some gimbap.
You can't starve on a day like this.
Today's your birthday.
- Eat up. - Really?
Happy birthday, my son.
Did you ask her to make seaweed soup?
Of course.
Eat.
- You should eat, too. - Okay.
What's that?
Open it.
Those are your mum's shoes.
Did she die?
Did you find him?
Tell me.
They went bankrupt soon after,
so they moved 30 years ago.
And then what happened? Where did they go?
Their entire family...
moved to Bongcheon-dong.
Bongcheon-dong?
They haven't updated their address, so it's difficult to find them.
It took me over a week...
just to find out that they moved to Bongcheon-dong.
Hurry up. Did you find him or not?
All I know is that he attended elementary school there.
He attended elementary school?
What about now?
They moved again to Miari. We're looking for them.
I have three of my guys on it.
It's not easy finding people.
Please, find him.
He must be alive, right? He has to be.
He was definitely alive at least until elementary school.
Let's go.
Cho Rong, I want this.
I'll make you ramyeon at home. It'll be delicious.
I'll add green onions and an egg.
No, I want this.
I'll give you a piggy back.
Cho Rong.
I heard you moved.
How are you?
Is Da Rong sick?
No, she fell asleep.
Okay. Go on, then.
Ms Shin.
Can you please come back?
Cho Rong!
Lucky you.
Look at you all carefree and going to the sauna.
I feel sorry for my brother who got kicked out.
You made up your mind, so don't drag this on.
Give him his share of the asset. Let him enjoy his life, too.
Our trip to Jeju Island got scrapped because of Nae Shim.
Going to the sauna is good enough.
Did you bring your towels?
- Of course we did. - Of course we did.
We can't forget our towels.
Exactly.
Where are you, Nae Shim? We're all here.
I won't be able to join. I have a family emergency.
I hope you enjoy yourselves.
One ticket to Sokcho, please.