(Waiting for Godot)
(Episode 3)
We're ready. Please step out.
What is all this?
It's a building completion ceremony.
Building completion ceremony?
A ceremony to celebrate the completion of a building.
It's not even their house.
- Please take a photo of us.
-  Okay.
We will now begin the building completion ceremony ritual.
Due to time constraint,
we will skip the salute to national flag and national anthem.
Go on.
We will now cut the tape.
After we cut the tape, please give a big hand.
Let's begin.
In 3, 2, 1.
That's not even funny.
Don't drink and come home early.
You should have used a pig's head.
It's not because of money issues.
We could buy twelve of those.
Don't get us wrong.
We don't belong in a house like this.
I used to...
We never used to belong in a house like this.
Even my son's name is Geum Soo Jo,
which means he was born with a golden spoon.
Do you remember my name? You saw it when I signed the contract.
Geum Do Geum.
I have two characters that stand for gold in my name.
Whatever. Just make sure to pay your rent on time.
We've already paid for the toilet fee.
What are you talking about?
Toilet fee.
She should have given me the money.
I think we made a mistake in letting them in.
What golden spoon?
What kind of a name is Geum Do Geum?
They're Geum Do Geum Soo Jo.
They don't seem like bad people.
Don't you even talk to them. You belong in a different pool.
Don't you think things will work out?
I think we'll do well in this house.
The daughter in the main building seems great.
Women without money has no charm.
She seems tawdry.
- What are you waiting for?
-  Godot.
What's Godot?
My goodness.
Let's tell our parents first.
No. You know how things are.
They'll be disappointed.
Gab Dol needs to know. He's the father.
No. He'll run away.
Then what do you want to do? You must have a plan.
I don't know. I really don't know.
My mind has gone completely blank.
I can't think of anything. I don't want to think.
- What can we do?
-  I think I might lose my mind.
Could you bring my phone from the house?
Don't get caught.
Is nobody home?
Okay, Mum.
No. I was just asking. Okay.
My goodness.
What?
Aunt.
It's not what you think it is.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof.
I can fix it.
Hello.
Jae Soon.
What's becoming of her?
Why did she say hello?
Jae Soon.
- Mum.
-  Why did you come?
I told you that I wasn't home.
I was in the area. I came to see what food you made.
Food?
Come to think of it, I need to make food for Gab Soon.
- When do you have time?
-  Why would you go there?
Why not?
Don't go. I don't have time either.
Then I'll go on my own.
I said, don't go.
You'll only get in the way of her studying.
It's not like she can't study because she can't eat.
Why would the whole family go there? There's no point in going there.
Why do you think she chose to go?
You are no help. She doesn't need food.
Am I right or wrong?
You're suddenly so logical.
Did you take speech lessons?
I made such a scene to get this.
- Did you get caught?
-  Who do you think I am?
I'm good at things like this.
You must be hungry. Let's eat something.
I'm not hungry.
Oh gosh. Hide.
Why?
Run!
Wait.
Gab Soon. Jae Soon.
Gab Soon.
- It hurts.
-  Oh my.
Gab Soon.
What should we do?
Pretend you didn't see her.
She saw us.
She's alone. We have each other.
Being stubborn will solve it all.
Think things out while staying here.
- Are you here to pay?
-  I'll pay with card.
I'd like to pay for a week in advance.
(President Jo Geum Sik)
(Approved: 77 dollars at Fire Dry Sauna)
I'm home.
You must be hungry. Go take a quick shower.
It smells good.
I made bulgogi.
Do you want to try?
How does it taste?
I made it a bit sweet for the kids.
It's tasty.
You're a great cook.
Did you go somewhere today?
No. Why?
Never mind. Let's eat dinner. I'm hungry.
What?
You're talking nonsense.
Say something.
Mal Nyeon. Are you going to keep like this?
I saw her.
She's in the temple studying. Why would she be in Seoul?
How would I know?
Gab Soon and Jae Soon ran away as soon as they saw me.
Don't be daft.
I'm not.
I guess Gab Soon couldn't handle the pressure here,
so she went to the temple.
But she couldn't concentrate on her studies over there either.
She couldn't concentrate in the first place.
I bet she came here because of Gab Dol.
How could she not? They dated for 10 years.
Jae Soon.
Did you see your aunt at the dry sauna today or not?
What are you talking about?
Why would I go there?
Your aunt insists that...
she saw you and Gab Soon at the dry sauna.
It's driving me crazy.
What's wrong with her?
Don't mind her. I didn't go.
Gab Soon's studying hard in the temple.
She says that she never went.
I thought you've gotten better.
What's wrong with you?
They can't fool me.
Go to the temple. I bet Gab Soon isn't there.
Do something with your sister.
- Mal Nyeon.
-  My goodness.
If you're like this, I'm really all on my own.
I'm the one on my own.
You wait and see.
We'll hear weeping soon.
Give up on Gab Soon.
I've seen plenty of parents weeping because of their child.
I've been through it all. I sure have.
Hey!
Please tell her to leave.
I don't need her money. Send her away.
Don't mind her. Just ignore her.
I can't ignore her.
It's not the first time she's made a fuss like this.
What she says comes true.
I'm in Seoul. Let's meet.
I'm pregnant.
- I thought you quit playing games.
-  Starting tomorrow.
Have you quit studying?
I would love to but I can't.
Gab Soon went to the temple to study. What are you doing?
What if Gab Soon passes?
She'll break up with you instantly.
Don't you know her?
She's firm.
She can't break up with me.
There's no man like me.
She must have done good deeds in her past life.
How arrogant.
You look lively.
I'm so happy now that...
I don't have to hear Gab Soon's nagging.
Gab Dol's day without Gab Soon.
What are you doing here?
I came to buy some books.
Why did you come all the way here?
I could've sent you the books if you called.
I'm studying so hard.
I've quit everything else.
Have you gained weight?
What are you talking about?
I'm just kidding.
Why are you drinking milk?
I'm fed up with coffee.
Don't you want something to drink?
Nobody's forcing us. Let's just stay with one drink.
I don't have any money.
What's the matter?
I'm concerned about my friend that I met earlier.
- Which friend?
-  Somebody.
She has a boyfriend.
They didn't even discuss about getting married,
but she's pregnant.
And her boyfriend is unemployed.
That sounds suffocating.
Look at the news.
Unemployed people are five times less likely to get married.
What's wrong with your friend?
She should have been careful.
Didn't they use contraceptives?
It was a mistake.
That's too big of a mistake.
What did you tell her?
I told her to talk it out.
There's nothing to talk about. They need to break up.
Break up? They have a baby.
- Would you if it were you?
-  Of course.
I hate those kind of women who are inconsiderate of their men.
Think about it.
She's pregnant and asks him to be responsible when he has no job.
That's dragging him down.
All men will be aghast.
I don't even want to think about it.
How could you be exactly as I predicted you would be?
I was a fool to have wanted to talk with you.
Why are you like that?
You must feel too connected to your friend.
Can't you be more humane?
Aghast?
I'm being realistic.
Quit meeting friends like her.
Meet sophisticated friends.
I'm sorry I don't meet your standard.
You're going to finish your drink, right?
You're leaving?
My mum wants me to receive a parcel.
It's marinated crab. I need to put it in the refrigerator right away.
I'll go see you in the temple sometime.
You won't be able to see me.
You must be studying hard.
Don't you pass by yourself.
I'll be off.
Heo Gab Dol.
I wasn't talking about my friend. I was talking about me.
Say it again.
It's about you?
Not me. It's about us.
Look me in the eyes and tell me.
I'm sorry that I'm a low-life...
who's pregnant when you are unemployed...
and dragging your life down.
What are we going to do?
Spend it well, Nae Shim.
Do you mind transferring the money to my account from now on?
Transfer?
I meant money transfer. You can send it directly to my bank account.
I've never done it before.
This is inconvenient for both of us.
That's something you have to deal with.
I don't want your family to go hungry.
I'm just joking.
Isn't it nice that we get to meet each other once a month?
We can come out for a coffee and look elegant.
Hotel coffee tastes different, right?
I don't think this is my type. I'll get going.
Why don't you stay? I'm sure you don't get these chances often.
I don't have time lying around.
I have errands to run. Bye.
You must have been making kimchi before you came out.
Oh dear.
You're back.
What a bossy woman!
I made my son a doctor and look what I'm doing.
How much money did we pour into him during six years of medical school?
She gives me less than 2,000 dollars and she goes,
"Spend it well, Nae Shim."
"You must have been making kimchi before you came out."
She calls me by name and speaks low of me all the time.
She's years below me.
This is all your fault.
We wouldn't be in this situation if you took good care of the pension.
You should go and get the money from next month.
Nae Shim. Drink some cold water and cool down.
Here. Don't abuse your precious husband.
Why are you not speaking out for yourself?
You should speak to your in-law like when you talk to Joong Nyeon.
Mal Nyeon, don't say anything. She'll get more upset.
Leave. Both of you, leave.
My goodness.
I have a headache.
Are you daydreaming?
Why do you do that once in a while?
You had stellar grades in school and you're very skilled,
but I don't understand you sometimes.
Tell me what the problem is.
There's nothing wrong.
How did you know to find me here?
I just had a hunch. You have something to say, right?
No, I don't.
I think you do.
Tell me what it is.
Let's have a drink later. It's on me.
What? What did you do?
I was clueless...
and I was crazy enough to do anything I can to support you.
Would you accept yourself as a son? You punk!
Why are you here, Relief Patch?
I don't have relief patch on me today.
I told you I don't need a caregiver.
Are you going to leave me up to the caregiver and roam around?
You do it. You!
But I can't give you a bath.
Do I have to give him a bath?
I'm just saying. He can do everything on his own.
He just gets anxious when nobody else is home.
- I see.
-  I don't need her. Send her back.
Dad, you fired the housekeeper so imagine if I left for grocery.
What if something happens to you during that time?
What was it? Was it five minutes?
They can't save you after a certain time. You never know what'll happen.
- Did you do a background check?
-  Sorry?
Is she trustworthy?
I did a check. She has no criminal record and she was never a spy.
Has she ever been a caregiver?
- I haven't...
-  She's done it a lot, Dad.
- What about certification?
-  I'm planning to get one.
Why would you trust a person who's not even certified?
If something goes wrong with me, will she take responsibility?
You can't trust people these days. Why would you bring a random person?
You are being too harsh right in front of my face.
I'm not just a random person.
Money doesn't give you the right to look down on others.
Fire her right away.
You can't fire me without hiring me.
I came all the way sacrificing my time.
Pay me for one hour at least!
What 1 hour? It hasn't even been 5 minutes.
- I'll sue you, then.
-  You can't do this.
Tell her to sue me.
Dad, if this leaks out to the media, it's your loss. It's abuse of power.
Then,
make her work for an hour and send her home with 10 dollars.
Tell her to wash her hands first.
You know the disinfectant Se Gye uses for surgery?
Tell her to use that and wear a mask.
Yes, Professor.
I was busy training the new caregiver.
Of course.
Let's meet up next week.
I miss you, too.
Fix the angle of the television.
- Like this?
-  It should be angled towards me.
The other way.
Can't you do it properly?
- Is this good?
-  Open the blinds.
- Like this?
-  What was that? Be gentle.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. What's wrong with this?
May I leave?
There's one minute left.
- What's this?
-  Ouch.
Oh dear. I'm sorry.
- Put me upright.
-  Oh dear.
It's been exactly an hour.
I'll leave, then.
Hey, woman! Relief Patch!
Ma'am. Here you go.
You can keep it. I don't need your 10 dollars.
Bring her back. Now!
Oh gosh.
Doesn't this look good?
You should be the one cooking from now on.
Both Mum and I are busy.
Don't waste your time. You should be studying.
Don't worry, Mum. Once I pass next time...
There's no next time. It's this year. That's what you said.
Of course.
Once I pass this year, I'll tear this place down and build...
a second or a third-story house.
So 1st floor is for you, 2nd floor is for me and 3rd is for her.
- Keep me out of it.
-  Why would you count her in?
I feel bad for her.
I feel more bad for you. And I...
can't live with her.
Just eat and study. Why are you being so chatty?
Mum.
You know my childhood friend who got married last time?
- The professor?
-  Yes.
She got pregnant before they were married.
- I'm so envious.
-  You're envious?
What if your daughter-in-law got pregnant...
That's only when you can support yourself.
Do you know how worried I was when you were dating Gab Soon?
I couldn't even sleep thinking that someone incompetent like her...
might get pregnant and drag you down with her.
If a woman is old enough, she should take proper care of herself.
You must have been out of your mind.
Why would you date a petty girl like her?
She speaks bluntly to you just because you're the same age.
She has no job, looks or money.
She has nothing.
She has guts, she's bold and she's loyal.
She can fight, too.
And why is her name Gab Soon?
Well, he's Gab Dol.
That's why I hate her even more.
It sounds like they're a pair.
You bossed her around.
She came here voluntarily so why not?
Only an idiot like you would date Gab Soon.
Men these days are shrewd so they're very picky with women.
They won't date a woman if they don't have a good job or a family.
It's not like he has money.
He's got the looks.
On top of that,
you've just turned 29 but she's already 29.
That's the same.
Age is different for men and women.
You're good for another 10 years.
Just pass the exam and you can date a woman who's 10 years younger.
She never did anything for me.
It's not like she ever got me a sock for my birthday...
or a piece of apple for any holiday.
They don't sell a sock on its own or a piece of apple.
Why are you talking about Gab Soon all of a sudden?
Don't ever mention her again. You're making me lose my appetite.
Is she pregnant?
What?
Hello, is it Seokbulsa Temple?
Please, speak up.
I have bad hearing.
What did you say?
There's a student named...
Shin Gab Soon in your temple.
May I speak to her?
What did he say?
Where did I leave my hearing aid?
Ma'am!
- Her name is Shin Gab Soon...
-  Sorry?
Who is it again?
It's a student.
A student?
Yes.
Is she doing well?
My goodness.
She's busy studying with a band around her head.
Is that right?
Would you like to speak to her?
No, it's okay.
I shouldn't interrupt her.
Thank you.
You see.
She's spending her time studying.
She has a band around her head...
and she's solely focused on her studies.
- It's not true.
-  Don't act up.
You're isolating me from my family.
This is between us...
but we weren't going to have her...
and guess what?
Gab Soon is the most thoughtful one out of our three children.
She hasn't made it yet but watch. She'll become somebody important.
Sure she will.
Don't speak so carelessly.
If you ever do that again...
What?
Are you going to rip my mouth?
It looks like you are.
It doesn't matter. Gab Soon is in Seoul.
- Shin Mal Nyeon!
-  Mal Nyeon!
Have some. You wanted naengmyeon.
You didn't have to do this.
We could have gone to a snack bar.
- Do you want me to cut it up?
-  Sure.
Should we order more suyuk?
You don't have money. This is enough.
It's delicious.
Aren't you going to eat?
I will.
Gab Soon.
Let's...
have a baby later.
Later? Later when? What are you trying to say?
It's exactly what I said. Let's have a baby later.
What about this one? What am I supposed to do with it?
You know how it is.
We're in no circumstance to have a baby.
I don't even have a job.
You wanted to sleep on it for a few days...
and this is what you come to?
What's your conclusion, then?
Don't just get upset. Let's be realistic.
Can you tell your parents?
I can't.
Even if I did, I'll never be able to convince my mum...
and I couldn't bring myself to tell her that you got pregnant...
when she prays for me every day.
You only care about your mum.
You don't care about me at all, right?
I'm not taking sides.
I thought you'd be a man and take responsibility for it.
I thought you'd at least say, "I'll take care of it. Don't worry."
Is it being a man to promise something you can't do?
Women are so weird.
It's not like you want a baby at this point either.
What do you want to hear from me?
It's not like we can handle a baby.
We can't event take care of ourselves.
You can blame me but be reasonable about it.
You should have been careful.
What?
If you were careful, this wouldn't have happened!
What did you say?
Don't pick at what I say.
You dragged me!
You never said no!
If you gave me the sign, I wouldn't have done that.
How could you...
To put it bluntly, you're old enough to take care of yourself.
Why would you make the man take all the responsibility?
Aren't you responsible?
Would you be happy if I was miserable because of you?
I take that back.
I won't drag you down.
I'll go to the hospital so come when I call you.
What a jerk.
(Department of Gynaecology)
(Foetal Growth Process)
This is your first time, right?
- Yes.
-  Please fill out this form.
(Department Gynaecology Questionnaire)
Are you the dad?
- Yes.
-  You should have been careful.
You probably lived together without your parents' consent and did this.
I can tell whether you are a married couple or not.
You know abortion is illegal, right?
You should get married at any cost if you get pregnant.
You'll regret it later for doing this to your body.
You might become infertile.
You have to get tested...
so write down when your last period was...
and the date of your sexual intercourse.
Then, get a urine sample.
The baby is healthy, right?
Yes, the baby has a strong heartbeat, too.
I'm so happy for you. You couldn't get pregnant for a while.
You'll finally see the baby next month.
Yes.
Thank you.
- Take care.
-  See you.
Be careful.
You have to watch it.
Mind your own business.
I'll raise the baby on my own.
Don't ever call me.
Consider it again.
No.
Being stubborn won't get you anything.
I'm not being stubborn.
Let's tell Mum, then.
You know what she's going to make me do.
She'll drag me to the hospital.
This is impossible.
How are you going to do it all by yourself?
I always wanted to get married like every other people...
and raise my own kids.
My career is important to me,
but I always dreamed of having a happy family with Gab Dol.
But...
this happened.
That's what I mean.
I want you to get married like other people,
have babies and have a happy family.
This is not the right time.
- Like Gab Dol said...
-  Stop it, Jae Soon.
You get so stubborn with strange things.
Do you know what it means to be a single mum?
Do you know how hard it is to raise a kid on your own?
Nobody in this world wants to be a single mum.
When I saw those women, I wondered why they'd do that to themselves.
But...
it's a living thing that came to me.
How could I betray it so that I can survive?
Let it go this once.
This one mistake might ruin your whole life.
Your baby's life, too.
You can say anything,
but please don't call it a mistake.
You should be on my side.
- You're good.
-  I love babies.
I'll have many children.
With whom?
Gab Soon. Let's have a baby.
Stop it.
What's the matter? They all know we're together.
Gab Soon. Let's have...
a baby who looks like you, a baby who looks like me...
and a baby who looks like us. Let's have three children.
- Promise me.
-  I promise you.
I'll raise the baby on my own. You should stay out of it.
Don't ever look for me. You jerk.
Gab Soon!
You fool. You can't do it alone.
I want to take my responsibility.
Let's have this baby.
Live together?
Let's live together until the baby comes.
That's absurd. We should get married first.
I don't want to just live together. I won't.
There is no other way.
You know what our parents are going to say.
Still, I don't want that.
Can you tell other people that we live together proudly?
Can you tell our parents and friends that we live together?
People are not used to that idea yet.
They talk about living together before marriage on media,
but it's different in reality.
I don't want people to point a finger at us.
I'm scared and embarrassed.
Then convince your parents.
I'll convince my mum.
You're not confident, right? I don't want to do this either,
but this is the only option we have.
I don't want you to hide somewhere and have a baby alone.
I should be there with you.
I have nothing,
but I'll be there until the end.
Let's do this together.
Let's get a place first, and convince our parents later.
At the worst, they will only beat us up.
Stop sighing,
and stop crying.
You're with a baby.
- Trust me.
-  How can I trust you?
Why can't you?
Just trust me this once.
How can I trust you? I can't.
I'll be your precious husband. From now on, do as I say.
Da Hae.
Don't ask for money. I'm not the person you should come to.
Money?
I promise I'll pay you back.
We should get a place to stay.
I'll try.
What is this?
I sent her that, but she refused to take it and sent it back.
Okay.
Hello?
- Don't send things like that.
-  It's nothing big.
- It's just some meat.
-  I don't need it.
You don't have to send me food. I'm eating just fine.
I missed my grandchildren, but I tried not to.
I'll have to reconsider things.
They're my grandchildren. Why should I try not to miss them?
I'm hanging up now.
Cho Rong, Da Rong.
You're home.
You should do it on a side. Why do you have to do it here?
You're here.
Make him do it on a side.
Play here.
It hurts when people step on them.
Aren't kids home?
They are. They must be playing with their smartphones.
It's not good to play with it for a long time, but they won't listen.
What are you doing?
Why won't you greet me at the door?
Cho Rong.
- Dad.
-  I heard you always play with this.
I'll take it away for a while.
I don't always play with it. It was only two hours.
Da Rong, let's go.
What's the matter with you? Do you want me to scold you?
Dad, you know what?
- You feel like a stepfather to us.
-  She's right. You're different.
What did you want to say?
Nothing. I'll tell you later.
You told me to come home early because you have something to say.
I'll tell you later.
Jae Soon.
I want you to stop lying to me.
I lied to you?
Cho Rong says she plays with her phone for only two hours.
- That's...
-  You lied about going to dry sauna.
-  I hate people lying to me.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
How did you know I went to the dry sauna?
Did you see me?
Was it...
the credit card?
You might lose it, so I got the notification service.
I didn't do it to check where you spend the money on.
Don't mind it, and use it. As you always did.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Pick one.
That's not right.
Watch.
Walk to the hotel lobby.
Push the revolving door. Don't do it frivolously.
Watch the speed of the rotation,
and calculate the number of steps.
The girl is sitting over there.
Take off your sunglasses and run your fingers through your hair.
The girl will fall in love with you.
Sit across from her,
and throw your car key carelessly.
Act like you don't care about it.
Put down your cell phone naturally,
and say, "I'm sorry. My meeting ran late."
For the first time, look her in the eyes.
Okay?
You should look classy and natural when you do this.
Be natural.
Don't forget to be nonchalant.
You're sometimes too nice. That's not charming.
Also, when you move to another place...
It was such a long meeting.
Let's take your car.
Find a good timing when you pay.
I was in a hurry and I forgot to bring my wallet.
I can't call my secretary over this.
I'll buy you a nice meal next time.
Let's do a final check.
I'm sorry I'm late.
My meeting ran late.
To make it up to you,
let me settle the bills today.
No. I just got here.
Order something.
Let's go to somewhere else.
I'll go wash my hands first.
(Deposit: 45,000 dollars)
How many zeros is that?
10,000... Oh, my.
(Deposit: 32,000 dollars)
My gosh.
Grandpa is still asleep, right?
Go upstairs now.
You're driving me crazy.
If he finds out, both of us will...
You know that, right?
Mum, I'm sorry.
Se Gye. You're still awake.
You shouldn't stay out until so late.
I just had fun to relieve stress.
You're hardly at home when I come home from work.
You sneak out after your grandfather goes to sleep.
If you keep doing this, I'll have to tell him.
What do you want me to do?
I have to relieve stress.
What stresses you?
This is what stresses me out.
You don't let me do what I want.
Be quiet.
Ms Yeo.
Do you want my father to wake up and kick us out?
What's the matter?
I told her not to stay out until late.
Gong Joo is only 24 years old.
It must stress her out that she got married so young.
All her friends are still students.
Let her have fun.
Stop crying and come out.
You're old enough. Why can't you soothe a young girl?
Here is 1,000 dollars.
I knew it. You saved up some money.
I saved it up for an emergency.
This is an emergency.
1,000 dollars for deposit and 100 dollars for monthly rent?
Even a small room that only 1 person can fit is 200 dollars.
I can pitch in 100 dollars per month.
Please find a place that rents for 200.
We can get a good place, right?
A good place?
It'd be better if it has big windows,
gets a lot of sun and faces south.
I don't want a basement.
Right. It must have mould.
Water should come out well and drain well.
Thieves mustn't easily come in.
It should be close to bus stops and subway station.
It should be three minutes' walk.
Shouldn't the kitchen be separated from the room?
Of course. Otherwise, the room will smell bad.
We will cook fish and pork.
The room should be big.
The kitchen should be big.
I want built-in furniture like a desk and a bed.
It'd be better if it has a sink, a cooking table and a fridge.
Right. Built-in furniture.
Also, it should be clean.
It shouldn't have cockroaches or mould.
It shouldn't leak rain, and it must have clean wallpaper.
If it's a new apartment, we'll sign the paper today.
The place you just mentioned...
is at least 1,000 dollars per month.
Let's be realistic.
You don't need a bathroom, right?
Water would stop running once in a while.
You should heat up the water yourselves.
They have built-in furniture, but it won't be clean.
Even if it is, the room won't be vacant for long.
Are you newly-weds?
When is your wedding?
We haven't set the date yet.
If you register your marriage, you can get loans.
- We can't do that.
-  We can't do that.
Are you just going to live together?
You should get married first,
register your marriage and then live together.
Young people always want to live together first. You'll regret it.
Look, young lady.
What if you live together,
he gets tired of you and leaves you?
What kind of person do you think I am?
I'm not like that.
You never know what will happen.
I'm saying this because you're my daughter's age.
Think again carefully.
Let's go to another place.
Take a look.
Gab Soon.
What is it?
(My friends forever)
(This is my lovely house. Visit me soon!)
Why are you looking at this?
They're the enemies of this country. They give you sense of deprivation.
They just want to feel superior.
I hope they get struck by lightening.
This would make Gab Soon upset.
Aren't you hungry?
Let's go and eat.
What do you want to eat?
Gimbap? Tteokbokki, too?
I'll pay.
(Prime Rib)
Hey, Gab Soon! This isn't right!
- This isn't right.
-  Why not?
This will cost us a month's rent.
So?
Five servings of beef ribs, please.
No. Just one serving, please.
You can't order one serving.
You should order at least two servings.
Then just two servings, please.
You can eat it all. I won't even smell it.
Just give us five servings.
What now?
You were eating just fine.
People are looking.
So what?
- Miss.
-  I'm so sorry.
Let's go to the restroom.
Go by yourself.
This is my seat.
This is my seat until I finish my meal.
Who can say anything to me?
I don't have any place I can stay, but this is my seat.
We have other customers. You shouldn't do this here.
She says you shouldn't do this here.
Let's go out.
Let's talk outside.
You're acting like a drunken person.
Let me go.
I have nothing to say to you.
I can't stand this squalid life with you any more.
Go. I said go!
Bring me more lettuce.
You will have a hoarse throat. Stop crying.
I'll get a place no matter what.
Don't cry.
It's not good for our baby.
You have a hoarse throat.
Cho Rong.
This is mine.
- Just for today.
-  That's the newest one I have.
I have a business meeting today.
You won't be taking off your pants.
A gentleman should always be prepared.
Goodness. I can't believe you're my son.
What is it?
Gosh.
Is someone in there?
A resident of the main building.
It's urgent.
It's urgent for me, too.
Please, hurry.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Don't talk to me while I'm taking a shower.
Excuse me. Can I close my eyes and use the restroom?
I promise I won't look.
Use the public bathroom down the hill.
I paid the toilet fee!
I can't go as far as the public bathroom.
We live under the same roof so we should say hi to each other.
What are you saying?
Return my toilet fee.
Welcome.
Hello.
- Go on.
-  Come in.
Hello, we're here to light up the mood.
Let's enjoy our time, guys!
Hey, let's pair up first.
Guys, we'll pick you today.
- That sounds good. Pick me.
-  Pick me.
I choose...
him right there.
Don't mess with him. He's mine.
I choose him, then.
- I choose him.
-  Come over.
Excellent!
Say it again.
I'm quitting. I can't do this any more.
You're funny.
You walked in here voluntarily but you can't just walk out.
You! I'm not letting go of you until you pay off your debt.
It's hot. Don't touch it.
Mum, can you lend me some money?
You lunatic. I don't have a penny for myself.
Can you lend me just 5,000 dollars?
You must be joking.
I'll pay you off right away.
Get your act together. Aren't you embarrassed to face your children?
Why are you talking about them?
You know I hate talking about them.
Act like a mum.
You have no reason to be in debt.
I never raised you guys like that.
I fed you, clothed you and sent you to school all on my own.
- But you...
-  Forget it!
Geum Sik got remarried.
Whether he gets remarried or not doesn't have anything to do with me.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Don't ever speak of him again.
(Karaoke)
My goodness.
One tiger swallowtail
Landed in a flower field
Not one person
Was there to look at it
Fly, tiger swallowtail
Above the sky
You can't slip so I'll go on my own.
Would you be okay? You have the deposit on you, right?
I do.
- Be careful.
-  Don't worry, Your Highness.
That's the restroom.
Look around.
It's vacant so we can move in right away. What do you think?
Don't sign the contract, yet.
Let's go back tomorrow.
This station is Oksu Station.
The door is on your right.
Excuse me. I'm getting off. Give me a second.
(Our Gab Soon)
How are you going to take responsibility?
Forget the baby. I'm sick of everything.
I won't have it.
Gab Soon is roaming about in Seoul.
Do you keep seeing things?
Take her to the hospital. She must've gone out of her mind.
Where is Ddol Ee? Ddol Ee!
Mum.
You've been doing well since school. Hang in there.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
She's not fit for our family.
She's the only one who didn't try to flatter me.
I have a good feeling.
How could you be so annoying every time?
Live properly.
I told you not to come!
I don't need a mum.
Don't lose it.
I'll protect it with my life.
Is he not here yet? He must have run away.
He would never do that.