BioskopKeren
(Episode 30)
Why are you here?
What good will you get out of this?
Don't ever come here again. You've seen how I live now.
To be honest, I want to hold onto you.
I desperately want to.
I need you more than anything in the world right now.
You're the only one I can trust the kids with.
But if I do hold onto you now,
it'll only prove how unworthy I am.
Don't waste your affections on me.
Don't look back.
Let's file the papers within this week.
I'll see you in court.
My goodness. This is so dirty.
- What are you doing? - It's my turn to clean.
I dropped Ddol Ee off at his art class.
Where have you been? Did you get off work late today?
It's obvious. She probably went to see Geum Sik.
Geum Sik?
- Yes. - Will you keep up with that?
What's wrong with you? Let me ask you one thing.
Now that you've decided to get a divorce, are your feelings growing?
You're usually hungry when there's nothing much to eat.
And your lover can't be more charming when he leaves you.
It's nothing like that.
We're going to court this week.
- Does he want that? - Yes.
- He should. - It's true.
You need to file the papers to end the relationship.
You've always been too soft.
I guess you feel sorry for the kids. But why should you?
Do they not have a father, a mother or a grandmother?
He can send them to their grandmother's if he needs to.
Don't you ever contact them again. All right?
Do you understand or not?
Why won't she respond?
Since there's no reason to.
- What? - Nothing.
Don't mind her. Mind your own business.
She must be frustrated.
She can't do this nor that.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
My gosh.
- Really? - I saw it with my own two eyes.
Maybe you're mistaken. Why would he?
I know, right?
They looked very close. They looked like lovers.
Like lovers?
What are you doing?
Do you want some help with that?
No thanks. You'll push me again when someone sees us.
I won't do that.
If we kick them out and live together, I'll cook for you.
- Don't do that. - Come on.
- Give it to me. - Ms Nam.
What are you doing?
Why did that fall?
It does that sometimes.
Did you both eat sweet potatoes?
- What are you talking about? - Gong Joo saw you both.
Right. We did.
- With Ms Nam? - No.
I was eating sweet potatoes.
But she kept begging me to give her one bite.
That's why I gave her some.
You keep bothering people when they're eating something.
Right.
I guess I do that sometimes.
Ms Nam. Be careful of your actions, and don't make people misunderstand.
My dad lived alone decently until now.
Think of what will happen if you make rumours...
about my father and a housekeeper.
Even the thought of it is dreadful.
During the 30 years after my mum passed away,
he didn't cause any trouble with women.
Although there wouldn't be such a thing with an old woman like you,
you should still be careful.
Dad, I need a word with you.
Okay.
Dad. There's nothing going on between you and her, right?
Of course not.
Gong Joo said you two looked like lovers.
Don't be nice to her. She might think differently.
Men with wealth need to be careful of women.
I told you it's nothing like that. Mind your own business.
Be careful. Don't get blind-sided.
It's so obvious what to expect from women like her.
What's the time? I need to eat.
- You're cooking? - Yes.
- What are you making? - Kimchi fried rice.
My goodness.
Don't disturb me.
Stop.
- Why? - You shouldn't put it back in.
It's clean enough.
You still shouldn't. You should throw it out.
All right.
Don't stare at me. Go back in. I'll manage on my own.
You have everything out on the table.
You took out the pots,
spice jars and frying pans.
You don't need all this to make kimchi fried rice.
Leave me to do it on my own.
All right.
That'll take ages to clean up.
Is it not ready yet?
It won't open if you're scared of opening that.
You need to hold it tightly and just open it using your strength.
You'll hurt your hand. Let me do it for you.
I did it.
Go in. It's time for me to use the kitchen.
Use a knife to get it out.
Oh, no. My goodness.
It's best not to look at this.
He's taking ages to make kimchi fried rice. I'm so hungry.
He's using the kitchen all to himself.
How long are you going to take?
Don't pester me. You're not helping one bit.
All right.
- This looks tasty. - I want some.
- Go away. - You have yours.
- Stop it. - I don't want to.
You can't have any.
That'll be a dollar and 60 cents.
You're the best. You really are.
- Isn't it tasty? - It is.
This is fun.
I don't understand why people don't want to do it.
What shall we eat tomorrow?
What's your problem?
- Catch me. - Give it.
- You're so annoying. - You have yours.
What are you doing? Give it.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
My gosh.
My goodness.
What are you doing? I cleaned them.
It's not clean enough.
Don't be fussy. You'll only wear yourself out.
Why do it twice? Just leave it if it's all right.
I washed them nice and clean.
Yes, I can see that.
- Let's eat. - I don't want to. It's not tasty.
Let's eat this today and ask Dad to take us out tomorrow.
No. I want pork cutlet.
We don't have money.
Dad gave us money.
We need to save up. Eat up.
No!
What do you think you're doing?
Who told you to behave like this?
Why won't you listen to me?
I'm having a hard time as it is.
You should behave.
Why are you doing this to me?
Dad's having a hard time as it is. We should be considerate.
What will he think if you're like this?
I don't care. I want to go to Grandma's place.
Come here, Da Rong.
Don't cry.
You need to listen to Cho Rong.
Cho Rong.
Don't yell at Da Rong.
Let's eat out. What would you like to eat?
I want pork cutlet.
Okay, pork cutlet it is.
I'll buy you that this week.
Cho Rong.
When did this start?
Did this happen before? Does anywhere else hurt?
I'm okay. I'm just tired.
Let's see.
How did you end up like this?
You never used to step into the kitchen.
Now, you make food for yourself and do the dishes.
You'll make a good wife.
Why not?
If somebody wants to marry me, I'll gladly go.
- When you fold laundry... - No more nagging.
I'll do it my style.
There's no style to folding laundry.
You have to fold it properly. Watch.
Like this.
This is straight. It's nice to keep it this way.
You should do it, then. Don't make Joong Nyeon do it.
Don't be so fussy. I'm tired.
He says he's tired.
He has to cook, do the dishes, clean and do the laundry.
You're going to kill Joong Nyeon.
It's that hard to feed yourself.
Imagine if you had to feed your family.
I agree.
And when you use the kitchen,
I want you to keep to your designated time.
I didn't think about that.
You must've been hungry waiting for me to finish.
You should have waited. We could've had kimchi fried rice together.
I had something simple outside.
This family doesn't care any more.
You fold laundry however you want, and you eat whatever.
How convenient.
- My gosh. - What's wrong with that?
It's great.
Turn right.
Turn the steering wheel slowly.
What now? Was that wrong?
When you turn the steering wheel, turn slower...
than you think you should. It's a tiny movement.
You have to be confident. It's an empty space.
Turn left.
Your hand.
Focus on driving.
Let's take a U-turn.
Drive up to there.
Be careful. Be careful.
Brake. Brake.
Are you okay?
I nearly had a heart attack.
Goodness.
I already had one.
No daydreaming when you drive.
I didn't daydream.
Weren't you thinking about me?
Thank you, Instructor. This one's on me.
That's why I ordered jjajangmyeon, the tastiest and cheapest dish.
Driving's fun.
I'm still scared, but it's fun.
When you go to bed, you'll be thinking about the steering wheel.
When you first start, you are eager to drive.
I agree.
- Let's eat here. - Let's go somewhere else.
Let's just stay. We don't have much time.
Hello. We see each other again.
Hi.
You must be out for lunch. Join us.
Shall we?
It's okay.
I'll have jjamppong. What about you, Gab Dol?
- I'll have the same. - Sure.
You two look good together.
You look good together as well.
Doesn't your mum tell you to go on blind dates?
Yes, I guess.
I think people are happy when they meet a partner at their level.
I heard couples who work in the same field last longer.
My parents are both teachers.
They are companions for life.
They get a lot of pension, too.
I want to be like my parents.
I found my office space.
You have the location?
Yes, it's a good location. I'll decorate it nicely.
Once I finish practising driving, I'll get a car...
and hire some employees.
I thought you said you don't want employees.
I'll be the owner. I need people working for me.
Businesses are the best for making money.
You can be a salaried employee,
but all they have is their pension.
I don't understand why people are so obsessed about it.
You should have the best life you can have.
How cool.
All right.
Enjoy.
It's so hot.
You should have taken your time. Here's water.
It's hot water.
I'm sorry.
I like their jjajangmyeon.
- You got sauce on your lips. - Here?
Here.
You're like a baby.
Should we eat and go outdoors?
I can practise driving.
Okay.
I already paid.
We're paying separately.
Just a moment, please.
(Chinese Restaurant)
Where should we go?
Sorry?
You wanted to practise driving.
It's okay.
How much should I invest in you?
You have to lease the office and hire people.
I don't know. Just take me back.
- Are they going out? - No.
Why are they acting like that, then?
I thought she was your girlfriend.
Us women know women.
They're not going out.
The guy likes her, so he's following her around.
You're her boyfriend,
and she's letting another man follow her around?
And she tells you, "I don't care about him."
"He's following me around because he likes me. So what?"
Was this her excuse?
You are so nice, Gab Dol.
How could you let her do that...
when you've been going out for 10 years?
If she had common sense,
she would have never done that.
Let's go.
Let's be honest about this.
- I have nothing to say. - Did you...
Fine. You're going to be all mad if I swear again.
What are you doing hanging around with him?
Why are you around him? Are you going out with him?
What is it you want to say?
During our 10-year relationship,
you're the one who hung around with other girls.
Do you finally get it?
That's totally different. I hung out with them to get free food.
I'm doing that, too.
He's going to invest in me.
You're the one hanging out with your female co-worker all the time.
I was doing my job. It's not an excuse.
My mum nags me about going on blind dates, but I keep refusing.
What about you?
You use driving practice as an excuse to go on dates?
This is cheating. It's obvious.
I've been letting it go only because I'm a considerate person.
Other people already think you two are a couple.
"Other people"? Who? Dal Tong?
That's right.
You leave behind your boyfriend of 10 years,
and you go on dates with him.
Then you say, "I don't care about him. He's following me around..."
"because he likes me. So what?"
But if you had common sense, you would have never done that.
Is that what your co-worker said?
Yes.
That's why you're doing this?
You never change, do you?
You used to tell me exactly what your mum said.
Now, you tell me exactly what your co-worker says?
You must have made fun of me together.
She wanted to marry you and get pension when you retire.
- That'll work. - Tell me what you have in mind.
It's like you said. I know he likes me, but I'm letting him be.
- So what? - How could you?
I can't talk to you.
Finish talking.
What should I say? Do you want the truth?
You can't break up with me because of what our friends would say.
I wanted to ask if you were interested in your co-worker,
but I couldn't ask because of my pride.
Do you want me to end it off?
Should I dump you so that our friends don't criticise you?
Are you serious?
Is that the kind of person you think I am?
What did you do for our relationship?
What did you do?
You didn't do anything. You were being a coward.
You're afraid of what our friends would say so you can't dump me.
You're only waiting for me to get away. Am I not right?
I wouldn't have done this if I were you.
Even if your mum beats you to death,
you should have brought me to your mum at least once.
Only then, could you say you tried.
You're just making excuses.
I'm disgusted.
Do you know that you've changed?
Our friends say that, too. They say that you've changed.
Don't come back again.
Let's file the papers within this week.
I'll see you in court.
What would you like?
- Hello. - Hi.
- Is it six dollars for the bag? - Yes.
If I buy a lot, can you give me a discount?
That's how you fry it.
You know everything now.
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
Okay.
- Can I have fried chicken? - Sure.
- One fried chicken, please. - Okay.
You didn't go to bed yet?
No, I have to study.
I've never seen you study.
Don't waste your time. Save some electricity.
If you studied before, you would have made it to college.
That's what I was thinking.
If I studied like this, I would've gone to Seoul National University.
That's far-fetched.
Mum.
I'll pay for your knee surgery as soon as I make enough money.
Just look after yourself.
On top of that,
we'll have warm water during winter.
I'll let you use the heater so that you don't have to wear a sweater.
My nose is cold.
Some people don't even have a house like this.
Look at Mr Geum.
He thinks we're well off.
You just wait. I'll make you rich.
I don't know what kind of a lunatic is investing in your business.
He must be out of his mind.
Watch me. I'll become successful.
I'm tired.
Oh, dear.
It's cold. You must be working hard.
You deliver water during the day and alcohol at night.
What are you going to do with all that money?
How's your business doing?
It's good. Good night. It's cold.
It's cold.
Welcome home.
Don't do that. You have bad eye sight.
Why won't you listen to me?
I should get new glasses.
- It'll cost more though. - Stop doing that.
I have nothing to do at home. I'll pitch in some money.
Stop doing that.
I spent two hours on them.
It's at least 50 cents.
You should be helping me, not knocking it over.
What now?
I won't play with you.
Don't do this again.
I'll make money.
Gosh.
I think I need to tell him.
He threaded the beads overnight.
He must have been tired from work.
Would it make any difference?
He still has to know the truth.
I don't want to be a dad who makes his son suffer.
(What kind of chicken will I sell?)
What is your predicted income?
If you invest 50,000 dollars...
and take out the expected cost, the margin is...
Do you get 100,000 dollars?
No. Even if I get wholesale products,
I can't bring the cost down too much. It sacrifices the quality.
Even I don't go to restaurants that have low quality food.
I'm going to use the best ingredients...
and use less employees. I'll work extra hard.
I realised that's what business comes down to.
I'll do what I can by myself.
I'll use a part-time worker during busy hours.
I'll save enough for a monthly wage.
- Approved. - Really?
It's worth investing.
Really?
I'm so happy. Are you serious?
- Let's go somewhere else. - Why?
Are you sure? Okay.
Grandpa is acting weird.
He dresses younger than his age and he even texts.
I think he's seeing a younger woman.
Dad, are you seeing somebody? Is it a young woman?
What are you talking about?
You were at a coffee shop, hugging and kissing her.
Gong Joo saw you.
How could you do that?
I didn't do that, but what if I did?
Who is that woman?
Don't tell me who to meet or what to do.
You promised me.
I've done enough.
Fine. Let me see who it is.
You don't have to. It's my privacy. Leave.
That's as far as it goes. Don't think otherwise.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Can I sit down for a minute?
Do you have something to say?
- You're such a playboy. - What are you talking about?
You flirt with any women because you have money.
I heard that you're seeing a young woman.
Are you going to do this to me, too? It's not what you think.
I heard what your daughter said.
Why did you treat me like that when you already have someone?
It's not that.
- It's just a misunderstanding. - No, it's not.
I'm not a fool. I can take the hint.
I'm getting old. I don't want to get into a messy situation.
I need to make a living, so I can't quit right now.
Please find a replacement within this month.
- Relief Patch. - Don't ever call me that again.
My gosh.
Don't think about anything silly. Keep your promise to me.
Wow, Man Joo.
It looks weird, right?
I feel so awkward and uncomfortable.
You look nice. What's the occasion?
My friend pestered me to go on a blind date.
Did you go on a blind date?
- I thought you weren't interested. - I wasn't.
But you're married, and you don't work at the hospital any more.
All my friends are married.
I just thought I was acting pitiful all by myself.
So I thought, "I should at least meet some guys."
- So you're thinking about marriage. - Not exactly.
- Are you going to marry that guy? - I just met him once.
- What does he do? - He's the hospital director's son.
He is a plastic surgeon.
I'm hungry. Let's go out to eat.
You were on a blind date. Didn't he buy you a meal?
He got paged from the hospital, so he had to go.
He said he was sorry and said he'll buy me a nice meal next time.
- So he asked you out again. - Kind of.
- What is it? - I can't eat.
Even my niece got upset because of my social network page.
You can't take that lightly.
I told you not to do it.
Don't do it any more.
It's already all over the place. I can't do anything about it.
It's not like I can delete them.
- I'll try to delete them. - How are you going to do that?
What are you two doing here?
I told you not to stay together, didn't I?
Don't you ever come back!
I heard your stepmother ran away, too.
Your birth mother ran away a long time ago.
Your family went bankrupt, and your stepmother ran away.
How pitiful you are.
- Hey! Get off of me! - Stop.
- Let me go! - Stop it.
- Stop. - My gosh.
Cho Rong.
What happened to your face? What's the matter?
Ms Shin.
Ms Shin...
Hello.
Hello. How can I help you?
I'm Cho Rong's stepmother.
Hello.
Cho Rong has been living with me ever since last year.
Is that Cho Rong's fault?
We're having some difficulties at home,
so we're living in a rooftop room right now.
Is that something that the children should tease her with?
I'm sure there are other children with a single parent...
or a step-parent in Cho Rong's class.
Why should they be teased...
and bullied because of that?
Can you be sure that...
it won't happen to any of your own children?
Girls. Do I look like a mean witch?
No, right?
Stepmothers don't look mean and ugly.
Bullying someone on the social network service is...
the same thing as hurting that person's heart.
It really hurts.
Who is Joo Hee? I won't scold you.
She my daughter. What is it?
I heard you're a good singer.
Your dream is to become an idol singer, right?
I heard you're popular in your class, too.
Ga Eun.
I heard you're a fast runner and a good drawer.
Cho Rong envied you.
You must be Jeong Rim.
Your make-up looks nice.
Cho Rong told me about how good you are at doing make-up.
She complimented that you do make-up for your friends, too.
Cho Rong writes a lot about you guys on her diary.
She wants to be close to you.
Please don't hurt Cho Rong.
She's your friend.
I told you not to do that.
You should be studying. What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
Apologise to Cho Rong.
Go on.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
My daughter was also bullied last year. She had a very hard time.
But I couldn't be as brave as you.
You're amazing.
I'm going to the market. Do you want anything?
I'll make some side dishes today.
- I'll come with you. - I want to...
- Not you, Mal Nyeon. - She doesn't want you to come.
Joong Nyeon. This is a betrayal.
Give me that. I'll carry it.
Save your face. You don't carry this stuff.
I lost my face a long time ago.
- Thank you. Come again. - Okay.
- Hello. - Hi.
I guess you came grocery shopping.
It's obvious. Why would you ask?
Goodbye, then.
Wait for me.
Hello. You're Gab Dol's mother, aren't you?
I met you when you visited the district office before.
I'm Kim Young Ran. I work with Gab Dol.
Hello.
Please get in. I was on my way home. I'll give you a ride.
My house isn't far away.
It's on a hill, so cars can't go up there.
- I'm a strong girl. - You don't have to.
This is my house. We live a humble life.
I like it. The air is clear, and it has a nice view.
It's just air, and it's not such a pretty view.
I'll be going, then.
You came all the way here. Do you want to come in for some tea?
May I?
I would've been disappointed if you hadn't asked me.
- Hurry home. - Why?
This is why all our friends call you a jerk.
I have food to deliver.
We don't buy fruits often, so there isn't anything to give you.
A cup of tea is more than enough.
It smells nice.
Someone gave me this as a gift.
It has been in the cupboard for a while.
This place is a bit shabby, right?
It's an old house, and it's cold.
I turned on the heater, so it will get warm soon.
I'm fine.
You seem like a very nice person.
- How old are you? - I'm 26 years old.
My goodness. You must be very smart.
Did you pass your exam right after you graduated university?
Yes. I was lucky.
Some people study for 10 years, but they still fail the exam.
What do your parents do?
They're both teachers.
How great!
Your family is going to get a tremendous amount of pensions.
Yes. They wanted me to become a teacher as well,
but I suppose I was meant to become a public official to meet Gab Dol.
Do you like Gab Dol?
Yes. He caught my eyes on his first day.
I was thinking I should marry a public official as well.
My gosh. That'd be great.
Don't feel burdened because I'm a single mother.
I will never live off my son and his wife.
It's okay if we live with you. You can help us raise our children.
I think it's good to live with an elder in the house.
My gosh.
- What's going on? - You must be surprised.
She gave me a ride,
so I invited her in for a cup of tea.
I was just leaving.
Luckily, I was able to get acquainted with your mother.
I'll visit you again.
You're welcome any time.
One thing I'm good at is cooking. I'll make you nice food.
I'll be looking forward to that. Goodbye.
See her off.
Go on.
I hope you won't do something like this again.
Isn't it natural to carry the baggage of a colleague's mother?
See you tomorrow.
She's such a nice person.
She sounds so gentle and says all the nice things.
Maybe it's because she's a public official. She's so classy.
Why did you invite her in?
She said she liked you ever since your first day.
Why wouldn't she? No one is as handsome as you.
Forget it.
She wants to marry a public official as well.
Gab Soon studied for 10 years, but she failed every time.
She isn't gentle, and she doesn't know how to flatter.
She's always sulky and stubborn.
Why did you date her for 10 years?
You have such a bad taste in women.
You should date a woman like Young Ran.
If you like her that much, date her yourself.
Get a hold of yourself. Don't kick away good fortune.
We had dinner already, but I'm still hungry.
Taste this for me.
Oh, right. I forgot to add salt.
Nae Shim.
Look at this.
It's hurting my eyes.
What are you two doing?
Don't let her come between us.
- Don't come between us. - My gosh.
Fine. Goodness.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
My gosh.
Did you see how that women didn't even say hello to me?
You didn't, either.
What do you think she thought when she saw us...
shopping for groceries together?
"She's such an unlucky woman."
"She still has a husband who follows around her."
Maybe I'm a bit mean.
Looking at her carrying things on each arm...
made me feel bad. She looked so small.
Maybe it's because I was with you. I strutted along without realising.
I guess it looks bad if you grow old and live by yourself.
You were jealous of women who lived alone.
I told you about my friend...
who looked after her sick husband for seven years, right?
Yes. You said he died last summer.
She said children are useless.
She said a husband is the best even if he's sick.
They weren't even a happily married couple,
but she realised how good it is to have a husband.
Men are worse than women.
An old men without a wife is only an empty shell.
No one would treat him like human any more.
So be grateful to me.
We're not married.
Gosh.
Don't you try to cling onto me.
That's what I want to say.
Nae Shim.
Now that you're not my wife, I somehow want you more.
Shall I sleep in your room tonight?
My goodness.
Gosh.
Ms Shin. You were great at school today.
You're the best.
My friends apologised to me, and I'm so happy now.
I hope you'll come and live with us.
Did you make the side dishes?
What were you and Dad laughing about?
- What's this? - What?
Why would Cho Rong send you a text message?
Why did you look through my phone?
It says you went to her school.
I had to take care of something.
You're getting divorced. Why would you go to her school?
"I hope you'll come and live with us"?
She must be saying that because they have been talking about it.
I get that you're in a difficult situation,
but you should let her go now.
You may think I'm cold-hearted, but I have no choice.
No. I will file the papers soon.
Then please do it faster.
Jae Soon has always been soft-hearted and sympathetic.
She always helps people in need.
It looks like she went to Cho Rong's school...
because she came to her crying.
Please manage your children.
Okay.
I'm sorry I caused you trouble.
I won't let that happen again.
Here you go.
Dad. I'm so excited.
- Did something good happen, Dad? - Yes.
I found many new clients, and the company is doing great.
Let's hold out for a little longer.
Here.
- Is it delicious, Da Rong? - Yes, it's delicious.
Why aren't you eating, Dad?
I'm just happy to watch you eat.
Don't be depressed because things aren't good at home.
Da Rong, you should listen to your sister.
Cho Rong, you should study hard at school.
You made up with your friends, right?
From now on,
don't call Ms Shin.
Even if you do, she can't come any more. She won't.
Hello? I'm at a restaurant nearby.
Now? Okay.
I'll be back in 10 minutes. Eat up and stay right here.
(Discount Store)
Hello.
This phone is turned off. You'll be directed to voice mail.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Cho Rong. Why isn't Dad coming back?
He'll be back soon.
Study hard at school, and take good care of Da Rong.
Da Rong. Stay here for a minute.
This phone is turned off. You'll be directed to voice mail.
(Court)
Cho Rong!
Dad.
Cho Rong.
I'm sorry. I'm late because of work.
My mobile battery died.
I thought you weren't coming.
I thought you abandoned us.
What are you talking about? Why would I abandon you?
I thought you abandoned us after buying us delicious food.
I thought you left us because we're burdening you.
I wouldn't do that. I would never leave you.
Don't you ever think that way.
Everything's going to be okay.
It's okay.
(Courthouse)
I'm sorry.
You must've been waiting for so long in this cold weather.
I thought you ran away without divorcing me.
I'm hearing that a lot today.
- Who else said that? - Someone.
Let's go in.
You haven't eaten, have you?
I haven't eaten at all. I've been running around all day.
Then let's eat first.
Our divorce can wait a little longer.
What are you waiting for? I'm hungry, too.
Eat some more.
This place has good kkakdugi.
Yours is better.
Thank you...
for handling Cho Rong's friends.
You took care of something I couldn't.
My children and my life are all messed up right now.
Just like the last time I was divorced,
I am in a desperate situation.
While we were together,
I regret about many things.
I'm sorry that I didn't treat you right.
I was afraid of getting hurt again.
I put a wall around me,
even though you are such a kind person.
I know that you bore it all...
despite knowing I was doing that.
The things I regret the most is...
not taking care of you better while I had money,
and not caring about Ddol Ee as much as you've cared about my children.
That breaks my heart.
I am sorry.
And thank you.
Although we go our separate ways,
I hope you'll happy wherever you go.
It's yours now.
Here are the key and the receipts.
- I hope you become successful. - Thank you.
I will become successful for sure.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
Is this really true? It's yours?
Yes.
I'm the boss now.
This is a very thoroughly done.
You've gotten smarter.
You've been studying a lot these days.
I told you. You just needed to apply yourself more in school.
If you studied hard, you'd have gone to Seoul National University.
I would've not only gone, but I would've also graduated.
Let's check out the store.
Here.
It's nice and cosy.
This is awesome.
I will become successful here.
I'll surely make that happen.
If I work hard and cut staffing cost,
I should be able to make some good money.
When I have money,
I will bring back my children.
You still have no idea where they moved to, right?
No.
They don't answer the phone.
I'm even thinking about going to their school.
No matter how upset they are at you, they should still contact me.
Don't look for them. Leave them alone.
Don't ruin this great day.
Cheer up, Da Hae.
You need to come and help out after work.
When are you having the grand opening?
After I practice frying chicken a few times.
I need to clean up, too.
We can help with cleaning right now.
- Gab Dol, let's do it. - Really?
I want a whole chicken for my effort.
Whatever.
You're not open today?
No, we'll have our grand opening soon.
I own this place.
I will come back, then.
Please do. I will provide great service for you.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I already have a customer. I'm so excited.
Good job, everyone.
It's 3am already.
Go to sleep. You have to go to work in the morning.
Thank you, Gab Dol.
My goodness!
I shouldn't have let you help me clean.
Wait a little longer. I will help you get surgery.
I just hope your business does well.
Who gave you the money?
Is it someone who's been after you?
My gosh. I'm not into people like that.
He must have invested only because he's really into you.
Mum.
I've learned a lot thanks to my investor.
He set my mind straight.
- Who is he? - It's a secret.
He told me not to tell.
Don't meet him often if he's weird. Just pay his interest on time.
At least, I don't have to worry about you.
Gab Dol is a public official. You have a business.
I guess our family will finally do well.
I want to take a couple of months off.
Why? Did you quit?
I'm going to quit.
I thought he was a good person despite being so difficult.
He's two faced.
I can't believe he treats me that way.
No, he is a really nice guy.
He is my investor.
What?
I'm here.
Did you look for another position?
I have many places to go.
- Where will you go? - I'm not telling you.
How could you keep that from me?
I thought you were seeing a younger woman.
I had no idea you were helping my daughter.
Why did you keep that from me?
Your daughter can't be trusted.
She doesn't know how to be discreet.
She's never listened to anyone.
She said that she's learned a lot...
thanks to you.
I don't know how to thank you.
There's no need to do that.
Your children are...
mine, too.
Ms Nam, when did you get here?
Just now.
What were you doing in my dad's room?
I'll hurry up and prepare breakfast.
Is this the express delivery service?
Cho Rong, I cooked this.
Eat it with Da Rong while it's hot.
Cho Rong, it's fried chicken. It smells good.
You can eat it by yourself.
Why did you come all the way here?
I wanted to get your approval.
Please eat this and give me your review.
I will.
What is going on?
What?
- Who is she? - You can go.
Okay. Please visit my store soon.
Goodbye.
- Are you seeing her these days? - You have the wrong idea.
Are you going to deny even when I saw with my own eyes?
Dad, please come to your senses.
She looks really young.
What would she see in you?
It's so obvious. Can't you see that?
You got it all wrong. You have no idea.
She looks like someone who works at a hostess bar.
I'm so disappointed in you. Why would you meet someone like her?
I'm not seeing her. I made an investment.
See this? I invested in a fried chicken business.
She even made you invest money on her?
How long have you been seeing her? How much money did she get?
That's not it. She's Relief Patch's daughter.
- What? - Her daughter wanted to run...
a business, so I made a small investment.
Si Nae! Si Nae!
Ms Nam, I see that you are very rotten.
What... What are you talking about?
You came here to lure my father, didn't you?
What are you saying?
You came here pretending to take care of my father.
But your real motive was to get money from him with your daughter.
What did you say?
What do you call this situation?
That's right. You're a gold digger.
You've gone too far. I'm not a gold digger.
Just because I work for you, you shouldn't say such a thing.
Am I wrong? You and your daughter conned my father...
into giving you money. You and your daughter are gold diggers.
"Gold diggers"?
Look. I can take anything from you,
but I can't tolerate you calling my daughter a gold digger.
I may be poor, but I didn't raise my daughter to be a gold digger.
You think you can say anything you want because you're rich?
Do you think that poor people like me don't have any self-esteem?
It's true that you conned money from my father.
We never conned anything. He made an investment.
There is no difference.
Let's settle this at the police station.
I won't go to the police.
Why won't you go? Are you afraid of your crime?
That's enough.
Whether I committed a crime or not,
I won't go to the police station because it may harm my son's career.
I will pay back the money.
You see? They approached you for your money.
You were completely conned.
Ms Nam, tell your daughter to bring the money back now.
You've gone too far this time.
- Leave us. - How can you let her go?
We have to hold her until her daughter comes back with the money.
Leave us alone.
Don't let her go. Hey, Ms Nam.
Dad, don't you get it?
I will talk to you later.
Relief Patch!
Don't be upset.
I will take care of this. Go home for now.
Are your feeling for me sincere?
Of course.
Then, let's get married.