BK
(Da Hae's Luxury Chicken)
(Episode 31)
You guys, be quiet.
This is not a karaoke room. It's a chicken restaurant.
Da Hae, you should take good care of sanitation.
- You should clean up thoroughly. - Don't worry.
You might get caught if they come for inspection.
Stay clean in advance, okay?
Sanitation comes first when it comes to food.
I get it. What a nagger.
My public official brother is so annoying.
I'll join you as soon as I quit the Chinese restaurant.
All right.
I'll get going. Mum is late.
How many boxes did you bring?
Soo Jo, I'll be going first.
- Okay. - Bye.
Three boxes of beer and a box of soju for now.
That's not enough.
I think I can sell 10 boxes tonight.
You can leave some hard liquor, too.
I'll sell you hard liquor in my next life.
Soo Jo, eat some rice cake.
- I can't because I'm busy. - Eat some.
Soo Jo, wait.
(Da Hae's Luxury Chicken)
I think I'm coming down with a cold. I'm not feeling so well.
I'll go to your restaurant later.
Are your feeling for me sincere?
Of course.
Then, let's get married.
Gosh.
I must've been crazy.
I was out of my mind.
I'm so embarrassed. What should I do?
Ms Nam.
I brought this food from Da Hae's opening ceremony.
- This is for you. - Did Da Hae send this?
No. I brought it myself.
Please have some.
My goodness. What a mess.
It's delicious, though.
How are things going with Dad?
It's okay.
We didn't get the papers done yet.
It doesn't feel real since we still live together.
Is it convenient to live by your own ways?
It's hard to turn a blind eye when I'm not blind.
When he tries to cook something,
all the pots and dishes are out in the kitchen.
I don't know where he finds those stuff.
There are even some stuff that I've never seen before.
He should catch on if he tried a few times.
I guess he's a little stupid.
I end up washing the dishes all over again.
Men are all like that.
It's so hard to stop myself from nagging at him...
that I might become a monk or something.
I'm sure he's clumsy since it's something he's never done before.
Just pretend like you don't know.
I'm pretending already.
But I think he's enjoying it.
It was a torture to make food just for others...
when I didn't want to eat.
I like that part.
As I get older, I hate cooking.
Ready-made food is the most delicious.
- Don't you feel that way yet? - I feel like it's a hassle, too.
But I don't hate housework that much yet.
You were born to be a house wife.
After a while, try to meet...
a rich man who will care about you a lot and...
Forget it. Do you still want to sell me off?
Yes.
Let me sell my daughter off and get a fortune.
The past two were bad deals. I want to make a great deal this time.
How can you say that about marriage?
I can't even go to a hotel. I came to a motel instead. How miserable.
Then go to a sauna and sleep comfortably.
How can I sleep in a sauna? Think about my social position.
Then go home.
My brother will beat me up.
Do you want to follow me then?
- Do you have a place to stay? - No. I mean my car.
Forget it. This is all because of you.
I don't want to see you.
I'll try to find the 100,000 dollars.
How will you find that money? Just go. I don't want to see you.
Good night. Make sure you lock the door.
Gosh. It's cold.
Who is it?
Who is it at this late hour? Who is it?
It's me, Dal Pa.
Dal Pa.
- What brings you here? - Hi, Uncle.
What brings you here without notice?
- It's been a long time. - Let me bow to you.
No. It's okay. Don't bother. Sit down.
I couldn't buy anything because it's late.
Go wake up your aunt.
Okay.
Is mum here?
Sit down. Sleep here tonight.
- Don't wake her up. - Did someone visit us?
Aunt, it's me.
- Please give me some food. - I'm not even full awake yet.
I'll do it.
Aunt, Dal Pa is here.
What? When did he come?
A minute ago. He's going to sleep over.
He comes here without notice sometimes.
Why didn't you let me know that you're coming?
I could've made more food for you.
Is your health all right?
Where do you live now?
Do you want more rice?
Don't talk to me and get out.
How unfortunate I am.
He's an annoying guest.
How could he ask me for food as soon as he sees me?
You practically raised him, so he must feel comfortable with you.
I only recently freed myself from cooking for your dad.
What is this in the middle of night?
I feel bad for him because...
he didn't get enough love from his mum and had to wander around.
But I get upset when I think of Mal Nyeon.
What if he ends up living here?
How could she do that to her own child?
- No wonder he disrespects his mum. - Be quiet.
Aunt is in the living room.
I don't mind if she hears it. I didn't say anything wrong.
Dal Pa.
Please make it quick.
It's almost done. Wait a moment, please.
- Please bring me a bottle of beer. - Yes.
Enjoy your food.
You came here to lure my father, didn't you?
You came here pretending to take care of my father.
But your real motive was to get money from him with your daughter.
- Excuse me? - What is this called?
That's right. You're a gold digger.
Da Hae, go sleep in your room.
I need to calculate this.
Do it after you get some sleep. What time did you come in?
I don't know. I worked until early morning.
Go get some sleep first.
I should do that.
Please leave them as they are.
It's this way.
Right.
- Hello? - Come out.
Right now?
Bundle up since it's cold.
Get in.
- Where are we going? - Don't say anything and get in.
This is a hotel.
- Follow me. - Mr Yeo.
You're going to scold me, aren't you?
Are you afraid of being scolded? Just follow me.
I couldn't sleep at all.
Me neither.
I'm sorry. It's all because of me.
My daughter had to take your money, and it became a big deal.
I said something ridiculous because I was angry.
I can't believe I asked you to marry me.
You shouldn't say that just because you're angry.
Gosh.
It's because I'm narrow-minded.
I was upset because she even badmouthed my daughter.
What did she say again?
She called both of us gold diggers or something.
I had never heard that from anybody, so I got furious.
I thought, "Okay, then. I'll marry your dad and crush you."
I told you that since I didn't want to lose to her and couldn't sleep.
Since I got old, I can't control my mouth or anger.
I regretted all night.
I apologise.
Crush her.
- Pardon? - Take it out.
(Report of Marriage)
This is...
a marriage registration paper.
Although you asked to get married first,
I'm the one who will make the official marriage proposal.
What? You don't like it?
I didn't even dream...
about marriage.
You just said it out of anger? Do you want me to take it back?
Thank you...
for making me realise that...
I can still be a man and have passion.
I'm grateful to you, too.
Ever since my husband died,
I never had feelings for any man.
I lived like a log that feels nothing.
I thought I was like a dried squid,
but I realised that I'm a woman inside.
I'd find myself looking in the mirror more often.
Whenever I went to work, I felt my heart flutter so much.
I was embarrassed to feel that way at this age.
You saved me.
It's all thanks to you.
Dreary hospital visits were my everyday life.
Thanks to you, I found happiness and laughter.
Laughing was a rarity for me.
Whenever I think of you,
my heart beats with joy.
Every passing day...
is so precious.
No matter how much I profess my love, it's useless.
Getting the law to support you is all I can do.
Then even without me around, you'll be able to make a living.
This is the most I can do for you.
Don't tire yourself out by working any more.
Stop the milk delivery side job.
Your body is no longer your own.
You belong to me.
You will get scolded if you ever overexert yourself.
What do you want to do the most once we get married?
Hello, there.
I want to shop at the market together.
Are you fit enough to carry a shopping basket for me?
I'm quite strong.
Don't you worry, I got it. What else?
You crazy woman. Do you think your son is any better?
If I ever get into an argument,
can you take my side no matter what?
Are you kidding? Whoever crosses you is done for.
Let's break the news...
to our kids soon.
Then let's hold a simple wedding ceremony...
and live together.
Live together?
Of course. We'll kick the kids out.
It'll be just the two of us.
Didn't you say everyone mistakes you for my wife?
Was that a lie?
Of course not.
Everyone refers to me as the madame of the household.
Hey, Cho Rong.
This is for you.
Let's be good friends from now on.
I'm sorry for what I did.
Jae Soon!
A girl wanted me to deliver this to you.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thanks.
(To Ms Shin, From Cho Rong)
Thank you for everything, Ms Shin.
Please forgive me for giving you such a hard time.
Dad won't allow me to see you,
but I'll be good from now on. Can you please come back?
Let's all live together again.
What are you doing?
It's nothing, Mum.
Are the the documents taken care of?
Yes, I just need to submit them to the district office.
You should've taken care of them right away.
Don't worry about it. I'll take care of it.
Of course, you will.
It's not even your first divorce. I'm sure you're an expert.
Do you really have to spoil the morning mood like that?
Mal Nyeon, didn't I tell you?
If you want to say something,
- think before spitting it out. - Whatever.
Old habits die hard.
No need to rush into getting married, okay?
Make sure to choose wisely.
You want her to get married again?
Just don't.
How can such a young woman live alone?
She's not alone. She has Ddol Ee.
It's not like she makes good money with a decent job.
She needs to get married before she gets any older.
Mum, I'm not going to.
I tried so hard not to get divorced twice.
I'm never going to go through this again.
Then what will you do alone?
She can follow Gab Soon around and clean things here and there.
Watch it!
When you get lonely with old age,
just befriend another divorced woman for comfort.
Become self-sufficient while you're young.
There's no need to cause Ddol Ee more pain.
- I understand. - Just let things go.
Two attempts are enough.
Don't count on the third person to be a keeper.
Don't do that. Marriage isn't a lottery.
But she's been so unfortunate.
Once she gets older, no one will pity her any longer.
Mum, I don't want to get married.
Did Dal Pa stop by last night? I didn't even get to speak to him.
He came in late and took a nap.
He left at dawn.
You should've given him something to eat.
He never eats the food I make.
Where is he nowadays?
It's obvious. He wouldn't sleep here if he had a place to go.
He lives in his car.
The heater in his car broke, so he came without a choice.
I guess things aren't going well for him, either.
He does seem to have a conscience.
Of course, he does.
I told him to come in for the time being, but he refused.
Come in? Not a chance.
If you let him in, he'll never change.
Tell him to rent a place somewhere with his mum.
They're not on speaking terms.
That's their problem.
It's unfortunate for him, but I can't forgive her.
Do you remember all the trouble she put me through?
Life will reward you for your patience.
Living like this is my reward.
I'm so blessed that it's starting to get annoying.
What are you talking about?
Are you going away somewhere far?
I'm not exactly leaving. Just stop worrying for me.
I'm all set up for retirement.
Just take good care of yourselves.
What's with you all of a sudden?
I just need to rest.
I'll be quitting work soon, too.
Good choice, Mum.
Quit delivering milk and your housekeeping side job.
You seem to have saved up a lot of money.
I knew it.
You didn't even bother to invest in my business.
Let's wait and see.
Don't even think of wanting her money.
How much did you save up to take care of your retirement?
- Is it at least a million dollars? - That's chump change.
My goodness.
You're acting strange.
What are you talking about?
You wouldn't quit your jobs for no reason.
Did you win the lottery or something?
I have to start taking care of my well-being.
Doesn't the chairman object to you quitting?
I thought he liked you. Maybe I'm wrong.
What nonsense is that?
You must be full, so go take a nap. You need to go to work soon.
All right.
Come work at our shop sometimes.
The grandpas would love you.
I'm not interested at all.
What do you take me for?
Gosh, Mum.
A director?
You need to start exploring your potential.
You'll be appointed next week.
Take charge of the overall responsibilities.
My daughter will be appointed as the president.
What's wrong?
I never imagined this would happen.
It's unaffiliated with my major. I'm not sure if I'll do well.
One talent gives way to another.
If you were a doctor, I wouldn't have thought of this.
But now, I think the right choice has been made.
No matter what my daughter says, don't let it hinder you.
You have a difficult road ahead, but tackle it head on.
You'll learn from your role and benefit the company.
- Where were you this morning? - I visited the factory.
I had a meeting with some designers.
What business would you have with the designers?
Your father instructed me to go.
I'm the director here.
Do you think I'm unaware of your schemes?
Don't be fooled. My father and I think very differently.
I thought you'd be more sensible.
Why are you so worried? Others would be so envious.
I heard inheriting wealth from the in-laws...
is every man's dream.
You can't complain. It's a tough world out there.
I didn't quit the hospital for this.
Things just happened.
I'm not sure what to do.
How is it going with that guy?
You should know. Dating isn't easy for doctors.
Hello?
I stepped out for a bit.
Grandfather? Right now?
I got it.
I have to get going. I've been called for.
Doctor or not, I guess I just go when I'm needed.
Your humour is so self-deprecating.
Get going.
(Report of Marriage)
(Wife: Nam Gi Ja)
Let's break the news to our kids soon.
Then let's hold a simple wedding ceremony and live together.
What's the occasion, Dad?
We haven't dined together like this in a while.
What should we eat? How about a course meal?
Can I order something expensive?
Of course. Order whatever you like.
I'm getting married.
What are you talking about?
With whom? Were you dating someone, Grandpa?
Yes, you all know her well.
Who do you mean?
Gi Ja.
Our housekeeper?
- There's nothing more to hear. - Mum!
Congratulations.
Sit down.
Do you have something to say?
Did you forget our promise?
I have not.
- Si Nae... - Take it back.
Don't even think about persuading me.
I'm in my 70s now.
I need someone to lean on.
You don't have the right to say that.
Mum died because of you.
A surgery could've saved her.
Nothing could've saved her.
Stop your excuses.
You were scared of the expenses. That was all Mum's money.
If you sold the land, Mum would've lived.
Your mum pleaded for us not to.
She said the living must continue to live.
Do you think that makes sense?
It wasn't easy for me to let your mother go.
It took me decades to get over her death.
I lived my life in repentance.
For over thirty years, my eyes were closed.
It's not a simple dating proposal.
You're speaking of marriage.
That's right.
Who you meet or lean on is not my concern.
But an official marriage can never happen.
I refuse to share this household's inheritance.
Can't you see that she has ulterior motives?
No matter what you say,
my decision is final.
Do you remember me running away...
after Mum passed away?
I was a sophomore in high school.
Of course I remember.
I searched the whole country for a year.
During that time,
I gave birth to a son.
What did you say?
You had a child?
My dear husband, have you been well?
It's been a while.
Isn't it cold?
Thank you for helping Gab Dol get employed.
Da Hae opened her shop, too.
Our children are growing up just fine.
I've done well, right?
I came because I have something to tell you.
Some fellow says he likes me.
He wants to get married.
I'm old now.
I need someone to lean on and be taken care of.
Soon, there will be no energy left in my bones.
Housekeeping is hard work.
When I'm older,
I want someone to eat beside me...
and to look after me when I'm sick.
Will that be all right?
Will it be okay if I don't apologise?
Hello?
It's me, Ha Soo.
We need to meet and talk.
Sure, let's do that.
Let's call it a day.
Let's go Dutch and reward ourselves...
with a nice meal for working on an off day.
I have someone to meet. I'll see you tomorrow.
What's the issue?
I need to confirm your attitude.
What do you mean?
I think it was the day you passed your exam.
Do you know what your mother said to Gab Soon that day?
I couldn't allow Gab Soon to get victimised like that,
so I dragged her away.
But I wouldn't let my girl hear something like that.
What have you done for her?
I don't want to interfere with a 10-year relationship.
But now, I think it's time to act.
From now on, I won't make any guarantees.
You understand me, right?
I made my intentions clear.
- Are you waiting for Gab Soon? - Yes.
Do you even have the right to stand here?
- What? - Why was that girl at your house?
She already seems so close with your mum.
Isn't it because you guys are already thinking of marriage?
If Gab Soon found out, things would get serious.
No matter how I look at it, it's not right.
- Stop it. - Stop what? Am I wrong?
What are you talking about?
What's the thing I shouldn't know?
- Let me explain. - I couldn't stand watching him...
get friendly with a female co-worker outside of work.
I have to make a delivery.
- Let's talk. - There's nothing to talk about.
What's wrong with you? Let go.
My gosh. What's wrong with you?
Just wait one week. That's all I ask for.
- I'll get my mum's permission. - She won't allow it.
I don't care. We're getting married no matter what.
Just give me a week.
I won't believe you no matter what you say.
I'm sorry for being weak and indecisive.
Let's grow old together.
I promise you.
It's been 10 years. Can't you wait a week?
Just one week, all right?
Please trust me this once.
What are you doing?
- Mum... - Hello, Ma'am.
Do I look happy to see you?
- I thought you separated. - Don't do this, Mum.
You head on home. Gab Soon, we have to talk.
Mum.
Didn't I warn you not to meet him ever again?
Are you deaf? How can you be so defiant?
Stop it. Blame me instead.
Go home.
- Gab Soon... - Mum, let's talk at home.
You don't need to listen to this any further.
Goodness.
You sure spent a fortune for Gab Soon.
(European Interior Design)
Hello.
May I help you?
Yes, I understand.
Mal Nyeon, put these books on Gab Soon's desk.
Who was that? A woman?
Yes, it's a woman.
My goodness.
You must be happy that Gab Dol is a public official now.
Congratulations.
I'm not here to be congratulated. I want to ask you a favour.
What favour?
You already know that they're back together again, don't you?
I'm guessing you even encouraged them to get back together.
Did you change your mind now that he's a public official?
- How could you say that? - No matter what happens,
I won't allow Gab Dol to marry Gab Soon.
She's not even studying to be a teacher. She's just a cleaning lady.
Ask anyone who has a son.
Who would allow such a girl to marry their son?
My son is seeing someone.
He's seeing someone?
Yes, she works at the same office as a public official.
She's way better than Gab Soon.
I hope you will set Gab Soon straight...
since you seem to understand what I'm saying.
Isn't this just nonsense?
I understand.
I will make sure they never see each other.
However, you shouldn't say that about another person's child.
What is so special about Gab Dol?
He may have escaped being a loser now that he's a public official.
But not long ago, he was just a loser...
who didn't have a job.
What did you say?
I only said that because you said the same thing about my child.
All people are equal.
Don't you dare look down on Gab Soon.
Who knows how she will turn out?
She might become the CEO of the biggest interior decorating company.
What's so special about being a public official?
What's so special about receiving pension?
At least Gab Soon had part-time jobs.
Gab Dol didn't even have a job. All he did was study, right?
If he didn't pass the test even after that, he's a fool.
- My goodness! - Don't be surprised.
I came out...
thinking that you might want them to get married.
I'm the one who should be surprised.
Do you think it's okay to step all over someone else's feelings?
Even if you beg me to change my mind,
I will not allow Gab Soon to marry Gab Dol.
I'm leaving now.
My goodness!
What's the matter?
I thought you were meeting a woman.
Did she hit you?
- Shin Gab Soon. Come out. - Come out, Gab Soon.
She came in crying, too.
Sit.
What's wrong?
What are you going to do about Gab Dol?
Gab Dol's mother thinks you guys aren't seeing each other any more.
That means he didn't even mention you to her.
He told me to wait one week. He said he will get her approval.
Do you think that will happen?
He told me that he will get married even without her approval.
Stop seeing him.
I want you to end it.
- Dad. - In my opinion,
his mother will never approve.
Gab Dol is not strong enough to overcome her, either.
True. If not, he would've gotten her approval a long time ago.
What could a fool like him accomplish?
Didn't you know that Gab Dol is seeing another girl?
He's seeing another girl?
That rotten scoundrel. He didn't say anything the last time I saw him.
Why did you meet with him?
Did you beg him to take back Gab Soon?
I couldn't stand to watch her being a cleaning lady.
Gab Soon took care of him for 10 years. How can he do such a thing?
But now, he's seeing another girl? What a scoundrel!
People are like that.
People change when they taste success.
He's not seeing her. She's just a co-worker.
I don't care. I no longer approve.
I don't want to be in-laws with that family.
You better become successful in the future.
I want you to be more successful than Gab Dol.
Yes. You must become more successful.
You should marry someone more successful than Gab Dol.
You should live next to him...
and show him how happy you are.
That's how you get back at him.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
How could he leave me standing...
and take her by her wrist and tell her that she doesn't need to listen?
I'm flabbergasted.
You can't count on your son.
Now that he's making money, he's treating his mother like garbage.
You always favoured him over me. I'm glad he treats you that way.
I expected Gab Dol to be different.
Wake up. All sons are alike.
Mothers with sons are all alike, too.
Leave it to me.
I will take care of this.
Your mother met my father.
My father told me to end my relationship with you.
My father has never been this upset.
- What should I do? - What did my mother say?
Mum, this is all you amount to?
You should have stopped when I dragged Gab Soon away.
Did you have to meet Gab Soon's father?
How could you say such hurtful things to him?
What's so special about me?
I'm so disappointed in you.
I can't believe what you're saying.
I'm flabbergasted.
I think he's definitely changed.
How dare you speak to her that way!
Did you become a public official all by yourself?
Don't you know that mum prayed everyday for you?
Stop being so arrogant.
Be quiet.
Don't mention Gab Soon in front of me from now on.
Mum.
I can't leave Gab Soon.
- What? - What?
I was going to wait until you approved.
I know what you had to go through because of me.
That's why I was cold to her.
Gab Soon stood by me for 10 years.
But I ignored her even when all my friends badmouthed me.
It was all because I didn't want to hurt you.
But I can't do this any more.
Mum, I'm sorry.
I am going to marry Gab Soon.
What?
I wonder if Gab Soon understands how her father feels.
Where are you? I heard that you're still not home.
Go home while I'm still nice.
(Where are you? I heard that you're still not home.)
(Go home while I'm still nice.)
I brought some left over sweet and sour pork, too.
Are you not going to go home?
What's your plan?
You know that all this will return to Gab Soon, right?
Let's just drink tonight.
My goodness.
I was afraid of getting hurt again.
I put a wall around me,
even though you are such a kind person.
(Jae Soon)
Can we meet?
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
I feel like I should tell you something.
I thought you were very strong.
It was my first time seeing you cry like that.
I could imagine...
how hard it must have been for you. I keep thinking about that.
Please erase it from your memory. I shouldn't have done that.
What do you think about me?
You don't really know much about me, do you?
We got married only three months after we met.
We didn't have time to get to know each other.
We didn't even date each other properly.
Now that I look back, I have many regrets.
I wanted you to think highly of me because I already had a son.
I wanted to make sure that your children liked me.
I tried to cling on so I could avoid going through another divorce.
I didn't get the chance to get to know you.
You are a very nice person.
I wish I had known earlier.
Do you want to be friends?
- Friends? - I can drink, too.
I know.
I can curse, too. I can be mean.
I've been trying to behave well in front of you.
I had no idea.
I'm not who you think I am.
Aren't you curious of what I'm really like?
If you're curious, let's be drink buddies.
We're similar in situations.
We've been divorced twice. We both have children, too.
You only have 1, but I have 2.
Let's take one step at a time.
Let's get to know each other better.
I don't where that may lead us to.
Here's to being good friends.
Thank you for reaching out to me.
Hello.
- Bye. - Wait.
- Did you see a watch on my desk? - No, I didn't.
I left my watch here. You didn't see it?
I didn't even go near that desk.
You're the only one who entered this room. Who else would take it?
- I didn't do it. - Then who took it?
Are we good now?
No. Let's go to the police.
Why? Are you afraid?
I have to deliver water.
Don't try to escape. Give it to me now.
Then I will pretend like it didn't happen.
Let me make a phone call.
Go ahead. Call everyone. Call your parents.
It's me.
I have to go somewhere urgently. I can't do any deliveries right now.
I will finish even if it takes all night.
Let's go.
I am certain that I left it on my desk.
He's the only one who came into the office. He's denying everything.
Did you look everywhere?
He emptied his pockets,
but who knows where he hid it?
I will go through any investigation.
Let's go and have a look.
Could you take off your trousers?
You found it, didn't you?
I searched him. It's not on him.
That can't be.
I could tell that it wasn't his first time by the way he denied it.
Could you do a background check?
You mean a criminal record check?
Yes, please check his criminal records. I'm sure he has records.
Yes.
Can I see your identification?
I don't have it with me.
Can you give me your registration number and name?
Mum, what happened? Why are you at the police station?
He stole my watch, but he won't admit it.
I can't believe my luck.
I'm stressed out as it is.
Watch? This one?
Why are you wearing that?
I told you this morning that I was going to wear it.
Is this what you were looking for?
You should have been more careful.
He must've been so mortified.
- Please apologise. - Well...
Hurry up and apologise.
The worst thing in the world is to be wrongly accused.
Things like this can happen.
I asked for an apology.
Mum, just apologise. I'm so embarrassed.
It's unfortunate that this happened.
I was just stressed out today.
Instead, I will have you deliver water at my factory, too.
Please apologise properly!
Why are you raising your voice?
Don't you have parents?
I apologised. What more do you want?
Do you want money?
Just let it go.
That's enough. Just leave please.
I don't know how rich you are,
but you shouldn't mistreat people just because they're poor.
Shame on you.
What's wrong with him? Mistakes can happen. What a terrible temper!
You went too far.
You should apologise properly the next time you see him.
You should know better.
Mum, let's go. You should have been more careful.
My son doesn't want me to do this any more.
He's worried that my body will be ruined.
He's already delivering water and alcohol.
He groans all night from the body ache.
You haven't told him, have you?
I was going to tell him before his marriage, but I haven't.
I feel really bad.
What's there to be sorry about? You gave your all to him.
What are you going to do now that you're jobless?
Why don't you work on these?
I'd rather go work at the senior club.
I was going to quit being a waiter.
Can you make a decent living out of this?
It's enough for a pack of instant noodles.
(Dongsan District Office)
- Hi. - Hi.
Are you here to see Gab Dol?
He's not answering his phone.
- Could you give this to him? - Sure.
It looks like underwear. Did you stay out all night?
You can eat anywhere, but you should sleep at home.
Public officials must behave properly.
Did you see him? What did he say?
I didn't even get to see him.
He won't answer his phone.
He seems to be at work at least.
What an ingrate! He refused to see you?
Did they spend the night together?
- What? - Let's see.
What do you want?
How dare you stay out all night.
- What's wrong with you? - Be honest.
Were you with Gab Soon last night?
It's my business whom I was with.
So I guess you were together.
Are you going to live together again?
Whether I marry her or live with her is my business.
You will do it without Mum's approval, is that it?
- I will. - You will regret later.
I didn't realise this before,
but when I look back,
it kills me to think that I made Mum worry.
Mum is the most unfortunate person I know.
She didn't date anyone because of us.
She never enjoyed luxury and worked all her life.
If you cause her any trouble, I will not tolerate it.
I don't care if you're my brother.
It's enough that I made her suffer. Don't add to her suffering.
You and I are not the same.
Why should I pay for your mistakes?
You should worry about yourself.
I have the right.
I have the right to say this to you.
Whenever Mum went to work,
I fed you and took care of you.
I gave up on going to university because of you.
Can't I say this much to you?
I'm not telling you to be good to me.
Be good to Mum, you jerk.
Mum.
Give up on Gab Dol. He's different this time.
I think he made up his mind.
I believe he was with her last night.
He says he'll marry her or live with her.
I don't think Gab Soon will let him go.
Give up on that jerk.
I have to go. I need to open the store.
Gab Soon.
I finished making the ladder.
Do you want to see it?
Are you in the area?
Come quick.
Are you here already?
- Excuse me. - Okay.
- Where was Gab Soon last night? - Pardon?
Come in first.
Tell me the truth.
She wasn't home last night, was she?
What are you talking about?
- Your pants... - My pants?
Oh, goodness.
Since you're here, please come in and sit down.
There's no need for that.
Where was she last night?
Why are you asking me that?
I have to check something.
She went out to do a night cleaning.
A night cleaning?
- That means she wasn't home. - Yes.
How did you raise your daughter?
She seduced my innocent son to spend the night out.
Do you think this makes sense?
Pardon?
Did you think I'd approve of her if she did that?
No way.
What on earth are you talking about?
She cleaned all night and came home early in the morning.
Did you see her cleaning? You didn't, did you?
I didn't, but I'm sure she did.
What's going on?
Why is she here?
She's asking me where Gab Soon was last night.
She has no manners at all!
You're talking nonsense.
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
What are you doing at my house?
- Where is your sister? - She went to buy ice cream.
Gab Soon went cleaning last night, right?
Yes, that's what she said.
It looks like you guys are all in on this.
She tried to hold onto my son by putting on a show...
and saying she was pregnant.
The whole family's plotting, now that my son is a public official.
Plotting? I can't believe what this woman is saying.
Where were you last night?
Tell me where you were.
You went cleaning last night, right?
Did you meet Gab Dol?
You can't answer us because you were with him.
- Did you seduce him? - Tell me the truth.
I cleaned all night because someone was moving in today.
I didn't meet Gab Dol. I ended it with him already.
That's what you say.
Come on, I know you.
Everyone knows that you've been after Gab Dol for 10 years.
Your son was after my daughter!
Get out.
We won't see Gab Dol, and we won't let her see him.
Let's not see each other like this. Please leave.
Yes. That's what I want to say.
Please, I beg you. Let's not see each other any more.
Please don't follow my son and lure him in.
Don't you think I know?
I can see clearly what you're thinking.
- That wench. - Hey.
Let me go.
Did you see that?
Did you see how that woman treated us?
She even rolled her eyes at us.
If you had a proper job, she wouldn't have looked down on us.
She's belittling all of us. Are you happy now?
- Mum! - Come on. What are you doing?
What good did she do to deserve this?
My pride has been hurt. I can't live like this.
If you had lived your life properly,
a woman like her wouldn't look down on us.
Mum.
- Mum. - Get out.
Get out right now!
Okay, Mum. I'll take her out.
I'm so mad.
How can she come all the way here and make a fuss?
I can't believe her.
She thinks I spent the night with him.
Mum even broke the ladder.
What's wrong with Gab Dol's mum?
I'll end it with him.
Can you do that?
I can't go on when my parents are acting like that.
I don't want to break their hearts.
I see no solution for this, either.
Where are you?
I just bought sushi. Let's eat together.
I'll help you clean.
I was going to call you.
Let's meet now.
You read my mind. I'll be right there.
What do you mean?
I told you to wait a week.
There are only three days left. Can't you wait?
Even if they approve, I can't do this any more.
Let's not go the hard way.
Let's stop here.
I'm happy I got to see how you felt about me.
Thank you.
No.
I can't break up with you.
Gab Dol.
I can't win against my parents. I just can't.
We can't break up like this. Do you want me to go crazy?
I won't change my mind.
I tried my best to get a job.
"I'll do something once I get a job."
You were always on my mind.
I could push myself to study hard to make something of myself...
because of you.
Gab Soon.
Without you, I have no life.
To me, success means nothing without you.
I lived for you and because of you.
What am I going to do if you fall apart like this?
I could come this far because you stood strong.
What will I do?
Cho Rong.
Drinking buddy, are you asleep?
Can you come out for a minute?
Mum, are you sleeping?
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going out to meet a friend.
Is your mum fast asleep?
Gosh, I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
It's not like that.
You're here.
- Aren't you cold? - No.
I love eel!
That's why I ordered it.
What about Ddol Ee?
I forced him to go to bed so I can come out.
What about your kids?
I left them at home, too.
They're sleeping with A Young.
Cheers.
I'm not sure if I should say this.
I don't know why,
but my heart was pounding while I was waiting for you.
If your heart doesn't pound for a woman like me,
that means something's wrong with you.
I wasn't going to tell you this,
but I felt the same way.
I never felt this way when we were living together.
What am I going to do? I feel like I'm cheating.
- Here. - Pour me a glass.
It's snowing.
It is!
(Sesak Kindergarten)
Ddol Ee!
(Our Gab Soon)
It's me, Mother. Your son-in-law.
Why did you come to my house? How dare you show up.
He's Ddol Ee's father. Of course he should come here to see his son.
Is it because of Geum Sik?
Where have you been? Did you meet with that doctor?
I heard you two almost got married.
He's a married man. Don't meet him.
How would you feel if Gab Dol married someone else?
I deleted Gab Dol from my life.
Will you be okay with not seeing him again?
I will marry Gab Soon. Please give me your permission.
Is marriage even possible?
I can never let her marry you.
You're acting strange. Did you meet with Geum Sik?
Mum.