BioskopKeren
(Episode 32)
Ddol Ee, do you remember me?
No, I don't.
Did you...
miss me a lot?
I will buy you whatever you want.
I have this much money.
I will buy you everything next time.
Go ahead and eat.
Is Mum doing well?
She works at a supermarket.
At a supermarket?
She works there?
Yes.
Is your stepfather good to you?
I don't know. I live with Mum at Grandma's place.
Are you and your mother living at your grandparents' place?
Ddol Ee, don't tell anyone that we met today.
It's our secret.
Keep eating.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you drinking all the time as if you've failed?
Wake up. Take off your clothes before falling asleep at least.
Leave me alone. Just leave me be!
Are you doing this on purpose?
I did everything you asked me to.
I've become a public official because you wanted me to.
I split up with Gab Soon because you wanted me to.
All that remains for me is to marry someone you like.
What else do you want me to do?
Tell me what to do next. I will do everything you want me to do.
Isn't that what you want?
I want to be alone. Leave.
Mr Yeo, what have you been up to?
You haven't called in a while.
I hope you are not sick.
It's so cold outside.
You are so late. Were there a lot of customers?
It's too early to tell.
It's all about getting loyal customers in the food business.
Why are you still up? Did something happen?
What's wrong?
I don't know why I'm so sad.
Gab Dol has been drinking a lot lately.
He talks back to me. He's never done that.
What does he say?
He says that he did everything I asked him to do.
- "What else?" he asks. - He said that?
Leave him alone. He's sleeping.
How can he say that to you?
I'm just saying.
He thinks it's okay to drink like that since he split with Gab Soon.
Crazy jerk.
He used to cause trouble before...
only to apologise after a few hours.
He's changed since he got a job.
Maybe he's become arrogant now that he's making money.
Money changes people.
At times like this, she would be the answer.
What are you talking about?
Remember that girl who works with him?
If Gab Dol goes out with her, he will forget about Gab Soon.
Has Gab Dol said anything to you?
Don't talk about him. I'm no longer interested in men.
My goodness! Will you live alone for the rest of your life?
Don't be ridiculous. I can't live without a man.
I'm temporarily not interested.
If I meet someone in the future,
I want my family to like him.
I've dated with hope before,
but from now on, I won't date unless I am sure.
I am tired of getting hurt.
My family will like you.
I learned my lesson after going through so much.
You and I live in a different world.
And you're just curious and fascinated with me because of that.
After a while, your feelings will go away.
Our family is not like that.
They told me that they will like whoever I like.
This is why I keep telling you to grow up.
All parents are alike.
Let's not talk about this.
I need to get back on my feet first...
before I think about loving someone else.
Go now.
I will be by your side until then.
I will always be where you need me to be.
Is that okay?
You have a way with words.
You must be starving.
Yes, I will eat some ramyeon.
- I smell bulgogi. - I made it for you.
It's past midnight. Why aren't you sleeping?
How can I sleep when you're not home?
Eat. I'm not sure about the taste because I was half asleep.
It's delicious. You can cook well even when you're half asleep.
That's all that matters.
I will enjoy this food, but tell me what you want to say.
Please grant me one wish.
Can you please stop cleaning?
I know you're frustrated.
You tried to become a teacher, but it didn't work out.
Gab Dol's been acting arrogant ever since he became a public official.
On top of that, his mother doesn't even like you.
So I know that you were desperate to do anything.
I know that's why you started your cleaning business.
But to be honest, even I don't like what you do.
If I were Gab Dol's mother, I would act the same way.
Who would want you as a daughter-in-law?
Sit down.
Gab Soon, can't you get a job at an office...
before you get any older?
You have a college degree.
You can get an office job somewhere...
even if the salary is not much.
If you have a job, it's easier to get married.
Mum, please grant me one wish, too.
I may have started with cleaning, but that's not the end.
I'm interested in interior decorating now.
I stay up all night because I have so many ideas.
I'm really excited about this.
I know you're frustrated. Just give me three years.
I will have an interior decorating firm with 10 employees in 3 years.
If I fail, I will do whatever you ask.
Just pretend like I'm not around for three years.
I see you everyday. How can I pretend?
Then should I get my own place?
No way.
Go inside. Let her eat.
My goodness!
I can't have a normal conversation with you.
I don't like arguing with you everyday either.
Can't you just leave me alone?
I wish you would just pretend like I don't exist.
Did you hear that?
Just go into your room.
Let's just wait and see.
Just pretend as if she doesn't exist like she wants you to.
- Do you have faith in her? - I do since she's my daughter.
She will have 10 employees? How audacious!
She will go as far as you believe in her. That's what I think.
Gab Soon belongs to you, doesn't she?
There's no use in getting frustrated.
Don't you know that by now?
We have no control over our kids.
From now on, just ignore her whether she come in or goes out.
I know that you're sad, but do what he says.
What else can you do?
I'm sorry for asking you to meet me so suddenly.
It's okay. I've wanted to talk to you, too.
I'm not sure if I should say this.
I'm not good with words.
Go ahead. I will try to understand.
You said that you liked Gab Dol from the very beginning.
Is that true?
Yes.
However, Gab Dol doesn't know women very well.
He's always been focused on his school and family.
It looks like he has a girlfriend.
He doesn't have a girlfriend.
They just went to elementary school together.
She's the one who's been chasing Gab Dol all along.
That's all over now.
I don't care about that.
It would be weirder if he never went out with anyone at his age.
You are so wise.
Since you work in the same office, could you...
I know what you're trying to say.
You want me to be more proactive about asking him out...
and letting him know how I feel, right?
That's exactly right.
I said it poorly, but you understood it perfectly.
You are so smart.
And as I mentioned to you before,
I will not meddle with your marriage life, so don't worry about me.
I already have my retirement plan.
Thank you for the first transaction.
I am thankful.
Hi.
How awkward.
Do you want to get some coffee?
We don't have much to talk about. Let's just go our separate ways.
That's fine.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
Wait.
I'm very sorry.
I've been...
meaning to tell you this.
Goodbye.
Alcohol can mess you up.
You must be tired.
I cooked some sweet potatoes. Eat before you wash up.
Let me just put this away.
Don't eat too fast. Drink some water.
Thank you, Jae Soon.
I've been eating too much. I'm going to gain weight.
You should eat a lot since you work a lot.
It must be so hard.
I'm sure you're suffering.
It's something I've decided to do.
You seem a lot tougher than before.
I got beat up so much that I got tougher without trying.
Getting tougher is okay, but it's painful to watch you get hurt.
Gab Soon.
Just ignore what mother says. Just keep doing your best.
I heard that you plan to build a company with 10 employees.
You can do it.
I will do it no matter what. I'll show Mum and Dad.
Have you heard from Gab Dol since then?
We're no longer together.
Jae Soon, I don't have time to meet guys.
In relationships, you have to receive as much as you give.
Now, you have to bear with the break up all by yourself.
Will you be okay?
You've known each other for almost 11 years now.
He's all I've thought about for more than 10 years.
It will take more than 10 years to forget him.
That will be hard.
Anyway, he's no longer part of my life.
How would you feel if he got married to someone else?
I don't care.
Wouldn't you get jealous if he went out with another girl?
It's possible that he can fall for someone at his office.
I don't care.
I'm going to wash up now. I have to leave early tomorrow.
- This is very delicious. - Thanks.
- Enjoy your meal. - Yes.
Why did you come so late? Were you making deliveries until now?
Yes, I was busy making deliveries.
I smell something unfamiliar from you these days.
Something delicious.
It's because I deliver alcohols to restaurants.
Finally, my nose is working properly.
I smell something from the main building...
It's chicken.
Why didn't you say it earlier?
Don't. I'll buy it for you.
The food you get from others is better than the food you buy.
Don't call me over.
Just come out.
I said no. I'm not going to eat.
Are you not going to listen to me?
Close the door!
What's gotten into you? You never do this.
I thought I'd never get to taste your chicken.
This is the last time. If you want to eat, you'll have to pay for it.
How does it taste?
It's good. It's crunchy and flavourful.
Is he not eating?
He doesn't listen to me.
Let him be. Let's just enjoy this by ourselves.
Let's see who's sorry.
You still get anxious whenever he doesn't come in.
Don't wait in the cold. Come in.
Thank you. I thought I was going to freeze to death.
Why are you here by yourself? Where is Soo Jo?
He told me not to call him. He said he won't eat from here any more.
He's finally mature.
He should join us.
Why should he join us?
Gab Dol!
Gab Dol, come out.
What's the matter?
What do you want?
What is this?
What do you mean? I threw it out because it's empty.
This is empty?
There's enough to last us a month.
I don't know about a month, but there's enough for three more days.
You're being so frivolous now that you make money.
Becoming a millionaire starts by saving a dollar.
You should be thrifty with things like this.
Do you think it's easy to make money? Does money grow on trees?
My goodness!
Did someone hit her head?
She's not the type to get hit by someone.
Pay attention and listen to me.
Look.
See this?
I hope you become rich by squeezing that toothpaste tube.
I can't believe you just wasted my time with this.
How dare you!
What's gotten into you?
You used to throw away tooth paste all the time before.
You used to waste soap, too.
I will be frugal from now on.
I saw black bags inside the freezer. What are they?
What do you think? They're food.
- Do you know what this is? - I have to open the bag to know.
That's not acceptable.
You're going to throw them out when they go bad, right?
You should label the bag.
You have to write what they are.
If you keep them in black bags, you'll have no idea.
I learned from using the refrigerator at the store.
You are wasting money this way.
My goodness.
Do you think it's easy to make money?
I can't think enough about money.
Before, I underestimated the value of 10 or 20 dollars.
But now, I don't even take the taxi. I walk instead.
I wonder if the taxi drivers are doing well without me.
My goodness. My daughter has become a female Scrooge.
You used to take deluxe taxis only. Now you're walking.
Even when you dropped a dollar on the floor,
you didn't pick it up because you didn't want to bend your back.
Now, I even pick up a penny.
Mum, I opened a bank account.
This one's for instalment savings, and this one's a deposit passbook.
This is the very first time I have my own bankbook.
With the money I make, I'll give you some for your expenses,
and I'll deposit the rest.
I'll make money persistently...
and bring my kids back again.
I wonder where they live. They don't even pick up the phone.
You don't know where they moved to, do you?
I'm sure they're doing well.
They have their father.
I'm sorry.
Baby!
Baby, later on,
I will come find you no matter what.
I'm sorry.
Until then, please stay alive.
My blood pressure has been seriously problematic for the past few days.
There's nothing I can tell you.
Si Nae, I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I'll beg for your forgiveness for the rest of my life.
That's that, and we must look for your son first.
I already did, but they said there's no way I can find him any more.
I don't even know if he's alive.
I totally forgot about him all this time.
For some time, I tried to forget about him.
After that, I really forgot about him...
as if I never even gave birth to him.
I acted as if he doesn't exist in this world.
I'm so brazen and bad.
You were only 18. You were young.
Don't blame yourself too much. I'm the bad guy.
Thinking that Se Gye might take over the company,
I thought it'd be better to give the company to my own blood line.
That's why I began to look for him.
It's been so long, so I'm not sure if I'll be able to find him.
Let's look for him together.
We'll be able to find him as long as he's alive.
It wouldn't be hard to find a man these days.
Be specific. How much will you pay back each time?
- How much per month? - 100 dollars.
- 100 dollars only? - 100 dollars per month.
There are 12 months in a year,
so let's multiply 100 by 12. That comes to...
1,200 dollars. Multiply that by 10 years, and that's 12,000 dollars.
When will you ever pay back all the 100,000 dollars?
All right, I'll give you 200 dollars.
Multiply 200 by 12. That's 2,400 dollars.
(Are you the famous Jo A Young?)
I'm so frustrated.
Please do something about them.
They're driving me insane.
- Let's go. - What are you talking about?
We've already deleted them.
She can't even go to work because of the malicious comments.
People captured the screen and posted it online. What do you want?
She shouldn't have done that to begin with.
Liar.
Please tell your friends to delete them.
I beg you.
What a poor guy. All right.
Don't live like that.
Let's go.
See? Even middle school kids neglect me.
Let's solve one thing at at time.
What are you doing at this hour?
Nothing. Go back to sleep.
Hey, alcohol buddy. Do you want to grab a drink?
My mum's still awake.
Mum, are you sleeping?
What's up?
- Do you want some water? - No. I'm going to sleep.
I live with Mum at grandma's place.
Mum works at a supermarket.
Is she taking good care of Ddol Ee?
She is. You have nothing to worry about.
Mum.
Jae Soon.
It's freezing.
She really had a hard time falling asleep tonight.
I asked her so many times if she was sleeping or not.
She got mad and said, "Why do you keep calling me?"
She finally fell asleep, but on my way out,
I was afraid that she might suddenly grab me from the back.
I was so nervous.
I need to hurry up and get back on my feet soon.
That way, I'll be able to date you openly.
I feel bad for not doing anything nice to your parents.
They would've hated to have a son-in-law like me.
You finally figured that out? I hated you so much back then.
You couldn't do much because that's your personality.
You know what my personality is like? You said you didn't.
At first, you're cold and unfriendly.
You're not very likeable.
But with time, I realised how genuine you are.
That's correct.
You're so full of yourself.
I shouldn't compliment you.
What about me?
You're a total prude and vixen.
Hey!
I'm kidding.
Go home first.
Please wait a little bit.
I'm saving money at the moment.
I'm going to...
take back my kids, so until then,
take good care of them.
Mum.
Be honest with me.
Where have you been at this hour?
You even tried to disguise me with a pillow.
- I met a friend. - Which one?
You don't know all of my friends.
You can meet them during the day.
Why leave in the middle of the night? You're fishy.
There's nothing to suspect.
I listened to my friend venting about her quarrel with her husband.
I'm an expert when it comes to divorce.
Good for you.
What did you say as an expert?
"Try your best not to get a divorce."
Did you drink alcohol?
I had beer. Go back to sleep.
You didn't go see Geum Sik, did you?
Why would I go see him in the middle of the night...
even if I liked him so much?
I'm not happy with any of my daughters.
You're still awake.
Why in the world are you running about at this hour?
Aunt Nae Shim.
- What? - Give me some rice.
I don't like him, either.
Even my sister-in-law's son treats me like a maid.
What a great fate I have.
Once the soup is heated, serve yourself.
Clean up once you're finished, and don't make a mess.
Let me serve it for you.
I don't want to see you. Go back in.
When you're finished, leave the dishes. I'll clean them up.
Get some sleep and do it tomorrow. You'll faint.
- I'll just finish this. - Are there customers until late?
I should serve at least one more customer.
Don't accept the ones who come too late.
You should look after yourself, too.
What are you talking about?
Who knows if they'll bring their friends next time?
You're a mother after all.
That's how a parent feels.
Look at you, working persistently to take your kids back.
Mum.
I've blamed others all my life.
Even if I did something wrong, I blamed others.
"This is how I am. What do you want me to do?"
I always had lame excuses.
Cho Rong and Da Rong must have been through a lot.
Thinking back now,
my husband must have put up with me a lot.
I wonder how he managed to live with a person like me.
When I think back on the past,
I have a lot of regrets.
Regretting won't make any difference now.
It'll only break your heart. Forget it.
I liked your report. It's much more clear now.
Continue working like this.
- Revise the ones I've ticked off. - All right.
Congratulations. It's your first monthly pay cheque today.
- I know. - It's great, isn't it?
Let's go buy your mother a gift.
Pardon?
Please give me a pair of female long Johns.
You don't know her size, do you?
You must have received your first monthly pay cheque.
- What is her size? - It's...
She's 162cm tall and 50kg.
She's a bit slim with an average figure. Am I right?
Kind of.
Then this will do.
You should get one more for your sister.
See? You got nice gifts because of me.
You couldn't go in alone and ask for female long Johns, could you?
You owe me a favour.
You know you should return the favour, right?
How should I return it?
Buy me a beer this weekend.
I'm excited. The most delicious beer is the one a male junior buys.
I hope your mother will like it.
She will.
My gosh, I'm wearing long Johns that my son got me.
It's my first time in my life.
- My goodness. - Gosh, how old-fashioned.
- What's up with the red long Johns? - What do you mean, "old-fashioned"?
I've wanted to wear these long Johns so much.
Every time my friends bragged about their children getting them...
red long Johns with their first pay cheque, I was so jealous.
I wanted to get one for myself discreetly.
I better go out and brag tomorrow.
I'll get you another one, so wear it often.
- Is there nothing for me? - Of course, there is.
Hey!
I still care about fashion. You're treating me like an old lady.
You should wear this.
It's cold, so wear this. Wearing red underwear will bring you money.
Really?
If wearing this will bring me money, I'll wear 10 of them.
Can I wear yours, too?
No, you can't.
Thank you, Gab Dol.
- What will you get for me? - I'm not spending a penny.
Even if it's freezing outside, I won't buy clothes.
You said you'd pay for expenses. You make money, so pay a lot.
I'll give you enough money.
You're better off than I am, so I'll take advantage of it.
What a Scrooge.
Gab Dol.
Since you received your pay cheque, spend some money at my store.
- What a Scrooge. - Come on!
Both of your names should change...
to Ms Scrooge and Mr Scrooge.
A parcel came for you earlier.
What is it? I was going to open it, then I decided not to.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
This must be really expensive. Who sent it?
- It's from Gab Dol, isn't it? - Please leave.
Is it the last gift from him? If you won't wear it, give it to me.
- Get out. - Gab Soon!
I'm leaving.
Come on.
I promised I'd get you a ring with my first pay cheque,
but things turned out like this.
I picked out a necklace for you.
It's not a cheap one. I got it at the department store,
so don't throw it away on the street.
Take care and don't get sick.
Eat well.
(Mr Yeo)
- It's me. - Come on outside.
There's nothing wrong with my age
Age doesn't matter when it comes to love
What are you talking about?
You trust me, right?
If you do, stay calm for a while. Don't contact me.
Is it because your daughter is not approving of me?
I was worried about that.
It's not like I was on good terms with your daughter.
I would have felt the same way.
I would also think that some woman is after my father's money.
It's not like that.
Mr Yeo.
Let's not walk the difficult path.
Do you mean you want to break up?
You said you trust me. Then trust me.
I promised to take care of you.
There's no need.
I can take care of myself.
If I can't, then I'll just die.
I have no regrets.
What are you saying? You're too young.
Don't think otherwise.
It's because I can't give a definite answer at the moment.
It's only because you can't say you want to break up with me.
I have that much sense.
I'm only a housekeeper, and I didn't learn much.
But I do have enough sense to know how you feel.
While you get paid by me, listen to me.
I won't any more.
Don't talk any more. I'll be going.
Is it true or not?
Is it reality or a dream?
You're back.
How about some drinks?
Drink up.
Is something wrong?
Did someone run away with your money?
Is Gab Dol living with that girl again?
You don't usually drink alone.
But at a time like this,
I cant help but drink.
How am I as a woman?
That never crossed my mind.
I swear that I never have.
When you give me food,
I imagined twice that if I live with you,
I won't ever be hungry.
I mean, three times. However, I haven't thought more about it.
I'm being honest.
You're not my type of woman.
So you're saying I'm not that attractive.
I don't know anything about that.
Just don't think of me the wrong way.
I didn't mean anything when I brought rice cake for you last time.
I actually brought it for Soo Jo.
But he didn't want to eat it, so I gave it to you.
Don't think of me that way.
That's scary.
Can...
I leave?
Could you sing one song for me?
A song?
What song?
Will that be all?
Sing a song for me and eat the mandarin.
Okay.
What about my age
Not that song.
The song with the lyrics that says, "I don't know why I'm like this".
Sit down and sing it.
I don't know why I'm like this
I have no idea
I can put a finger on it
I have a sorrowful heart
I know I shouldn't
I know we're strangers
I don't know why I'm like this
I have tears in my eyes
- What are you cooking? - Kimchi pancakes.
Don't stare and go back in.
It's not easy to make.
Leave me alone. I'm making it for myself, not for you.
I knew it.
You shouldn't use perilla oil.
It's nice and savoury.
Who doesn't know that?
It's expensive.
Everyone knows that it's tasty.
This is for frying pancakes.
You have these.
Soy bean oil and corn oil.
Don't you waste perilla oil.
I was able to get just two bottles of perilla oil last autumn and...
couldn't even use a drop of it because it's so precious.
You usually can't find things.
How did you know where the perilla oil was?
Which do you love better? Perilla oil or a person?
Perilla oil.
It's not tasty if it's thick.
Don't expect much from me.
It's better to be good.
Leave it. This is who I am.
A person is precious for being that person in itself.
It's not because he's talented, rich...
or good at something.
That's what I think nowadays.
Who cares who I am?
Who cares what my job is and how much my yearly salary is?
I'm precious just by the fact that I am alive.
My goodness.
Don't lose your focus and just cook those pancakes.
Leave it. I'm the only person who's going to eat it anyway.
Who cares if it's not pretty or neat?
Even if it's ugly, it's all right if it's tasty.
Don't expect much from our kids, either.
Just be thankful that they never got in an accident and got hurt.
It's a blessing that they're alive and well beside us.
They did their part when they were little.
What did they do for us?
We did all the work raising them.
Did you forget?
We...
were happy thanks to them.
We laughed when they took their first step.
They made us happy when they first started talking and went to school.
Thanks to them, we lived without knowing the difficulties in life.
They did their part by doing that.
I never wanted them to do anything for me.
I just want them to be the best for themselves.
You're right. I didn't want anything from them when I gave birth to them.
I just wished that they'd be healthy and well.
Then you wanted them to get good grades,
a good job and earn lots of money.
Don't be greedy.
That's not the problem. Your pancakes are getting burnt.
My goodness.
It is getting burnt.
I can't bear to watch this.
What brings you here?
You wouldn't call. I was worried that something might've happened.
I was worried you were sick.
I'm not sick. Something came up recently.
Have you eaten yet?
I have some money.
Why? Is it not tasty?
It is tasty. I'm just not hungry.
You must be happy that you have a son.
He says that he'll drop by to say hello.
He says that he's nearby.
I can't wait to meet him.
Did you fire your housekeeper?
She's at home all day these days.
Yes, I did. I don't like her.
I see.
- That's why. - Do Geum. Can't you move?
The place is cheap and nice.
I'll get you a house. I wish you'd move.
Si Nae. Why do you care for a person like me?
I was a bad person who tried to pull a scam on you.
You aren't a bad person.
There are people who try to exploit one's wealth using their family.
But you didn't get to do anything.
It's obvious seeing that you still live in room for rent.
- Dad. - You're here.
He's my son.
Say hello. This is my girlfriend.
I'll be going.
Soo Jo.
Leave him.
What's wrong with him? Excuse me.
Soo Jo. What's wrong?
Don't you like my girlfriend?
- Don't meet that woman. - Why not?
There's something about her.
- Do you know her? - I don't want to talk about it.
Don't ask any more questions. Just stop seeing her.
She lives in a totally different world from us.
I'm busy. I need to get back to work.
What's his reason?
He won't say. He just told me not to see her.
I wonder why.
Will you stop seeing her just because he doesn't want you to?
Yes.
That's just your son talking. She's still your girlfriend.
That's not how I live my life.
If my son doesn't agree, I won't see her.
Jae Soon.
Come here.
- Look. - What is it?
Gab Dol must have given it to her.
Gab Soon didn't sleep all night because she was crying.
Can I keep this necklace?
It's such a waste. It looks expensive.
Aunt. Don't be funny. You know what she's going through.
Let's go.
Isn't that your friend?
Let's go. This is uncomfortable.
She must be on a date. They look great together.
What are you saying? They looked awkward.
She went on a blind date not long ago.
- She went on a blind date? - That's what I heard.
You must be keeping in touch with her.
Our friends have a chatting room.
Where should we go now?
How about we go see my parents?
Mother, I'm here.
What brings you here?
I missed your food, Mum.
- I'm here. - Hello, both of you.
Yes, Father. Hello, Aunt.
Did you not bring any presents?
What do you want to eat?
Joong Nyeon, let's eat sujebi.
How about sujebi?
He wants sujebi.
Not you. I was asking Se Gye.
There's no point in trying to satisfy your kids.
Your husband should always be number one.
I like sujebi. I was thinking of it on my way here.
As if you were really thinking of that.
I'm the loner in this house.
Should I make the dough, Mother? I can do that.
You've never done anything like that. Just sit and wait comfortably.
My goodness.
You change your mind so easily.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about your attitude toward Gong Joo.
Now that Se Gye will definitely receive the wealth,
don't you just love Gong Joo?
It wasn't because I didn't like her. I was just teaching her a lesson.
If an elderly tells her something, she should follow it.
That's what is good for her.
She needs to know the basics to raise her own kids.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Mr Yeo will appoint me as the chief director.
I guess he wants you to take more responsibility.
He wants you to engage in the company's business...
and learn how to manage things.
- But... - What's wrong?
Is your mother-in-law unhappy about it?
It's difficult to keep the balance.
You should listen to Mr Yeo first. He's the eldest.
It must be difficult to work with your mother-in-law.
You must be worried.
What are you doing?
I'm looking through Se Gye's old photos.
Se Gye was handsome even when he was little.
This is your husband when he was a baby.
He's really cute.
My goodness.
I don't know if she got married or not.
They broke up when they were still in love.
Who?
Se Gye's old girlfriend.
They were going to get married, but they couldn't.
I should help out with the cooking.
Me?
I think it would be best if you talk to him.
I feel bad for Gab Soon.
I think she broke up because she doesn't know how to handle it.
She must be having a hard time. I heard that she cried a lot.
Gab Dol sent her a farewell gift.
What should we do with them?
- Should we just let them be? - Jae Soon.
This just isn't meant to be.
He'll feel more comfortable talking with you. Just go and talk with him.
Even if it's the end, it still feels strange.
I thought they were meant for each other.
I thought so too.
(Se Gye)
- Se Gye? - Did you get off work? Let's meet.
I have plans.
Really?
I was hoping we could meet today.
Couldn't you take a rain check on that?
Is it urgent?
- It's about Gab Soon. - Gab Soon?
Okay.
Can I buy you drinks next weekend?
Okay. Buy me twice as much instead.
Thank you. Good bye.
It must be your first time at a bar like this.
Yes.
Do you usually come here?
I used to in the past, but I haven't been able to these days.
I heard what happened.
I heard your mother came and our family had a fight after that.
Father made a ladder for Gab Soon to use at work.
But Mother broke that.
I heard that she told Gab Soon to end things with you.
I didn't know the details.
I'm sorry about my mum.
There's no need.
Let me ask you one question.
Will you be all right without Gab Soon?
Even if you break up with her and never see her again?
That's what she wants.
Gab Dol, you know my story, right?
I had a girlfriend that I went out with for a long time.
I met her as a freshman and thought I'd marry her.
But we broke up.
- I know. - I couldn't go against my parents.
I don't have any right to say this to you.
But don't do something you'll regret later.
Once you let someone go, they don't come back.
She says she's not confident.
She's not confident to go against our parents.
I told her to give me one week to settle things with my mother.
She says she doesn't want that.
I think it's best for her...
to let her go now.
You don't know Gab Soon, do you?
I think I know what she's thinking.
Since we were young, I was closer to Gab Soon than I was to Jae Soon.
We didn't have much of an age difference.
So I think I know how she feels.
Have you ever told Gab Soon that you want to break up with her?
- Yes. - How many times?
- Once. - Because you didn't like her?
No.
I just didn't want her to have a hard time.
She slapped me 10 times after I said that.
That's exactly how Gab Soon feels right now.
That's the only thing Gab Soon can do at the moment.
To a guy who thinks so dearly of his mother,
how could she dare ask you to pick her?
Especially when you've become a public official.
My parents are also disapproving because they're disappointed.
The most important thing at this point is your attitude.
Gab Soon's opinion doesn't matter.
Women tend to think that breaking up is the answer.
Welcome.
It's the first time you asked to meet. What's up?
- Invest in me. - What?
I'm thinking of getting an office and officially starting my business.
Review it. I wrote up a business plan based on my experience.
I told you to invest in me when I'm confident.
I'm confident now. Review it and call me.
(Business Plan for Sparkly Clean Gab Soon)
- There's no need to review it. - You shouldn't invest in anyone.
I wasn't following you around for no reason.
I was watching over your work.
I've already reviewed your business.
I will talk to my father and proceed.
Really?
I take that back.
It's kiss to celebrate this investment.
Dal Tong, does Gab Soon really love me?
You're so foolish.
Everyone knows that except you.
If she didn't love you, she would have left you a long time ago.
I'm the only one who didn't know.
If you don't like her, can I take a shot at Gab Soon?
I liked Gab Soon ever since elementary school.
Who hasn't liked Gab Soon among our friends?
Everyone held back because of you.
Even your names show that you belong together.
Dal Tong and Gab Soon don't go together very well.
Gab Dol and Gab Soon sound perfect.
Even though we've dated for 10 years,
I still feel like I don't know her.
Even you and Se Kyung know her better.
From now on, I won't believe her.
You will believe the other girl, but not Gab Soon?
Poor Gab Soon.
I will do whatever I want from now on.
I will make decisions from now on.
(Realtor Office)
There is a clean office space.
It's not very expensive.
What do you want?
Let's meet.
I don't care about the declaration you made before.
Stop seeing Gab Soon.
You told me to take action.
I'm going to start today.
I am making it clear to you.
I will take care of you...
until I am able to.
I promise.
This is...
a petition for a marriage license.
You brought up the word about marriage,
but I'm going to make the proposal.
It seems like he's doing all right.
He stirred my heart for nothing.
I misjudged him.
No, he's not changed. I just made a wrong decision.
I was so foolish.
Why did I think that he would be...
interested in a widow like me?
He must have thought I was such a fool.
I hope you are miserable, you rotten scoundrel.
For now, we cannot make a conclusion.
It's been so long that it's hard to find him.
Find him no matter what it takes.
Whether he's dead or alive.
If you find him, I will give you double.
- Yes, I understand. - Please hurry.
Where is my Thermos?
Have you seen the Thermos?
Jae Soon took it with her.
She put doenjangguk in it.
Doenjangguk? Where did she go?
How can I say this?
You are so dim.
I can hear the wailing.
I've been through it all. I'm living proof.
Is he meeting Geum Sik?
- How is it? - This is it.
Your doenjangguk is fantastic.
Eat. You have to get going soon.
I wish I can spend all day with you.
My heart is pounding.
Do you only work in the mornings?
I work in the mornings because of Ddol Ee, but more when it's busy.
Are Cho Rong and Da Rong doing well?
What's wrong?
We agreed that we would become good friends...
and slowly get to know each other better.
I don't want to talk about our children.
Let's focus on ourselves when we're together.
I remember the first day we met.
I feel so foolish when I think about that day.
As soon as we met,
I asked you if you could raise my children properly.
How could you like someone who says that?
Even I think that was ridiculous.
I only considered your status.
You weren't bad looking.
Your body is not bad either.
Not bad?
I can't eat.
What about me? What did you think of me?
- You looked sexy. - Really?
Do you not like being sexy?
Why wouldn't I? I love it.
I've never heard anyone say that before.
People say I seem nice and wholesome.
I'm tired of hearing that.
They say I will make a good wife.
We've agreed. Let's not talk about kids.
When we meet, let's act like people without kids.
I'm young, and I have no kids.
Hold it still.
- My goodness! - Go open the door.
Why can't you do it? Who is it?
- It's me. - Who could it be?
My goodness!
It's me, Se Bang.
- Father. - Oh, my.
What are you doing here?
Mr Kim, put those down here.
What's going on?
- Wait for me downstairs. - Yes, Sir.
Let me properly greet you.
Please sit down.
Let me bow.