BioskopKeren
He bought meat, fish and fruit.
He even bought toys for Ddol Ee. How amazing.
You're still the same.
You are known for your generosity.
You seem to have bought the whole store.
I should bow to you properly.
Don't bother.
I don't know what to do now that you're here all of a sudden.
What are you going through everything?
Whenever he came to visit,
it was as if Santa Claus came to us.
That's why we all used to wait for him.
I didn't prepare separate gifts for you two.
I'll prepare them next time. Yours too, Aunt.
Are you going to buy me a fur coat?
You just bought one for your mother-in-law but not for me.
You look healthier now.
It's because I led a well-regulated life there.
You don't lead a well-regulated life.
You always come home late at night and drink a lot.
- I'm not like that any more. - Are you...
well now?
Yes, since I lived a well-regulated life.
Where have you been? You didn't contact us at all.
I was not able to because Jae Soon told me not to.
It seems like you earned a lot of money,
seeing that you even have your own driver.
You look much better now.
My business is going very well now.
What do you do?
(Jeon Se Bang, CEO)
Gosh. I'm watching a noble CEO...
sitting right in front of me.
Se Bang, you're going to give me some allowance, right?
Mal Nyeon.
Here you go.
How kind of you.
You brought me lunch. I should do at least this much.
This is delicious.
I don't want to get interrupted while we're alone.
You'll be directed to voicemail.
Please speak after the beep.
- You haven't changed at all. - Of course.
Goodness.
What kind of a business does Sebang Company do?
We do construction, imports and many other things.
What do you import?
Why are you asking so many questions?
I'm just curious.
Did you get married again?
Would he have come here if he got married?
You're quick-witted as usual.
I had no chance to meet a woman there.
- Where is that? - Pardon?
He was in China.
Yes, I was in China.
Then how did you get Ddol Ee's paperwork done there?
Father came to see me.
When did he go to China?
He came to Korea briefly,
and I met him at the airport to talk about that.
You try to know too much.
It's time that Jae Soon came home. Give her a call.
What for?
You should get going.
I'm sorry we had to meet at a convenience store. Just wait.
If my business gets better, let's go to a fancy place.
A date at a convenience store is not so bad.
- I'll text you later. - You'll be in trouble if you don't.
Please get going.
I'd like to go far away with you today.
My heart is fluttering.
Let's go to a ski resort someday to see snow and have a snow fight.
- Sure. When the kids go on... - Be quiet.
We don't have kids, do we? We didn't even get married yet.
When did you get out?
I got out of there a month after you visited me.
How could you come to my house? What were you thinking?
I wanted to see you and Mother.
No, you didn't.
Why would you want to see the parents of your ex-wife?
It's not like we bumped into each other on the street.
I met Ddol Ee.
He told me that Jae Soon works at a supermarket...
and that he is living at your house.
- Did she get divorced? - Yes, she did.
Then what happened to Ddol Ee's family registration?
They got divorced right before they registered.
That's great. Why did they get divorced?
There are various reasons why a married couple gets divorced.
They had a hard time because of the kids from both families.
I'll take care of Ddol Ee from now.
I'll come to see him as well.
I can't stop you from seeing your own child,
but if they find out that you were in jail...
Are you saying a man with a criminal record doesn't deserve to be a dad?
I'm not a shameless, petty criminal. I ended up like that doing business.
Whatever the case,
it is true that you were punished because you violated the law.
It's already the second time and you can't guarantee the future.
Ddol Ee is still young. You can't take care of him.
If Jae Soon finds out, she'll go mad.
They say your attitude changes after urgent things are taken care of.
You're not the exception.
When you visited me to talk about Ddol Ee's registration,
you didn't turn a cold shoulder like this.
You broke your promise. That's why.
You said you won't come to see Ddol Ee.
It was you who told me to come to see him any time.
I have a right to see my own child.
I don't want to become uncomfortable with you any more.
Please be nice to me next time.
What did he say? Why did he say he came?
He said he came to see Ddol Ee. Don't have any false hope.
He says he came for Ddol Ee, but I think he thought of Jae Soon, too.
He didn't even get remarried.
Don't get ahead of yourself. You don't even look nice from behind.
Since he looks rich, has a driver...
and is a CEO, do you now see him differently?
- That's not what I was saying. - What's wrong with that?
Who would hate money?
By the way, even though she doesn't, I look pretty from behind.
There were many guys who followed me after watching me from behind.
But they all ran away after looking at your face. Don't criticise me.
- Didn't he say anything else? - No, he didn't.
You guys are so materialistic. You go crazy about money.
Does money show all of one's ability?
Money is what makes a person attractive.
Even when one is short and ugly, if he has money,
he'll look attractive. Don't you agree?
Tell me about it. You don't have to look at his appearance at all.
Even my family is like this. I have no right to criticise others.
They got divorced because they wanted to.
That's in the past.
How can I ignore him when he came to visit us? He's Ddol Ee's dad.
Of course, we can't.
Maybe, they're just meant to be after all.
Be quiet.
You should be happy since you're so popular.
Once a man goes, another man comes to see you.
You never run out of men.
What do you mean?
I heard you made soup for Geum Sik.
No, that's not true.
What's this then?
I made some soup to eat at the supermarket.
I shared it with my co-workers.
Ddol Ee's dad came here just now.
He's rich, and he became a CEO.
He even brought a chauffeur. He looked splendid.
He was like that back then, too. He's such a show-off.
He looked better than before.
He seemed to have come here to see you.
He must be crazy. I don't need to see him any more.
She seems to be totally into Geum Sik.
Geum Sik? He's a stranger now. Don't call him by his first name.
- What should I call him then? - Just call him Jo.
Jae Soon is totally into Jo.
Stop it already.
- Enjoy your food. - Thank you.
Bye.
Come again, please.
- Bring us a beer. - Yes.
Please enjoy.
Hey, let's have some drinks since there are no other customers.
I'm sorry, but I don't sit at my customers' tables.
I can't drink, either.
Stop acting shy and drink with us.
You look like you drink a lot.
Please enjoy.
Hey, did you get married?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
Gosh. She's completely ignoring us.
- Hey! - Go easy on her.
If you become my girlfriend, I'll come here every day to buy food.
How dare she?
Hey.
Are you going to ignore your customer like this?
She's making me lose my appetite.
What are you doing?
You punks.
I tried to tolerate you because I wanted to earn money, but I can't.
I didn't put up with you because I don't have a temper.
I swallowed my pride only to be nice to my customers.
Am I married?
Yes, I'm married. What are you going to do about that?
I even have two children. Do you have a problem?
I'm not going to sell food to jerks like you.
So don't ever come near my restaurant.
If I catch you one more time, I'm going to kill you.
Let's go.
Why are you home so early? Didn't you get any customers?
Mum.
What? What is it?
Did something happen?
You should've called me.
Those jerks.
They must've looked down on you because you run the store alone.
That's what makes you sad.
I thought about calling the police,
but I couldn't because I might lose customers over it.
Those crazy punks. If they do this again, I'll kill them.
You're so amazing, Mum.
You sold all kinds of stuff...
and raised two children by yourself when you were so young.
I still didn't sell alcohol.
This is what I was worried about.
I was worried that...
guys would bother you if you sold alcohol by yourself.
But I thought you'd handle it well because you worked at karaokes.
Can't you change your store to something else?
Are you crazy? I can't quit just because of some guys.
I'm on a roll these days.
I live here with you,
and I don't even raise my children.
All I do is run a store, but it's so hard.
How did you overcome all those hard times?
What were you thinking when overcoming them?
I didn't even have time to think.
I was just struggling to feed you and Gab Dol.
Whenever guys bothered me,
I held back my anger and cried alone at home.
I didn't realise this before,
but the person I admire the most isn't King Sejong or Yi Sun Shin.
You're the person I admire the most in the world.
There is nothing about me that you should admire.
I just did what I had to do to take care of my children.
Now I regret what I did.
I should've been a better mother.
Will Cho Rong and Da Rong...
come and see me when they grow up?
They will.
Kids always come back to their parents.
They'd be furious when they do. They'd want to get revenge.
They wouldn't even want to run into me on the street.
I'm not scared of anything else,
but I'm so scared of Cho Rong and Da Rong.
Have you eaten?
It's cold outside, right?
You're late.
Come and sit.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Are you going to talk to your mother at all?
I don't want to.
What have you been up to these days?
I've been doing things to make money.
Gab Soon asked me to work with her, so I'm thinking about it.
Don't just think about it. Do the cleaning job with Gab Soon.
Even if it's hard, you should do something you're not ashamed of.
I made kimchi soup.
Why don't you eat it with some rice while it's hot?
I also fried an egg. It's your favourite.
Every problem a child has is 100 percent the parents' fault.
Are you going to let him wander off like that?
Why don't you just move out and live with your son?
Do you want that?
He doesn't even eat the food I make. I can't live with him alone.
He doesn't eat the food I give him.
I'm scared of Dal Pa, Joong Nyeon.
He's my son, but I feel uneasy and uncomfortable around him.
I sometimes forget about him when I don't see him,
but when I do see him,
it drives me crazy.
Try living with him alone.
If you do, he will have to talk to you eventually.
Isn't it obvious? He comes here to sleep.
He doesn't have a place to go.
You should rent a room or something and move out.
I don't want to have two people sponge off of me.
I wanted to have a simple life. That's why...
Joong Nyeon and I don't even eat together any more.
You should've been better to him.
You ordered him around when he was little.
If I were him, I would hate you, too
I feel frustrated when I see you.
Gosh. What a lonely life.
Clean here.
Here, too. Brush these parts well.
My mum wants you to clean these stairs well.
Okay. I'll clean them thoroughly.
- Is this a follow-up service? - Yes.
Is it profitable to provide a follow-up service?
It gets dirty even after a day.
I'm doing it to get regular customers.
I introduced you to my mum because we went to the same high school.
If you do a bad job like this, she will scold me.
She promised me that she'll give me this building.
If you do a nice job, I will introduce you to other people, too.
Look at the dirt here.
Here, too.
I guess you should eat well to keep up your strength.
Yes. I eat a lot these days.
Please tell many people about my business. I will do my best.
You're only a cleaner. Don't you dare to see my son.
I'm having a hard time already.
Everyone else may badmouth me and point their fingers at me,
but you should understand me. I don't have a choice.
This is the only thing I can do without money.
Mum. Please give me three years.
I'll succeed no matter what.
What are you doing?
I'm making some rags for Gab Soon.
What's going on?
She said she'll become a cleaner and succeed in three years,
so I went to see what she's up to.
Her friend from high school was nagging her,
and she was crouching and cleaning the stairs.
Her friend had her arms folded,
pointed her foot and ordered Gab Soon to clean.
She said, "Do a good job. I guess you should eat well."
But Gab Soon only said yes.
She was swallowing her anger and tried to satisfy her friend.
She was doing something I can't even do myself.
I wanted to drag her out of there, but I didn't.
It's good that you didn't.
It'll make her grow up.
She'll grow up a lot.
How great would it be...
if I can give my children money when they're having a hard time?
I can't do that, so I'll just make her some rags.
Do you still have things to say to me?
No, right?
You must've come for the necklace.
Wait here. I'll go and get it.
Don't touch me. It offends me.
Did it feel good to shop for your mum's gift with that woman?
Your mum must've been so happy.
Her future daughter-in-law gave her underclothes.
Why don't you lie to me again and say she's just your colleague?
Did she pick out the necklace, too?
Was it thrilling to lie to me...
and fool around with her instead of working?
That's right. I told you to go.
But how could you really go right away?
Do you call yourself a man?
I'm not hearing anything you're saying right now.
Of course not.
You only hear the words of that woman.
Are we done here?
Don't ever show up in front of me.
I'm going to visit your parents this Saturday.
What?
I'll ask them to approve our marriage.
- Don't get cute with me. - I'm not.
- I know you can't. - I can.
Do you think my parents are easy?
You can't even convince your own mum.
Do you think my parents will...
gladly approve of you if you tell them that you'll marry me?
I told you. I don't hear anything you say.
I'll handle it in my own way.
You've trusted me for over 10 years.
Why don't you trust me one last time?
Are you crazy? Don't you dare come to our house.
I'm done talking.
I'm not here to convince you.
I just didn't want to surprise you later.
Bye.
Gab Dol! You must've gone crazy!
Mum, I'm home.
Here.
They're rags.
Rags wear down, too. You need good rags to clean.
You can't clean well with rags that are worn down.
Did you make them yourself?
Children are always trouble.
Your dad made you a ladder, and I made you rag.
Everyone is supporting you. If you don't succeed, I'll kick you out.
Mum. I can't believe you made me rags.
I'm so touched.
You shouldn't be. Just try to eat well.
You can't do anything if you're weak.
Also, if someone gives you a hard time, just quit.
You'll be fine even if you lose one customer.
You're wrong. Word-of-mouth reputation is very important.
I will never succeed if I stand on pride.
I put my pride in the fridge before I go to work. Didn't you see it?
What should I do? I accidentally ate it for dinner.
When I was pregnant with you, I had such an amazing dream.
You said you didn't even realise you were pregnant.
What are you talking about?
I prayed so hard to have another daughter.
It was such a great dream.
What was it?
A tiger.
A huge tiger like this came into my arms.
It's still so vivid.
I'm sure you'll succeed.
I'll succeed no matter what. I'll live up to the dream.
I have something to tell you. Come out for a second.
Dad.
It's hard to lie about a dream.
How can I resign as her parent?
Someone invested in your business?
Yes. I was going to wait until the opening ceremony,
but I was so touched to receive rags from Mum.
I'm looking for an office to rent.
That's why I asked Dal Pa to work with me.
- Did he say he'll do it? - He said he'll think about it.
I told him to just do it.
You'd better not order him around just because you're his boss.
Gab Soon. Don't worry and order him around. I have your back.
Are you done with driving practice?
Yes. I'm going to buy a used car.
I'm looking for a small car.
How much would that be?
Why do you ask? It's not like you're going to pay for it.
A usable car would cost at least 1,000 dollars.
I will...
buy it for you.
- Really? - Do you have money?
I saved some money to take with me when I die.
I should use that.
Dad!
(Sparkly Clean Gab Soon)
If you're going to do that, do a better job.
Gosh.
Mind your own business and go on your way.
Go ahead and try.
This is for Dad,
and this is for you, Mum.
- What are these? - They're vitamins.
You don't have money. You shouldn't have bought them.
If I make a lot of money, I'll buy you something better.
I couldn't have started my own business if it weren't for you.
You support me and stood by me. That's why I could start this.
I feel like I have everything.
Live until you're 100 years old, and don't get sick.
I'll take care of your health for my own sake.
It looks like I can't get sick because of my daughter.
I told you children are always trouble.
Who is it?
It's me.
Is it Se Bang?
I don't know which of Jae Soon's ex-husband it is.
Mal Nyeon. When you think of something...
All right.
I shouldn't just say it,
but think about it one more time before I say it.
My gosh.
Oh, my. What brings you here, Gab Dol?
Let's see. It's Gab Dol.
Your future son-in-law is here, Nae Shim.
Hello. Please take these.
Goodness. What's all this?
Now that you're a public official, you spend a lot of money.
This is your first time bringing us something, isn't it?
Gosh. Your sons-in-law bring you a lot of things these days.
- You won't need to spend money. - Why are you here?
I came to tell you something. Let me make a bow to you.
We don't need your bow.
- Forget it. - Why bother to come? It's all over.
It's not over. Please let me make a bow to you.
Since you're here already,
say what you want to say. Don't make any bows.
He wants you to talk and not make bows.
I'm sorry for all the trouble I caused you.
Things turned out this way because I didn't handle matters like a man.
I hope you would forgive me for the things I did.
I want to marry Gab Soon. Please let me marry her.
That's enough. I don't need to hear more.
She doesn't need to hear more.
Please trust me one more time.
I know I looked shabby when I was studying,
but now I can have my own family and take care of Gab Soon.
You only talk big.
How are you going to take care of her?
Can you even marry her?
I wasn't opposed to it at first.
You remember that, right?
When you were studying, I made good dishes for you several times.
If you consider that, you can't do this to Gab Soon.
Your mother barged in here and threw a fit. I can't have that.
Even if we're okay, what are you going to do with your family?
Your mother is against it. Can you convince her?
I'll convince her no matter what.
What if you can't? Are you going to let Gab Soon down again?
Even if she doesn't approve,
I'll marry her.
Why do you kids always cause trouble?
If you can't convince your mother, just give up.
I can't let my daughter marry that kind of family.
Why would she marry you when your mother isn't welcoming her?
Besides, you should consider your mother's hard work...
and give up on Gab Soon.
We and Gab Soon don't feel comfortable about this.
Of course not. If they give away Gab Soon to that family,
there will be tears in everyone's eyes.
I'll think about it if you say you are confident to convince your mum,
but I can't approve of it now.
Don't sweat it and just end it here.
He wants you to end it.
It's natural for you to say so.
I will marry Gab Soon no matter what.
Please believe me.
What brings you here?
I told you that I'd be visiting your parents.
What's the matter with you?
Just trust me and follow my lead.
Now that he makes money, it's different.
Even when your parents were being so harsh on him,
he didn't even move a muscle.
He said he will marry you no matter what.
Bring this to table number three.
Mum. What brings you here?
I came to help you.
Why are you here?
He came to deliver the beverage, and I asked him for help.
What if rumour spreads?
- What rumour? - People might misunderstand...
that he's your pimp.
Mum. It doesn't matter if rumour spreads or not.
I don't care what people say. I should make him work.
I'm here now, so you can go.
Goodbye, then.
Don't spend so much time with him.
He only delivers water. What are you going to do with him?
It's not what you think.
How bad is it?
I think I'm getting sick. I can't stand it any more.
I need to take some medicine.
You should quit working at the restaurant.
Working at a restaurant is tough even for young people.
There's no other way. I have to work.
If I quit the job, no one will pay me anything.
I thought you already had a plan for retirement.
- What? - That's what you told me.
You said you already have a plan,
so we should only worry about ourselves.
I thought about it, and I don't think I have enough money after all.
I need more money if I'm going to live until I'm 100 years old.
You said a million dollars is nothing.
I need 100,000 dollars more.
Do you even have 900,000 dollars?
Mum, quit the job.
I will make money and feed you.
That's the last thing I want. No matter what happens,
I will earn money for myself.
You'd better work hard and pay off the debt.
He said I could take my time.
The later you pay, the more interest you will have.
Did something happen at his place?
I'd rather have you work at his place than at a restaurant.
Didn't you say it's comfortable and nice there?
Stop talking about that place. It's annoying.
Why?
Did he say something?
Those people don't even care about people like us.
They probably hired someone else already.
My gosh. My goodness.
- Relief Patch. - Yes?
Mr Yeo!
I got you.
It's because you can't say you want to break up.
I can take care of myself, so don't mind me.
Mr Yeo.
I was passing by and just wanted to check how it's going here.
It's going all right.
I'm a little busy now because the store is opening soon.
Have a seat here. I'll be done soon.
Don't bother. I need to go somewhere.
Have some chicken before you leave. I'll cook some for you.
Everybody says it's tasty.
Next time.
Is your mother well?
- No. - Why?
Is she sick?
She's working at a restaurant these days.
She's sick,
but she insists that she needs to prepare for her retirement.
She's so stubborn.
I remember her saying that she enjoyed nursing you.
But I heard you have a new nurse now.
What?
Yes.
Can my mum start working there again?
We already hired someone, so I'm afraid that's not possible.
What's up?
What are you doing, Mum? You're not working today, are you?
I'm taking a day off because I'm sick.
Why don't you come out and go on a date with me?
I'll buy you dinner.
Don't bother. You should save money.
I want to introduce someone to you.
What?
All right.
No. I'm not going to meet you.
Let's end this thing between us today.
You must come. I'll text you where I am.
What are you talking about?
Gab Dol.
I've never been to such a nice place in my life.
Even the entrance looked really fancy.
The customers looked really classy, too.
Help yourself.
How much is the meal?
Is it about 100 dollars?
It's not that expensive. Stop talking about money.
I'll spend more time with you and take you to fancy places like this.
I'll buy you delicious food and nice clothes.
I'll also send you on trips.
Hearing that makes me proud of you already.
Mum, you had a tough life.
Whenever you visited my school,
you had to come directly from work.
So when other mothers dressed up and looked nice...
I would be wearing my work pants...
and a shabby jacket.
Back then, I used to be embarrassed of you.
But now, it breaks my heart because you can't...
live like they do.
I'll be nicer to you.
I'll treat you well.
I don't ask for much.
Just get married to a nice girl...
and give me a grandchild. That's enough to make me happy.
You said you're going to introduce me to her today.
Yes, she's coming today.
She said she fell in love with you at first sight.
You guys must be meant for each other.
You're both government officials, so you'll have a decent life.
You'll receive a good amount of pension as well.
Mum.
Please grant me one wish.
Could you let me choose whom I want to get married with?
Then I'll do whatever you want me to do. I mean it.
What are you talking about?
Is the girl you want to show me...
That's right.
It's Gab Soon.
You jerk.
She's the girl you wanted to introduce me to?
I can't believe you'd do something like this.
Do you really want to hold onto a man like this?
Fine. Let's see who wins this game.
Mum!
She's right. I can't believe you'd do something like this.
Did you think a sudden meeting like this would solve everything?
Is this what you meant by solving things?
Didn't you see that coming? You should've at least asked me.
I just wanted to end this somehow.
I thought they had to meet to come to a conclusion.
It just became worse for you.
I feel bad for your mother who's been trusting you the whole time.
I feel bad for Gab Soon as well.
My mum doesn't know anything and wants me to learn from you.
But I'm not sure what I can learn from you.
This is so frustrating.
Let's go drink.
Mum.
Can you please let it go just once?
Your son is suffering so much.
What do you want me to do?
I can't leave Gab Soon. I can't break up with her.
I promise that I'll treat you well.
Could you please let it go just once?
I'll be nice to you.
I promise.
Cho Rong, Da Rong.
- Ms Shin! - Ms Shin!
How have you been doing?
(2016 International Beauty Exposition)
I'm afraid this company isn't on the list.
I'm sure it is. Could you check again?
It's not on the list.
Are you sure you made the final confirmation yesterday?
Pardon? Yesterday?
Didn't you check?
Well...
I thought it was confirmed.
We don't have enough booths, so we sent the emails again.
Only those who replied to the email got invited.
This is so unprofessional of you.
It's not like you to make such a mistake.
You know how important this expo is for us.
It would've been a great chance to promote our products.
You should've checked it yourself.
What brings you here?
I came here to make you some food.
The kids just ate and went to study. Did you eat?
Is something wrong?
No. I'm just tired.
Tell me.
I can't help you, but it'll make you feel better.
I'll get upset if you don't tell me.
My work isn't going well.
Be patient.
I don't usually say this to anyone,
but I have a feeling that things will work out well for you.
I told you that you met my criteria.
It's hard to satisfy the criteria.
Actually, I didn't get a booth at the expo.
I prepared everything, but I didn't do the final check last night.
I'd be happy with just a small booth in the corner.
Put your coat on.
Pardon?
You can't be like this.
You have to do your best until the end.
You have to be tenacious. You're too mellow.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Okay.
Mum, I'll be home late because of work.
Did Ddol Ee have dinner? Please put him to bed.
Are you really coming home late because of work?
Of course. I'm busy. I have to go.
Excuse me.
Jae Soon.
Please help me. Is it really impossible?
You're still here?
I told you that we're full. There aren't any booths left.
That's why I asked you to do a final check.
Please help us.
We have three kids.
If this doesn't work out, my whole family will starve.
He just needs a small space in the corner.
Please help us just this once.
There's a small space in the corner,
but it's not exactly a booth.
Just let us in. We can set it up really quickly.
You persuaded me. You can go inside.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you!
What are you doing? Hurry up.
I totally misjudged you.
How are you going to run a business like this?
You need to be more professional.
What are you doing?
You're still awake?
Where have you been?
The lights were off at the supermarket.
- Were you with Geum Sik? - Why would I be with him?
We turned the light off so that the customers won't come in.
Mum, I'll cook rice and go to bed.
Go and sleep.
(Jae Soon)
Jae Soon, you saved me.
(Jae Soon, you saved me.)
I'm dead because of my mum.
(I'm dead because of my mum.)
Come in.
Mother! I'm here to eat.
Welcome.
Se Bang is here to eat.
I missed your cooking, Mother.
Here.
You don't have to.
What about me?
Here it is.
My goodness. Thank you so much.
You're a big spender. You're so tall and handsome.
What else?
He has a big heart, too.
You can stay and meet Jae Soon when she comes home.
She should quit her job at the supermarket.
She should.
Father, let me pour you a glass.
Who drinks during the day?
Finish your meal and leave quickly.
This isn't comfortable.
Jae Soon's home. How long has it been since you've seen her?
They never saw each other after the divorce.
What are you doing?
He's obviously eating.
Se Bang's been waiting for you...
Come out.
She wants you to come out.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof.
Why did you come to my place? You have no right.
Don't be so cold. The weather's cold enough.
Do I need a right? I just wanted to see Ddol Ee.
You wanted to see Ddol Ee?
I've been through so much after our divorce.
You're shameless to show up here.
I almost died repaying the debt you left me with.
I know.
I know that he married you and paid off the debt.
It broke my heart when I heard that.
To think that you married someone you didn't love for money...
It wasn't like that.
You should've waited for me.
You got divorced so soon because it was a forced marriage.
You don't look like it, but you're quite short-tempered.
You got divorced because of me, right?
What kind of trash are you spitting out?
You don't have to explain. I understand.
Let's discuss our relationship slowly.
I'll take care of Ddol Ee first.
Move him to a different day care centre.
Send him to an expensive one.
I'll give you money.
Whatever. I don't need it. Don't ever come back.
- I'll take the responsibility. - You have no right.
I'm his dad.
What did you say in court when we got divorced?
You said he wasn't your child.
You said you won't pay for child support and you won't see him.
I said that out of anger because you so desperately...
wanted to get a divorce.
Anyway, stop being angry.
I have a legal right to see Ddol Ee.
I now want to be a dad, a son-in-law...
and a husband.
Shut that mouth of yours.
How can you let him in?
You know what I've been through because of him.
How can you eat with him like nothing ever happened?
I told him to leave several times.
I'm sorry I didn't kick him out.
You know how he smooth he is with his words.
He's Ddol Ee's dad. He has to come here to see his son.
- Is it because of Geum Sik? - Mum.
You should call him Mr Jo.
Se Bang is better than Mr Jo in many ways.
He's Ddol Ee's real father.
This is how it's supposed to be.
How can you say that?
Do you think I have no brain?
You don't need any other man.
Your child's father is the best husband.
I'm going to say this just once.
I don't want to talk about him ever again.
Is Jae Soon seeing Geum Sik?
She didn't even like him before, but now, she's head over heels for him.
She's having an affair...
with Mr Jo.
What's bothering you?
- It's not normal, is it? - Your blood pressure isn't normal.
Are you taking your medication?
- Sometimes. - That's not good.
You have to take it regularly and make sure not to get stressed.
How is he?
I'll have to monitor his blood pressure.
Don't appoint Se Gye as the chief director.
That's not right, Dad.
I know.
Find him first, and we can discuss it then.
Don't let Se Gye work on any important company work.
Aren't you busy these days?
I thought you were getting promoted.
I turned it down.
- Why? - I still have lots to learn.
I don't know how businesses run.
What would the employees think if I became the chief director?
I'll learn first and transition slowly.
Where have you been?
Look.
What is it?
Don't you like it? Try it on.
It looks great on you. It's pretty.
Where did you get this from?
You couldn't have paid for it.
Si Nae wanted to say sorry, so she got this for you.
This didn't do anything wrong. Don't throw it.
Give it back to her. I don't need it.
Tell me what's wrong.
- I need to know. - Ask her yourself.
Soo Jo.
Is that true?
I was mistaken.
It wasn't something serious.
It wasn't something serious?
I mean,
it wasn't a big deal. I apologised.
I bet my son has never been that humiliated in his life.
Imagine how shameful and miserable he would have been.
He had to undress himself at the police station...
and got strip searched. He was treated like a thief.
Imagine how...
My son doesn't deserve to be treated like that.
I'll leave change for the coffee.
Where have you been?
I was at my parents' house. I told you on the phone.
Who were you with last time?
That night when you drank.
I told you I was with Gab Dol. It was because of Gab Soon.
Weren't you with that woman?
- Gong Joo. - What's between you two?
She's just my friend from college.
- Be honest with me. - I'm being honest.
Where did you get this?
I heard you two were planning to get married.
And you tell me that she's just your friend?
You thought I was a fool?
I may be young, but I'm not a fool.
Let me ask you this.
How are things between you two now?
You are not saying anything. I'll think whatever I want.
Hello.
What brings you here?
I have something to say to you.
Don't meet Se Gye. Don't even call him.
Se Gye is a married man. I'm his wife.
Please watch yourself.
Eat.
Hey.
What's wrong with you? You want to see Mum faint?
What are we going to do with him?
He's being so cold.
He doesn't care about us at all.
Leave him be. We'll see who wins.
You haven't had breakfast, right?
If you fast, you won't have any energy to work.
I got lunch for you.
Ms Kim.
Do you have feelings for me?
- Yes. - I have a girlfriend.
We're going to get married soon.
Thank you for your kindness,
but I can't pay it back.
I'll take the lunch just for today.
Thank you.
Don't be nice to me from now on.
My son doesn't deserve to be treated like that.
Your son really can keep a secret.
I guess you two are done, then.
That's not the important part.
I feel so bad for my son.
If it weren't for me, he wouldn't have been humiliated like that.
I should tell him.
What difference would it make?
He won't have to suffer because of me.
His life won't be any different.
You must be mad at me. I'm sorry, Professor.
Please, let me see your son one more time.
I want to ask for his forgiveness.
- Who is it? - The creditor.
I thought you didn't have any debt.
I might have no money, but I never borrowed any.
That's incredible, you know.
Do you want to go dancing?
The atmosphere's great.
There are women in their 40s to 80s.
Forget it.
Where are you going?
I'm going to a year-end party with my co-workers.
Are you going to get back late?
We'll have dinner and go to a karaoke. I might be a bit late.
Are you really going with your co-workers?
Yes.
I'm leaving, Mum.
Don't go out at night. Stay home.
Where are you going? It's as if you're going on a date.
It's something like that.
- Are you seeing somebody? - That's not it.
I'm getting suspicious.
You look brighter these days.
It's none of your business.
- Good luck, Dad. - What do you mean?
I know everything.
Me, too.
Good luck, Dad.
My heart started pounding when you asked me out.
I've never dated anybody.
That's a lie.
You're good at this.
I'm serious.
I got married both times right after going on a blind date.
That's not something a lady should say.
I wish it was snowing.
Who do you think of when you open your eyes in the morning?
My customers.
Same here.
When I open my eyes in the morning,
I think about how many customers I'll get today.
And then?
The lady at the convenience store.
She's weird.
She always arranges the items different from how I want it.
- And then? - And then...
- The lady at the supermarket? - No.
I think about the landlord who lives a level below me.
She comes upstairs sometimes and yells at us.
I need to save up so that we can move back to our old house.
And then?
That's it.
You're so mean.
Who do you think about, Jae Soon?
I'm not telling.
Come on.
I do worry about somebody as soon as I wake up in the morning.
I wonder if he's eating right or keeping warm.
I wonder if it's difficult for him to start everything over again...
and whether something's bothering him.
It's as if he's a child.
It saddens me.
For goodness' sake.
I told you to give it to me. Give it to me now!
I can't give it to you for free.
I told you that I can't give it to you for free.
Hey!
Don't you know who I am?
How would I know you?
Pay me. It's 38 dollars.
Look at this woman.
Don't come near me. I'm going to kill both of us.
You're busted. How dare you mess with me?
What's this?
Let go of me! He hit me first.
- My goodness. - You're back again.
He hit me!
He was threatening her with a beer bottle so I hit him to restrain him.
No, I hit him.
What's it called? When you protect yourself from an attacker?
- You mean self-defence? - Yes, that's what I did.
He wasn't the one who hit him.
I did.
When are you ever going to stop?
He goes around to restaurants where there's only women.
You can give your testimony and go.
I'll do it. You can go home first.
My restaurant's a mess.
I have to clean up for tomorrow.
I'll clean up after leaving here.
Go home.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm hungry. Should we eat something?
Let's go there.
Okay. It's on me.
Let's invite your landlord to eat with us.
Madam, would you like to go on a date? I'll buy you chicken.
I'll be fine.
Let's go. I can do it.
- That hurts. - It was supposed to.
Welcome.
Let's go.
Sit here. I just have to clean up this side.
What would you like?
How's draft beer and chicken?