BioskopKeren
I didn't know it was your ex-wife's restaurant.
I didn't know, either.
Let's stop talking about that.
Okay. You should go home.
Goodbye. I'll text you before I go to bed.
What are you doing?
Hello.
I thought you had a gathering with your coworkers.
Did you even lie to me to meet him?
I met him briefly after the party.
Do you think this makes sense?
I already told you not to meet her. You should listen to me.
You're already divorced. Why won't you let her go?
It's not like that. Let's go, Mum. You should go, too.
You already gave her a hard time when you lived together.
If you know that, you should let go of her at least now.
Because you're broke and there is no one to do the housework,
are you trying to use her to take care of your kids?
Why are you doing this?
This just isn't right. Don't you have any conscience?
Let's go, Mum. You should go.
- Just go. - You idiot.
He's doing this because he thinks you're easy.
You should know better than this.
Why would you meet another man when Ddol Ee's dad is back?
I can't believe it. You're not a teenager, you know.
You are 40 years old already,
but you are not mature at all.
Can't you tell which is the right choice for you?
Why would you get on a bus with a flat tire?
You should be jumping out of it.
Who got on a bus with a flat tire?
Who else could it be? It's your oldest daughter.
Geum Sik...
I mean, Mr Jo was with her, and they got caught by Nae Shim.
I'm so upset.
She is completely out of her mind.
He's only luring her because he needs someone by his side.
You should meet him yourself and tell him to stop.
Have a seat.
They're both grown-ups. Scolding them won't solve anything.
They're madly in love.
Are you really in love with him?
She went out to meet him in the middle of night.
She even lied to us to meet him. That says it all.
Tell me honestly about how you feel.
You guys got a divorce.
I'm sure you have a good reason behind seeing him.
You don't date someone because there's a reason.
It's your emotion that matters.
You see them because of your feelings.
Stop talking nonsense.
Why does it have to be him?
Tell us frankly.
Do you really have feelings for him?
- Yes. - See? I told you so.
I didn't know him that well when we lived together.
I didn't know anything about him and didn't have feelings for him.
But after I got divorced with him...
Did you fall in love with him after you got divorced?
Please let me talk.
I just recently realised that he's a really nice guy.
You are crazy.
What a load of nonsense.
What kind of a nice person would give you such a hard time?
You used to tell me that he's nice and that I should go back to him.
The situation is different now.
What's different? He's still the same person.
He doesn't have any money.
You grew old, but you know nothing about life.
You don't know how precious money is.
You only remember things that are beneficial to you.
That's what she is good at.
So what is your plan?
Are you going to live with him?
No.
Please leave this up to me. I'll handle it on my own.
You must be out of your mind.
Why don't you punish her?
I also think Geum Sik is a nice person.
You are making it worse.
But...
you already ended things by getting a divorce.
You don't have kids between you.
And each of you have your own kids to take care of.
You already tried living with him.
You shouldn't meet him without having a plan.
I don't really have a plan at the moment.
This is why I always tell you that you're immature and thoughtless.
Do you think you're young enough to fool around like that?
You should meet the right guy before it gets too late.
Or just get back together Se Bang.
Don't mention him again.
Please leave this up to me.
I am 40 years old.
I don't want to be controlled by parents any more...
like an elementary school kid.
My goodness.
Did you hear what she said?
She's totally head over heels for him.
She's completely in love.
Stop it!
You should get back together with Ddol Ee's dad.
Why would you meet a man who is penniless?
You'll be directed to voicemail.
Please speak after the beep.
I'm home.
I don't know.
Didn't she say anything to you?
No, she didn't.
We don't talk these days.
Did she say she wants some fresh air?
She just suddenly told me that she wanted to get some fresh air.
I knew it.
She is not persistent at all.
She said she'll save money for her kids.
She even had a fight at her restaurant with some jerks.
It's not her first time running away from home.
I thought she was doing quite well this time.
Gosh.
Don't mind her. She'll be back after a while.
Soo Jo, are you sick?
Lie on your stomach.
I'm okay. Get back to sleep.
Go on and lie on your stomach.
What are you doing?
Your rent is not overdue any more.
Is something on your mind?
I don't know why this house is so full of worries.
Can you give me five minutes?
Why?
Make it quick, please. I have a lot to deliver today.
This is the money you have earned so far.
I only paid the rent and saved all the rest.
Get a nice studio and start living alone.
Are you upset with me?
It is uncomfortable to live with you.
I have my own life, but you won't let me meet the woman who likes me.
You're not doing this because of that. Tell me the truth.
I don't want to live with you any more.
Since you're all grown up, live your own life.
It's not time for that yet.
I can't afford to do that.
I don't want to see you grunt every night any more...
just because you deliver water and liquor all the time.
- I won't grunt. - You don't need to feed me.
You even got humiliated at the police station.
Without me, you can live a nice life by yourself.
Please leave.
Even without you, I have to work to make a living.
Listen to me. You don't have to suffer because of me.
I'm not suffering!
I'll come home early. Let's have dinner together.
I'm not your dad.
I'm not your biological father.
I should have said this earlier, but I didn't want to hurt you.
I was also afraid that you might leave me.
Soo Jo.
Soo Jo. Geum Soo Jo.
Dad. They found him.
Did they? Where is he?
I told them to come home. I'll be there, too.
Okay.
- I'm nervous. - Hey, don't be.
You better pull this off well.
What if we get caught?
Don't talk too much. If they ask something, just say yes or no.
- How old are you? - I'm 32.
- When is your birthday? - December 3.
If they ask you anything else, say that you don't remember anything.
Just do what we always do at the police station.
I know. I just have to remain silent.
If you do a good job, all of their fortune will come to us.
There she comes.
Put on a sad face. Cue.
Put on a sad face and keep it that way.
Keep pretending.
Goodness, Ms Yeo.
This is your long-lost son.
Mum.
You were alive, my son. You were alive all along.
- Mum. - You brats.
You punks.
- What is it, Dad? - They're swindlers.
They're doing this to take our money.
- You little punks. - Goodness.
Wait. Wait for me.
Don't cry.
How could they think of doing something like this?
Some people even try to take money from people who are dying.
Let's report this to the police.
It will get complicated if this goes public.
People who are after money will gather like ants.
I also want to use mass media to find him.
But I can't because of people like them.
I bet they'll even manipulate genetic test results.
What should we do then? How can we find him?
Let's not rush ourselves. Let's do this step by step.
I'm sure we'll find him.
I would've found him if I tried sooner.
It's my fault.
While I was leading a decent life,
I bet he resented me so much.
It was a rough day today.
Can we meet for a moment?
I think I'll feel better if I see you.
- Is it Soo Jo? - No.
Why did you tell him that?
He's going through a lot because of me.
What if he goes to find his biological parents?
Then I should let him go.
I hope his parents have enough money to feed him.
Soo Jo would be miserable if they end up to be poorer than me.
What if he suffers there, too?
I'm 100 percent sure he will.
They must've abandoned him because they didn't have enough money.
He'll still live a rough life even if he does find his real parents.
We can't do anything about his fate.
Why did you even bother telling him that?
You just caused your own trouble.
My goodness. What a fool.
I'll get going. Call me if something happens.
Gosh.
You'll be directed to voicemail.
Please speak after the beep.
Soo Jo. I bet you're quite shocked, aren't you?
Just forget what I said.
Don't think of anything else.
No matter what happens, you're my son.
You are my own son even if the world ends.
I take back what I said...
about me not being your biological father.
- Where should he put this? - Over here, please.
The office looks nice.
They're all used, but they look fine, don't they?
- You're so frugal. - I have to be frugal to survive.
Say hello. This is my cousin. This is my investor.
Aren't I your boyfriend, as well?
Stop joking.
Hello. I'm Choi Ha Soo.
I'm Go Dal Pa. I have a funny name.
So do I.
Let's go out. I'll treat you to celebrate your grand opening.
I ordered Chinese food already.
Delivery.
Goodness.
My goodness. I'm so sorry.
- You should've quickly avoided me. - Dal Tong.
It was my mistake.
- Where is Gab Dol? - Why would he be here?
You should have come sooner.
You should've gotten here earlier to congratulate your future wife.
Be quiet.
Dal Pa. It's been a long time.
- How have you been? - Good.
- Who's your boyfriend? - Neither of them.
Dal Pa, let's eat. We need to go clean in the afternoon.
Mother.
I invited you, but there is nothing much to eat.
No. I like this kind of food.
I starved for a week after we made an appointment.
People say it's delicious once they try it, but I'm not sure.
- Try it. - Thank you for the meal.
It's delicious, Mother.
I'm relieved then. Help yourself.
Will your parents like Gab Dol as your husband?
Don't you think they'll oppose your marriage?
What is there to not like about Gab Dol?
You're so sweet to say that.
I like you more than Gab Dol.
My mum can't cook delicious food like you.
Well, she's a teacher. I'm sure she's busy with work.
Gab Dol doesn't know I'm here, right?
I didn't tell him because you didn't want me to.
- What's up? Have you eaten? - I grabbed a bite.
Don't just grab a bite. Eat properly.
- What's up? - I came by because I missed you.
Liar.
I'm sorry for yesterday.
Don't mind what my mum said.
She's not really like that, but she uses harsh words.
My siblings and I also get shocked and hurt often.
I understand her.
I have something to ask you.
Are you seeing Ddol Ee's dad these days?
No. We got divorced years ago.
Then why did your mother say that?
He came to my parents' house to see Ddol Ee.
We didn't meet alone.
I just saw him because he came to our house. Don't mind him.
I guess it bothered you.
I don't know why I feel like this.
I couldn't sleep.
I can beat every man in the world,
but I can't do anything with your ex-husband.
He's Ddol Ee's dad.
He's just his biological father.
You couldn't sleep?
My gosh.
I'm serious.
You should experience it yourself to understand me.
What do you mean?
When you once met your ex-wife behind my back,
I felt the same way.
When I think of that, I want to drag you to a remote place and...
And what?
I'll leave the rest to your imagination.
She is just my kids' mum and that's all.
He is like that, too. I don't have any feelings for him.
He means nothing to me. I mean it.
Okay.
(Saesak Kindergarten)
Ddol Ee.
You haven't forgotten me, have you?
- It's me. Cho Rong. - Hello.
How have you been?
You've grown so big. You look handsome.
I made this at school.
I made it for you.
Here.
I brought you candy. Take some.
"Ddol Ee, I'm sorry for everything."
"I regret I wasn't friendly with you when we lived together."
"Let's be good friends from now on."
"Ddol Ee, see you again. Goodbye."
What is this nonsense?
I can't believe he made his children do this.
It doesn't seem like they were made to do it.
It looks like she made it at school.
Perhaps she was reminded of Ddol Ee.
It's not something kids can think of doing.
How could a person be so cunning like that?
Ddol Ee can hear you.
Ddol Ee.
Even if you hear it and you know, pretend like you don't know.
We don't have ears.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
That's right.
We've been through the Korean War.
We've been through everything.
Let's go to our rooms. Let's go.
Let's go.
Watch what you say.
Geum Sik wouldn't do anything like that. Don't you know him?
If you're urgent, you can do anything.
Since it's difficult to live alone with two children,
he's trying to get Jae Soon back to take advantage of her.
It's been a while since they got divorced. He's not our son-in-law.
Why are you so against Ddol Ee's father?
He's Ddol Ee's father.
Plus he's in love with her.
I won't allow him.
Don't bring him up any more.
Grandfather, do you feel all right?
Not really.
You don't look happy.
Do you want to go shopping with me?
I can't be bothered to do anything.
About Se Gye...
I hope you appoint him as the director of the headquarters soon.
It's not pleasant to see him do petty chores.
Mum keeps bossing him around.
It would be nice if he works as the director of the headquarters.
I'm considering that.
I will make it happen soon.
What is that?
It's the sample for the new product.
Hang it up over there.
Yes, Mother.
Call me Director at work.
Okay, Director.
I really don't understand you.
You should have stayed as a doctor that everyone looks up to.
Why would you want to do this?
You must have other reasons.
- What are you doing? - I'm making kalguksu.
My goodness.
- My gosh. - Joong Nyeon.
What happened?
You're at it again.
- It's because of you. - Oh, my.
Go in. You'll be stressed when you see me cook.
Do you at least know?
There's no need to be stressed. He'll clean it up.
- Bring a rag. - Okay.
You should just eat the food I made.
I don't understand why you want to cook.
Isn't it tiresome?
I'm into housekeeping these days.
A hobby late in life is more dear.
Go get the door.
Okay.
What brings you here?
Hello, Mother.
Are you hear alone? What about Se Gye?
He's at work right now. I'm here by myself.
You come and go by yourself now.
You didn't bring any presents?
- Pardon? - How could you...
come here without any presents?
You should at least bring some candy.
What did your mother teach you?
You're not like me.
Should I go buy some candy?
My goodness.
I'm here to order you some food.
- Order food? - Yes.
I'm not a great cook, so I'll order some food and get brownie points.
- Where's Father? - In the kitchen.
Joong Nyeon, your daughter-in-law wants to order you food.
Father.
You're here.
Do you clean the house yourself?
I sometimes do it to workout.
Father. Would you like jokbal, pizza or sweet and sour pork?
You can order anything you want.
There's no need for that. We can fix a meal at home.
Your rich daughter-in-law wants to buy you food. Don't turn it down.
When will you get served food like this?
Stop it.
What do you want to eat?
I'll buy it. Order anything you want.
No, I really want to buy it for you.
Let's let her treat us.
If you can't cook, you should at least do this.
She wants to please us.
Great.
We were about to starve since somebody spilled the flour.
Let's order.
What would you like to eat?
Let's order sashimi.
Your father-in-law will do anything for sashimi.
Then I'll start off with sashimi that Father will do anything for.
You shouldn't repeat what she says word by word.
Mother, what would you do anything for?
Mal Nyeon.
What brings you here?
I came to see Chief.
I wasn't going to come here again.
It's great that you came.
How does the hospital air feel like?
It's like perfume. It's wonderful.
What did Chief say?
He told me that I'm always welcome to come back.
So?
You know what I'm good at.
Smiling?
I fell in love with you because of that and look at me now.
You have a way of making jokes...
out of sad stories.
Are you done?
Let's go for some drinks.
I can't today.
I have plans.
Your blind date?
- Is it going well? - It's not bad.
I don't expect it to be passionate at this age, but it's all right.
We would have eaten already if we made kalguksu.
Why isn't it coming?
Joong Nyeon loses his temper if he gets hungry.
Hello? We ordered food, but why isn't it here yet?
Okay.
Did they say they're on their way?
I knew it.
- Is it coming? - Yes.
I feel more hungry...
waiting for food like this.
Bring us some soju or some snacks.
Don't be like that in front of your daughter-in-law.
Joong Nyeon, you're getting...
your mouth ready for good food.
It's me.
It's been a while.
Really?
My goodness.
Oh, my. That's what you heard?
Hold on. I'm on my way.
- It's here. - It's food!
It's here.
- Here. - It's sashimi.
- Okay. - It'll be 40 dollars.
Where is she? Gong Joo?
She went out to get a call.
- What? - Don't you have 40 dollars?
That girl.
Jokbal's here.
It'll be 35 dollars.
Why is it so expensive?
You ordered a large size.
Hello. Sweet and sour pork is here.
It's been a while since you ordered this.
Is it a special day today?
No. How much is this?
It's 20 dollars.
I asked my boss for some free fried dumplings.
Don't you have any cash?
Me?
Mal Nyeon.
I don't have any money. I have everything else.
Dal Tong. Don't you have any money?
I just gave my boss all the money.
You should have told me earlier.
- Don't you have a card? - I don't have much money in it.
Try it.
There's no money in this.
I'm out of money in my account. Don't you have a card?
I got rid of it recently.
My goodness. What is this?
Where did she go? She must look down on us.
Could you hurry up? I need to make my next delivery.
- Well... - Oh, my.
- You're here. - I'm glad you're here.
- What are you doing? - You have money, right?
Pay these men. They're in a hurry.
- Okay. - Good.
- It'll be 20 dollars. - 20 dollars?
Yes.
Let's appoint...
Se Gye as the director next week.
I'll appoint you as the president.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I'm not trying to give the company to Se Gye.
If we find your son, I have a plan.
A son-in-law is better than a stranger.
Since we have wealth, all kinds of people come after us.
It's best for our family for Se Gye to take up our business.
I'm not a pushover.
If you trust me, stay low for a while.
Don't call me.
Say no more. I'll be off.
What brings you here without calling me?
I thought you didn't want me to call you.
I'm here to pay you back your money.
- Here. It's 50,000 dollars. - What's this money for?
It's the money you invested in my daughter.
I paid the monthly interest. There's only the principal left, right?
Where did you get this money? Did you sell the restaurant?
It's not your business. Did you think I didn't have that much money?
Your daughter takes after you.
Are you going to make your daughter work at a karaoke again?
She seems to be enjoying it. You should let her run her business.
- Take it with you. - Take it. My arm hurts.
If you want to pay me back, pay it when the business is doing well.
- I told you to go. - What are you doing?
It's nothing. I told you to go.
Why are you here? You have no business here.
I'm here to pay back the money.
Goodbye. Let's not meet again.
You told me that she paid you back all ready.
My goodness. Relief Patch.
Why don't you believe in me? I told you to wait.
(Marriage Registration Form: Yeo Bong and Nam Gi Ja)
Mrs Nam.
I bought soju because I'm upset.
Do you want to join me?
Things must be going pretty bad for you, as well.
You're kids won't listen to you. You got fired from work.
You must not want to live.
If I were you, I would...
I know I shouldn't be like this
I know we're strangers now
I know it but I don't know why I'm like this
I have tears in my eyes
It's your schedule for today.
Okay.
(List of new companies: Sparkly Clean Gab Soon)
(Gab Dol)
Please speak after the beep.
Gab Soon. Your cleaning company will be under inspection today.
I know you're ready. But check once again just to be sure.
Two Hoovers, two floor shiners,
dust detector, carbon dioxide detector,
safety belt, safety rope and safety helmet.
Besides the basic cleaning supplies, these are the necessary supplies.
People usually forget about safety helmets. Don't forget that.
- Gab Dol. Let's go. - Okay.
Don't be caught off guard. Don't let your pride get hurt.
It's something you have to go through when you open a business.
Gab Soon, good luck!
- Gab Dol! - Yes!
Hello.
What brings you here?
I'm Kim Young Ran, an officer from the borough office.
We're here to inspect the supplies for sanitation service businesses.
You heard him, right?
It's over here.
Two Hoovers.
Safety belt. Two floor polishers.
- Where's the safety helmet? - Pardon?
Safety is the most important.
I forgot about it. I'll get it ready right away.
You need to correct it right away.
If you don't, you'll be penalised.
We'll be back.
I hope the best for your business.
Let's go.
Goodbye. I wish the best for your business.
(Shin Gab Soon)
You must have been surprised when I called you to meet.
Say what you need to say. I don't want to avoid you.
I'm sure you didn't call me out to talk about work.
You're right. I'll get straight to the point.
Can't you let Gab Dol go?
Did he say that I didn't let him go?
Please be understanding if I offended you.
I know that you were his girlfriend.
I also know that Gab Dol's family was against your relationship.
To be frank, I liked Gab Dol from the first time I saw him.
Marriage works out best when they're of similar living standards.
His mother seems to be worried.
You met his mother?
Yes. I've even been to his house many times.
I guess he didn't mention that.
I love his mother's food. She gets along well with me.
It seems that Gab Dol can't make up his mind...
because he is trying to be considerate.
Let's make it a win-win for us all.
If you have something to say, say it quickly and leave.
The inspection is mandatory.
Don't wedge me in between your love.
Is your love more ardent because you have an ex-girlfriend...
that you've dated for 10 years in the backdrop?
Don't say that.
I shouldn't have made you and Mum meet each other like that.
It was because I was desperate.
I know. I'm sure you wanted me to get scolded.
Don't be sarcastic.
Please be cooperative. You know my feelings.
I thought I did.
I don't any more.
What did you do?
How did we seem that she would say such a thing?
What do you mean? What did Young Ran say?
- You know well. - I don't.
Tell me. What did she say?
She told me to let you go.
And I will.
I'll meet a guy that suits me as a cleaner.
You go meet a public official that fits you.
I heard that's the way it should be.
I heard she even went to your house.
What?
Why didn't you tell me she talked with your mother about marriage?
How much more do you need to hurt me to end it?
When I was being inspected in front of you two,
I kept telling myself that this is just for business.
But I felt like I was naked.
I don't want to be humiliated any more.
Did you like watching me like that together?
Couldn't you have called me earlier?
- You didn't pick up. - You could have sent me a text.
Was it funny?
Didn't you get the voice mail?
What?
Listen to it first before you say that.
Gab Soon, your cleaning company will be under inspection today.
I know you're ready. But, check once again just to be sure.
Two Hoovers...
I didn't know that she even came to my house.
What are you doing?
What are we here for?
Ms Kim. What did you say to Gab Soon?
Gab Soon isn't someone you can walk all over.
Don't look down on her just because she's a cleaner.
What gives you the right to treat her this way?
I never thought you'd do this. I'm disappointed in you.
"Date someone on your own level"?
What level?
I'm not on your level.
Please find someone else who is.
Apologise to Gab Soon.
I guess I overstepped the line.
I'm sorry. That was thoughtless of me.
Please stop coming to my house.
I apologise for my mother's mistake on behalf of her.
I decide whom I'm going to marry,
not my mother.
Your feelings must've been hurt.
You have a strong pride, and I made you hear things like that.
I want to quit my job if I could.
Gab Dol.
Do you really want to marry me?
Yes.
Do you really want to do this?
Are you sure you will stay with me until the end?
Follow me, then.
What's wrong with you two?
Mum, Dad. We want to get married.
Goodness.
We already said no.
Look at these brats. Get out right now.
Please let us.
It doesn't matter if you disapprove. We'll do it anyway.
You know how stubborn she can be.
We'll live a happy life.
We've been together for 10 years.
Please help us, so those years can finally pay off.
We'll be good to you.
Are you kidding me?
If you want to be good to us, break up. I don't need to hear more.
Get out.
I told you many times. Let's say we're fine with it.
Gab Dol. Do you think your mother will approve?
Even if she doesn't, we'll do it. It doesn't matter.
Did I raise you to be so reckless?
How can you get married without your parents' permission?
- You little... - Please don't hit her.
Have pity on your dad.
He devoted his whole life to you.
He begged others for milk in the cold winter to raise you.
He didn't even get married because of you.
Dad.
Soo Jo. My dear Soo Jo.
- My son. - Stop it.
Don't hug me. I'm not a child.
I bought some meat. It's rib eye, your favourite.
I haven't eaten all day. I'm starving.
You haven't eaten either, right?
Take care of the vegetables.
I'll cook the meat.
You must've been very surprised.
I'm not a kid in adolescence.
I'm 32 years old.
It doesn't matter if you're not my biological father at this age.
I'm relieved you're not my brother.
If you were my brother, it'd be terrible.
Soo Jo.
Don't say anything.
You've always been my dad, and that's not going to change.
Do you suddenly find me bothersome?
I'm sorry, but I'm going to cling on to you and never let go.
I can't abandon my dad who begged others for milk to raise me.
You couldn't get married because of me.
You might die without a spouse.
I can't abandon my poor dad.
No matter what others say, you're my dad.
Let me ask you one thing.
How did we meet?
We met at the riverside.
How romantic.
Did you and I meet for the first time at the riverside?
Yes.
I still remember that day distinctly.
I was also an orphan who had no parents or siblings.
Ever since I was little,
I barely managed to survive...
by living off Sam Sik's family.
Nothing was working out, and I had no one to rely on.
I thought I shouldn't live any more,
so I went to that riverside to kill myself.
It was a very cold day.
There was a snowstorm.
I was about to throw myself...
in the river with my eyes closed.
That's when I heard a baby crying.
I didn't know why, but I ran toward it like crazy.
Then I found you, a beautiful baby boy,
wrapped in a baby blanket on the riverbank.
The moment I saw you, I held you in my arms and ran without thinking.
I wanted to save you.
I thought I shouldn't let anything happen to you,
so I ran like crazy.
I never ran even if someone paid me.
I know that.
After that,
you and I became inseparable.
After you came to my life,
I strangely stopped thinking about dying.
You're the saviour of my life.
You're like a treasure I found.
I'm a burden, not a treasure.
You couldn't get married because of me.
I had no woman to marry anyway.
What about the lady at the restaurant who used to give us food?
I flirted with her only to get food from her.
I still remember it.
She said she'd marry you if you sent me to an orphanage.
You said you could never abandon me.
Do you remember that?
To be honest,
I was so scared that you might run away with her.
She's not my type.
I dated her only because of the food.
Soo Jo.
We should...
look for your real parents now.
I'm not interested.
If they're poorer than us, let's just ignore them.
If they're rich, let's sponge off them.
We'll be able to find them with these sneakers.
I think they belong to your mum.
Even if they live right next to us, I won't meet them.
Even if they're rich, I don't care.
I only need you.
Thank you for saying that, my son.
Don't ever tell me to leave.
I don't have anywhere else to go. You shouldn't kick me out.
Is it delicious?
Shall we open the door and make the people in the main building jealous?
Let's shout out we're having rib eye.
We're eating rib eye!
Come on in.
He's lucky in getting free food.
When I had only two meals a day,
that punk always had all three meals.
That's why his name is Sam Sik.
What are you doing?
I'm boiling eggs for Dal Pa.
Dal Pa always liked eggs ever since he was little.
He can finish 10 eggs in one sitting.
I think he can even eat 30 eggs.
Does he like it that much?
Yes. When Gab Soon comes back, I'll give her some, as well.
Gab Soon gets to eat it thanks to Dal Pa.
It's cold. Why did you call me out?
Eat it. It's hotteok.
My gosh. It's just hotteok.
Don't be so mad.
- If you're done, I'm going in. - I came to give you money.
It's 80 dollars for today.
I wanted to make it 100 dollars per day, but it's not easy.
I'll make 100,000 dollars by any means.
It's going to take forever this way.
Let's see how much is left.
100,000 dollars minus 80 dollars is...
It's 99,920 dollars.
I'll come back if I get more money.
Good night.
My gosh.
Why are you home so late? It's cold outside, right?
Aren't you hungry?
Aunt. Here.
- What is this? - It's hotteok.
I didn't expect to eat hotteok at this hour.
Do you want some?
I'm fine.
I boiled some eggs for you.
Take them inside and eat.
I don't need it.
What do you think you're doing?
Your mum boiled them for you. How dare you?
I won't allow this kind of behaviour in my house.
Stop it, Joong Nyeon.
Apologise to your mum. Now.
Why are you yelling?
It's my fault.
Go inside.
Why did you boil the eggs?
For me?
I don't like eggs. I'm sick and tired of them.
Since I was little, you boiled dozens of eggs before leaving me.
Don't you know that I got sick and stopped eating them?
Didn't you know he got sick?
- You're late. - Yes. It's quite cold.
The problem isn't the weather. It's your mother.
Excuse me?
It looks like something happened. She was crying earlier.
Mum was crying?
She was washing the blankets, then she suddenly started to feel bad.
I know it's not my place to say this,
but I'm saying this because I live here and you feel like my family.
Don't make you mother worry. What are you going to do if she dies?
Mothers are the most pitiful people in the world.
Did you take your medicine?
Don't you need to go to the doctor?
(How to make beef vegetable rice porridge)
Mum.
I made some porridge.
I know you don't want to see me,
but you should eat and get your strength back to scold me.
I'll come by during lunch break.
Finish this all and tell me if there's something you want to eat.
I don't want to see you. Get out.
It's good to hear you answer me.
I'm going to work now.
- What are you doing? - I'm eating short rib soup.
Why are you eating it alone? I like short rib soup, too.
- Haven't you eaten? - I was too busy.
Enjoy your meal.
- Can I have a short rib soup to go? - Sure.
(Pharmacy)
What's this?
It's short rib soup. You said you like it.
I was only kidding.
Don't you like it?
It's my favourite.
I almost got married to it.
Eat it while it's hot. We work to eat, you know.
Why do you starve to work?
You've grown thin.
I've lost 2kg while secretly dating you.
Don't I look prettier?
I don't like skinny women.
I'll give you a good scolding if you lose weight.
Eat it, and take this medicine.
- What is this for? - You were coughing.
I guess I can't even cough freely.
You can do whatever you want. I'll do anything to take care of it.
What a great man.
Our family is making kimchi later today.
If you eat it with boiled pork, it's really delicious.
I hope you could come and eat it.
Are you teasing me?
Gosh, my mouth is watering.
I wish my mum goes out of town at times like this.
- I'll pack some and give it to you. - You don't have to.
I'll get going. You should eat. I'll call you.
Be careful on your way back.
Mal Nyeon. Come out. We should make kimchi.
This won't make any difference. It's something you've done in the past.
Don't be so pathetic and come out.
All I want to do is just die.
Even if you don't want to, we're all going to die anyway.
So let's just make kimchi first before we do.
You're great at making the sauce. Come on.
See? We're already done with making the sauce, thanks to you.
You're so great at making things look nice.
Why don't you make nice with your son, too?
Even if I want to, he won't give me a chance.
He's not like that to others,
but he's so cold towards his own mother.
Think of it as your punishment.
Your children grow up, and you start to walk on eggshells around them.
Even if you didn't do anything wrong, it's the same.
- Bring me the containers. - Okay.
What's taking Dad so long?
I guess he went to slaughter a pig himself instead of buying it.
- Is it Dad? - He's here.
My gosh. It's Se Bang.
Hello, Mother.
Gosh, you're making kimchi.
I'm right on time.
How have you been, Ddol Ee?
I guess Se Bang is lucky in getting free food.
He always comes in when we eat something.
Your kimchi is the best, Mother.
People just buy kimchi these days. Isn't it hard to make it?
We thought about buying it, but we just decided to make it.
It's a bit late to make it.
Let me do the hard work.
Should I move them to the back porch?
By the way, where is Father?
- He went to buy some pork. - I see.
That one's for me, right?
Goodness. You're quick-witted.
Gosh. You're the best! This is what I'm talking about.
Can I talk to you for a second?
She wants to talk to you.
Try to soothe her nicely.
What is it?
Do you want me to slap you in the face with these rubber gloves on?
You've changed too much.
You couldn't talk like this.
I could, but I just chose not to.
Don't turn a gentle lamb into a poisonous snake.
Leave now while I'm being nice.
Both Ddol Ee and Mother like it when I'm here.
What's the matter?
- Let's just let it slide. - "Mother"?
My mum's not your mother-in-law.
If you come to our house again,
I'll report you to the police for housebreaking.
You should come to my house with Ddol Ee, then.
- What? - You can't, right?
I come here to make things more convenient for you.
Don't be so agitated, okay?
Do you want to have lunch together?
I'm busy today, so I have to eat here at the cafeteria.
I'll call you later.
Mum.
(Marriage Registration Form)
Don't worry.
Someone gave me this money to buy you a suit.
I'm all prepared for my retirement. Don't worry about me.
She was fired from that place.
There must have been an incident there.
It's nice to meet you. My name is Heo Gab Dol.
I talked to you earlier on the telephone.
Have a seat.
You must be her son who just became a public official.
Is your mother okay?
She's fine. I just wanted to deliver this.
What is it?
Please open it later.
I think this will tell you how she feels.
Did you mother tell you to do this?
No, she doesn't know about this meeting.
My mother...
has never done anything that she's not proud of.
While she may not be educated and has a menial job,
she's never done anything improper...
nor has she misbehaved.
I don't know what went on between two of you,
but do not mistreat or disrespect her.
Don't say that.
It hurts.
I am intentionally telling you this.
I know that you bought this suit for me. I appreciate it.
Thank you.
I should get going.
Please do not tell my mother that we met today.
You probably won't see her anyway.
(Your shipment will arrive today. Please keep it refrigerated.)
A box of soy sauce marinated crab will be delivered soon.
Take the delivery and put it in the refrigerator.
It's perishable, so make sure to put it in the refrigerator.
Yes, Madame.
(Marriage Registration Form)
Si Nae, can you come home early today?
I have an important matter to discuss with you.
What is it?
I will tell you in person.
Okay.
(Nam Gi Ja)
Is anyone here? Professor Geum Do Geum?
How did you find this place?
I had Ms Nam's address.
Please leave.
I don't want to hurt my son's feelings.
I understand.
It's cold. Can we talk inside just for a little while?
It probably not any warmer in here.
Please leave now.
I'm truly sorry.
I didn't know he was your son.
My mind hasn't changed.
Until my son forgives you, I will not see you.
Please give me another chance.
Let me just meet your son. I will beg for his forgiveness.
I was having an especially bad day. I was very sensitive.
Are you the only one who is sensitive?
Everyone is sensitive.
Do not try to use it as an excuse.
You have a package.
I have to take the delivery.
(Waiting for Godot. Stay focused. Be persistent. Money is power.)