BioskopKeren
(Episode 35)
Soy sauce marinated crab.
You arouse way too much appetite.
You're a swindler. I hate you.
One day, I will eat you up.
Si Nae.
Why are you so surprised?
Hey, I mistook you for someone else.
- What brings you here now? - I came to see you.
You're not stringing beads again, are you?
No, I'm not. I can't do it because my eyes hurt.
Here's the rent. Today's the day to pay rent.
Make sure you don't forget to pay.
It's my first time paying the rent on time.
This makes us highbred people, right?
Of course. I'll get going now.
Soo Jo.
- Didn't you see her on your way? - Who?
Si Nae.
She even came here?
She came to ask for my forgiveness earlier,
but she was gone once I put the soy sauce marinated crab in the fridge.
I guess she felt awkward.
I'm not interested.
No need to ask for your forgiveness. She's not worth forgiving.
I guess she came because of you.
If you like her, date her.
However, you must keep it discreet from me.
Are you out of your mind? I won't date someone you hate.
Where did it go?
Soo Jo, did you wear your mum's sneakers?
No, I didn't.
They're in the box, aren't they?
What?
Never mind.
Oh, no. I need them no matter what.
What are you doing?
Ms Nam, by any chance, did you see any sneakers?
Sneakers?
They're blue female sneakers.
Did you wear them by any chance?
What are you talking about?
My goodness. I need them.
Why would you need female sneakers?
I need them!
If you know nothing, stay still!
Why must you yell?
Clean this up.
Did you put the soy sauce marinated crab inside?
I don't know!
(Marriage Registration Form)
Si Nae.
I'll yield to everything else.
Please grant me just this.
It's my last wish.
I want to spend the rest of my life with her.
Si Nae, come to my room for a second.
I found him.
How could there be such a coincidence?
What is he doing right now?
He's 32 years old. Is he married?
No, it's been the two of them up until now.
What about his education?
From what I heard, he barely graduated high school.
He couldn't even dream of going to college because they're broke.
My goodness.
He delivers water now, Dad.
Water delivery?
The guy who's been delivering water to the office.
It's him.
- Leave. - All right.
How could I have not recognised him? He was right in front of me.
Oh, dear. What shall we do?
Si Nae, let's meet him first. Wait.
He might be shocked.
Let's talk to the professor first.
(Si Nae)
Professor, it's me.
Why did you leave without a word?
Please don't ask anything. Let's meet.
Why?
Don't ask anything. Please.
Please meet me.
I won't see you without my son's permission.
I'm not that crazy about women.
Please forget me.
- Goodbye. - Professor, wait.
If you see me, I'll give you 1,000 dollars.
1,000...
1,000 dollars?
(Available for rent)
Why are you here?
You should listen to adults.
Is it because you haven't learned much? Why don't you get it?
You must look down on me because I'm a divorcee who lives alone.
As long as I'm alive, there's no way.
Why are you showing interest in her?
You're unbelievable.
If you ever get caught again, you'll get kicked out of my house.
What's the matter?
Why are you scolding my son?
He deserves to be scolded.
I've told him so many times. He should get it by now.
How could you be wandering in front of her store like that?
Say something if you just heard what I said.
You should respond to adults.
You remain silent. Do you want me to get frustrated to death?
- I'm sorry. - It's so hard to hear your voice.
Gosh, how frustrating.
Are you keeping in touch with her?
I don't even know her number.
Keep your son in control.
I really can't stand the way you talk to my son.
Why are you treating my precious son like this?
- Dad, let's go in. - Let go!
Ms Nam, this is wrong!
Didn't you know...
that your son has a crush on my daughter?
What?
A crush? My son?
Is it true? Do you have a crush on her?
You're his father. How could you not know about this?
This is too much.
My son doesn't lack anything. Why would he have a crush on her?
What's so great about your daughter?
Don't look down on my son!
Be quiet and move out.
Sure, we'll move out.
What do you take us for?
Does she think I'm that dumb?
You're not inadequate.
Why would you have a crush on a divorcee with two kids?
She's old, too. Am I not right?
She's out of her mind these days.
She's insane.
She's not even picking up her phone.
The phone's turned off. I can't reach her.
Didn't she call you?
She never calls me.
I wonder when she came. She even put the store up for rent.
I knew it.
I thought she was determined, but she's back to herself.
It's hard to change oneself.
She's never stayed home long enough.
Empty your mind, Mum. You haven't eaten, have you?
Let's go eat something.
Forget it. I need to go work.
You two frustrate me way too much.
I have no luck with my husband or my children.
What an unfortunate fate I have.
Come on out.
What is wrong with you? I have to clean this up.
She is no longer working here as of today.
Wait...
My goodness.
Don't resist me with force. I have no energy.
Why did you come here?
- I don't want to see you. - I came because I missed you.
Why aren't you listening to me? I told you...
not to work at the restaurant.
Why would I listen to you?
You should listen to me while you work at my house.
It's been a while since I quit working at your house.
You should've waited like I told you to.
Why are you working here?
You're not even well.
I told you that I have a reason behind all this.
You should've counted on me. Why can't you understand?
What are you talking about? I understand you very well.
I know that you're doing this because of your daughter.
- That's not it. - What do you mean, that's not it?
You will never overcome your daughter.
If you weren't a woman,
I would've beaten you up.
I'm holding it in.
How would you know a man's considerate heart?
Is that why you ripped the marriage registration form?
How did you know that?
I thought you'd do that because of your personality.
I'm glad you know it.
If you're done speaking, please go.
Please listen to me. I told you I have no energy.
Take this with you again.
You saved this money for your son's marriage.
I'll pay you back even if I have to sell my body.
Is there anyone who would pay you for that?
You have a nice son.
When did you ever see my son?
If he takes after you, he'll be nice.
Take this.
Make do with this for now...
and don't work.
What do you take me for?
Are you playing with me?
Do you think money can buy you everything?
There are some things you can't solve with money.
You said all those sweet words as you suggested to get married.
Now, you're giving me a few bucks so I'd leave.
Even though I'm penniless who cleans others' dirty houses,
you got me wrong.
I've chased after money all my life,
but I don't need this kind of money.
Don't sway my mind like this.
I haven't moved out yet.
Do you have soju?
Do you want me to sing you a song?
I know we're now strangers
- Forget it. - All right.
There's a snowstorm in this frigid winter.
Where would I go with my son?
Don't move out.
Thank you, Ms Nam.
We might become attached with one another.
"I don't know why I'm doing this."
"I really don't know why I'm doing this."
Wait.
- You're going to buy socks? - Yes.
Pick what you want. I'll buy you socks of all colours.
You're getting me socks by each colour?
I'll get you socks today, but once I make money, I'll get you cars.
Handbags are not fun.
You should get me houses by each colour, too.
Sure, I can do that. I'll get you houses by each colour.
What a liar. Is that how you coaxed women?
That's what I'm doing right now.
I don't know if I should go along with it or not.
It's so pretty. Can I get a lot?
Buy enough to last the winter.
I'm going to wear them by myself.
I'll think about you whenever I put them on.
There are no gloves here. Do you sell gloves too?
They're pretty.
What is it? Is it food?
- No, it's not food. - What is it, then?
It's not food.
What is it, then?
You bought socks?
Good thing you bought socks. I was about to get them.
That's why I got them.
You got all the colourful ones.
- Who got them for you? - Who would get me socks?
Where did you get them? They're warm.
We can share it amongst the family.
- Sure. - They're nice.
They're nice.
I feel bad for you.
I don't know what to do.
I told my mum I'll marry Gab Soon,
but I don't want to watch my mum like that.
You can't betray Gab Soon just because of your mum.
- This is driving me nuts. - Don't go nuts.
This is all because you became a public official.
(Gab Soon)
Why aren't you calling? Is something going on?
We're going to stick to our plan, right?
Aren't you eating?
I have to go clean early.
And I'm going to marry Gab Dol, just to let you know.
We need to talk.
I'm busy. I need to go clean and get ready for my wedding.
She's so stubborn.
What's wrong with you? Are you mad?
I should have been this way from the beginning. It's time.
Do you like him that much? Do you like him more than your parents?
- Did he talk you into this? - No, this is all my idea.
Don't you know your own daughter?
It's not like I'm going to let anybody talk me into anything.
I wooed Gab Dol from the beginning.
You must be proud of yourself.
Mum, I have a long way to go.
I need to get his mum's approval, and I have a lot of cleaning jobs.
Please, don't make my life harder.
I'm going to marry Gab Dol no matter what.
Do something about your daughter.
We can't let her go crazy like that.
You can't do anything to stop her.
Let her be. The wedding won't happen. I'm 100 percent sure.
She can't marry by herself. She won't last long, Mum. Let her be.
What do you think will happen? I need your psychic ability.
I don't know what to say about this.
My psychic ability must have waned.
If I get some money,
I might get it right.
Just eat.
My goodness.
Mum, did you eat?
I don't have an appetite.
Don't starve. I'll get food on my way home.
Mother.
What brings you here?
How dare you come here?
I wanted to say my season's greetings and talk to you.
You said these were pretty when I wore them a few years ago.
I didn't mean it. You really think I found them pretty?
You're clueless and foolishly daring.
Is that how your parents taught you?
This is expensive Korean beef. I make money now.
I don't get pension,
but I earn a little more than a public official's wage.
Please, take my bow.
- Have a seat. - What's wrong with you?
This is why I don't like you.
How dare you come here on your own when Gab Dol is not here?
Do you want to have a fight?
Sure, let's do this.
I have made my determination.
I'll let you criticise me.
If you hit me, I'll take it.
It's been over 10 years. I know you well.
Please, approve our marriage.
Gab Dol wanted to go ahead without your approval, but I'll wait.
What did you say?
Get out. Get out right now.
- What's going on? - I'm speechless.
Do you think this makes sense? You heard everything, right?
I was busy minding my own business, so I didn't hear everything.
Look at her.
She's pretty. Hanbok looks nice on you.
That's not why I wanted you to look at her.
She's so spoiled. This is why I don't like you.
She's been controlling Gab Dol for 10 years like this.
How could you think of wearing hanbok and visiting me?
Drag her out for me.
Me?
I can't do that.
I have no energy. I have a headache.
Mother, I'll be good to you.
I'll be your daughter and a daughter-in-law.
I don't want to hear that from you. I just don't like you.
I already want someone else as my daughter-in-law, so leave.
Don't just watch. Drag her out.
Excuse me, Gab Soon.
I won't back down.
Mother, take my bow.
- What? - She wants to bow.
What are you doing? Didn't you hear me?
What's wrong with you?
Please, have a seat.
Let go of me.
Why are you doing this?
Gab Soon, bow now if you're going to.
I won't take your bow. I'll never take it.
She's done.
I'm lacking in many ways,
but I'll become a better daughter-in-law than office workers.
I won't let Gab Dol work too hard. I'll make him happy.
I don't want to hear it.
Gab Dol and I have been...
dating for 11 years now.
We tried breaking up a few times, but we couldn't.
I'll never meet anybody more precious than him.
We're childhood friends, so I didn't treat him with respect.
I know you didn't like that about me.
Once we get married, I'll treat him respectfully as my husband.
Mother, please give us your approval.
I want to make you my daughter-in-law.
She bought expensive meat.
I don't want this.
Did you see that? Do you want me to die of anger?
If you don't want it, can I have it?
She comes to my house wearing hanbok,
forces me to take her bow and says whatever she wants to.
Do I deserve to hear this from her?
Was this your idea or hers?
It was mine.
Is it so incredible that your son is a public official?
Other people will laugh at us.
We have so little to be proud of in our family except this.
If I had other abilities, I wouldn't have become a public official.
What's wrong with Gab Soon? She's 1,000 times better than me.
If I manage to keep my post, I'll consider myself lucky.
Gab Soon will make her company grow and do an interior design business.
She'll also own a car and hire a personal chauffeur.
A person like me will never be able to do that.
I don't want to live a poor life any more.
I'm going to marry Gab Soon and benefit from her.
I'll marry her even if you say no.
You saw that, right? You saw that with your own eyes.
You saw him yelling at me, right?
Are you happy that you drove my family apart?
Things are bad already. Imagine how it'll be once you get married.
Isn't it obvious how things will be?
Get out! Get away from me!
How did you think of coming to my house by yourself?
That was unexpected.
Do you think I'd only do what you expect?
I'm unpredictable.
Don't come by yourself from now on. You'll get all the abuse.
I don't want to hide.
It's something we have to go through.
Don't get angry at your mum. She'll take it out on me.
Okay.
You're pretty today.
You look like a newly-wed.
Gab Dol, do you really think I'll be successful?
I was touched by what you said earlier.
I didn't know you believed in me that much.
I'm marrying you to benefit from you.
Don't you worry. I'll be the breadwinner.
That's what I wanted to hear the most.
"I'll be the breadwinner."
That's a lot more touching...
than hearing you say that you love me.
I'm serious, too. I'll be successful.
I'll make her regret for looking down on me.
I'm going to marry you and not give up.
Remember what you said before?
You said I was the one who protected our love.
No, it was all you.
I didn't do anything.
I was timid and cowardly.
All I did was complain.
- You're incredible. - I know. I'm incredible.
I'm late. I have to go and clean. See you.
Be careful. You'll fall.
- Welcome. - Hello.
Put them here.
Thank you.
Come out, Nae Shim.
- Wait for me downstairs. - Yes, Sir.
- How have you been? - Great.
- I'm here, Mother. - Welcome, Se Bang.
Why did you bring so many things?
What's all this?
I got New Year's gifts for everybody.
Where's Father? I reserved a restaurant for lunch.
He left a while ago. I don't know where he went.
We can wait for him. He should be home soon.
You should be asking for Jae Soon,
not my brother.
I want to talk to you for a second.
You own a big business so you can feed yourself, right?
Of course.
I think about how much I need to earn to buy a bank.
You're going to buy a bank?
You buy and sell banks?
I'm just saying.
While I was living a routine life there,
I was always thinking about how to make money.
- Where were you? - I was in China.
I guess you were living a routine life in China.
Yes. I always ate and slept on schedule.
Why were you in China?
I went there for business.
Are you hiding something from me?
Like what?
A woman.
You look neat and earn a lot of money. You must have dated.
You could have dated them or lived with them.
No.
There weren't any woman there.
There are women everywhere.
Not everywhere.
China is huge, so I guess that's possible.
Are you sure about getting back together with Jae Soon?
I'll do it for Ddol Ee.
Try convincing her, then.
She has a lot of resentment, so she's still upset,
but it's all up to you.
All right, Mother.
Sleep at home.
Aunt goes crazy when you don't come home.
Fine.
Hi.
Don't come from now on. I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
You know I look forward to...
inspecting companies I've invested in.
I know that's not the only reason.
Don't be interested in me any more.
Why, all of a sudden?
I'm getting married.
I've heard you say that many times.
I'll just pretend like I didn't hear that.
Do it again.
None of this reflects what I asked you to fix.
Sure.
Don't daydream. Make sure you make no mistakes.
Okay.
I'm getting married.
What did you say?
I thought I should tell you.
I'll give you the wedding invitation once it gets made.
Mother, it's Young Ran.
Is Gab Dol getting married?
What do you mean?
He can't get married without my approval.
He said he'll hand out wedding invitations soon.
That won't happen. I know my son.
Okay. I'll trust you.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. Why are you back so early?
I'm going to take some rest and go for beer delivery.
Soo Jo, I'm coming home with 1,000 dollars today.
- What do you want? - It's okay.
I'm serious.
Let's buy some good food.
Do you want dress shoes?
The pair you had got ruined from getting soaked in water.
I don't need dress shoes. I have no occasion to wear it.
Wait for it. I'll come home with 1,000 dollars.
Where are you going?
- It's none of your business. - It's an important meeting.
Gong Joo went out with her friends. Tell her to order food.
Sure. See you later.
I didn't...
expect to see you here, Sir.
Welcome.
Professor,
thank you.
Why are you doing this?
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Why are you doing this to me?
This isn't going to change my mind.
I'm not going to date you.
You begged me to meet you,
so I came for the 1,000 dollars.
You shouldn't do this.
Why do you have this?
Do you know how precious this is?
Why did you steal this?
Do you think my son is a thief like you?
I thought wrong about you.
I'm leaving.
Those shoes...
are mine.
The son you raised...
is Si Nae's son.
My baby.
I'm sorry.
Why aren't you sleeping?
Is something bothering you?
What's up?
Did Ms Nam tell us to move out?
Wait here. I'll talk to her.
I found your biological mother.
What did you just say?
I said I found your biological mother.
I thought she passed away.
That's what I thought,
but she turned out to be alive.
I'm going to meet her tomorrow.
You must be surprised.
Still, it's nice that she's alive. You can meet her.
Let's go and meet her.
Soo Jo.
- What kind of person is she? - You'll see when you meet her.
Your father passed away. She's the only one who's alive.
Is she not poor?
No, you won't have to work to support them.
If she's not poor, why did she abandon me?
Why don't you ask her yourself?
- I don't need to meet her. - You should at least hear her out.
I don't need to hear anything.
I told you. Even if my parents live next door, I won't see them.
Aren't you curious?
I'm not curious at all.
She'll just be another human being who's full of excuses.
You're the only parent I have.
Let's not talk about this any more.
I'm sorry to say this,
but my son doesn't want to meet you.
Did you talk to him about me?
No. I didn't want to make him angry.
Then why doesn't he want to meet me?
He must be confused.
He thought his biological mother was dead all this time.
Imagine how shocked he would be.
I can't force him into doing something he doesn't want.
I never have until this day.
Please, Professor. Please help me meet him.
Once I meet him, I'll take care of the rest.
Can you please convince him?
And don't tell him about me.
Seriously?
What a small world!
How is this possible?
Tell me about it.
I still can't believe this. I'm still shocked.
I'm not sure if this is good or bad.
What are you talking about? You just won the lottery!
Once they take him in, he will inherit all their property.
Do Geum, your day has finally come.
Don't forget that I'm your friend.
I don't plan on taking anything. I'm happy as long as Soo Jo is happy.
I don't want to be a burden to him.
Stop lying.
Go home if you're going to say such things. You punk.
I'm sure Soo Jo won't abandon you and live abundantly on his own.
That's just ungrateful.
Sir, when will I become the director?
What? Director?
Yes, I need to prepare some stuff.
I'm also planning to launch several projects.
I'm planning to get them started once I become the director.
- Well... - That's unacceptable.
How can you talk about work directly to the chairman?
Am I just a puppet to you?
Are you that desperate to become the director?
It's not because I'm desperate.
I asked because he already mentioned it,
and Gong Joo also asked me to ask him.
That won't happen.
Pardon me?
From now on, anything that has to do with work should be reported to me.
There's a lot you can do even if you don't become the director.
Man Joo.
What brings you here?
I called you. I didn't know you were here.
Are you here with someone else?
I'm just enjoying time by myself.
What a coincidence.
Why are you here alone? What about that man?
- Who? - The blind date.
Did you have a fight?
There's nothing to fight over. We only just met.
Why didn't you answer my phone call? I called you several times.
I was going to let you off thinking that you're busy.
Your wife...
came to see me.
We shouldn't meet in private.
I'm going to leave.
Don't go.
I'm sorry.
I'm just...
selfish.
I always did things my way.
Even after I got married,
I thought you'd always stay by my side.
I never held onto you.
But I never let you go, either.
I'm being selfish again by saying this.
You should just...
Don't say anything.
Did you drink alcohol?
Why would you do something like that?
What did you say to Man Joo?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Did you tell her not to meet me and not to contact me?
Yes, I did. I have all the right to say that.
It's not about whether you have a right or not.
- I'm really disappointed in you. - You're the one who caused this.
You two almost got married to each other.
You kept seeing her even after you quit working at the hospital.
You told me that she was just a friend, so I trusted you.
You're on your way back from meeting her, aren't you?
I can smell her perfume on you.
Yes, I met her. I accidentally met her at a bar.
Accidentally?
Gong Joo. Let's not do this.
I can't do this.
Man Joo isn't the kind of person you think she is.
Are you taking her side instead of mine?
Do you think I'm stupid?
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing? You'll wake your grandfather.
Do you even throw things now?
Are you doing this because you won't become the director?
- I did it. - Why?
It's none of your business. It's a problem between us.
I want a word with you later.
- You're still awake. - Yes. Long time no see.
I told you to sleep at home.
Have a seat.
What do you think about moving out with your mother?
I can't live with her.
Just seeing her face makes me furious.
How can you ignore her when you're living under the same roof?
I can't allow that kind of behaviour in my house.
Then I won't ever come here again.
Joong Nyeon.
Don't say that to him.
He has nowhere to go.
If he has to leave, he should leave when it gets warmer.
Why don't you two move out and live together?
How can you ignore each other like this?
Whenever he comes, I'll just stay in my room or something.
Just let him stay here.
Dal Pa, do as I say.
You can't go out in this cold winter.
Dad.
I'll meet her.
Really?
Okay.
He'll meet us.
How much is it?
I'll take one.
Here.
There you go.
- Thank you. - Bye.
You want me to cook a meal?
Don't ask anything.
Please make something for my son.
You bought so much.
What's the occasion?
Your son's birthday wasn't too long ago.
My son is leaving.
I want to...
feed him a meal before he leaves.
Where is he going?
Are you sending him off to his real parents?
How do you know that?
I wasn't eavesdropping.
I just heard you telling him that you found his real mum.
Yes.
I'm going to send him back to his mother.
What is she like?
Is she well off?
I guess not, since she couldn't raise her own child.
Did he say he'll go to her?
I'll send him away even if he says no.
Since when did you raise him?
Since when he was a baby.
You must've been through a lot.
You raised him all this time. How will you send him away?
I thought it was strange because you two didn't look alike.
Anyway, you're so great.
I just thought your wife passed away early.
How did you raise him alone like he was your own child?
We both cried a lot.
You'll never know what we went through.
I can only imagine the kind of hardships you would've gone through.
I feel sorry for you.
Some people even abandon their own children.
How will you live on your own? You'll be so lonely.
Goodness.
What will do you?
I'll move out.
Will you go with him?
No.
I'll go somewhere else.
Don't tell my son.
I don't talk with him anyway.
- Will it take long? - It's almost done.
Must you make kalguksu?
When he puts his mind to it, he has to go through with it.
He was upset last time because he couldn't have kalguksu.
Just leave him be.
Put your mind to something else, not just food.
Don't bother me.
We agreed to use the kitchen at a set time.
Do you know how many times I had to go eat cup noodles?
Wait. Let's eat together today.
It's my treat.
He'll share. Just wait.
Joong Nyeon, the broth is boiling.
What's next?
You have to put those in.
I'm home.
Put those in.
How is it? Isn't it good?
Yes. You should open a restaurant.
Shall I?
It's perfect.
The noodles turned out well.
It's delicious, Dad.
By the way, I keep biting something weird.
I don't think there's anything.
Joong Nyeon. There's something.
There's something weird.
What is this?
Was there something in the flour?
I used the flour that I spilled last time.
What?
I'm not going to eat this.
I don't feel so good.
Dad, you can't use that flour. I'll get you a new bag of flour.
I guess I can't have kalguksu today.
(800 dollars has been deposited.)
I just sent you 800 dollars for child support.
(Available for rent)
I haven't seen you in a while.
How did you know about this place?
How have you been?
How could you cut off all contacts?
Were you keeping in touch with my daughter?
Are you saying the three of you ran into each other at her restaurant?
I didn't know it was her restaurant.
The restaurant was a mess. I guess she fought with customers.
Now I understand.
I'm sure she got furious after you saw her like that.
That's why she closed the restaurant.
She must've been so upset.
Are you seeing that woman again?
How could you keep the kids from contacting us though?
That's not what I intended.
I'm not doing well in many ways.
Why did you come to her restaurant?
Here.
- What is this? - Cho Rong's mum...
sent me child support.
I can't accept this. Please give it back to her.
She sent it to you as a mother. Use it for the children.
It's okay.
She started working so she could earn money for the kids.
Where did she...
get the money to open a restaurant?
Don't worry. She didn't get a private loan.
Tell her not to work if she's working because of the kids.
Why did she have to start a business that involves alcohol?
It's not an easy job.
It looked like she had a fight with the customers that day, too.
A woman can't do it alone.
She has no choice. She needs to earn money.
Mind your own business if you can't help her.
She has to learn for herself.
Where did you move to?
Are the kids doing okay?
They don't call, and they don't even answer my calls.
I know they're young,
but I'm still very upset.
I'm sorry.
Please...
tell her never to send money again.
Let me ask you one thing.
You said you turned...
the steering wheel to protect my daughter.
Why did you do that?
Because she's the mother of my kids.
Really? Okay.
I'll send Jae Soon right away.
Hey. Get changed...
and go to the restaurant near the intersection.
Se Bang is there with Ddol Ee.
He must be crazy.
He's not crazy.
He just wants to buy Ddol Ee something delicious.
- You should go. - That jerk.
I should get changed, too.
Gosh. You're so slow-witted.
What do you mean, I'm slow-witted?
How can I be slow-witted when I'm a shaman?
I've never heard anyone say that to me.
Let them have dinner together as a family.
Am I not family?
I mean just the three of them.
Hey.
Take your time eating and talk to him.
That won't happen.
I don't feel like it.
You should care about your child's feelings.
It's nice to have a family dinner, isn't it?
Ddol Ee must've been envious of other kids.
People live together for their children.
I'll pick Ddol Ee up and come right back.
She'll have dinner.
Is your shamanistic power back?
Have a good day.
Hi, this is Jo Geum Sik.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
- Honey! - Mum!
- Ddol Ee, let's go. - Don't do this.
We already ordered.
- Ddol Ee, let's eat together. - Okay.
Mum, can I eat before we go?
Of course you can.
What are you doing without telling me first?
Your anger is making me aroused.
He's listening.
Who cares? A couple can talk about such things.
They say kids respond positively when their parents get along.
Mum, Dad bought this for me. It's so nice.
Am I not the best dad in the world?
- Have a seat. - Mum, sit down.
Goodbye.
Mum, it's delicious.
Let's eat here often from now on, Ddol Ee.
This is for you, Ddol Ee.
This is for you.
Ddol Ee is watching.
That's why I'm putting up with this.
Otherwise, I would have smacked this plate on your face.
It's my fault. I'm the one who made you become so callous.
However, you being like this...
Just shut it and eat.
I'm only here because of Ddol Ee.
Does it make you feel better if you act that way?
Women are all the same.
If you were like this before, I wouldn't have divorced you.
I'm the one who filed for divorce.
You got divorced by me. Don't be arrogant.
Ddol Ee, let's take a picture together.
Let me be in it, too.
Smile.
(Where are you?)
Where are you?
Who is it from?
Mind your own business.
Let's go now.
Who sent the message? Why are you in such a hurry?
I'm your husband, remember?
Shut up. Do you still think I'm your wife?
Ddol Ee, let's go now.
(Jae Soon)
Don't ever meet her again.
Have you no conscience?
(Where are you?)
I'm waiting in front of your place.
Bye, Ddol Ee. Call me.
Bye, Dad.
- Mr Kim. - Yes, Sir.
It's a gift.
I don't want it.
Let's go in.
Take it inside.
Tell me honestly.
Why are you seeing her even after you got divorced?
You two aren't teenagers.
You both have children.
You shouldn't meet frivolously.
Is this a game? How long will this last?
You may not have much to lose,
but my daughter has to be careful...
about whom she meets from now on.
She can no longer be dating for fun.
I can't bear to watch her being like that as a parent.
You are not in a good financial situation, either.
Honestly, I don't want my daughter to suffer in poverty.
I am aware of that.
I am sorry.
You can't ignore reality.
Do you expect the entire family to live in that tiny place?
Don't you try to toy with her emotions.
It seems like you're seeing her...
without any kind of commitment.
You both shouldn't behave that way.
I may not know your true intentions,
but I know Jae Soon very well.
She gets swayed easily by other people.
She doesn't realise that she's falling into a trap.
I can't let her work at a supermarket all her life.
It's not like I can leave her a large inheritance, either.
Are you going to let her remarry...
Ddol Ee's father?
Let her go now.
That's all I ask of you.
I'm sorry, but that's what I want.
I understand what you're saying.
I don't want Jae Soon to suffer, either.
I am sorry.
- My goodness! - Try it on.
If you don't want it, let me have it.
It won't fit you. It might fit me, though.
You are so greedy.
Don't touch it. I will return it to him.
My goodness.
- Let me try it on. - Let me.
Be careful. You will rip it.
- No way. - I think you just ripped it.
Where have you been?
We agreed to not disclose everything.
Don't forget that we're just living together.
Thanks for reminding me.
Se Bang wanted to take the whole family out for a meal,
but I sent them out by themselves since you weren't here.
Since when was he our family?
Why can't he be?
He bought Jae Soon a mink coat.
So did she fall for him because of that?
She didn't even try it on.
Why are you so against Se Bang?
His business is doing well, and he has no other woman.
I already told you no.
Why can't you tell me the reason?
They had their chances. Why do you want them back together again?
He is Ddol Ee's father. He has better prospects than Mr Jo.
I don't like either of them.
Why didn't Jae Soon get a job after graduating from college?
She has to be dependent on men because she isn't independent.
My goodness!
In that sense, Gab Soon is much better.
Don't be ridiculous. She's so crazy about getting married.
Our daughters are both worthless.
You are so stubborn.
Are you really going through with it?
Yes.
What about you? Mum and Dad are so worried.
- Are you seeing him? - Who?
Cho Rong's dad.
We're just friends.
I don't know how he feels.
It seems like he's still seeing his ex-wife.
I don't know if he wants to get back with her.
I didn't hear anything about that.
Gab Dol would have told me if something like that was happening.
I saw him meeting Ms Nam.
He might still be supporting her. I saw him giving her an envelope.
No way. He's still doing that?
When I saw him doing that, my feelings for him waned.
Maybe I'm jealous.
I keep wondering if he still has feelings for his ex-wife.
I wonder how he feels about me.
I felt this sad feeling in my heart.
Perhaps that kind of woke me up.
I realise that he just might not be my man.
I think I know how you feel.
Women's feelings can be swayed by such little things.
One word or a single facial expression can change things.
That's right.
What about your first husband, Ddol Ee's father?
Mum seems to want him back as your husband.
I also think that's a good idea.
He might be the best option since he is Ddol Ee's father.
Of course, I'm saying this without knowing how you feel.
Your feelings are the most important factor.
Mr Geum Do Geum. You have a package.
Thank you.
I told you that we should meet at a cafe.
Let's not meet outside any more.
We should save money. Why waste money on coffee?
Let's go buy gifts.
Gifts are not important right now. Follow me.
Where are we going?
We should go to a nice place on a day like today.
We're going to a nice place.
What are we doing at my house?
Go in.
By myself?
You should spend time with your mum on a day like today.
I got some delicious food for you.
I have a big family, so they don't notice even when I'm not around,
but it's not like that for you. Especially with your sister gone.
Don't make your mum feel lonely.
Then let's go in together.
Do you want another battle?
I have no strength because I cleaned all day. Go in and make her happy.
Bye.
Mum!
Bye, Ddol Ee. Call me.
Bye, Dad.
(Where are you?)
Come out.
It's late.
Come out. I'm in front of your place.
I have to see you tonight.
Why are you here so late?
I got a gift for you.
It's a toy for Ddol Ee and something for you.
Please take it even if you don't like it.
I don't have anything for you.
Can we go someplace warm?
I sneaked out, so I have to get back in...
before my mother notices.
This may not seem appropriate,
but I'd better say it.
That might be good for you, too.
Let's not see each other any more.
I'm sure we both have a lot to say,
but let's just end this.
(Our Gab Soon)
I'm not seeing him any more.
Are you with my husband?
Yes, I'm with her. Why are you so suspicious?
Is Jae Soon still seeing her ex-husband?
You got divorced. You don't need to see her any more.
I don't think that's any of your business.
Mr Jo, do not wreck our family.
Please send him to our house no matter what it takes.
Do Geum, you sure are doing well now that you sold off your son.
Sold off my son? Take that back.
We are going to live together since you won't approve our marriage.
Do you think this is acceptable?
Instead of a wedding, we're going to have a small gathering with friends.
Get out! Get out now!