Why are you here so late?
I sneaked out, so I have to get back in before my mother notices.
This may sound inappropriate to say right now,
but let's not see each other any more.
Geum Do Geum. Delivery service.
I thought he might not have clothes for this occasion, so I bought some.
Please let him wear these when he meets me.
I'm not sure if this is the right size.
I just made a rough guess. I hope my dear Soo Jo will like them.
I hope my dear Soo Jo...
My dear Soo Jo. My dear Soo Jo.
This is mine.
- Just for today. - That is the newest one.
I have a business meeting today.
Gosh. I need to eat some, too.
Even if my parents live next door, I won't see them.
Even if they are rich, I don't care.
I only need you.
Thank you for saying that,
- my son. - Open up.
Are you going to send him off tomorrow?
I should.
I prepared dinner for him for the last time,
but he hasn't come home yet.
He must be busy delivering alcohol.
Are you going to be okay alone after you send him?
You guys stuck together like twin brothers.
It'll be hard, but I should still send him.
I'm going leave far away, too.
Where to?
You don't have any family. Where are you going to go?
Just like the nature of the wind and waves,
I will just wander around.
I feel so bad for you.
You got something from them, didn't you?
What do you mean?
They must have expressed their gratitude to you.
Do Geum, you're life will change now that you sold off your son.
Sold off my son? Take that back.
But it's true.
You had a tough time raising him for 32 years.
Of course, you should receive good money.
You... You jerk.
- Help! - You punk.
What's your problem?
You...
Hey. Are you crazy?
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
You jerk.
My gosh. Why did you have to come in right at that moment?
You should've ducked.
That totally woke me up.
Did you have a fight with Sam Sik?
Don't talk about Sam Sik any more.
What a brat. I even hate that he eats three meals a day.
I thought you were jealous of him.
Why did you prepare dinner?
Let's eat.
Ta-da.
I heated it again and again, so it boiled down too much.
It's your favourite, beef radish soup.
You must be hungry. Let's eat now.
Are you considering this as our last meal?
Forget it. I'm not going to eat.
Go ahead and eat.
Don't say a word and just do as I tell you to.
After eating dinner, let's go to a bathhouse.
Is that another part of your farewell ceremony?
- You should scrub off your dirt. - I don't like scrubbing.
You know I don't like taking baths.
Do you want to look filthy when you meet them?
Take a bath and wear new clothes before you meet them.
You look so skinny these days.
If you look so skinny and dirty when you meet them,
they'll blame me for that.
I'm 32 years old already.
You treat me like a three-year-old baby.
To me, you're still a baby.
Are you going to obey me or not?
Fine, I will.
I'll eat and gain weight. Then let's go to a bathhouse.
It's delicious to eat late at night.
- Did Ms Nam cook this? - Yes.
We don't have a kitchen.
If we had one, I would've cooked everything.
Don't expect anything else.
When I meet her, I'm going to ask her just one thing and come back.
What are you talking about? You should live with them.
I can't let you enjoy your life alone without me.
You should eat, too. You're giving the expensive fish only to me.
I can eat the head of the fish.
I guess you're really not my biological father.
The head is the most delicious part.
Watch out. You'll spill everything.
My son.
I thought you were sleeping.
No. I couldn't fall asleep.
Do you want to have a drink, too?
You're not supposed to drink alcohol.
Having a drink or two won't kill me.
I just can't wait to meet him.
I can't fall asleep because I'm so anxious and nervous.
The fact that I'm meeting your son for the first time...
feels surreal and makes me confused.
I'm sure you're going through worse.
I should've seen him more carefully when he came to deliver water.
Since I didn't pay attention to him, I don't remember how he looked.
I think he was quite tall.
Who does he resemble?
I don't know.
He must've went through a lot.
He didn't get to go to college, and he's now delivering water.
It's quite obvious that he's not doing so well.
It's heartbreaking.
Do you think he'll blame us for not looking for him in the past?
I'll devote my life to him and treat him well.
I'll try to compensate for all the hardships he had to go through.
Of course.
You should take responsibility for giving birth to him.
That's what a parent should do.
Are you that desperate to become the director?
Just pretend like it never happened.
I thought sons were useless.
But I guess it's nice to have one around.
Is it delicious?
It doesn't look like it's from an ordinary supermarket.
It's from a bakery. It's expensive.
My taste buds must know that it's expensive.
Gab Soon bought this.
What?
I won't eat this.
What's the matter?
Did she tell you to coax me with these biscuits?
It's not like that.
Did you think I would change my mind because of some biscuits?
Forget it.
You make me go crazy.
Gab Soon isn't like that. She's a nice girl.
A nice girl? Then am I mean?
Are you taking her side in front of me?
I'm not taking her side. I'm just telling you the truth.
She walked me home saying that you'll be lonely on a day like this.
Other girls would've expected to have a date at a fancy restaurant.
That's the kind of person she is.
She bought me biscuits and sent me home so I could spend time with you.
My gosh. Do you expect me to be so grateful about that?
How could you just fall for her tricks?
Whenever I did what she told me to, everything turned out good.
Gab Soon always took care of everything I couldn't.
I never once forgot your birthday thanks to Gab Soon.
She's also the one who told me to study to become a public official.
Are you Gab Soon's servant or what?
Yes. I'm her servant.
I can't do anything without her.
I did everything because she told me to.
And was there any kind of bad outcome?
She helped me become a public official. You don't know anything.
What a brat. Look at how you're talking to your own mother.
If you get married to her,
you'll only take her side and completely ignore me.
It's obvious.
- Ms Nam. - What is it?
Be quiet.
Please be quiet.
My son just fell asleep.
Why does everyone in your family have such a loud voice?
Ms Nam. If you yell like that, men won't like you.
If you want to do it, do it right.
Do you think splashing water on your face is enough?
Don't even think that I'll give in.
Even though you demonstrate against me in various ways, I won't budge.
Mum!
Gab Dol! Be quiet!
Today must be a day for water splashes.
Let's not see each other any more.
I'm sure we both have a lot to say,
but let's just end this.
Who is it?
Jae Soon.
What brings you here at this hour?
I got so frustrated, so I came here in the middle of washing rice.
In the middle of washing rice?
Should I go in, or should I say it here?
- The kids are sleeping. - Then I'll say it here.
I don't need this.
Why are you doing this?
Is this to fend me off?
Be honest. I was shocked so I couldn't say anything earlier.
Why do you want to break up? Is it because of your ex-wife?
I just woke up, so I don't understand what you're saying.
You asked to meet, but you didn't text me or call me once.
Were you trying to test me or what?
Then you suddenly came to see me at night wanting to break up.
Are you seeing her again?
It's not because of my ex-wife.
That's enough. I saw you meeting her mother.
- I saw you give her money. - It's not what you think.
Did you give her money because you feel sorry for your ex-wife?
No. I was just returning the money she gave me for the children.
I felt sorry that she had to go through such hardship.
What about me? Do you think I'm not going through anything?
That's not what I mean.
I don't want to be a part of this any more.
I already went through enough when we were living together.
You want to end things?
Is there even anything to end? What are we anyway?
Fine, let's end it.
I haven't opened it yet.
But since we're breaking up, I don't need to.
Where did you go in the middle of washing rice?
I just went out for a walk.
What did you say?
I went for a walk.
It's freezing cold. Why did you go out?
I hope you would stop asking me questions.
There are days when I want to go out for a walk.
My goodness. Why are both my daughters like that?
I can't believe their my daughters.
I have something to say. Should I do it here or outside?
I'm busy as you can see. I have nothing to hear from you.
If you're going to apologise, don't. I don't want to hear it.
I'm not here to apologise.
I couldn't respond yesterday because...
I was only half awake, not because I didn't have anything to say.
Don't you think I was hurt as well?
- Why were you hurt? - Why would I want to break up?
Because you don't have feelings for me any more.
There's no way that will happen.
It's not only you. I saw you too.
I saw you meet Ddol Ee's father.
Jae Soon. Come quick!
Okay!
What's this?
Your mum sent it for you. Wear it.
How does she know my size?
- That's easy to figure out. - Did she see me?
She didn't see you. I told her.
Do I need to?
She bought it for you, so you should wear it.
Look. She sent you clothes.
These are expensive brand clothes.
I can't buy you things like these.
I can only buy you fakes or second-hand clothes.
I still can't believe that I have a mum.
I don't really feel anything.
I don't miss her since I've never seen her. I'm not interested.
There were times when I wanted a mum.
But now, I'm not glad to meet her.
That was only when I was little.
I don't need a mum now. I'm all grown up.
- Do I need to see her today? - You do.
Change into these.
You look handsome. You're the best.
- What this? - Your luggage.
I packed your underwear and socks. I picked the ones without holes.
She'll probably buy you new ones.
You should have some spare ones in the meantime.
You can't be bare naked underneath.
Let's go.
You should go. It's the seventh floor.
Aren't you coming?
Why should I go? It'll be awkward.
- You should go alone. - No, come with me.
I'll be waiting here. Hurry up.
You have to stay here. It won't take more than five minutes.
You should at least eat and talk with her.
What is there to talk about?
I'm just going to ask her why she abandoned me.
Wait here.
Soo Jo.
Why?
I just wanted to take another look at you.
You look handsome.
Go on.
Geum Soo Jo.
You need to live happily.
My son.
Farewell.
My son. You're so adorable.
Study after you finish eating this.
Here.
- You must be cold. - I'm cold.
You must be tired.
It'd be nice if you could quit your job.
What do you want to eat? I'll cook you something.
Let's go inside.
Mum, I'm hungry.
Mum, stop it.
Mum, I love you more than anything in the world.
Mum.
Stop walking around and have a seat. You're making me anxious.
I'm nervous.
Me too.
Why isn't he coming?
Soo Jo.
Welcome.
What's wrong?
Soo Jo!
Soo Jo, wait.
Please. Just talk to me.
Can't you look at me just once?
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I apologise. Please forgive me.
Soo Jo.
I can't take my clothes off, so I'll send them to you when I get home.
(Room for rent)
I guess not.
Aren't you moving out?
Send it back.
Don't be angry. The reason I didn't tell you earlier...
Don't say another word.
How did that happen?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You should have told me.
He must be hurt.
How could you?
You could've recognised him. Didn't you even have a hunch?
My goodness. What should we do?
Mum.
This is for you.
What is it?
You don't need to know. Go up to your room.
It's what Soo Jo wore.
I want to die.
Don't be like that. I have a plan.
What plan?
Here.
- What's this? - Cho Rong's mum...
sent this for the kids.
I can't take it. Please give it back to her.
(Schubert Piano Academy)
Cho Rong. Da Rong.
- Grandma! - My sweethearts.
Grandma. What took you so long?
I missed you.
I missed you both, too.
Cho Rong, have you been well?
You're all grown up already. Da Rong, you too.
You need your mum at this age.
You should eat well.
I know you were hurt,
but you should answer my calls at least.
I missed you so much.
Where did you move to?
Take me there.
My goodness.
Where are you going?
- To the supermarket. - The supermarket?
You've just came back from the supermarket.
She sneaked out like an old man sneaking out to see another lover.
- Your brother? - He has no lover.
She took all the freshly made kimchi.
My goodness.
Oh, my.
We bought oysters and pears...
to make it for the whole family.
We haven't even tasted it yet.
Geum Sik will probably eat it all.
My goodness.
The house looks clean.
- Did you clean the house? - Pardon?
- Did you cook rice? - Grandma made it.
She came here?
Yes. She just left.
Mother.
How...
What is that?
Why are you living in a rooftop house?
It's too cold for the kids.
The heater didn't seem to be working well.
There wasn't any rice nor any food.
What happened?
Are you bankrupt?
No. Something happened to the company.
What happened?
Don't worry.
Things will work out soon.
I hope so.
I feel so bad for the kids.
Why are you making them go through this?
- I apologise. - It's obvious.
You were out of your mind because of a woman.
Did she leave with your money?
What?
Watch what your saying!
I'm just saying this because I'm upset.
If you took care of things properly,
my granddaughters wouldn't be like this.
They're my daughters.
Don't come here any more.
I'm not here to see you. I'm here to see my granddaughters.
Leave us alone. I'll take care of it.
Is this all you can do?
How bad of a businessman are you?
Mind your own business.
This isn't your place.
You're going too far.
I'll be off.
I'm home.
I made bossam with kimchi. Eat it with the children.
Eat it with the cooked rice.
I didn't cook the rice.
Cho Rong. Da Rong. I'll get going now.
You should go after her. She seems upset.
Leave her be.
Da Rong. Let's have lunch.
Well done. Are you stealing our kimchi for them?
Jae Soon!
You thief!
All daughters are thieves.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Are you ill?
I have indigestion.
Have a seat.
It hurts.
You must have an upset stomach. Did you take medicine?
I just did.
Then wait a while.
Aren't I the best doctor?
You made me ill in the first place.
I saw the kids today.
Where are they? How are they doing?
They live in the rooftop house across the intersection.
I followed Cho Rong there. It's a mess.
It's so windy that my hands were frozen from the cold.
I'm worried about the kids.
They never had to go through any hardships.
There's nothing in the refrigerator. I bet they eat ramyeon everyday.
I guess things aren't going well for my brother-in-law.
What brother-in-law? He's not your family.
He's still my brother-in-law.
That's only when he was around.
He changed. He even yelled at me.
I don't understand what happened to him.
That's why men should meet good women.
Nothing good happened to him after meeting Gab Soon's sister.
I've never seen any good coming out of marrying twice.
They got divorced because of Da Hae.
Whatever.
(Gab Soon)
You cannot reach this phone. You'll be directed to voicemail.
Please speak after the beep.
Here.
It's a goal!
Wait.
- Are you having fun? - Yes.
That's it.
Look ahead.
There you go.
You've grown up so much.
Look! You have a shark's head now!
Let's meet.
(Let's meet.)
Why do I have to be the one to text you first?
Why do you have to keep your mouth shut?
You haven't texted nor called me since yesterday.
Are you making me frustrated on purpose?
No matter how it might end, we need to deal with it in person.
You should know how to deal with an upset woman.
What kind of a man are you?
I don't have experience in that area. I don't know how to do that.
Why don't you give it a try then? That's not something to be proud of.
I was going to visit you after work.
I would've gone crazy before then.
I don't like fighting. I'm not good at that.
Me neither. I'm not a fighter, either.
Jae Soon.
I tend to stutter and say stupid things...
when a woman talks fast and starts arguing with me.
- Was I talking fast? - It's becoming faster these days.
I try hard not to act like this.
But I don't know why we keep having trouble.
I don't know why this keeps happening.
We promised to start fresh by acting like we didn't have children.
But things like this keep happening, so it's frustrating.
I'm sorry.
Just saying sorry isn't enough. We should find a solution.
We agreed to figure things out together.
But your ex-wife's families keep showing up.
This is absurd.
It has nothing to do with my will.
I heard she even went to see Cho Rong at her piano academy.
We already had an argument. I told her never to show up again.
Did you meet her again?
No, I just bumped into her on my way home.
I was feeling down, so I didn't have the energy to console you.
Let me explain about what happened last time.
It's true that I met Ddol Ee's father.
But I met him only because of Ddol Ee.
You know what it's like. It's because of the kids.
I know.
Still, I was upset.
I could also understand how you must have felt.
It serves you right. You should know what it feels like.
You're right.
You learn a lesson only through your own experience. Especially men.
Be honest with me. Why did you say you wanted to break up?
I thought you were seeing Ddol Ee's father again.
So that's why you threw me a present and broke up with me?
So that's why you came and woke me up in the middle of the night?
I'm probably the only person in Korea who woke up...
in the middle of the night only to be scolded in pyjamas.
Didn't you feel sorry for me?
I was half awake and shivering in my pyjamas.
Did you feel better after that?
That's why I brought you some kimchi.
My family even called me a thief because of that.
I guess I'm the one at fault.
Ddol Ee, let's go this way.
Ddol Ee, did you have fun today?
- Yes. - You two look like twins.
Of course they do. They're father and son.
Ddol Ee has grown up a lot.
Ddol Ee, you must have had a lot of fun today.
We want to play with him,
but we don't have enough energy.
Once, I became really sick after playing with him.
That's when Ddol Ee was going to the hospital.
He wouldn't have had to go if he grew up with his dad.
- He went a hospital? - What?
Was Ddol Ee sick?
That's not true.
He just had a cold.
Yes, it was just a cold.
Ddol Ee was sick from a cold.
- Oh, no. - Mum.
Ddol Ee, did you have fun?
I'm so excited.
I played basketball and rode a bicycle with Dad.
Did you?
Just quit your job at the supermarket.
Just take care of Ddol Ee at home.
He's right. You don't even earn that much. He's telling you to quit.
It's none of your business.
Come on. Look.
Don't they look like twins?
It's so cheesy.
I don't like matching clothes.
It looks nice to me.
Mum, I fell down today while riding the bicycle.
Are you all right?
What if he got hurt?
Don't worry. That's how boys grow up.
You don't need to worry.
- Dad, let's go ride it again. - Of course we will.
When you grow up, I'll teach you how to drive a car.
- I'm so excited! - Of course, you are.
My gosh, he looks happy.
I didn't earn much today. It's 60 dollars.
- You're annoying. - Last time,
I had 99,220 dollars left.
Since I gave you 60 dollars today, I'll minus that amount.
That's 99,860 dollars now.
Until when do I have to see you like this?
Until I pay the whole 100,000 dollars back.
Share this with your nieces.
It looked delicious, so I bought some.
- What is it? - It's bungeoppang.
- It's still warm. - I don't need it.
Hey, do you know where Dal Pa goes every night?
I don't know. He just told me that he was going to visit someone.
You should've convinced him to come home.
Dal Pa is going to throw a fit if he sees you again. Go to your room.
There he is.
Where have you been? I got scolded because of you.
Aunt Nae Shim.
This is for you.
You didn't need to. Thank you.
It's cold outside, isn't it?
Aren't you hungry?
Don't talk to me. Don't even look at me.
What are you doing?
She's your mother.
How could you talk like that to your own mother?
What are you doing here? Everyone, just go to sleep.
She's your mother no matter what.
She just made a mistake.
You can't use that against her to treat her like that.
Don't you feel bad for her?
A mistake?
How could you call that a mistake?
Do you even know what she did to me?
Hey. Dal Pa!
Why did you do that?
He finally came home. Why did you push him away?
It's so cold outside. He has nowhere to stay!
You made a mistake, but you're still his mother.
If only good parents were considered to be parents,
not many people can be treated as parents in this world.
The only reason why he comes here is because his mother is here.
It seems like your dad...
feels bad about his sister, but I don't feel like that at all.
You get what you deserve.
Why did she do that?
I have no idea.
She always says...
that she's living proof.
She's the one who made all that proof.
Whoever you are, you shouldn't do something you'll regret later.
I feel bad for Dal Pa. He's always intimidated at home.
It's because he used to live with us ever since he was little.
What's wrong with living with us?
I'm the one who had a hard time because of the mother and son.
I think he cares about you, though. He buys snacks for you like this.
It must be because I took care of him...
whenever his mum left him when he was young.
If he's not grateful for that, that'd be nonsense.
But...
I feel like there's some dirt inside.
- Me, too. - Me, too.
I kept tasting dirt.
Do you think he brought home what was thrown away?
Somehow, I always find something strange in my food these days.
- What do you mean? - I'm asking just to be sure.
Is Jae Soon seeing her ex-husband?
But you're her ex-husband.
I'm not talking about me. I meant the second husband.
It's all set now. They even took care of the documents.
Why do you ask all of a sudden?
She has to meet you because you two have a kid,
but there's no reason for them to meet.
It's nonsense.
They got divorced because Jae Soon didn't like him.
Are you sure she wasn't kicked out?
What are you talking about?
Jae Soon was the one who left him.
He was the one who cried and tried to get her back.
It seems like he keeps trying to reach her even now.
What kind of person is he?
He used to own a quite successful business,
but it looks like he's some kind of a salesperson these days.
He's not wealthy at all.
He's not even comparable to you. You don't need to worry.
I'm not the type to worry.
Good. I'll make some bibim guksu for you. Have some before you leave.
Your father-in-law isn't home.
Thank you, but I have a business meeting. Maybe next time.
What's wrong with you?
- What do you mean? - I think Se Bang...
saw you meeting Geum Sik.
What are you going to do?
You talk as if I did something unfaithful behind my husband's back.
How ridiculous.
Please think of Ddol Ee.
Ddol Ee, look over here.
Dad, play with me.
He's a carbon copy of me, right?
Let me ask you straightforwardly.
Who is it that's dragging this on?
Tell us.
Who is the one that won't let go?
It must be Gab Soon.
It's Gab Soon who won't let go of Gab Dol.
- She's right. - Can't you do without him?
She dated him for 10 years. Of course she can't do without him.
Whatever my reason is,
I won't let him go for my own sake.
Where else can I find someone like Gab Dol?
He's the best husband material since he's a public official.
On top of that, he's handsome and healthy.
I trained him for 10 years. I won't let someone else take him.
How do I know if my business will last or not?
If I have a public official as a husband,
I would have an insurance. Why would I let that go?
I'm doing this because I've thought about it.
I'm not stupid, Dad.
I'm not dumb, Mum.
I hope you'll all understand.
I'm so upset.
What are we going to do about Gab Soon? Can you talk to her?
- She listens to you. - All right.
I was going to meet with Jae Soon to talk anyway.
What is it?
It's a date.
How did you know I like younger men?
I like older women, but you're not my type.
It's hard to work at the supermarket, right?
The work isn't hard, but the overall situation is.
Is it because of Se Bang?
I don't want to discuss this with my brother.
Why did you want to see me?
Call me whenever you're down. We'll go for drinks.
I heard Gab Soon and Gab Dol want to get married.
The family's against it, but she's adamant.
I called them here so we can talk.
Se Gye. Jae Soon, you're here, too?
Hello.
Sit down.
- I heard you're getting married. - Yes.
Both of your parents are against it. Do you think it'll work?
We'll make it work.
Do you agree with her?
Yes. Well...
You dated for 10 years. It's about time you got married.
It's been 11 years.
Are you prepared for the wedding?
Of course not.
What about a place?
Where will you live?
Of course they don't have a place to live.
Gab Dol. How much have you saved up?
It's been just a few months since I got hired.
What about you, Gab Soon?
I'm not much different.
I only got to start my business thanks to the investment.
Of course they don't have anything.
They were jobless for a while.
It's not a surprise.
How will you get married when you don't have money for a place?
Gab Dol, can your family help?
- No. - What about you?
Don't bother asking. You're wasting your time.
Are you going to help us?
Don't mind him.
I want to help, but I don't have that much.
You can't even afford a place to live in.
Wanting to get married won't solve anything.
You should prepare yourselves and make a plan...
before you tell your parents.
Getting married costs a lot.
You have to prepare wedding gifts, too.
You can't just force a wedding to happen...
without preparing anything.
I would've been against it too if I were your parents.
They're still so immature. It's all just talk.
There's no need to listen. My ears hurt.
Let's go, Se Gye.
What Se Gye said is true.
We'll start off from a rental place.
- Rent? - Don't forget our circumstances.
I gave up on living a wealthy life when I decided to marry you.
Whenever I imagined marrying you,
I pictured living in the extra room or your room at your house.
Unfortunately, I've never dreamt of anything better than that.
Can't we delay the date?
Why? I don't want to move it to next year.
We were going to do it last year. We should do it this spring.
That fast?
Spring is too soon.
How about fall?
Let's get it over with while we're passionate.
If we get lukewarm, it'll be over.
Just follow my lead.
What is it?
I want to get married right now, too.
However, there's our family and the house.
My mum is sick.
Gab Soon, let's make it autumn.
That's so far away.
But I promise to prepare everything by then.
I'll get Mum's permission and find us a nice place to live.
Like Se Gye said,
how can I marry you without a place to live in?
All you have to do is marry me. I'll prepare everything.
Let's make it autumn, okay?
- Did you call me? - Come sit here.
Work is tough, isn't it?
I'm sure you were stressed while working with me.
On that note, what do you think about quitting?
- Pardon? - This place isn't right for you.
Someone else will be coming to replace you.
Can't you go back to being a doctor?
Your grandfather-in-law and I...
liked you because you were a doctor.
This isn't right.
If you work as a doctor for three years,
I'll help you open your clinic.
I'll take care of my own matters.
I feel sorry for your parents.
How can they just watch their son do this?
It's such a waste of your license.
Do your parents have an ulterior motive...
because of our family's wealth?
Please don't talk like that.
I'll take everything else,
but please do not talk bad about my family.
From now on, I'll take care of my business.
Please do not worry.
I repeat.
I have no interest in this business.
My parents have no interest in your wealth, either.
That's fine,
but that's no reason for you to glare at me.
I'll excuse myself.
I was about to go out. Did something happen?
No.
I was just craving your cooking.
I have to go out right now.
It's okay, then.
There's cheonggukjang from earlier. Do you want to eat it?
You should have ate out.
You were too busy to eat when you were a doctor,
but you have a lot of time now.
Why are you skipping meals?
There's so much good food out there.
Yes, I'm on my way.
They won't appreciate you if you visit too often.
You should only show up time to time.
Were you fired?
Those in-laws' of yours are really tough on you.
Eat some food while you're here.
I've never felt so useless...
in all my life.
I feel like the world doesn't need me.
I feel empty...
and ashamed.
I didn't know I was this worthless.
I thought I could do anything if I wasn't a doctor.
At least that's what I thought.
That's why I started working at the office.
However,
I've lost my way now.
You're not like yourself.
Don't think like that.
You're always logical and rational.
You'll be able to find your way.
Is there something you're hiding from me?
Even if I tell you,
nothing will change.
You can at least talk to me.
(Gong Joo)
Let's just drink.
Hello?
I'm Se Gye's wife.
Are you with him right now? He's not picking up.
I'm not with him right now.
I'll hang up.
What is it? Why are you calling her?
Don't do this.
You're with her?
Yes, I am. We're having a drink.
If I don't pick up, then there must be a reason.
What are you suspecting?
- Does it hurt a lot? - You should go sleep.
Let's see a doctor tomorrow.
Of course I'm sick after what you've done to me.
I'll be good, so don't be sick.
Come outside. I'm in front of your place.
I can't right now. I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll wait until you come out.
Why do I have to go to the washroom again?
What is it?
We dated for over 10 years, right?
- Yes. - We've known each other for 20.
Yes. Why?
Then you must know by just looking into my eyes or hearing my voice.
Well...
I can tell everything about you.
You're acting strange lately.
You don't call me or text me.
I have an idea, but I want you to tell me honestly.
- It's not like that. - Don't make an excuse.
I'm not mad. I just want to check, that's all.
Why do you want to change the date to autumn?
- There are several reasons... - Forget it.
Just pick. Is it me or your mum?
She's sick right now.
Answer me. Is it me or your mum?
What kind of question is that?
I said, answer me. Is it me or your mum?
I got it.
I heard your answer.
I won't get married.
What is she saying?
She won't get married.
- Really? - Yes. I won't get married.
I'm sorry about what happened. I won't take questions.
That's good news, but what happened to her?
Does she think this is a press conference?
She just announced what she wants and declined to take questions.
Se Gye and I met with them and scolded them.
It must have got to them.
In any case, I'm happy. They were being so arrogant.
It worked out.
It's cold. Why are you outside?
I can't sleep.
I heard you met your biological mother.
I only heard of such stories on dramas.
You must have a lot on your mind.
Why did she leave you?
I didn't even ask.
It's obvious. She probably left me to have a better life.
Let's not talk about it.
How is it going with Gab Soon? I heard you're getting married.
- What's wrong? - I'm so stupid.
I can't get anything right.
You're not stupid.
I'm most jealous of you in this world.
You talked about love one time.
You said nothing matters in the world without her.
You don't want to eat, and you can't laugh.
You said everything just comes to a halt.
You're know better about love than I do,
but I know one thing.
Love...
doesn't just come to you.
Mum, I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Gab Soon told us it's over.
No.
I came to ask for your permission.
Father, Mother, please give us permission.
Forget it. Get your family's permission first.
We'll consider it then.
Did you eat?
Don't ask him when we're not giving him food.
Go. Don't just sit there.
How did you visit just in time for a meal?
Father, please give us your permission.
I already said what I have to say when I saw you last time.
- Get me more soup. - Okay.
This year's kimchi is really good.
The cabbage was good.
That's because I grew them.
- Mother. - Don't talk to me when I'm eating.
What don't you understand?
You should listen to your elders. Are you ignoring me?
I won't move until you give me your permission.
Do as you wish. I don't care.
Here.
It tastes good.
Gab Soon, Gab Dol is at home.
Why is he there? Send him away.
I think you have to come.
Okay.
- The soup is so good. - It's good.
I like it.
It's so good.
Are you Jo Geum Man?
No. It's Jo Geum Sik.
You should go. I don't think today is the day.
I won't go.
Doing this won't help.
We already told you.
Get your mother's permission first.
If you give us your permission, we'll get married regardless.
You must be crazy.
You must you look down on our family.
Being stubborn won't help. It's not the right order.
In this situation, you must get your mother's permission first.
You should come to beg or do whatever else afterwards.
What you're doing doesn't make sense.
Don't you know any better?
- Leave. - Father.
You heard him, right? You should go.
I can't.
Please, Mother.
We'll get married no matter what my family says.
You're going to live without seeing your mother?
Can you do that?
- I won't see her. - My goodness.
Hello. Is this Gab Dol's mother?
- I'm Gab Soon's mum. - Mum.
I'm Gab Soon's mum.
So?
Why are you calling me?
I don't know what you want to say to me,
but I don't want to hear it.
You brat. You better listen to me.
Take your son away from here.
What?
Your son has been kneeling down...
and begging us for our approval of their marriage.
I can't bear to watch it any more.
I can't beat him since he's not my son, so please get him out of here.
Leave before your mother comes and cause a commotion.
I don't want to see her.
I can't leave.
It's better this way.
When she comes, I will settle it once and for all.
What's wrong with you?
Can't you understand what I'm saying?
You should obey when your elders tell you to do something.
Do you think it's proper to sit there stubbornly?
Take these with you. I don't need this.
Mum!
What?
I didn't mean to throw it that hard.
He's not even hurt.
This is too much. I can't believe you did this.
How can you treat him this way?
Do you expect his mum to treat me well when you're being like this?
Just as I'm precious to you, he is precious to his mother.
Stand up.
Stand up!
He probably can't get up because his legs fell asleep.
He's been kneeling down for two hours.
Stand up!
Why did you come by yourself?
What did you expect?
You came to my house by yourself, too.
I can handle your mother.
But you can't handle my family.
My family is a lot bigger.
Your legs must hurt a lot.
Gab Soon.
I feel so incompetent. I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry.
I know how you feel now, so it's okay.
Let's give up...
on trying to get married.
You want to break up?
Ms Nam.
It's over there.
Forget the marriage. Let's just live together.
What did you say?
Let's live together.