(Episode 38)
What brings you here at this hour?
What was that for?
Did it upset you that much when I told you that I paid off your debt?
Even so, how could you use violence to me like this all of a sudden?
If I fight back, I will only be reduced to your level.
I will let it go tonight.
For someone who's been harsh with my son, you have a lot to say.
- What did you say? - Because of what you did,
my son had to go through psychological treatments.
Do you think I raised you so you could live like this?
You make me so ashamed.
I am disappointed in you.
I didn't think you'd be so foolish.
Get out of the house now.
They had a ceremony at a fast food restaurant...
with tteokbokki and fish cake soup.
I was frustrated at the fact that she didn't listen to us.
But I felt bad when I heard about their ceremony.
They invited only a few of their elementary school friends.
Women remember their wedding ceremony forever.
I know it wasn't a proper wedding, but it's still the same thing.
That crazy wench. She's so foolish.
How can she drive a stake through our hearts like this?
Sooner or later, our relatives and friends will find out.
Let's just let them have a proper wedding ceremony.
Hey! What are you saying?
Do you think I raised you so you could live like this?
You have no idea how hard it was to raise you without a father.
How can you betray your own mother just because of a girl?
I don't need a son like you. Get out now!
He told me to keep it a secret, but I guess I have no choice.
Your son, Gab Dol, came to see me.
He did?
Why?
Did he ask you for money so he can get a place to stay?
No, it was nothing like that.
How can you be so ignorant of your own child?
Well, I'm not much better.
He brought the marriage registration form which you tore up.
He told me to treat you right because you are a respectable lady.
He told me to treat you with respect.
He sternly warned me.
He told me that you're the person he respects the most.
You should be proud of him. A son like that would make anyone happy.
I envy you.
I would be proud to have a son like him.
You might feel that he is still immature.
But he is a wise person.
You should trust a son like him.
If he wants to marry that girl, allow him to do so.
He may seem immature to you, but I think he's all grown up.
Trust him.
Jae Soon, wake up.
Why? What's wrong?
You said you know where Gab Soon lives, right?
Lead the way.
You're going, too?
I'm so annoyed that I can't sit still.
I may be old, but I'm still the head of this household.
How dare the youngest of the family cause so much trouble?
Exactly!
I don't know how many times...
I had to bring back my daughter trying to live with a guy.
It's your second time.
I didn't want to have Gab Soon.
Why did you make me give birth to her and cause all this headache?
You're the one who didn't know you were pregnant for six months.
She's been out of your womb for 30 years. You can't put her back in.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Gab Dol!
Jae Soon.
- Hello. - What are you doing at this hour?
- I was washing rice. - Where is it?
- Pardon? - Where is your honeymoon suite?
What do you mean, "honeymoon suite"?
Come this way.
Please come in.
Where is Gab Soon?
She went out for her morning cleaning job.
I was going to make breakfast and go to work.
Why is it so cold in here?
The heater broke a few days ago.
The water faucet is frozen, too.
Let's leave.
- Let's do it. - Let's try hard and live well.
I promise not to make Gab Soon unhappy.
Gab Dol will be fully responsible for everything.
We will respect each other and be happy.
Rules for a married couple.
(Heo Gab Dol, Shin Gab Soon)
Do not contact Gab Soon ever again.
Don't let her in the house, and don't ever call her.
Dad.
Just do as I say.
Do you understand?
Treat her as if she's not our child.
Hold on.
- Why? - Sit down.
What is it?
- Please do this one favour for me. - What?
I understand that you're feeling annoyed and disrespected.
I feel the same way.
I'm frustrated at the fact that I can't control my own child.
It annoys me so much.
However, I think we should just let them have their ways.
After seeing all that?
What else can we do?
She is still our child.
What do you want to do?
Regardless of what Gab Dol's mum says, let's let them get married.
I can't let them live like that.
Dad, just let them get married. It's better that way.
I'm not saying this because I approve of their actions.
And I'm not saying this because I'm not angry.
I just can't bear to watch them live like that.
Letting them get married is the only way I'll be able to live.
Where did you all go without me?
You saw their house.
Their heater doesn't work, and the water faucet is frozen.
I am angry at her, but how can we watch her live at a place like that?
She's our child no matter what happens.
You're so sympathetic.
That's why no parent can control his or her child.
This is my wish.
I'm not asking this for her sake.
It's solely for me to be at peace.
But Gab Dol's mum is against it.
Let's just do it with or without her approval.
Gab Dol already left home anyway.
If she saw them, she would have beaten up Gab Soon.
It's better that she didn't see them live like that.
She was so proud when Gab Dol became a public official.
If she saw her son washing rice...
with that cold water at that hour,
she would have beaten up Gab Soon.
- Let's go. - Where are we going?
We should at least notify her.
The sun hasn't even come up yet.
Let's go. They will freeze to death if we wait much longer.
Dal Tong, do you know where Gab Dol lives?
Aren't we here too early? The sun hasn't even come up.
Let's go in. I bet she can't sleep, either.
- My goodness! - Oh, my gosh!
I'm sorry for coming so early.
But we felt like this was urgent, so we came running to you.
What's going on?
It's not even morning yet, and you're both here.
Do you know that the two had an agreement ceremony yesterday?
Say whatever you need to.
Do you know that it wasn't Gab Dol...
but Gab Soon who made that happen?
If someone's talking to you, you should at least look at them.
It's not like I came here because I wanted to.
It's the truth.
Since things turned out like this,
we were thinking about just letting them get married.
- What? - What can we do?
They already took action.
We as adults need to sort things out.
We can't abandon our children, can we?
We were going to ignore them at first.
But we went to see how they were living, and it wasn't even funny.
He was washing rice in a tiny basement room...
with no heater and no running water.
What rice? Who was washing it?
Gab...
Let's just get to the point here.
On our side, we agreed to marry them off,
even if it's within this week.
Agreed with whom? I never approved.
We're not here for your approval. We're here to give you prior notice.
Pardon?
I wondered who Gab Soon took after. She takes after you.
Causing trouble and then giving notice.
Then we'll do as we please.
What are you saying?
We told you. We're going to let them get married.
We'll marry them off within this week.
And I'll take care of Gab Dol like he's my own son.
What are you saying? He's my son.
We'll marry them off our way,
and if you still won't see Gab Dol,
we're saying that we'll take him in.
So are you saying that...
you're going to make Gab Dol live with you?
We've never thought of it that way,
but we will if we need to.
Then is it okay to fix the date as we please?
We're done informing you. We'll be going now.
Let's go.
Wait.
You can't make Gab Dol live with you.
Why must he live with his in-laws?
If they need a place to live, they'll have to live with me.
With you? I can't let that happen.
I don't know what you'll do to Gab Soon.
As you know, I can't afford to buy a house for them.
Are you going to buy a house for them?
That's what the groom's side should prepare.
Wait.
So do you approve of their marriage?
That's what she means.
Then let's talk about the rest later.
Let's marry them off first.
Okay, Jae Soon.
Where are you going? Didn't you order jjajangmyeon?
- You have it instead. - I don't eat jjajangmyeon.
- Would you like jjajangmyeon? - Pardon?
I'll give you a 50 cent discount.
Does anyone here want jjajangmyeon?
Would you like jjajangmyeon?
I'll eat it.
I was thinking of not ever seeing you two again.
You went too far.
Is that how you want to live?
- I'm sorry. - I apologise.
Teach them a lesson this time.
Make sure you teach them what they did wrong.
Give them a good scolding.
Gab Dol, were you happy when you took my precious daughter...
into that kind of house?
I apologise.
Gab Dol, are you satisfied to see your parents-in-law...
give in to you like this?
I apologise.
They finally got it now.
- Father. - Dad.
Why aren't you calling me?
Mum and Dad, thank you.
Mother and Father, I promise I'll be good to her.
I'll move out and rent a house in three years.
How cheeky.
He calls us Mother and Father instantly.
Set a date for your wedding as soon as possible.
You're letting us have a wedding?
Of course. You guys didn't even have a proper wedding.
It's not like you don't have parents.
I won't have a wedding until my mother agrees.
She gave her approval.
- Really? - Really?
We went to see her early in the morning to set things straight.
We got her approval.
Go back to your places.
You should live with your parents until you get married.
- Yes, Sir. - Yes, Sir.
Why didn't you tell me?
I heard Ddol Ee had to undergo psychotherapy.
- How did you... - You should have told me.
How could you make me so ignorant?
I lived with him as his dad for a year.
How could you make me so shameful?
Did you have to make me look like a bad guy?
I didn't even know about that.
I was only caught up in adopting him.
Why didn't you tell me?
Was there no need to tell me since I don't deserve to be his dad?
I couldn't tell you.
I didn't know if I would live with you or not.
I couldn't tell you that he was ill.
I didn't want you to feel burdened as he isn't your child.
I couldn't tell you because I thought you wouldn't like it.
Since it's my child's problem,
I thought I should take care of it on my own.
I'm sorry.
You must have had a tough time on your own.
You're amazing, Jae Soon.
I wouldn't have been able to do it.
If that happened to Cho Rong or Da Rong,
I wouldn't have been able to hold up like you.
I probably would have blamed the other person.
I apologise.
I guess you couldn't tell me because I didn't give you time.
Thinking back, I lacked too much.
I wanted you to be a good stepmother for my kids.
But I wasn't ready to be a good step dad for Ddol Ee.
It's all in the past.
He's much better now.
Jae Soon.
Let's stop acting like we don't have kids.
Let's admit that we each have our burdens.
You're right.
I'm a pair with Ddol Ee.
You're a trio with Cho Rong and Da Rong.
Then if I take you,
I can have Ddol Ee as well, right?
You buy 1 and get 1 free.
This is why they say you can't fool your job.
Since I work at the supermarket,
I can't help but say those things.
But how did you find out about Ddol Ee's psychotherapy?
Are you a gangster? How dare you hit him?
He must have a big mouth.
Did he tell you that I hit him?
That's so low of you.
It's not for you to say.
You all shouldn't be so confident.
- What are you talking about? - You know.
Fine, I admit I should've taken better care of Ddol Ee.
But do you even have the right to say this to me?
You never called me after the divorce.
You didn't pay child support. You have no right to blame anybody.
You even left your debt behind.
If other people point their fingers at me...
and Ddol Ee blames me, I won't be able to say anything.
But you really should have nothing to say to me.
I'll take care of Ddol Ee from now on.
I'll take him.
What do you mean? Why would you take him?
He's my son. I don't need a reason.
You said so yourself that you had a hard time. I'll do it from now on.
Don't be absurd.
He finally became stable. Where will you take him now? Are you insane?
I'm the sanest I've ever been.
For Ddol Ee, I need to get back to my senses.
Ddol Ee can't live without me.
He only followed me around ever since he was young.
Then there's only one way left.
What are you talking about?
- Mum, what is it? - Se Gye, are you busy?
I'm not busy.
I'm looking over things at the store.
You should drop by.
I felt sad for making you leave like that last time.
I told you to eat, but why did you just leave?
- I saw you, and that was enough. - Can you come now?
Okay, I'll be there soon.
Really?
Yes. We decided to let them get married.
That's great news. You made a wise decision.
I went to their house, and it wasn't even funny.
I couldn't bare to see them live like that.
They love each other.
You should live with the person you want to live with.
You should have approved earlier.
You ended up being stressed for nothing.
You're right. I feel much better after giving them my approval.
They'll need to figure things out on their own now.
I envy them.
Why do you envy them?
What?
It's nothing.
To be honest, you're the one who's lucky.
It could be a little tiresome to live with your in-laws,
but you got to start off your marriage luxuriously.
Since they don't have a son, you'll inherit all their wealth.
Go ahead and eat it before it gets soggy.
So while were on that subject,
can you get me some money?
Money?
How much?
I need to get a house for them.
I can't let Gab Soon live with Gab Dol's mother.
How much will a two-bedroom apartment be?
Could you prepare that money within this week?
Within this week?
I just sounded like a creditor.
I'm asking you for money as if I lent you some.
I'm not asking you to give it to them for free.
I'll tell them to pay you back slowly.
Eat some more. Is it not delicious?
It is delicious, but I had something before I came here.
You're home.
You were here.
Why did you call Se Gye over?
I called him because I wanted to make him some noodles.
Be honest.
I know you.
You talked about money, didn't you?
I did. Why?
Since he is well off, he could lend his sister some money.
It's not like I asked him to give the money to them for free.
Are you out of your mind?
How can you make him ask his in-laws for money?
That's called selling off your son.
Please stop doing things like that.
They should start off their marriage life with the money they have.
I did that because Gab Dol's mother said she would live with them.
Who wants to live with their in-laws these days?
What a foolish woman.
Living with her is way better than living in that basement.
Men are pathetic.
You guys don't know anything.
Ask any woman, and they'll say the same thing.
We can't let Gab Soon live with her when we know how she'll treat her.
She'll suffer to death.
I also think it'll be better for them to live separately.
It would be uncomfortable for them to live together.
They'll just have to put up with that.
They're the ones who don't have money to rent a house.
In the past, they said your wife's parents' house...
and the restroom should be located as far away as possible.
But nowadays, they say it's your husband's parents' house...
that should be located far away.
Of course. I don't even want her living in the same neighbourhood.
What if she takes a walk with her guard down...
and bumps into her mother-in-law?
Imagine bumping into her while she walks around...
with no makeup on. How terrible.
She won't be able to get out of her house...
without having to worry about bumping into her mother-in-law.
She won't be able to do anything. Gosh. It would be so uncomfortable.
If living in the same neighbourhood is this uncomfortable,
living in the same house will feel like prison.
Are mother-in-laws monsters?
You talk about them like hateful enemies.
You are no better than other women.
Mal Nyeon, aren't you going to take my side?
I can't be on your side today.
I'm a woman, too.
- You're right. - You're right.
I'm home.
What do you want to do?
You don't want to live with that wench, do you?
You'd rather live separately even if it's a shabby house, right?
No. I'm going to live at Gab Dol's.
- What? - What?
I was going to tell you anyway.
Don't worry about getting me a house. I can use Gab Dol's room.
I imagined starting my marriage in his room when I was dating him.
How are you going to live with such a small dream?
Look at Jae Soon who only dreams big.
She married only rich men.
Hey, Mal Nyeon.
Aren't you scared of that wench?
Do you want to live there even when you know how she'll treat you?
It'll be impossible for us to visit you.
We've already been there before. There's no need to go again.
You can come.
I'm not afraid of my mother-in-law.
It's been more than 10 years, so I know how to deal with her.
If I know the enemy well, I can always win.
And Mum, stop calling her "that wench".
Treat her like your in-law.
People will blame you if you keep saying that.
Are you already her family member now?
She was her family ever since 10 years ago.
If that's what you've decided to do, go ahead.
But instead,
don't ever come here and complain.
"I shouldn't have lived with her."
"I'm going crazy because of her."
Don't say stuff like that.
I won't.
Blaming your parents is something my daughters are very good at.
I made it clear, okay?
I'll keep that in mind.
Me, too.
Mum.
Mother.
Your parents told me that they'd rent a house for you.
We don't have enough money for that, and I prefer living with you.
- Don't lie to me. - I'm not lying.
Living in separately costs a lot, and we won't be able to save up.
It's much more beneficial for me to live with you.
Did you calculate that already?
She finished calculating 10 years ago. She said it's a great deal.
Gab Soon is smart.
Mother, I have to go to work every day.
That means you'll be doing the housework.
And I'll gain weight from eating your delicious cooking.
I always loved everything you cooked.
To be honest, you cook better than my mum.
My mum is an awesome cook.
Goodbye.
Bye Gab Soon. Congratulations on your wedding.
Thank you.
- Get inside. - I'll see you off.
I won't let anyone kidnap my wife.
Ms Nam.
I didn't try to eavesdrop, but I heard everything in the bathroom.
Your daughter-in-law is so smart.
It seems like she'll be good to you. She says she'll live with you.
She's only willing to live with me so she can use me.
Then are you going to be used by her?
What do you take me for?
I have my own plans.
Men are supposed to provide a house when they get married.
But I don't have any money.
Me not having any money is one thing.
But I also don't like her enough to rent a house.
And if they live alone,
her family will visit them often and treat Gab Dol like their son.
I can't let that happen.
I can't let them take my son away from me.
Gab Dol is naive, so he's already being controlled by Gab Soon.
If I don't protect my own son,
she will keep him on a very short leash.
That's why I have to live with them.
You are so thoughtful.
You are really one of a kind.
You're very smart.
Ever since I was young, people told me that I was smart.
I just didn't have the chance to study.
But if I did, I would've become an important figure now.
Gab Soon thinks she's the smartest one.
How ridiculous.
I'm way smarter than her.
Bring it on.
Let's see who will win.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Soo Jo, wait.
Don't come looking for me.
I don't want to see you.
Hang on a second, Soo Jo.
Please listen to what I have to say.
- I don't want to. - Please. I beg you.
Could you please be generous just this once?
Your mother was...
only 18 years old then.
She lost her mother when she was so young.
She wasn't even talking to me then.
I made a lot of mistakes.
She didn't mean to abandon you.
She said she went to a river to kill both you and herself.
But she couldn't do that.
So she left you by the river and tried to kill herself only.
I don't want to hear anything.
It's something I hadn't heard of until now.
And I still have no desire to know.
You never looked for me. Why are you doing this now?
It's because we're related by blood.
I'm not a kid any more.
Frankly speaking, it's not like I need parents at this age, either.
I don't care who my parents are.
I've never thought about my biological parents.
Having one father is enough for me.
My name is Geum Soo Jo, and my father is Geum Do Geum.
I get it.
Still, I don't want to see you suffering like this.
Let's go home.
There are other people who suffer more than I do.
I don't hate nor blame my biological parents.
I just can't accept the fact that...
the woman who made a false report on me...
and took me to the police station...
is my mother.
Wait.
I'm going to get back together with Jae Soon.
Why are you so surprised? Didn't you see that coming?
I'm going to do everything I can for Ddol Ee.
I understand what you're saying,
but I'm not sure if Jae Soon wants the same.
Why are you so quiet?
We need to hear what Jae Soon thinks.
We don't need to. I'm doing this for our child.
I hope no one disapproves. I'll go ahead with it.
Come on! Attack him!
- Ddol Ee, are you having fun? - Yes, it's fun.
Let's do this again next time.
I wish dad could come with us, too.
We have 2 men and 3 women on each team.
Do you want to see which team eats more?
They say competing with food is the stupidest thing.
We can beat them. Let's eat!
- We can do it! - We can do it!
Let's start.
Da Rong, have some. Hurry up.
It's tasty.
Da Rong, try this one.
Eat some more.
Let's do this more often.
Sure. I'd love to.
I hope you both get a good night's sleep.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
- Ddol Ee, bye. - Goodbye.
Bye, Cho Rong.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
Mum, can I play with dad tomorrow?
What?
Sure.
So do I take turns to spend time with Mr Jo and Dad?
I went sledding and had meat with Mr Jo, Cho Rong and Da Rong.
I'm going to play with dad tomorrow.
Ddol Ee, you're so busy...
playing with two dads.
You spend one day with Geum Sik and the other day with Se Bang.
I'm sure other kids won't know how fun it is.
- Mal Nyeon. - Mal Nyeon.
Jae Soon. I need to talk to you.
Se Bang told me that he's going to get back together with you.
He just notified you?
He came earlier in the afternoon and just notified us.
He said it's the best way for Ddol Ee.
He talks as if he's the only one with an opinion.
What can we say when he says he'll do anything for his kid?
I couldn't even talk about Ddol Ee's psychotherapy.
Honestly, I want you guys to get back together,
but I don't know why your dad is so against it.
What do you want?
A Young, I'm not supposed to work today,
but I suddenly had to come to Busan for a business trip.
It seems like the meeting will take a while.
Could you take care of the children today?
I'm sorry, but I have a flight soon.
It's too late to rearrange the schedule.
All right. I get it.
Cho Rong.
Make sure the door is locked. Your aunt can't come today, either.
So don't open the door for anyone. Keep the door locked.
Okay, Dad.
Wedding present? What do you want?
If I may be honest, I want many things.
People send their daughters off because of that.
They say wealthy families send at least five jewelleries.
A diamond, pearl, gold...
What were the other ones?
Ruby and sapphire?
Yes, that's right.
Five jewelleries including ruby and sapphire.
That includes the earrings, necklace, ring and bracelet.
I've also heard some stuff, so let me share that with you.
Do you know that you need to give us at least three keys?
Did you only hear what you wanted to?
He should be at least a doctor or a lawyer to deserve three keys.
That's what I'm talking about.
Not everyone deserves five jewelleries, either.
Let's not waste our time talking about useless things.
We're not giving you any wedding presents,
so don't expect anything from us, either.
Sounds good. Let's make it even like that.
Her son isn't even that great. How could she ask for three keys?
Did she ask us for three keys?
I have 3 keys. There's 1 for the drawer, 1 for the main door and...
- I only have 2. - Let me give you 1 of my keys.
Give her these.
What's so special about being a public official?
By any chance, did you ask her for five jewelleries?
- Did you do that? - I was annoyed. That's why.
Mal Nyeon, why don't you become a professional fortune-teller?
Stop guessing everything.
So what did you decide to do?
We agreed not to give anything to each other.
Well done.
But don't you think we should give them a little something...
so that they don't complain later?
We're not giving them anything.
I'm sure she won't come in with nothing in her hands.
They should give us at least something cheap.
It'd be insane to send her over with nothing in her hands.
They look nice. Let's get these.
I don't mind buying cheaper ones.
We'll be wearing these forever, so let's get nice rings.
But promise me that this is it.
No matter what our parents say, there shouldn't be any presents.
All right.
We'll take these.
- Gab Soon. - Yes?
As you know, my mum can be a snob sometimes.
- So? - Well...
Do you want me to get presents?
No.
I'm not asking you to get them.
I'll give you money, so just pretend like you bought the presents.
Do you think that makes any sense?
That'd be just deceiving her.
We can't save money like that.
I'm just trying to help you.
Forget it. I didn't hear anything.
We need to come to an agreement.
This won't get us anywhere.
I won't let you loose if you ever do this again.
Cho Rong, is everything all right?
Dad, I'm scared.
Is the door locked?
Yes, when are you coming?
Cho Rong, I'll leave as soon as possible.
(Jae Soon)
Why can't you understand?
You guys got a divorce. Why won't you let her go?
Your not in the situation to date Jae Soon.
Cho Rong, I'm scared.
Why isn't Dad coming?
He'll be here soon. Don't be scared. I'm here.
My gosh!
Cho Rong.
Ms Shin.
Can you come to our place? Dad hasn't come home yet.
Are you by yourselves?
Okay.
Mum, I will be back soon.
Where are you going so late at night?
My boss at work called me.
He wants me to help clean up the warehouse.
I can't believe he's making you work at night.
Cho Rong.
- Ms Shin. - Ms Shin.
Da Rong.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm here now.
It's okay.
Why is the room so cold?
I'm not sure.
It's been cold for a while.
I wonder if the heater is broken.
Wait a minute.
I think the heater is broken. Get dressed.
My goodness! It's completely burned.
Come in.
What are you doing?
Why did you bring them here?
- Hi. - Hi.
Mum, they said hi.
Did you lie to me because you wanted to bring them here?
You left the tea pot burning on the stove.
I am sorry.
Their heater is broken. They have to spend a night here.
What does their broken heater have anything to do with you?
What if Se Bang finds out about you doing this?
He wants to get back together with you. How would this look to him?
They can hear you.
Let's go in and sleep.
My goodness!
What a sight!
What do you think you're doing?
Don't say anything. They will leave tomorrow.
Of course, they should leave. Were you going to raise them?
Do you think this makes any sense?
Why don't you bring their father, too?
He's on a business trip.
If he wasn't, would you have him here, too?
The heater's broken. What can I do?
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
Why don't you fix their heater, too?
I would have if I knew how.
I can't believe you're my child.
Are you sure you're mine?
I'm not sure since I didn't see.
Don't wake the kids up. Go to sleep.
How can I sleep with them?
It's okay. Go back to sleep.
Wake up.
What's wrong?
Did Gab Soon do something again?
It's not Gab Soon. It's Jae Soon.
They take turns causing trouble.
They are driving me crazy.
Just let it go.
- They drove me out of the room. - What?
She brought Geum Sik's children over.
A Rong and Da Rong or whatever their names are.
What?
She said that their heater is broken.
They're sleeping in my room right now.
What do we do with them?
We can't kick them out in the middle of the night.
I'm worried that Se Bang might find out.
He's already suspicious that Jae Soon and Geum Sik are meeting.
What's wrong with our daughters?
Se Gye is the only one we can count on.
We did a poor job on raising out children...
except for our son.
Cho Rong. Da Rong.
The kids are with me.
Eat quickly and let's go to the kindergarten.
Cho Rong, what time do you have to be at school?
I can go after breakfast.
Ddol Ee, here.
Are they back already?
Oh, my gosh!
What are you doing here this early?
The children just left. Joong Nyeon, Geum Sik is here.
Hi.
I'm sorry for barging in so early in the morning.
What do you want?
If you're sorry, you shouldn't have come. Why are you here?
I'm sorry for causing a lot of trouble.
Especially for having my children sleep over.
I'm sorry for causing inconvenience.
I'm sure you're not here just to apologise.
I came to get your approval.
Approval for what?
I would like to have a good relationship with Jae Soon.
My goodness!
We don't even need to respond. Just keep eating.
Why do your sons-in-law have the worst timing?
Why do they always come while we're eating?
I know I shouldn't say this while you're eating.
But I'd like to get your approval on dating Jae Soon.
We got married within three months of our first meeting.
The soup is cold now.
Please give him some hot soup.
Yes.
Did you have breakfast? Eat some here.
As I said earlier,
because we got married so fast,
we didn't know each other, and our marriage was rocky.
I made Jae Soon suffer a lot.
I know that it might sound strange...
Don't say it if you think it'll sound strange.
I am sorry.
I know that both of your are concerned.
We have feelings for each other.
Please approve our relationship.
You both have children to look after.
Do you think your relationship is a game?
What do you think you're doing?
- Eat. - Jae Soon.
I don't think he should be eating with us.
Actually, we've been seeing each other after our divorce.
I knew it.
I think Jae Soon was afraid to tell you about us.
But I think that it is proper for me to tell you...
and get your approval. We want to see each other without any guilt.
If Jae Soon had a decent job, I would give my approval.
Her life as a woman is just as important as her life as a mother.
Jae Soon needs to find a man who can provide for her.
She needs to marry someone who can provide financial stability.
- Do you understand? - Yes, I do.
- My situation... - I know that you can date.
You are both human, so you should date.
But after a few years of dating,
what happens if you break up and you get married to someone else?
She will be older and won't be able to get married.
Jae Soon will be in a desperate situation.
I've said it multiple times. Why can't you see that?
Don't be sad.
My mum and dad just don't know you well enough.
They don't know how wonderful you are.
I'm not wonderful.
They are right. I'm not financially stable.
I don't think I will let my daughters marry someone like me.
At times like this, I feel incompetent and lack confidence.
I guess a man's power does come from the size of his wallet.
Don't lose your confidence.
I'm with you.
You will be successful in no time.
Stop right in front of them.
Jo Geum Man, please move a little.
How can you be so immature?
You should come in soon. It's cold out here.
Do you want to use my car? You can talk in there.
I saw them in front.
How can he come here?
It's not what it seems. We summoned him...
and set him straight.
He just won't let Jae Soon alone.
He won't listen.
An amusement park?
Must you do that?
- Yes. - Soo Jo has no idea?
No.
Do Geum.
No matter where you go, please keep in touch. Stay alive.
Sam Sik, you stay alive, too.
We've never been apart.
Starting from elementary school to enrolling in the military,
we were always together.
Don't talk about the military.
Stop. Enough!
Stop! That's enough!
Excuse me.
- Can you take a picture of us? - Sure.
Move over.
In 1, 2, 3.
Three.
Geum Soo Jo.
You'll always be my son, right?
Don't forget me. I won't forget you.
You are a fantastic son.
Dad! Dad!
Stop!
Thank you.
What were you thinking?
You could have gotten hurt.
Open the door, please.
Okay.
Hello?
It's me, Geum Soo Jo.
Soo Jo.
Let's meet now.
Okay. Let's meet.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you, my Soo Jo.
I can't accept you as my family right away.
I know what you mean. I will be patient.
I don't know how long it will take.
It might never happen.
As long as you come home, I don't want anything else.
Thank you.
However, I have one condition.
Tell me. Whatever it is, I will do it for you.
I will buy everything you want.
I will buy you a car and clothes.
I will dress you in designer clothes.
I want to move in with my father.
- With your father? - Yes.
It's me. Are you busy?
It's okay. What is it?
Do you think you can get a loan for me?
A loan? Why?
I guess it's not possible.
What is it for? Is it urgent?
It's okay. I shouldn't have asked.
Just erase it from your memory. Bye, then.
Mum, about the money...
Don't worry about it.
They decided to live with Gab Dol's mum.
Really?
That's good.
I'm not so sure.
Instead,
you can give a wedding gift for her.
Perhaps, a TV or a refrigerator.
Okay.
But I'm not sure if such things will fit in their place.
What's all this?
I moved your stuff out.
This will be your brother's room. What do you think?
He will be here tomorrow.
Are your parents okay with you living with them so suddenly?
What?
- It's fine. - Let's move into the annex.
It's a bit cold, but we can bring in an additional heater.
It will be fixed up as soon as the weather gets warmer.
Please come back home.
Gong Joo.
I think...
it's best that we go our separate ways.
What are you saying?
It means just that.
Perhaps...
we were never meant to be.
We should have loved,
dated and then gotten married.
We didn't do that.
We rushed into our marriage because of our parents.
Even our current situation is just too hard to bear.
It's too hard for us to stay as a married couple.
This is all I can do for you.
I am so sorry.
Don't cry. This may be better for you.
He wants to end this marriage. Why are you crying?
I guess he wants to quit now that things are not working out for him.
How disrespectful.
Se Bang was just here.
Don't tell me anything about him. I don't care.
Were you meeting Geum Sik?
What if Se Bang finds out?
What's wrong with you, Mum?
My goodness!
What's going on?
She yelled at me when I told her not to meet Geum Sik.
What if Se Bang doesn't want to get back together?
Do whatever you want to do.
Let's talk.
Are you seeing both of them?
Why are you playing both of them?
You need to make up your mind.
Don't you think about your son?
You may not think this is a big deal.
You meet this guy today, and you meet another guy tomorrow.
It's not like that. Why are you saying that?
Se Bang is just Ddol Ee's father.
I know I should stop thinking about myself...
and just think about being a good mother.
But I can't do that.
I hate myself for being like this.
I don't like the fact that I put my own happiness first.
But I can't help myself.
I still have feelings for Geum Sik.
I like being with him.
I just want you to be happy.
I'm not asking you to give up your happiness as a woman.
You're still so young.
You can't live just for your child.
You have your own life to live, too.
But you still need to think about your child.
To be frank, he keeps spending time two fathers.
How confused do you think he'll be?
Do you think he won't realise what's going on?
Children know everything.
Even dogs are capable of sensing things.
Don't you think kids would sense it?
Look at your aunt.
She's getting everything back from her son.
What I mean is,
wait until your child grows up.
When your child grows up, you can meet whomever you want.
I can't let you see Geum Sik.
Even if you date someone, meet someone who's wealthy.
It's not good to see a guy...
with money problems who'll only make you worry about what to eat.
I don't like it.
You're not in your 20s any more.
You're nearly 40, and it's not so great to imagine you dating a guy...
out in the cold.
Stop seeing men for a while.
Just focus on your child.
That's my request.
Why all of a sudden?
It's not sudden. I've been thinking about this for a long time.
Do you want to break up?
Let's not decide on anything.
Let's take some time to think it through.
Tell me. What this is about?
It's not like we can afford to get married any time soon.
And we're not young enough to date each other...
without having any future plans.
We have kids to look after.
By any chance,
is this because you're getting back together with Ddol Ee's dad?
Please be honest. I'm ready.
That's not it.
I need to think about my life.
Don't call me for the time being.
Let's take time to think things through.
We're not breaking up.
If we do break up, I'll tell you.
I'll get going now.
What's gotten into you? You never call me first.
Your skirt seems too short. Do you want a hug?
This is new. Don't you dare.
What are you doing?
It's no use crying over spilled water.
This is us.
Don't ever show up in front of me again.
Hey! Jae Soon!
It's your grandfather.
- Ddol Ee. - Grandpa!
Grandpa!
- Stop! - DDol Ee, no!
(Our Gab Soon)