(Episode 4)
Gab Dol.
Hi.
You're late.
It was rush hour, so the subway was crowded.
That place looked good. Does it just look good on the pictures?
No.
The man at the first real estate agency we went to was the kindest.
I should've gone with you.
You must be tired.
Aren't you hungry? What do you want to eat?
Should we buy cup ramyeon and gimbap?
Do you want to go to a dry sauna and eat there?
Did you tell the real estate agency that...
we don't want him to show that place to other people?
Good places don't remain vacant for long.
What? What is it?
We can't get our place.
Why? Why can't we get our place?
Your bag.
Where is your bag? Where is it?
I lost it.
The strap broke.
Are you insane?
You know how hard it was to save that money.
That money is all we have.
What are we going to do now?
Don't waste your energy.
You'll get tired and sick.
Are you a fool? Why can't you take care of a bag?
You're not good at anything.
You haven't done anything good.
You say you'll take your responsibility.
You're not capable of taking responsibility for anyone.
- A bag?
-  Yes. I must find it.
It's this big. It's a black cross body bag.
This is the lost articles we got today. We haven't sorted them out.
I'll look for it.
Here is my ID card and cell phone.
Have you gotten any lost bags?
(Information Centre)
Gab Soon.
Don't do this.
- I'll get that money...
-  Gab Dol.
Let's stop.
I can't do this any more.
This isn't right.
I can't do this.
I don't think I can, and I don't want to.
It's so sad that we're fighting so hard...
for just 1,000 dollars.
You should think about our baby.
I don't care about anything now.
I won't have the baby.
You can't say that.
I was a fool.
I think I had an illusion.
I thought everything will be okay as long as we love each other.
We don't even have 1,000 dollars and can't get a place to stay.
How would we raise a child?
I don't want to have a dreadful life.
I hate myself, you and everything.
Stay still.
I'll get a place no matter what.
You just need to stay still.
You don't have a job, so it's hard to grant you a loan.
You haven't been working, so we can't grant you a credit loan.
You don't have a collateral, so you can't get a secured loan.
You're not a desirable candidate for loans.
What are you doing?
You should knock.
Why would I knock when it's my room?
I thought you went out.
My day hasn't started yet.
You didn't come home last night.
Did you go to an internet café?
I don't go there any more.
I don't care if you did or didn't,
but let me give you some advice.
You won't find anything in the closet drawers.
Mum would never leave money at home.
Come to your senses!
(Application for loan)
You're 29 years old. You're just a kid.
I'm doing this because I didn't get proper education.
You're well-educated. What's your problem?
You even went to a university.
You went to a fine university.
You have a healthy body.
Why do you need to take out a private loan?
I would've had a son like you if I hadn't failed at my first love.
Can't you just loan me the money?
You're not qualified.
Hey.
I can't take money from you.
Can you pay back the money in 3 months with 38 percent interest?
If you can't pay us back, we'd have to sell you...
to a whaling ship.
Your pale face tells me...
all you did was play game at home.
Whenever I look at someone like you,
I get indigestion.
Why does he want to see us?
He's jobless. He won't treat us dinner.
I heard he's trying to borrow money.
Is he into pyramid selling?
I don't know.
Are you going to lend him money?
I can't. Even if I did,
he won't pay me back.
His family was so poor when we were in high school.
His mother was working so hard.
Doesn't he have a girlfriend?
I feel bad for her...
for being his girlfriend.
Maybe it's because she's just like him.
Just like him?
You're right.
Hey.
Here. Let me.
That's great. Bring it to your mouth,
and blow.
That was good.
Blow it again.
- Gab Dol.
-  Dad.
Hang on tight.
Here we go.
Hold on tight.
Look straight ahead. Okay?
Let's go.
Get out.
You're so cute.
(Pawnshop)
How much can you give me?
It's very precious to me.
Today is your lucky day.
I don't need a large sum.
I'll take it back right away.
I only need...
5,000 dollars.
How much?
I can't even give you 50 cents for this.
You should take this to a junk shop.
It's not even in a good shape.
It's not so valuable, either.
Just buy some snacks with it.
Maybe you can't even buy snacks.
- What are you doing?
-  I'm sorry.
Where is she?
Answer your phone!
Jae Soon.
I feel so bad.
You look terrible.
You must be tired...
and hungry.
That's not the problem.
5,000 for deposit and 200 for rent?
You should consider yourself lucky.
We don't get places like this now.
They all want to get more rent.
I see.
I think you'd better...
let them get married.
- Don't they have parents?
-  They do...
but my sister got pregnant unexpectedly.
That's why they should register their marriage!
They will. We're going to tell our parents after they settle down.
Sir, please put the place on hold for a few days.
I'll bring the money.
- Give it to me!
-  No, it's mine!
Give it to me!
Cho Rong!
What is it? Can't you keep quiet?
Why are you being so loud?
I told you not to fight.
Go on your knees and put your hands up.
- What about you?
-  I didn't do anything wrong.
I was playing with it...
and he took it from me.
- It's mine.
-  It's not yours!
What's going on?
He wasn't behaving properly so I disciplined him.
He plays with the toys by himself...
and always takes Da Rong's.
You should discipline him.
You bought the toys with my dad's money so aren't they Da Rong's?
Don't fight with her. Be friends.
If Da Rong plays with your toys, play with something else.
- Okay?
-  But it's mine.
What do you want to discuss?
I have a meeting so I have to return soon.
I'm sorry...
but can you lend me some money?
Money? How much do you need?
I need 5,000 dollars.
It's too much, right?
Use the credit card.
I need cash, not credit card.
- What is it for?
-  I'll tell you later.
Please don't ask and can you...
It's not for anything bad.
I don't want any secrets between us.
Especially when it comes to finance.
People think businesses run themselves...
but it's all run on debt.
As soon as there's profit, you have to invest and pay off the debt.
Is this what you wanted to see me for?
I'm sorry. I know you're busy.
What's wrong with you?
Throw it away. Please throw it away.
Why? It's perfectly fine.
It's time to throw it away!
- It doesn't have needles.
-  Stop it.
I got this as a commemoration of my company's founding.
I can fix it.
It'll cost more to fix it.
Why are you still attached to the company that fired you?
Did you get fired, Joong Nyeon?
I didn't.
You couldn't stay so you got fired.
You have a great self-esteem.
Everybody else was trying to hang on...
and you hand in the resignation letter and quit.
It would have been great if you stayed for two more years.
Don't talk about what's in the past.
And you should not throw stuff like this. It's a bad habit.
Throw it away! The entire house is turning into a dumpster.
I want to throw away all that junk.
That sounds like you're going to throw away your husband, too.
Do you think he's the only one I want to throw away?
Fine. Throw away me and Mal Nyeon.
Live happily on your own.
Yes, Mum.
Come for some kimchi. Dad's not home.
Mum!
You.
Don't do that. You'll get punished.
- Sorry?
-  I bumped into you at the sauna...
and you decide to play dumb?
You were like that since you were young.
Look who's talking. Quit it.
It smells so good.
You saw me that day.
I didn't see you, Aunt. I don't even go to saunas.
The sky and earth know that you, I and Gab Soon saw each other.
Hey, Gab Soon is in Seoul, right?
No, she isn't. Why would she be in Seoul?
Sit down and eat.
Eat, Mal Nyeon.
You must be tired after accusing her.
Just watch, Nae Shim.
If you don't listen to me, you'll regret it. It's hot.
It's tasty. My kimchi jeon never tastes like this.
By the way,
why does your face look so tired?
I thought your husband treats you well.
There she goes again.
You were so bright a few days ago,
but you look so exhausted today.
Is your husband Mr Kim or Mr Park?
- It's Mr Jo.
-  Why does Mr Jo...
never call his in-laws...
or invite us for a meal?
I thought he earns a lot of money.
He did serve us dinner. You weren't there.
Her ex-husband would call you every day and say,
"Mother, would you like meat or seafood?"
If you say you want meat, he says,
"Would you like chewy beef rib..."
"or rib eye that melts at the tip of your tongue?"
He never bought us pork.
So what did he end up doing?
He was all talk.
No, he wasn't. Look.
He paid for Gab Soon's university admission fee...
and he paid for Se Gye's tuition several times.
That wasn't all. When was that?
Was it during fall?
Cut it out. Why are you talking about what's in the past?
He got Joong Nyeon's coat, your mink coat...
He was awesome.
He was so spontaneous.
I told you to cut it out!
Oh gosh.
Be gentle with it.
You'll turn it into a rag.
He was such a generous man.
He had so much cash on him.
He would give out cheques like that.
It wasn't any cheque.
He would dish out cheques that were worth so much.
He would pay for things just like that.
That's what made him go broke.
Thanks to him, Jae Soon went through so much.
She was drowning in his debt even after their divorce.
I'm afraid of seeing him in my dream.
I hope I dream about him. He might give me some money.
His family would insult her for preparing no wedding gift...
and his parents would tell her to call daily and take care of them.
They picked on her whenever they can.
Just thinking about their family gives me goose bumps.
That's why you made them get divorced.
I didn't make them divorce. They saw it coming.
Compared to him, Geum Sik is a gentleman.
He gives her more than enough money and she gets to use his credit card.
He considers Ddol Ee as his own son.
And their house is magnificent.
Have you gone over?
- I have.
-  You haven't.
It's already been a year.
I don't believe any of it.
That little...
Ignore her. She's like that.
Why does she never change?
I have to deal with her until I turn 100.
Are you planning to be around until you're 100?
I just realised you've never been to my place.
I'm just around the corner.
I wanted to drop by once in a while, but I was careful.
Your sister-in-law comes by often...
and he has his own kids so I didn't feel comfortable.
Once Geum Sik is less busy, I'll invite you over to my house.
Dad can come as well.
Take Dad out of this.
I don't like going out with him.
Mal Nyeon is like glue. She'll stick around.
For goodness' sake.
Don't spend too much money.
I don't make money easily just because I run a business.
Your ex-husband used to spend money. He was a thoughtful son-in-law.
I don't feel comfortable going to your house.
There's your sister-in-law and he has kids of his own.
Yes, A Young.
Didn't you go pick up my red heels?
I'll pick it up now!
I told you to pick it up earlier.
You stay at home and you can't even do this?
It's because of the kids.
Please give it a few months.
What's this?
Oh dear. I'm sorry.
- Put me upright.
-  Oh dear.
Put me upright.
Did you win a lottery?
I'd be dancing then, not sitting down laughing.
Where are you going? It's not time for you to go out, yet.
I'm going to roam...
and look for a sugar daddy who can pay off my debt and give me money.
You need to take some medication.
How can you see such a cheap woman?
She's absolutely unacceptable.
She's the only one who didn't try to flatter me.
I can feel she's the one.
That's not how you choose a girl.
You only need to see one thing.
Her family background is the most important thing.
Don't date any girls.
Don't give out your card to anyone.
- I don't.
-  If you choose a wrong girl...
What was it again?
"It can ruin our family at once."
That's right.
If you choose a wrong girl, it can ruin our family at once.
I forgot it all.
It only sounds good when you say it in a mansion.
Why would you mention it while we're having ramyeon?
You punk!
Let me eat.
Don't look at me!
You lied, right?
- What?
-  Your mum's not your real mum.
Who told you?
It was on the group chat.
Things like that spread fast.
Your biological mum ran away, right?
I feel bad for you.
- Stop it!
-  Stop!
Cho Rong!
Hello.
Cho Rong. Aren't you happy to see me?
I came by to see you.
You've grown a lot. You're prettier.
Look at me.
Cho Rong.
I told you not to come!
Why would you come? I don't need a mum!
Don't get angry. You're scaring me.
This is for you.
I don't need it!
Cho Rong!
I'm so happy to see you. I don't know why I'm crying.
What are you crying for?
It's for nothing.
I'm just...
happy to see you.
I'm sorry.
Let's see each other often.
Is Da Rong doing well?
She must have grown a lot.
Don't bother.
You never cared.
Is your step mum nice?
Don't ask questions like that.
You abandoned us so stay out of it.
I didn't abandon you.
You don't need us.
If you're finished, I'm leaving.
Cho Rong!
Take this.
You're late, Cho Rong.
You must be hungry.
You're home.
Here.
Thank you, Geum Sik.
Jae Soon.
Thank you.
I won't forget this.
Just be good to Gab Soon.
I told her you got the money.
Gab Soon will feel better that way.
She doesn't even pick up my calls.
I told her to come straight to the rooftop house.
The landlord got the place cleared out.
You can move in right away.
Is your shoulder strap sturdy?
You can't lose it again.
I'll guard it with my life.
I won't lose it again.
Get going. Gab Soon must be waiting.
Taxi!
Sir.
I'm sorry but can you let me off?
This is not it.
I think this might be right.
Is he not here, yet?
I thought he left earlier.
The landlord is not happy.
If she doesn't get the money by today, she'll cancel the contract.
Where are you? Are you almost here?
Yes, wait for a bit. I won't take long.
Excuse me. Do you know where the community centre is?
The community centre?
Let me see...
Go straight this way and turn right.
- Keep following...
-  I'm not sure if I get you.
I'm sorry but do you mind taking me there?
I'm in a rush. I have to go.
I'm from the rural area so I don't know my way around here.
I really need to get there.
Follow me, then.
Thank you.
If you turn right from that building, you'll see it.
- Got it?
-  Yes.
Thank you.
Leave a message after the tone.
Is he not picking up?
We'll have to cancel the contract.
He's coming. Please give him a few more minutes.
I don't know if I can say this,
but you're too naive.
Do you think a boyfriend who wants to move in together is a good man?
I'm only saying this because you seem like my daughter.
He ran off.
He'll never do that.
Where are you? Please answer me.
- Got it?
-  Yes.
Let go, you punk.
I wish we had 10,000 dollars.
I'll use 5,000 dollars to pay off my sister's debt...
and use the rest for our security deposit.
He's a thief.
Get your act together, young woman.
Is he not back, yet? You can't reach him either?
Jae Soon, I'm going to go crazy.
Okay. I'm on my way.
This one's clingy.
How much could it be?
We'll see who wins.
I'll put my life on the line.
Gab Dol.
Gab Soon.
Stop right there!
- Stop!
-  Hey.
Are you okay?
Excuse me.
Jae Soon, go ahead.
I told you he ran away.
I waited because I felt sorry for you. Let's go now.
Gab Soon.
What happened? Why are you hurt?
You must have been mugged.
Is he right?
What about the money?
What happened to the money?
Why are you crying?
Aren't you proud of me?
How could they do that to you?
Look up.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
I quit going to the hospital.
It's just a beating.
I could have beaten them if I had food in my stomach.
It's a pity.
Gab Dol. I'm so mean.
I'm really mean.
- I got you wrong.
-  You thought I ran away, right?
Why would I run away?
Since we were young, although it looked like I won on the outside,
you were the actual winner.
You tried to understand a narrow-minded person like me.
The reason we met for 10 years...
is all thanks to you.
Others think that it's all my doing.
That's not true.
You protected our love.
Thank you, Gab Dol.
Gab Soon, you became mature.
It's all because of money.
Imagine if I had got that stolen.
"What can you do right? You fool. You stupid fool."
"How can I trust a guy like you who gets his money stolen?"
"I can't live with you."
When was I like that?
Did your sister really give you the money?
Yes.
We'll have a lot to do tomorrow if we're going to move.
- Oh no.
-  What should we say?
I won't come home tonight.
I'm on a business trip to Busan.
Ddol Ee. Are you there?
Cho Rong.
Why?
Have you seen Ddol Ee?
I don't know. Don't disturb my sleep.
Were you home?
- Have you seen Ddol Ee?
-  Isn't he home?
He was here when we were eating pizza.
When was that?
I think it was about 9pm. We were eating pizza and he came out.
I asked if he wanted some, but he went out.
How could you let him leave in the night?
Then what can I say? He left.
Hello?
Mum.
Is there anything wrong?
What can go wrong to a person who's asleep?
What's the time?
It's past 12 o'clock.
- Is something wrong?
-  No.
I was wondering if you saw Ddol Ee.
I saw him a few days ago at the supermarket.
Why do you ask that?
Just...
- Sleep tight, Mum.
-  Okay.
I sent him home early in the day.
(Saessak Kindergarten)
He's been reported as a missing person. You'll be contacted.
We'll go around looking for him. Do what you can.
There's a chance that he might have been kidnapped.
If you receive a call, record it.
Okay.
She's living happily after she remarried.
Ddol Ee.
Mum.
Where did you go?
Why are you outside in the middle of the night?
Why did you do that?
Do you know how much I've been looking for you?
Where did you go without telling me?
I thought I lost you.
Why did you come outside?
Why are you out?
I came out to find you.
You should have slept even if I wasn't home.
I don't want to stay at home if you're not there.
Everyone hates me. They don't even give me pizza.
Mum. I'm sleepy.
Look.
It's like a prison for me after the housekeeper was fired.
Say something to Grandfather for me.
It would be nice if he hires some people,
and gives his inheritance to us in advance.
Once I receive inheritance, I'm going to buy all that.
I can't be satisfied by just looking at it.
Grandfather scares me too. He's so stubborn.
Mum, since Grandfather said it's okay,
let's watch a movie and eat out.
Do you want go dancing?
- Yes!
-  Yes!
Great idea.
I'm home.
Se Gye, call an ambulance.
Call the emergency room.
Is something wrong?
I ran up the stairs just a while ago.
I can't catch my breath.
That happens to everyone.
It's different this time.
Please be quiet.
Is it normal?
It's quite normal.
I can relax now.
This is why we should have a doctor in the house.
You're still awake.
Why are you so late?
I told you to come home before 10 o'clock.
We didn't know it was that late.
Do you think you're a kid?
Show me the receipt.
Here you go.
Fill in the housekeeping book and show me.
Are you two friends?
She's married now. Let her go.
Stop hanging out with your mum. It's not good to see.
Looking at you two just makes me ill.
What kind of a mum are you?
Dad. Stop telling me off in front of others.
My son-in-law is watching.
If you're living under my roof, listen to me.
It's time for your medication.
Dad, I'll bring a cup of water.
Okay.
Se Gye.
Take Gong Joo upstairs.
Let's sleep now. I have an operation early in the morning.
After I'm done with this. You go ahead and sleep.
You need to leave the house?
That's the only way to pass the exam.
I heard that I don't get along with the vibe of this house.
The reason why I fell down and hurt myself in the streets...
is because I don't fit with the house.
He's saying that this house is full of bad luck.
I'm not wrong.
What good things happened here?
We only went through trouble.
You work at the restaurant and I work at the karaoke.
He's a waiter.
Look at you talk.
Why is he a waiter?
What else can he do if he flunks the exam?
He won't find a job at that age.
Stop talking like that.
So will you pass the exam if you study in another house?
- 3,000 percent.
-  You don't need that much.
Just pass.
We should follow what an expert fortune-teller said.
I'll go with you to your friend's house tomorrow.
There's no need.
If you come, you'll spoil the vibe of the house.
You have a strong vibe.
Excuse me.
That looks tasty.
I...
love that.
This too.
It looks tasty.
He always comes when we're eating.
We need to fix a time.
What is this?
Oh my.
- I'm sorry.
-  Put me upright.
Put me upright.
It's been exactly an hour.
I'll leave, then.
Hey, woman! Relief Patch!
Bring that lady here.
Which one?
Relief Patch.
I won't work there. Look for another person.
She won't come.
Tell her it's daily wage.
We'll pay daily wage.
She asks how much we'll pay her.
Tell her it'll be more than enough.
If you will pay.
All right. I'll go.
I cleaned it.
Sit on it.
Where?
On the bed.
Oh my.
- Garlic.
-  Powdered red pepper.
Then, salt.
I'll let it slide this time because of the money.
Pardon?
- It's nothing.
-  Put in some more.
- More.
-  What are you doing?
I'm making doenjang jjigae.
It would be nice if he ate something simple like a salad.
Without the housekeeper, I'm going through all these trouble.
Grandfather is so old-fashioned.
He always wants these stuff.
Move over.
Why are you measuring it with all this?
You can measure with your eye.
Do you know how to make it?
Doenjang jjigae is easy.
I can't guarantee the taste, though.
Come and have supper.
Why are you empty-handed?
- Pardon?
-  I asked for a glass of water.
Where are your senses?
I left it in the refrigerator at my home.
Quit if you're going to be like that.
How could you be this annoying?
Don't live your life like that.
I don't know how much you have left of it though.
Relief Patch!
What is it?
It's not like you bought a relief patch for me.
I'm not called Relief Patch, my name is Nam Gi Ja.
Nam Gi Ja.
How much are you going to leave?
What did you say?
Never mind.
I didn't want to come here in the first place.
Send me the wage to my account.
Relief Patch!
Did you make it?
- No.
-  Did you buy it?
- We didn't buy it.
-  Then?
Relief Patch made it.
Relief Patch made it?
Is it bad?
Dad. I'll do what I want with my marriage.
I'll marry who I want to marry.
How could you freeze all my credit cards?
Do as you please!
- I'm sorry.
-  Oh no.
It's because of me, right?
Since I don't suit your family.
Please enjoy your food, Sir.
I'm in the middle of a conversation.
Excuse me.
Don't worry.
It's just some discomfort.
I see.
Enjoy your food.
Okay.
- Yes, Sir.
-  What's with this?
I'd like the usual.
I apologise.
I'll bring a new dish.
Wait.
How much is that?
I don't have any cash.
I have cash on me.
Give me all you have.
Thank you, Sir.
Here's 10 percent. Is that enough?
Get a grip.
What if you get caught?
Is your dad doing well?
You're eating well, aren't you?
Yes.
Kid.
This is pretty. I'll have this.
I'd like all of these.
Here you go.
Dad. Let's have a party.
Why have a party?
What did he do well?
He'll have a tough time when he moves out.
We need to let him eat some meat.
Bring out the pork belly. I bought some earlier today.
Gab Dol.
Did you cook meat?
Not yet.
You can't cook samgyeopsal here without my permission.
It's not samgyeopsal.
It's rib eye.
- What should we do?
-  What's the problem?
We can still go out and eat.
It's our house.
We moved to a nice place.
A detached house is the best.
I don't like apartments.
You're renting a room. You're in no position to say such a thing.
How can they eat rib eye when they're renting a room?
If you don't want to live like that, get a grip on yourselves.
You can lose a grip once in a while.
Otherwise, it will be so tiring.
You're right. You're the best.
I'll visit your karaoke sometime later.
My expectation makes me imagine how it would be.
Your imagination is what makes you expect.
It's the same thing.
What do you expect and imagine?
I can't tell you that.
There is no one in this town as beautiful as your daughter.
Stop it. That's not a compliment.
That's why we ended up having a life like this.
Ms Karaoke. Which cosmetics do you use?
I'm not telling you that.
Gosh. I've had enough of this rib eye.
Do you want an exchange?
Is 1 piece of rib eye for 3 pieces of samgyeopsal okay?
You all know Korean beef is expensive, right?
Make it two pieces.
I'll give you some kimchi.
We have a deal.
All right.
This is amazing.
It just melts away.
Try it, Mum.
It's as good as it costs.
- You've never eaten rib eye before.
-  What did you say?
You should just swallow rib eye, not chew it.
It just slips down your throat.
Let me give you some advice.
If you want to barbecue, get the permission from the main building.
There is no such rule.
I just made one up.
Eat up, so you can go and study from tomorrow.
Are you going to live with a girl?
That's not what I said.
I said he will go and study.
Is he hard of hearing?
It does sound similar in a way.
Study, live together.
What do you do for living?
Are you a gilder?
- Why do you ask? It's obvious.
-  Why is it obvious?
Don't look down on us just because we're renters.
I used to...
Gosh, it's funny.
Goodness. I guess our family is truly unlucky.
- What?
-  Look at them.
I don't know if they're gilders, but they are like...
two pieces of gold whose coating is peeling off.
You work at a restaurant, I work at a karaoke...
and you're jobless.
This is a very rare mix of unsuccessful people.
Leave Gab Dol out of it.
Gosh.
I want to move out.
Hey!
I got you.
You're staying in Seoul, right?
Who are you? Do I know you?
What?
You little brat. Let's go.
Let's go to your mum and dad.
What's wrong with you? Are you crazy?
You're right. I'm crazy. Let's go.
- Help me!
-  My gosh.
Goodness. Gab Soon!
My goodness.
You little brat!
Gab Soon, you crazy girl!
Stop right there!
Gab Soon!
Gab Soon.
Stop it.
Take her to the hospital. She's out of her mind.
- Get up. Let's go to the hospital.
-  Joong Nyeon.
It drives me crazy when something like this happens.
Gab Soon is wandering around Seoul.
Is this Seokbulsa Temple?
Please speak up.
What did you say?
A student who studies here?
Gosh. Don't worry.
She's studying hard with a band tied around her head.
All right. Thank you.
Goodbye.
Did you hear that?
Goodness.
The sky knows, the land knows,
I know and everyone knows.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof.
Goodness. What a lonely life.
What a lonely life! My gosh.
You've been holding out since you were in school.
You're talented and you've gained academic recognition.
Whenever I go into the operating room, I get nervous.
I still don't want you to make a decision so hastily.
I'm not brave enough anyway.
I know...
what my family and my wife's family expect from me.
I have no choice but to be a doctor for the rest of my life.
Do you want to go to some place else? It's boring here.
Shall we go to our school? It's been a while.
(Ms Yeo)
You should answer it.
- Hello?
-  It's me.
You should come straight home from work.
You know my dad doesn't like it if you don't.
He's in a bad mood today. Make an appointment at the hospital.
Okay.
- Let's go to the school.
-  No. You should go home.
You can go ahead. I'm not drunk.
I'm not drunk, either.
- Sir. Please take her home safe.
-  Okay.
- What is it?
-  Man Joo.
I'm sorry.
One bottle of soju, please.
I will carry it for you.
It will bring me bad luck. I'm not supposed to see you for a while.
Let's listen to the fortune-teller.
You didn't get caught, right?
Of course not. She wanted to come with me,
but I refused saying it's bad luck.
My mum is so clingy.
Didn't you know that already? Let's clean up here.
We have to go grocery shopping.
Wait. I want to say something.
I know you'll say you want to hug me. Forget it.
Hey.
Gosh. Stop it.
Take some medicine,
so you get better soon.
I'm sick because of loneliness.
I'll be fine only if you believe my words.
Mal Nyeon.
Do you keep seeing things?
Shall we go see a doctor?
Goodness. This is so frustrating.
It feels as if I haven't had any water.
If you keep doing this...
You want me to leave?
I don't know.
Gosh.
Abalones...
Shrimps.
Can we try it?
Try it.
It's nice.
- It is.
-  Try some quail eggs.
- It's nice.
-  It's tasty.
I'm hungry.
Let's get the grill for pork belly.
No.
We don't have enough money. Let's just use this for everything.
A pot for ramyeon.
Ramyeon.
Get pretty matching cups.
- Which one...
-  I'll have this one.
Cheers.
(West Incheon to Jincheon)
Taste this.
What?
Cheers.
Our first day of living together.
I'm excited.
It's like we're married, right?
All right.
Is it tasty?
(Our Gab Soon)
Have a seat, Geum Sik.
It's okay. I have to get going.
Look how impolite he is, rejecting your offer.
He must look down on our family.
How could he do this on his father-in-law's birthday?
You've insulted me.
Apologise for bossing around.
I know my life is done for,
but shouldn't you get a grip?
Mum's going to die if she finds out.
A man must meet the right woman.
Your life can change depending on which woman you meet.
- You jerk.
-  Se Gye!
You seduced innocent Gab Soon and look what you did.
Do you call yourself a human?
I didn't know you were this low.
Let's put an end here.