About the allowance...
We won't be able to give it to you for a while, but don't be upset.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Once I make a lot of money, I'll give you a lot.
Did you two decide what to say beforehand?
Yes. What? No.
We should give her allowance.
You told me to take care of it.
We can't afford to give her allowance.
We should save up quickly to buy a house.
- Also, Mother... - What now?
All right. You've already started, so keep going. What else?
Please give me my husband's passbook.
What?
I'll take care of my husband's passbook from now on.
You'll only pay me 600 dollars...
without any allowance, and you'll make me do all the household work.
And now, you're asking me to give you my son's passbook?
I guess you take me for a complete fool.
I'm not eating.
Where did it go?
Here it is. Live a happy life with this.
Thank you, Mother.
Must you check it right now?
I should know how much there is.
You gave me the wrong passbook, Mother.
This one is for a house application.
What's gotten into you?
I told you that my mum is sensitive about money.
Did you have to bring it up during breakfast?
Everyone is sensitive about money.
She would've gotten upset even if I talked about this during dinner.
It's something I had to say anyway.
Where did it go?
It's harder to find now that I'm in a rush.
Here you go.
Were you afraid that I might take my son's money?
Do you think I'll steal from my own son?
I was going to give it to you when the time is right.
I made a savings account and an account for a house application.
I even joined a private fund to increase his money.
What kind of a daughter-in-law...
asks for a passbook on the first day of her marriage?
From now, you two lead a happy life of your own.
Mum.
Mother, thank you.
Why did you have to ask for the passbook so early in the morning?
It's been less than 24 hours since we got married.
She'll do a good job in taking care of my money.
She's not someone who'll steal from me.
Then are you saying I am?
She rarely throws away food because she thinks it's a waste.
I'm getting really anxious already.
You said you could deal with my mum. But look what's going on already.
I need to say what I must. Do you want me to bring it up later?
I'm telling you to go easy on her.
She's been through a lot all her life.
Honey, I've heard enough. So please go to work.
Please do a good job so I don't have to worry, Honey.
Mother, I washed all the dishes.
I put the laundry in the washer. So before you go out to work,
please shake them off and hang them.
Are you telling me what to do?
I'm just doing exactly what you taught me.
I won't be able to do the dishes since I have to leave early.
If it is too hard to do the dishes, just leave them in the sink.
I'll do it when I come home late at night.
I can cut my sleeping time to do that.
Mother, I'll be off to earn money now.
You...
Just one more bite.
I don't want to eat it.
If you eat this, I'll buy anything you want.
- I want a robot. - Okay. I'll buy you a robot.
Good job, my son.
Ms Shin.
- What brings you here? - We came to see Ddol Ee.
How is Ddol Ee doing?
- He doing much better. - That's a relief.
Can we see Ddol Ee?
Go back. You can't meet Ddol Ee now.
Then please give this to him.
I made this card for him.
Please give him this chocolate, too.
Thank you.
Go home now.
Goodbye.
Are they who I think they are? Why did they come here?
They must've come because they were worried about Ddol Ee.
They obviously came here because you called them over.
I don't like them, either.
Don't be like that. They're still young kids.
Young kids?
Did you forget how they treated Ddol Ee?
They were mean to Ddol Ee along with their Dad.
That's why he had to undergo psychotherapy.
That's all in the past.
Don't raise your voice at the hospital.
Just wait until Ddol Ee gets discharged from the hospital.
- You went to the hospital? - Yes.
Did you get to see Ddol Ee? How is he doing?
We didn't get to see him. Ms Shin told us to leave.
It seemed like she was afraid of him.
"Him"?
Ddol Ee's dad?
He's scary. He kept staring at us.
Don't ever go there again.
Dad, are things over with Ms Shin?
What's wrong with my meat?
- It's perfect for romance - What are you doing?
I'm going to cook some meat for Soo Jo.
He works so hard everyday, so I should cook some meat for him.
Soo Jo really loves meat.
He must take after me.
He takes after me.
At first, he didn't even touch meat. He only drank milk.
As soon as his teeth came out, he started to eat meat like me.
You don't know anything.
What is in the bag?
I bought some strawberries.
I bought organic strawberries just for Soo Jo.
Gong Joo, we're going to have meat later.
Just wash your hands and wait.
These are for your brother.
My goodness. Look what you've done.
You're the one who dropped them.
My goodness.
Always ask before you eat.
Don't just eat anything.
Why? Do you think it's a waste if I eat them?
It's not that.
I just wanted you to eat them with Soo Jo.
Since when did you care so much about him?
Am I not your child?
What's wrong with her?
Don't ask me. You'll only put me in a bad spot.
You're home.
You must be tired.
Why are you still delivering water when you don't have to?
- Dad, I'm here. - Hey.
- I have meat ready to be cooked. - I ate already.
- But it's meat. - I don't want it.
He never eats at home.
You're right.
- Should I grill some meat? - No, don't bother.
I made some doenjang stew and braised tofu. Try them.
- Where's Gong Joo? - She went out.
She went out because she got upset.
Why did she get upset?
She got scolded because she tried to eat a strawberry.
What is he talking about?
She wasn't like that before, but she's acting rude lately.
You should discipline her.
How does it taste?
It needs salt.
You shouldn't eat too much salt.
It should still have some flavour at least.
I see.
I keep making things the way I like them.
Should we hire a housekeeper?
We should hire a housekeeper who can cook well.
No, I can do a good job.
Please be patient. I'm doing my best.
Si Nae.
Do you want to have a drink with me?
You're troubled these days, aren't you?
Both So Joo and Gong Joo...
are causing you a lot of trouble.
Whether I'm here or there,
I run into mothers who go through hard times because of their kids.
It's really not easy.
Soo Jo has had...
a trauma ever since he was young.
What?
He has a deep scar.
Where is that scar?
Is it on his stomach or his back?
It's not a scar on his body. It's in his heart.
We were always poor.
So we moved around a lot, and he didn't have many friends.
When something went missing at school,
everyone suspected that Soo Jo stole it.
He was teased because he didn't have a mother.
I didn't know. I can't believe I dragged him to the police station.
How is Ddol Ee?
We'll have to observe him more.
He may suffer from shock.
A car accident can be a traumatic experience for a child.
Let's wait and see.
You said you were going to get your own place. What happened?
I met Dr Choi recently.
Are you thinking about going to Africa?
I'm not going to Africa,
but I may have to practice medicine again.
Really? It would be nice for you to come back to the hospital.
The chief asked about you recently.
I don't want to get a paying job.
I don't think I'm good with money.
I wanted to become a rich doctor, but I guess that won't happen.
Will you be a medical volunteer?
I'm considering it.
Yes, Mum.
Where are you right now?
What? I'm at the store.
Can you stop by?
I won't talk about money. Just come.
Okay, Mum. I'll stop by.
You said you were at the store.
Well...
I'm actually coming from there.
Why are you dressed like that?
Why are you wearing those sandals?
My friend lives nearby. I was visiting him.
He wanted me to get some soju and ramyeon for him.
I borrowed his sandals.
These are comfortable.
These are his clothes, too.
This is so not like you.
At school, everyone but you wore sandals.
You said they didn't look cool.
I'm surprised that you're wearing those.
Every student in Korea wore those except you.
That's right. I was the exception.
Drop them off quickly, and let's go together.
We can go right away. Did you go grocery shopping?
Don't even think about it. You shouldn't carry this.
I want to make some food for your sister.
The hospital food is terrible.
What is going on with your in-laws?
They didn't even come to Gab Soon's wedding.
They don't even come to the hospital to visit Ddol Ee.
I told you that Grandfather and my mother-in-law are traveling.
They're traveling?
I thought they were on a business trip.
Yes, they're overseas, so they're practically traveling.
That old man is away for so long.
What about your wife?
It's obviously 1 of 2 reasons.
Either she doesn't want to come...
or she's just not able to.
Are you having trouble with them?
Did something happen at the company?
- Nothing happened. - Did you fight with your wife?
No, it's not like that.
I feel like Se Gye is going through some serious trouble.
You feel that way, too, right?
I'm sure everyone else will feel the same.
What do you think is going on?
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
What is it?
"I didn't become living proof for this."
Se Gye is probably saying that to himself.
I came to pick up the empty plates.
Hey, Gab Dol. How are you doing?
How dare you speak to me like I'm your friend?
Address your senior properly.
You are still a bachelor.
I envy you.
But I'll only be a loser if I keep envying you.
You're already a loser.
You used to like Gab Soon, but I took her away.
I can't argue with that. I hope you live happily ever after.
I'm so sorry. I feel terrible.
It's okay.
I'll take care of it.
I am a public official.
I must never get angry at a citizen.
The citizens are...
my bosses.
It's okay.
When are you going to throw a party to celebrate your marriage?
We'll set a date soon.
Men usually look good when they get married.
You actually look worse than before.
- What? - Did you fight with your wife?
How did you know? You're not even married.
Feel free to ask me anything.
I've become an expert on marriage thanks to my older sisters.
Did you fight because of money?
There's no need to be surprised.
I'll give you advice soon.
Honey, are you off work?
Honey, are you watching me?
Of course. I'm going to keep an eye on you.
Honey, don't go anywhere else. Go straight home.
All right, Honey.
It's cooking well. It looks delicious.
Why isn't he here yet?
Joong Nyeon's getting impatient waiting for his son-in-law.
I may be hungry, but I'm not that impatient.
It's him. He's here!
- He's here. - You're home.
Your cute son-in-law is here.
Come here and sit.
It's tasty.
I made fish cake soup, your favourite.
It's cold. Come home quick.
Oh, my.
Oh, my. I'm usually bored in the evenings.
Thanks to Gab Dol, I'm having so much fun.
Us three usually sit together in the long evenings.
We would count how many wrinkles we have.
In the past, we would catch lice together.
Did you catch lice?
That's not the only thing we did.
What? Watch your language.
I was going to say we watched television.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
You don't even look great from behind.
Mother looks beautiful from behind.
When did you see me from behind?
"Why are you saying hello?"
"Don't you talk to me."
"Aren't you going to move?"
"Do you think you can pass the exam if you walk around like this?"
Then she turned around. The only thing I could see was her back.
I understand how that would have gotten stuck in your mind.
The image of her back as she turned around and walked away from you.
You're home early.
- Have you eaten? - Come join us.
I'm tired. I need to go out again after I take a short nap.
It's not easy cleaning.
Did you think it was going to be easy?
He's always tired.
I've never seen him with his eyes properly open.
It's because he had to mind others ever since he was young.
Have some of this.
Let's drink.
Have you eaten?
Are you ill?
Get out.
Don't touch me.
I won't.
Go to sleep.
You should sleep in your room. Go sleep in your bedroom.
Gab Dol, you should go home.
Oh, my.
That must be Gab Dol's phone.
(Mum)
Gab Dol, answer your phone.
- Hello? - Where are you?
I called the office. They said you left a while ago. Where are you?
Hello.
Hello? Isn't this Gab Dol's phone?
It's Gab Soon's mum. He's at our house.
Why is he there?
He had a few drinks with my husband.
He had a few too many. He's sleeping now.
You shouldn't have made him drink so much.
We didn't mean to.
He can sleep over. Don't worry.
What are you talking about? I'm going to go pick him up.
Hello?
She hung up when I wasn't even finished talking.
She didn't even treat me like her in-law like I did.
I can't grow fond of her at all.
- Is she coming to pick him up? - I guess so.
He's not a child. She's really overreacting.
Oh, my.
My goodness.
Get up. Go sleep in your room.
My gosh.
What a disaster. Help me out.
I don't have the strength to. Leave him here.
That wench is on her way. Help me out.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my.
My gosh.
Why is he being like this today?
Joong Nyeon got taller.
He gained weight.
He ate so well these days that his belly got so big.
- Oh, my. - Help me out.
This isn't why I made living proof.
Don't let her in yet!
- You're here. - Yes.
Gab Dol. Oh, my.
Please wake Gab Dol up.
Please come in.
I don't think I should. Please wake him up for me.
Gab Dol. Your mother is here. Wake up.
Oh, my.
Joong Nyeon is flaunting his large belly.
- Gab Dol. - Your mother is here.
My mum?
Mum.
- My mum's here. - Come on out.
Why did you make him drink?
We didn't force him.
Why did you drink so much?
I was happy, so I drank a little.
My father-in-law loves me so much.
Good for you.
I feel better now.
Why did you come?
Why do you think?
You were so drunk. You couldn't even answer your phone.
I'm not a child. I can sleep over.
Why would you sleep at a stranger's house?
They're not strangers. They're my parents-in-law.
Why do they call you over every day?
I went there myself.
They're fun to be with.
They love me so much.
Did you entertain them like you do for me?
- A bit. - Don't do that to anyone else.
They loved it.
We don't have many people in our family, so it feels lonely.
There are many people there.
So they fight over food. It makes it even more tasty.
- They want me to live there. - Are you insane?
People hate living with their in-laws.
Don't go there too often.
You should meet them once in a while to be treated well.
If you show your face too often, it'll seem like you lack discretion.
What if you make a mistake when you're drunk?
They'll blame it on you not having a father.
Only visit them on holidays from now on.
- My goodness. - What?
- My goodness. - Why you...
- Are you asleep? - No.
I want ramyeon.
I want some too.
This is great.
I'm so happy to eat ramyeon with you late at night.
Me too.
I thought people living in big houses like this were all happy.
- But I guess not. - You're just not comfortable yet.
Once you get used to this place, you'll become happy.
My goodness.
Soo Jo. Hey.
Hey.
(Nam Gi Ja)
You're home.
What time is it now?
It's late.
Get changed and sleep comfortably.
I don't mind. I'm too sleepy.
Tell your wife to wake up.
It's not fair for the mother-in-law to cook for her.
- She's sleeping. - That's why you should wake her up.
Gab Soon already told you that she can't cook breakfast.
She has to do what a daughter-in-law should do at least for a month.
How could she abuse me just because she earns money?
She has to at least show that she's trying...
in order for me to feel bad and say that I'll cook for her.
She is shameless to sleep until broad daylight.
She came in at dawn and fell asleep without even washing.
It's not easy to earn money.
And I wouldn't know that because I never made money, right?
You've been working for a while now, but Gab Soon...
Are you saying I'm okay because I'm made of steal,
and your wife is not because she is fragile?
To be honest, you guys are working hard to feed yourselves, not me.
She ignores me because you act like this.
If you can't wake her up, I will.
Gosh, stop it. I'll cook then.
Mum.
Good morning, Mother.
It's not a good morning for me.
Even if you came home late, how could you not see your husband off?
Gab Dol told me that I didn't need to.
Calling your husband by his name isn't appropriate.
You said you'll respect him as your husband.
I don't know what else to call him.
And I heard that I shouldn't call him "Honey" in front of our parents.
I'll be careful from now on.
And why does your dad call Gab Dol over so often?
He has to go to work, but your dad offers him drinks.
Does he need someone to drink with?
He has a lot of friends to drink with.
Are you going to live with your parents later?
We never said we will.
My parents don't want to live with their children.
They don't want to burden us.
Then are you saying I live with my children to burden them?
That's not it. They said living with their kids is hard for them, too,
since they need to be careful.
Mother, I'll wash quickly and go to work.
Goodness.
I didn't call him over.
He came here himself.
How ridiculous. Did he say your dad called him over?
Send him back early from now and don't give him too much alcohol.
He has a hard time waking up.
My goodness.
I thought he said I was the best.
It won't be a problem if we live alone, but his mum doesn't like it.
Did you tell him that you want to live with us later?
I didn't.
I guess she got angry and took it out on Gab Soon.
Everything goes around and comes to Gab Soon in the end, so be careful.
I think I should live with you to make her go mad.
I won't live with you.
Do you have any problems with your mother-in-law?
No, I don't. Gab Dol tells me to do as I want.
I guess he doesn't want you to feel small in front of his mum.
- Who takes care of the money? - I do.
I took care of the money ever since we started dating.
I also got his passbook from my mother-in-law.
You even got his passbook?
- Did she give it to you right away? - Yes.
You did a good job. You're smart.
I told you not to worry about me. I'm Gab Soon.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Gab Soon, let's go. - Okay.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
My gosh, you didn't even get enough sleep.
Gab Soon, don't make Dal Pa work too hard.
He became thinner.
Did he go out without eating breakfast again?
Yes. I'm not sure if he eats outside or not.
Please don't eat ramyeon at night.
- Okay. - Did you eat ramyeon?
Yes. It became a habit.
He should start eating with us and stop delivering water soon.
He won't listen to anybody.
There's one person he'll listen to.
I thought no one was home.
If anyone finds out about this,
I'll get kicked out.
- No one's home, right? - Yes.
Geum Do Geum!
Slow down. You'll get an upset stomach.
You said you'll get kicked out if anyone finds out.
They won't be home any time soon. I'm just worried about Soo Jo.
I can't watch him deliver water any more.
Mr Yeo is worried, too.
He's having a hard time living here,
but I think he's putting up with it because of me.
What's wrong with him?
If I were him, I'd stay here comfortably and let them feed me.
They would even call a chef for me if I asked for one.
I wish I had a chance to live in a house like this.
Your life must've become much better now.
It became so much better that I feel burdened.
Do Geum, please get a job for me.
I'll ask if they need a driver.
In the military, I used to cook, and you used to drive.
I told you to stop talking about the military.
Let it go now. You're only making yourself suffer.
Could you let it go if it were you?
I'll never forget about anything.
Stop grinding your teeth.
Think about how to deal with Soo Jo.
There's a tactic you use often.
Dad.
Let me do this with you.
You can't do it.
- If you can, I can do it, too. - Stop it.
You'll hurt your back.
You don't like me working here, right?
The same goes for me.
You're putting me in a difficult situation.
Would you be okay if your kid delivered water without eating?
Why won't you listen to me? Did I raise you to be like this?
If you keep doing this,
I will vanish without a trace.
I washed up in a long time. I feel so refreshed.
It's tiring to take care of a patient.
On top of that, it's your own child. You must've gone through a lot.
You lost so much weight.
She lost weight without having to spend any money.
Please think before you speak.
She didn't lose weight because she went on a diet.
Okay.
I set the table for you. Go ahead and eat some.
And take the side dishes I made.
Thank you, Mum.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Somebody, please come help!
Excuse me.
Quickly please. My Ddol Ee is almost dying.
Did Ddol Ee go to get a checkup?
Come to the intensive care unit.
What happened?
I don't know. It was so sudden.
Pull yourself together.
We can't afford to be weak.
We have to hold on just like Ddol Ee.
How did it go?
He passed the crisis now.
Because it was such a big accident for your child,
I think he was in shock.
My gosh.
After watching him for a while, we'll move him to a general ward.
If this ever happens again, don't get flustered too much.
We'll check him up again tomorrow.
He will be okay for now.
Back when...
you and Se Gye wanted to get married,
I'm sorry I couldn't be on your side.
Se Bang is trying really hard this time.
Of course he should. It's his own son.
In the past, he'd just leave everything with Jae Soon.
He would try to make up for everything by just giving her money.
When Ddol Ee had surgery before, he didn't even come to see him.
He's become mature.
He should be mature. He's old enough.
When Ddol Ee leaves the hospital,
they should get back together and live with their child.
Who are you to decide?
I talked to Jae Soon earlier, but she didn't say much about it.
- She didn't? - She must've learned a lesson.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
(Father)
Hello, Father.
Stop by my house after you get off work.
Okay.
(Mum)
- What's up, Mum? - Are you coming late today?
Let's have dinner together.
I have to stop by Gab Soon's parents' place.
Again? I told you to visit them only on holidays.
Father wants to see me.
It won't take long.
I can't stay long because I'm tired anyway.
If you're tired, just make up an excuse and don't go.
I can't do that. Bye, Mum.
I can't believe he's bothering my son like this.
I'm so thankful they're not well off.
If they were rich, they would abuse him even more.
A real man...
shouldn't talk about what happened outside of his home.
Do you tell your mother about every little thing that happened to you?
I didn't tell her anything.
You're the one who decided to come here yesterday.
- You told her I called you over? - That's...
You don't need to tell your mother everything.
You told her that we said we'd like to live with you.
You told her I looked lonely because I don't have anyone to drink with.
You also told her that I forced you to stay even though you were tired.
How am I supposed to say anything to you from now on?
There are two things men should be careful about.
One is your mouth.
You shouldn't have a big mouth if you want to become successful.
I see. But what's the other thing?
The other thing that men should always be careful about is...
- What's wrong with you? - Stop talking nonsense.
Can't I talk about this in front of him?
He's married. He should know what he's supposed to know.
- Men... - That's...
should be careful with their pockets.
A heavy wallet makes a proud man.
That's right. Your pocket.
I was thinking the same thing.
I'll keep that in mind.
Gab Dol, how much money are you going to give to Gab Soon's parents?
Money?
Gab Soon is supposed to take care of that.
Gab Soon is going to take care of it?
How much money per month?
I'll finally receive some pocket money thanks to you.
I'm home.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
You should come see me if you're home.
You just said "I'm home". Is that it?
It's because I'm tired.
You went to see your in-laws, but you have no energy to say hi to me?
Don't add on to the scolding I got from them.
What? What did you do to get a scolding from them?
- What did they say? - Nothing.
I'm going to get changed. Close the door.
They say you lose your son once he gets married.
I'm the one who raised him to become a public official,
but they're treating him like he's their own.
Don't go to their house any more. Don't answer their calls, either.
Oh, my goodness.
My goodness. It's burning.
I didn't even get to eat this. What a waste.
You shouldn't have gotten married to her.
My gosh, he has such a bad taste in women.
He must've gotten it from his dad.
Gosh, it's hot.
Allowance?
Are you not going to give each of our parents' any allowance?
All of my married friends give some money to their parents.
Didn't you give me the right to decide?
So you're not going to give them any?
Think about it. We don't even have a house.
We're living with your mother because we can't afford to pay rent.
How can we give them money?
You mother seemed to want some.
Just ignore what she says. Think about it.
If we give money to each of our parents every month...
and give them money again on every birthday and holiday, it's too much.
We shouldn't be so cheap.
We need to save money.
Both of our parents are wealthier than us right now.
We should just endure it until we get our own house.
But that would be very rude of us.
Since we're married now, we're adults.
I think we should at least give some money to our parents to thank them.
Many parents brag about how much money they got from their children.
But my mum gets nothing.
My mum went through so much.
The same goes for your parents.
How much do you think is enough?
About 500 dollars?
What?
- At least 300 dollars. - 300 dollars?
If it's 300 dollars for each person, that adds up to 900 dollars.
Think about how much we earn.
We'll end up with nothing forever.
- What about 200 dollars? - Still, it'd be 600 dollars.
To us, 600 dollars a month isn't a small amount of money.
What about 100 dollars?
If your parents get 200 dollars and my mum gets 100 dollars,
that would be unfair.
It's fair. It's 100 dollars per person.
If your house gets 200 dollars, my house deserves 200 dollars as well.
Your mum works.
Then ask your mum to work as well.
- What? - What you're saying is nonsense.
My mum went through a lot.
The least we can do is give her enough pocket money.
Your mum isn't the only one who went through a lot.
You always tell me that she's been through a lot.
I'm saying this because we don't have enough money ourselves.
I want to give her a lot of money, too.
I thought you were going to let me handle it.
Forget it. Why do we have to fight over 100 dollars?
You take care of the money.
Are you going to be like this?
- Then you cook. - What?
Even when my mum delivered milk and worked at a restaurant,
she never once forgot to make a meal for us.
She prepared breakfast for us everyday.
But just because you earn some money, you don't even cook.
What did you say? I earn more than you do.
You should cook. It's your family anyway.
"Your family"?
That's what you're doing. You keep defending your mum.
If you feel so bad for your mum, you should live with her.
Why did you even get married?
Get out! Right now!
This is not why let you get married.
I shouldn't have let you live here in the first place.
Get out!
Really?
I'll quit delivering water.
Thank you, Soo Jo.
Good for you.
Thank you for this, Professor.
It's no big deal. I just tried my best.
So what do you want to do now?
Since you don't want me to deliver water, I'll look for another job.
Dad, tell him.
How about working as a director in my company?
Really?
I've only seen directors in dramas.
We'll appoint you as the director right away.
How can you appoint me as a director like this?
Stay still. You're going to become a director.
I want you to take the position and learn about the company.
I don't even know anything about your company.
I can't start as a director.
Give me some time to learn.
Learn? Do you want to go to a university?
Or do you want to study abroad?
That's not what I mean.
I also didn't go to a university, but I have no problem working.
Then what do you want to learn?
He wants to learn the work at the company.
I see.
Which department is the most difficult to work in?
- It's the warehouse. - I'll work there then.
No, you can't.
It's very poorly paid and difficult. It's not for you.
You don't have to do a heavy task. Do an easy one.
All right.
You can start from there. The meeting is over.
You shouldn't have left home like that.
Are you going to end things with Gong Joo?
Yes.
I'm glad you didn't register your marriage. It made things easier.
You should come to work, though. You still have a lot to do.
No, thanks.
I'm sorry for canceling on your position.
It must've been hard for you since it happened so suddenly.
I hope you understand our situation.
I understand it must be hard for you, but you should come back.
That won't happen. I'm sorry.
Are you serious about this?
You're really going to divorce Gong Joo, too?
I'm sorry.
What did your parents say?
He hasn't told his parents. That means he hasn't made up his mind.
I want you to meet him and talk him out of it.
What's the point?
You shouldn't cut off relationships frivolously like that.
You should think about Gong Joo.
I will handle it myself.
Gong Joo is my daughter. I will do what's right for her.
However, I can't treat him and my son equally.
I think he has some ambitious plans.
Don't worry. I will handle this situation.
Okay. She's your child, so you should handle it.
Kids.
Can you do me a favour?
An old man asked us to give this to you.
- Bye. - Bye.
This letter will be the first and last from me.
Now that I look back,
the time I spent working at your home...
was the highlight of my life.
I was so happy as a woman.
I hate you, but I don't blame you.
I know that you can't do whatever you want to do.
Although it didn't last,
you made me feel alive.
I thank you for that.
The gift that you sent for my son's wedding...
will be given to my son.
I will never forget your generosity.
Please don't be sick.
Make sure you eat well.
In another life,
I'm praying that we will both be single...
so that we don't have to worry about what our children might think.
Why are you quitting so suddenly?
Thanks to you, our sales have gone up.
I have a personal reason.
What is that reason? Please tell us.
We were getting ready to promote you as our CEO soon.
Please tell us why you're doing this.
Did we do anything to cause you to make this decision?
It has nothing to do with the company.
I can't tell you because it's personal.
I can't believe you're asking us to transfer you to an office overseas.
My goodness.
Please do this for me.
I think...
I will be going overseas soon.
- When? - Very soon.
I just wanted you to know.
- Where will you be going? - I'm not sure yet.
What am I going to do?
You have to take care of yourself.
I wanted to find you a nice husband.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to do that.
- Will you be gone for a long time? - I will be gone for a few years.
Go back to your dorm.
Don't tell Cho Rong and Da Rong.
I will tell them myself.
Can I go with you?
What will you do if you quit your job?
Also,
don't go near Go Dal Pa.
I don't. He's the one following me around.
Regardless.
What kind of name is Go Dal Pa anyway?
He'll only make you suffer.
Hi.
- It's cold, isn't it? - It's not bad.
I love eels.
What about Ddol Ee?
I forced him to fall asleep so I can come out quickly.
As I was waiting for you,
my heart was beating so much.
I felt the same way.
I never felt that way when we lived together.
Oh, no. I think I've fallen for you.
Get in the car, Soo Jo.
I will take the bus.
You don't know the way.
Just get in.
Get in.
- Dad, I will see you later. - Bye.
Do you know how to drive?
I guess you do.
Would you like me to buy you a car?
Pick any car you'd like regardless of the price.
I don't want one.
Okay. If you don't want it, that's fine.
I talked to the factory manager.
You told me not to, so I didn't tell him about our relationship.
I will work just like the other workers here.
Don't do any difficult tasks. You can quit any time.
Who is Geum Soo Jo? I heard he's the new employee.
Oh, my!
It's you?
We meet again. It's nice to see you.
The manager told me to supervise you.
That means you need to follow my order.
- Did you quit delivering water? - Yes.
Ask me if you have any questions.
Hey, you!
Did you clean up everything? I told you to work quickly.
Yes, Sir.
Follow me.
- Ma'am, the strawberries are nice. - Okay.
Ms Nam!
Oh, my gosh!
What's wrong with you? You're embarrassing me.
Meeting you so unexpectedly...
feels like reuniting with a long lost family member.
Do you live around here?
I live nearby.
I take care of the house, you see.
Let's have a drink together.
Get off me.
Do you have something to tell me?
Why are we meeting here?
Let's eat first.
I don't want anything from his marriage,
but I feel very sad.
I wonder why I tried so hard to raise him.
I guess it was all for nothing.
Life is so meaningless,
and I feel so lonely.
Don't let Gab Dol dictate your life.
Ms Nam, do you want to go to a club?
My friend can set you up with a nice gentleman.
He's so popular among older ladies.
There are many old men who receive pension there.
A lot of older ladies come just to meet them.
Tell me when you're ready to go.
You will feel less lonely if you meet a nice, rich old man.
I know that...
you've suffered a lot.
Now that Soo Jo is at home and working at our company,
take some time off and go travel.
You've suffered a lot, too.
Si Nae.
I have a wish that I want you to grant.
What is it?
Every day has been torture,
but I kept it in because of your missing son.
I don't think I have a lot of time left.
Are you ill?
I'm not seriously ill.
How many days do I have left in me?
They say that people can live until 100 these days,
but I think it's meaningless to live...
the rest of your days at a hospital or a nursing home.
It's important to live a healthy life.
What are you trying to say?
Is this...
about that Pas lady?
Yes, I will...
marry her.
- Dad. - Don't talk me out of it.
It's my wish...
to live with a woman I love.
I'm not asking for your approval. I'm notifying you.
Dad, are you out of your mind?
- My mind is sound as ever. - Let's go to the hospital.
Why? Do you think I have dementia?
It's strange that you're being so unreasonable.
I got a check up recently. I'm perfectly fine.
I can't allow this marriage.
Do you know why?
First,
you are way older than her.
When there is a large age gap, there has to be another motive.
Second, she has her own children.
How can we be sure that she won't steal our money from us?
You may not see it clearly right now.
Think about it.
Why do you think she came to work at our house?
Why do you think she was so nice to you?
It's so obvious. Why can't you see that?
I know. I saw those things in the news.
My friend was a victim, too. However, she's different.
I already tested her.
Just ask her one question.
If you weren't the CEO,
and you were penniless,
would she still get married to you?
I'm 70 years old. I can tell what kind of person she is.
Perhaps you could before. Now, I don't think you can.
Your decision making skills have deteriorated. You're being rash.
Even if I'm wrong, it's still my decision.
Dad, get it together. Other people will mock at you.
Why? Is it because they'll think I'm too old to get married?
Is it because they'll think I'm senile? I don't care.
Frankly, it's not like you need a woman by your side at your age.
If you're asking...
if I can still function as a man,
yes, I'm still...
a man.
I know that it's embarrassing to say this in front of my child,
but I'm still a man and a human being.
Don't treat me like a corpse because I'm old.
Do I have to get your permission...
to see a woman because of I'm old?
You're not dating her. You're marrying her.
You want to get officially married so that she can inherit your wealth.
- What floor are we on? - The 10th floor.
I can't believe I have to hear such things from my child.
I don't want to live a life like this.
The window won't open. It's fixed.
At my age,
I may seem like a woman crazed, senile old man.
I may seem like an old man waiting to die.
But I am...
still alive and well.
I've been...
so lonely.
I can't...
live alone any more.
Why are you lonely? You have a child and grandchildren.
I've been living alone, too.
You're still young,
but I'm old.
- I don't have many chances. - If you're lonely,
I will find someone...
who's closer to your age and without children.
If you insist on going through with this,
I have my own plans.