(Episode 42)
Where did you go this early?
You must've been in the snow.
Are you going somewhere?
Please eat some porridge.
Are you mad at me?
I think I should eat this instead.
My life is a mess and now,
I have to eat leftovers.
Wait.
Don't forget me.
I won't.
I won't forget you...
but you should forget such a jerk like me.
I will cherish your face in my eyes,
your voice...
in my ears...
and your heart...
in mine all the time.
Mum.
- Dad.
- You brat.
It's all over.
Come back home.
I think I can't do without you.
You are pitiful and so am I.
Who else do we have to rely on?
You only have me...
and I only have you.
Let's feel sorry for each other...
and live together.
Why is she ill?
She's been ill for days now.
Shouldn't we take her to the hospital?
Leave it to me.
You should have something to eat. Come out.
Don't mind me. I'm aching all over.
Why all of a sudden?
It's because I'm not used to not working.
Should I bring the food?
I'll get it when I want to. Don't mind me.
How can I not mind?
What do you think you're doing?
What are you saying?
Who's the old man?
What have you done to
make me hear about him?
Do you think his family will accept you?
Don't you have self-respect?
How could you let yourself
be called a gold digger?
Our team is going out for lunch.
What do you want to eat?
I'm sorry. I have plans.
(Han Sung Samgyetang)
I bought you samgyetang. Get up.
I'm not hungry.
Get up. You like samgyetang.
It's expensive.
- Come on.
- Leave it there and go.
I'm not leaving until you finish it.
Get up.
I'll have it later.
I'm just aching all over. Leave me alone.
Why did you come out during work?
What's wrong with you?
I don't want to see you like this.
What's so great about that old man?
You haven't known him for so long.
You said I'm the only one you trust.
Was that all a lie?
I don't want to see you like this.
Dal Pa, go and clean first.
I need to drop by my house.
- Gab Soon.
- If it's about money, stop.
She's cold-hearted.
Goodbye.
Hello.
(True Samgyetang)
(Chicken porridge)
(7 dollars)
I'll have one chicken
porridge for take out.
Okay.
Mother.
Why did you buy chicken porridge?
I bought it for you.
I'll buy you samgyetang next time.
An expensive one.
I'll be going.
I got chicken porridge out of thin air.
I don't think it was meant for you.
- What?
- I think she found it somewhere.
I'm always having someone
else's food these days.
Ddol Ee, blow the candles.
Good job.
Oh, my.
You're even more amazing than
a soldier returning home.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Is this why I lived for so long?
Ddol Ee, beware of cars from now on.
Always take care of your health.
Ddol Ee, you must be happy
to receive a present.
I'm relieved.
You did well. Se Bang too.
Don't mention it. You
both did all the work.
I felt guilty.
I felt like it happened because of me.
I was so shocked I couldn't sleep for days.
My husband too.
I apologize for getting angry at
you like that at the hospital.
Anybody would have been like that.
I was scared to death at the time too.
Thanks to you, I got closer with Ddol Ee.
I was happy.
It felt like you gave me a present.
What are you going to do now?
It's not like you're going to live here.
There isn't room.
I can't leave this house. Don't
think of moving into my room.
Se Bang found a house. Let's
go see the house later.
Take me with you.
You should go with Mother to see the house.
If you like it, we'll take the house.
You should.
Oh, my.
I wish I could live in a house like this.
If an old man told me to come live
in a house like this, I would.
I'll leave your dad in a second.
Do you think old men don't have taste?
What?
You should say the facts.
What kind of sane man would ask
you to come live in such a house?
There are younger and prettier girls.
You and your mouth...
Goodness. Even if I don't have a man,
I'd love to marry a house.
Jae Soon, you're lucky.
Money is great.
What do you think?
Houses are the same.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you seem unhappy?
What?
If you decided to get back together
with Se Bang, you should be happy.
Why do you look forced to do
something against your will?
Should I be dancing?
I don't understand you.
You must want to get back
together since you've come here.
Jae Soon always says she
won't have anything to eat.
Then when everyone else is
done, she'll start eating.
You're so frustrating.
I don't understand what
Se Bang sees in her.
Oh, my.
There must be something guys see in her.
She doesn't look great both
from the front and behind.
Take me with you, you who
look pretty from behind.
How's the house?
It's a great house.
If I could live in a house
just for a day, I would.
I don't get how I lived in a
house like this for years.
It only ruined my taste.
You don't have anything else but taste.
I wish someone would buy
me a house like that.
- Who?
- My son or son-in-law.
I don't expect anything from Gab Dol.
I'd love it if one of them
would buy me a house.
Either Se Bang or Se Gye.
Dream on. What did Jae Soon say?
I don't know whom she takes after.
She should go look around the house
if she's going to live in it.
She just stood there. She was
like a fish out of water.
It was as if she was a third wheel.
There's no use.
I don't see what Se Bang sees in her.
It's weirder if she's
bursting out with joy.
Leave her be.
Seeing how she's going with it, she
must want to get back together.
- When will they buy the house?
- They're going to do it soon.
How did Se Bang get so much money?
When he got divorced, he
had nothing but debt.
I need to see you.
Not at home. Outside.
Do you like the house?
Mum does.
Not your mother. I'm asking you.
If you like it, let's go with it.
Before that, I want to ask you something.
What?
Do you want to live with me?
Can't you see?
Setting our child aside, I'm
asking about you and me.
Are you sure about us?
I am. And you?
Do you still have feelings for him?
- What are you saying?
- I understand.
You lived with him for over a year.
You must've developed feelings.
I'm sure it won't go away that easily.
I'm not talking about that man.
I'm talking about us.
"That man"?
You seem to still have feelings for him.
Are you hesitating because of him?
It's not like that.
Didn't you say you got
married because of the debt?
I guess not.
He abused his own child
and made him get therapy.
Why do you keep clinging onto such a guy?
Tell me.
Aren't you hesitating...
because of that Jo Geum Sik or whatever?
You and I...
are like a broken bowl and spilled water.
I'm afraid of...
getting back together just
because of the child.
I was in such a pain...
and I don't want to repeat that.
That's why I wanted to check.
Could you be a little more
respectful to your husband?
So what's your point?
Am I still...
a woman to you?
Of course, you're a woman.
You're not a man.
We're still young.
I don't think it's right to get back
together just because of our kid.
I think we both need to be ready...
to live as a man and a woman, as a couple.
I don't want to remarry you
just because of the child.
You're still not over him, are you?
Could you please listen to me?
Why do you only hear what you want to hear?
You were like that throughout our marriage.
That's why I was frustrated. We
couldn't have a proper conversation.
You don't listen to what I say.
You interpret and remember
my words as you like.
You're stubborn and unreasonable.
So it is because of him.
(International Study Agency)
I'm not going.
Cho Rong.
I hope you understand.
We have to go because of my work.
I heard there are many
good schools in the US.
Some can't study abroad
even if they want to.
She doesn't know how lucky she is.
Don't mind about her and bring me instead.
I don't want to go.
I want to study here.
There will be a lot of Korean
friends there as well.
Please, Cho Rong.
We need to deal with the school first.
We don't have time.
Cho...
Daddy, she looks really upset.
Mister.
Hello, Ma'am.
- Hi, Ms Ban. How is it going?
- Good.
Please report the clearance
items by this week.
All right, Ma'am.
Come. Let me introduce you to her.
He's a new employee.
You should be honoured.
He's still a bit clumsy. I'll make sure...
I train him to be a good worker.
Don't be too harsh on him.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
You're not supposed to
touch others like that.
You're right. I'm not supposed
to touch a man like that.
Be careful and stay healthy.
- Sir, let's go.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Gosh, she cares a lot about...
new employees.
She told you to be careful.
She seemed nice, didn't she?
To be honest...
Don't tell others.
She doesn't have a strong
academic background...
but she's amazingly skilled. She
does a lot of good deeds, too.
She does good deeds?
She does a lot of charity work
which helped me a lot as well.
- How?
- That's a secret.
Anyway, if you need any
help, you can just tell me.
We're really close.
I'm, so to speak, "a secret adviser".
But you seem to have a lot of
secrets as well. You don't talk.
You said you had a big family, didn't you?
- Yes.
- You're not married.
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
No.
If you have a big family to support,
it'd be hard to date someone.
I can imagine.
Here.
No, thank you.
Just keep it.
I took some for myself as well.
You should eat when you can.
You should be a little
brazen not to starve.
I'm home.
How do you like the work?
Isn't it too tough?
Why do you bring bread every day?
Is everything all right with Grandfather?
- Is it because of me?
- No.
I think it's something with your mother.
It seems like your mother defeated him...
after a severe fight.
Ever since then, he looks very depressed.
I'm so lucky to have a son who
brings me expensive strawberries.
You shouldn't have spent so much money.
You got me samgyetang, strawberries...
and some pocket money as well.
You should quit your job
and take a good rest.
We'll do the housework.
Sleep well too.
When did you come home?
You should've let me know that you're home.
Why? Did you say something
I shouldn't hear?
Do you want some?
I don't.
Are you asking me to eat the bruised ones?
Well...
I didn't know they're bruised.
They remind me of myself.
You could've prepared rice if you're home.
We don't have rice?
Let's say whoever comes home
first prepares the rice.
You just said we're going to
do the housework, didn't you?
Who are "we"? Is it me?
I hope it doesn't mean you want
me to do all the housework.
I'll do the darn rice.
What's wrong with women?
What's the big deal? You
flip out whenever...
we ask you to cook rice.
I don't want to eat.
Gab Soon.
Could you...
give me the allowance a little earlier?
- What?
- I just need some in advance.
I need to spend some money.
I think I already have withdrawal
from the lack of money.
Sure you do.
Pocket money, samgyetang and
strawberries for your mother...
must be expensive.
I did that because she's sick.
What would you think if I gave some
money to my parents behind you?
My mum has been through a lot.
What about my mum?
My mum has been through a lot as well.
You said she's going to
quit her job as well.
She must think we make a lot
of money since we both work.
You should rather try to tighten your belt,
not waste money.
Know how to be economical.
Stop talking about money.
You talk like a wife who's been
living with me for ten years.
Why are you so unhappy about
my mum's quitting her job?
It's nothing about us.
It's because she's sick.
I don't want her to work
even if she wants to.
I don't want her to work in a
restaurant despite the fact...
that her son is a public
official and married.
Imagine how others would think of me.
Why do you care so much about others?
Many people keep working
at old age these days.
Then why aren't your parents working?
- What?
- Am I wrong? They both don't work.
You can't compare my
parents to your mother.
What's the difference?
Because their son is a doctor?
Don't be sarcastic.
My parents are not dependent on us.
Your mother isn't even 60 yet.
She can help us out for
at least 10 more years.
We live for 100 years, which means
we need to support her for 40 years.
Don't you want to buy a
house and have children?
I didn't ask you to take
the responsibility.
You care about nothing but your mother.
You always talk about your mother.
I should've noticed when we were dating.
You didn't care when I was
sick for the entire night,
but you got samgyetang and
strawberries for your mum.
I like samgyetang and strawberries as well.
I'm just striving to save
as much money as possible.
I'm not sure why I married you.
I'd like to order samgyetang.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Is it tasty?
Yes, it is.
Good for you.
So this is what you want.
All right. Let's become penniless together.
That's not going to happen just
because of a bowl of samgyetang.
That's what I mean. Let's eat
whatever we want to eat.
If you want, you can order yours as well.
I'll stop being frugal from now on.
I don't care about a house or children.
I'll eat and buy...
whatever I want.
- Let's manage our own money then.
- Sure.
Give me my bankbook.
I was insane.
I was crazy to marry you even though
I already knew you were like this.
Do you know what makes me angry?
I feel as if I split you in half
and shared you with your mum.
It's like I barged in
between you and your mum.
How could you say so? Do you know
what my mum is going through now?
What is she going through?
Forget it.
I'm so upset.
Why? Did your mother-in-law
say something again?
No. I hate Gab Dol more than her now.
For what?
He gave her money without my knowing.
Without your knowing?
I knew it. He cares about her too much.
A widow's son usually
takes great care of her.
Gab Dol is not doing his job very
well between you and his mum.
Just like Joong Nyeon in the past.
- I was good at it.
- As if.
They should live alone. Why did they
take my daughter and let her suffer?
He was all talk.
He said he won't let you have a hard
time and live happily with you.
What a liar.
Gab Soon, go home.
Did you come here to tell on him?
Take care of your problems
at your own place.
Money is the most important
issue between married couples.
Sure, it is.
It was money that ruined your
parents' relationship of 40 years.
Once he makes a promise, he must keep it.
He should not save his own money...
and give his mum allowance
without letting you know.
If so, you won't be able
to trust each other later.
I think you should call
him over and tell him.
No matter what, I'd better go to work.
I should earn my own bread.
Whom would I rely on?
Welcome.
Hello, Ma'am. You were working here.
Yes.
Did you come here for work?
You said you quit.
You ached all over. Why did you come here?
Even though I'm sick, I
would die while working.
Until I die, I will make my own living.
Don't worry and stop
arguing with your wife.
Are you arguing even
before I become a burden?
We didn't argue.
Once your children gets married,
you want to see them live happily.
No parent would want to hear them fight.
I won't live off of you so don't worry.
Just take care of yourselves.
I told you I would take
responsibility for you.
Quit the job immediately. Or
don't say that you're sick.
You must feel upset...
to see her doing hard work.
When my mum comes back
exhausted after teaching,
I feel so sorry for her too.
You must feel worse since your
mum is doing harder work.
Shall we go?
Hello, Father.
Please stop by after work.
Okay, I will.
Don't feel hurt...
and think of this as an
advice from your father.
Money...
may seem to be nothing, but it is not true.
Does the money you earn all belong to you?
Yes.
You are married. How could
you think like that?
That's what we promised.
The money I earn is mine and the
money Gab Soon earns is hers.
Do you own money separately? I heard
she would take care of the money.
We'll each pay for living expenses...
and the accountant will
take care of the money.
- The accountant?
I mean Gab Soon.
Do you think you are still school friends?
You can't call her that.
No matter how much each of you earn,
the money belongs to both of you.
If you only keep the money you earn...
and use separately, that's not a marriage.
They say young people are
like that these days.
In my generation, we gave all the
money we earned to the wives,
let them buy houses and raise kids.
Do you want to take care of your own money?
That's ridiculous.
We should follow as the world changes.
What else can we do?
I heard you gave your mum...
allowance without Gab Soon's knowing.
It's not wrong to give her allowance but...
If you made a promise, you have to keep it.
At least, you shouldn't have
let her know until the end.
If they find out, any woman would
feel angry and wouldn't trust you.
You can say that again.
Whenever you bought something delicious...
and gave your mum without letting
me know, I was so upset.
I still have a grudge against it.
Don't buy samgyetang or strawberries...
only for your mum.
Gab Soon must have been so sad.
Food can either make you click
or ruin the relationship.
Why didn't you buy enough to share?
It was shameful of you.
Gab Soon also ordered samgyetang
and ate it in the end.
Imagine how mad she was.
You think it's trivial, don't you?
Those trivial things can
ruin the love of couples...
and make you lose faith.
I'm saying this since I think of
you as my son so don't be upset...
- and do what I tell you to do.
- Sure, you have to.
Listen to him carefully.
Is something wrong? That was a big sigh.
Are you not talking to me any more?
You get upset so easily.
You haven't changed at all
for the last 10 years.
What is wrong with your father?
What do you mean?
He tells me to think of him as my
father but he keeps telling me off.
- What did he say to you?
- You know very well.
You told on me about everything.
Why do you ask?
Do you feel happy when your
husband gets humiliated?
You told them every detail. There
will be no secret between us.
How could a wife reveal everything
about us to her parents?
You are the one who treated
me as an accountant.
Do you now realise that
it is not appropriate?
Does your father think so little of me?
Everyone in your family
took turns to scold me.
Forget it.
Mum.
Were you scolded again
by the in-laws today?
Yes.
We are out of green onions.
Should I buy some?
- Can you go grocery shopping?
- I've done many times.
But you didn't do it alone.
Please do grocery shopping then.
I'll make a list.
- Okay.
- Joong Nyeon, let me tag along.
I want to buy a corn dog.
- Are you sure it was around here?
- Yes.
She came out of that store
while eating a corn dog.
I kept watching for days
but I can't see her.
Maybe you didn't notice her.
But you said she hadn't changed a bit.
Her height remains the same, too.
She didn't grow at all.
She already grew up back then.
If she remained the same, I
couldn't have missed her.
She is dead if I catch her.
I didn't forget your corn dog.
I bought two of them.
Miss.
- Hello.
I did some grocery shopping.
Would you like to eat some?
I don't like eating food on the street.
I didn't buy them for myself. I
bought them for someone else.
Are you sick or something?
You don't look well.
I think I have a cold. I don't feel good.
Since you are alone, you should
take care of yourself very well.
Now that you married your son off,
enjoy your life and go on trips too.
Since we already met, I'd
like to say something.
I don't understand what you mean.
How could you call my precious son
over and scold him every day?
- Sorry?
- How could you be his father?
His father is lying down in his grave.
Would you feel happy if I told
Gab Soon off every day...
when she comes home after work?
He is busy while doing his
job as a public official.
I can barely watch him
because he is so precious.
I didn't call him over every day.
You called him over so many times.
They just got married, but you tell
him to come for drinks too often.
I wanted to say something,
but I tolerated it.
But you were training
my son as you do a dog.
A dog?
Then are you saying Gab Dol is a dog?
I already knew that you say harsh words...
but you are going too far.
I wouldn't feel this upset if
you gave him a lot of money.
I'm very careful not to
hurt my own son's feelings.
How could you tell my son off?
I think you're nagging my son
because you don't work at all.
If you don't have anything to do,
do some shopping and run errands.
- Sorry?
- I've tolerated a lot.
I'm tolerating whatever Gab Soon does.
Just remember Gab Soon
is in my house with me.
I'm leaving.
What was that?
Don't ask me to do errands again.
Since I carry a grocery bag, I'm
considered to have nothing to do.
Buy your own food.
I said I'd tag along.
You insisted on going yourself. Did
someone say something about it?
Whatever.
Take one.
What's wrong with him?
I hear you only had porridge this morning.
Grandpa.
Try eating this and feel better.
You should eat something.
I have no appetite.
I don't feel like eating.
What if you have to go
to the hospital again?
Do you keep in touch with Se Gye?
No.
I need to see him but I'm
too tired right now.
I'll have to see him next time.
Have some pastries.
- Great.
- Thank you.
Geum Soo Jo!
Give it back.
I took one for Ban Ji Ha.
He learned a bad habit from you.
Don't steal pastries, okay?
Did you keep one for me?
Thanks.
Follow me.
Sit down.
This is my secret place.
I take a nap here when I'm tired.
The manager can't find me here.
I come here to cry out loud...
and nobody will know.
Why don't you tell me
anything about yourself?
Tell me something.
Why are you being chased?
You don't have to know.
Anyway, thanks for saving me twice.
You even got kissed.
Thinking about that day...
makes me laugh.
What are you doing?
Hey.
- A girlfriend?
- Yes.
He doesn't have a girlfriend, right?
He never had one and he
probably doesn't have one now.
He's only been trained to marry
a girl from a rich family.
- All right.
- Why do you ask?
He should get married.
I'll find a nice girl from a good family...
and make Soo Jo marry her.
Should I buy you dinner as a thank you?
You work as a driver at night.
I'll have a quick dinner.
- Come here.
- Run away.
Who are you?
What are you?
- Darn...
- Who the heck are you?
Gosh.
What happened?
Bring it quickly!
I'm coming.
Who did this to you?
I'll beat him up.
I bumped into something at work.
At work?
Why do you do that kind of work?
What will we do with your face?
You should stop working at the warehouse.
- No.
- If being a director is too much,
how about working at a store?
It's close to home and it's not hard work.
I won't do anything other
than warehouse work.
Since when have you been so
attached to the warehouse?
What will we do with the bruise?
You didn't brush your teeth, did you?
No.
A very small car
A tiny car is driving
All right.
Look at you eating a corn dog and
carrying around a grocery basket.
All you do is stay at home...
and nag at your son-in-law.
Gosh. What a jerk.
A security guard?
I feel bad doing nothing at home.
I need some more pocket money.
I should work.
Did you forget?
You worked as a guard for three months...
after losing your severance pay.
You got looked down on by the tenants...
and went through so much. Do
you want to do that again?
Not all places are like that.
People even treated you like a thief.
You kept bringing food that wasn't edible.
I told you to quit because
I didn't like that.
Back then, when we went out,
people thought I was your older sister.
But look now.
You've gotten so old.
They think you're my father.
Nobody thinks that far.
Don't be a guard. Just stay home.
I think he'll get ill.
He won't eat anything.
He needs to eat.
What if he collapses?
Didn't he have anything for dinner?
He had a bit of porridge.
I asked him what he wanted
but he won't answer.
I heard you didn't eat.
Sir, tell me what you want to eat.
I'll cook it for you.
He's asking you what you want.
Do you not like what I cook?
People who cook always make what they like.
It doesn't suit my taste.
I'm sorry. I keep following my palate.
Tell me what you want to eat.
There's nothing I want to eat.
- You can go.
- Okay.
Dad. Why are you like this?
You said you'd end it. Why
didn't you get over it yet?
You're doing this on
purpose to make me upset.
- It's not like that.
- Then what is it?
Do you want to be carried to a hospital?
I'm tired. Stop talking and get out.
You said you stopped delivering milk.
I should do it until
they find a replacement.
- You're doing this on purpose.
- What?
You're doing this because I'm not
letting you see that old man.
I don't want to talk to you about this.
Then what is it?
You hurt your son's pride,
so stop it already.
Did I have to hear those
words from that woman?
Do you know how crushed I was?
I'm your retirement plan.
I'll do everything,
so don't get seduced by any old man.
Mum! Big news!
Was Gab Soon here?
Gab Soon's mother-in-law...
got caught dating.
- What?
- She was dating a rich, old man...
but they broke up because his
children didn't approve.
That's why she's upset these days.
That's why she was like that.
I didn't know that. I feel sorry now.
About what?
What? It's nothing.
She looked like...
she wouldn't date anyone
after her husband died.
Who knew she'd be dating?
She probably seduced him
because he was rich.
Even if he's rich, he's so old.
She's been living alone all this time.
Why would she...
date a corpse-to-be?
- Come on.
- I'm right.
She shouldn't cook and do
laundry for some old man.
She should just live alone comfortably.
It's because she's lonely.
Of course.
You get really lonely when you get old.
You get lonelier when it gets cold.
You should just be happy with
your children and grandchildren.
I don't understand...
old people who get married again.
I'd understand if they
were married since young.
It's all case by case.
She lived alone this long
so she should get married.
Since you lived with my
brother your entire life,
you wouldn't understand.
During the middle of the night,
you wake up but you don't find
any warmth under the blanket.
How would you know about loneliness?
Why would you be lonely
when you're sleeping?
You'd be bothered if you find
something under the blanket.
You should know that you're lucky.
Is this why I lived this long?
Did they disapprove?
That's what I heard.
Kids are all selfish.
They should be the ones to find someone.
They do as they wish.
Kids are like that.
Can children make their
parents feel less lonely?
Children and grandchildren
have their limits.
They shouldn't feel embarrassed
about their parents.
Gab Dol is still immature.
Should I talk to him about it?
The other family disapproved.
It's all over.
You'll leave Gab Soon in a tough spot.
Leave it.
She has a lot of years ahead. She
should get married if she can.
I heard he's old. I wonder how rich
he is that his family disapproved.
No matter how their old
parents live their lives,
children shouldn't meddle.
He might have his money taken.
They're worried that he'll
return to them penniless.
You should think about how
the children may feel.
You heard about Doo Shim's father-in-law.
He remarried a woman 10
years younger than him.
They lived for three years and the
woman ran away with all his money.
You can't blame the kids.
Why would you want to remarry?
Aren't you still a person
even if you're old?
It's only the body that aged.
Your feelings stay the same.
Someone I know wanted to marry.
His children disapproved so he couldn't.
He got ill and old. He
is in a hospital now.
Was he rich?
He had a pretty spacious flat.
He also had pension.
His children made such
a big deal about that.
My gosh.
Children with parents who aren't
rich worry about who'd take them.
Children with rich parents worry
that they'll get married.
Money is the best.
She doesn't seem charming to me.
How did she attract a rich guy?
He must have no taste.
Do you think she's all right?
Is she charming as a woman?
How can I see her as a woman?
I'm just saying. How is she objectively?
Do men like women like her?
I don't want to talk
about family like that.
What kind of women do you like?
Women that I've met first.
Let's say that we're both single.
Someone introduced us two at a coffee shop.
I entered the cafe.
"Hello."
What do you think?
- Is it the first time we've met?
- Yes.
Then I'll be happy than ever.
Men love women they've first met.
My goodness.
Say hello to me.
Hello.
Aren't I charming?
Why is an old man here?
I don't think I'd remarry.
There isn't a man who wants you.
I've seen you since we were young...
and saw you age so it's
not a big deal for me.
If I meet a man that I haven't seen
before, I'd feel awkward and weird.
How he lived and...
how he aged, I wouldn't have a clue
about that. How can I live with him?
If you don't want to
live like that, be good.
When you lost all the money and
all you did was ask for food,
I didn't want to see you.
I'm happy I'm with you.
I'm not jealous of women living alone.
Meeting a person and living
all your life with them...
It's great fortune.
You have to live long.
We're strangers. We aren't married.
Living with a stranger at
this age is fortunate enough.
- Does your heart flutter?
- It does.
Nobody's home, right?
My goodness.
Oh, my.
Where's Gab Soon?
She went to clean. What brings you here?
I can't sleep because of a
woman who's in love with me.
I don't think I can escape her this time.
Is it one of your customers?
How many times has it been?
I didn't know she liked me so much.
The reason she liked you was to get to me.
Who? Kim Young Ran?
Yes.
Go back to sleep!
She asked for my number! Isn't that proof?
Do you know Dal Tong who
delivers jajangmyeon?
Of course. He lives in our
district so I know him.
Do you know everyone in your district?
Almost everyone.
You're a natural, public official.
I heard you asked for his number.
I asked for the restaurant's number.
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
We've appointed you as branch manager.
You can go.
- Thank you.
- It's a pity.
You're needed in the head office.
We just discussed it over at
the shareholders' meeting.
We hope that you'll manage the firm
in the second half of the year.
I'll leave this time.
I'll think about the next step later.
What I learned during sales and
what needs to be corrected,
I'll arrange the materials
and hand them over.
I'll make sure things
go smoothly without me.
(Village hall)
You're blood pressure is normal
and you're in good health.
- We'll give you some vitamins.
- Okay.
Please show her the way.
Sir. Please come this way.
(Free physical checkup for the elderly)
Please take a seat.
- Are you Lee Byung Hoon?
- Yes.
Please open your mouth.
Wider, please.
Do you feel pain anywhere?
(Great Side Dishes)
Even if you live for just
a day, you should eat.
You shouldn't live on cup noodles.
I bought some side dishes from the shop.
Whatever you do, I'm on your side.
(I bought some side dishes.
Whatever you do, I'm on your side.)
What brings you here?
You should have called.
I'm here to pay you for the food.
I almost froze to death waiting for you.
How's volunteer work?
It feels like I'm home.
You can't only do volunteer work.
You need to make a living.
I'm looking for a woman who'll buy me rice.
I have a woman who buys me side dishes.
Does your family know?
If they find out, they'll drag me out.
I dropped by my house but said nothing.
What will you do?
Let's leave our worries aside.
Let's go.
Do you have money?
Don't belittle me.
I've worked as a doctor at a
university hospital for years.
I was a son-in-law of a wealthy
family for over a year.
Don't joke about your wounds.
I paid earlier.
You should go home.
I should walk you home.
I'm worried a girl who'd buy
you rice would take you.
Are you making a move with the side dishes?
I'll eat up and gain weight.
Here.
I have money.
I can spend this much.
Please drive her home safely.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Geum Sik?
Hi. What brings you here?
It's been a while. Take a seat.
- Are you alone?
- Yes.
- Are you with someone?
- No.
- We'll have a bottle of soju.
- Okay.
You're eating without food.
Should we have some?
Order anything you want.
- We'll have some soup.
- Okay.
You must be having a tough time.
I'm fine as long as your sister's happy.
I understand her.
I felt bad and upset but I
guess this is my limit.
Men are like that.
We feel hopeless when we can't
do everything for our women.
When you can't be confident,
you feel ugly.
I know.
Not being able to take
her by the hand and say,
"I'll take care of you,"
feels terrible.
I know how it feels.
I'm leaving.
Where to?
What brings you here?
Why are you alone? What about Se Gye?
I have something to tell you.
Leaving our child aside,
are you confident that we'll
be able to live as a couple...
while trusting each other?
I don't see you as a man.
Mr Jo, let's have a talk.
- I called earlier.
- Yes, Boss.
I arranged the best room here.
It's all ready.
Please come in.
Come in.
Please take a seat.
I've arranged what you usually have, Boss.
There are also beautiful ladies waiting.
Please leave us be. We have to talk.
- Wait outside.
- Yes, Boss.
You must've drunk already.
Yes, I did.
We decided to get back together.
I feel sorry for you.
I also have something to ask.
That's why I wanted to talk to you.
Why did you remarry?
Excuse me?
They say they had no choice
because you paid their debt.
You must have remarried as it's hard
to live alone with your children.
Things have changed now.
You should let it go.
Thank you for being so considerate.
I feel sorry for you.
It's not like us to be mushy.
She has a husband...
but you had the nerve to
come to the hospital.
She's over you...
but you haven't cleaned up your mess yet.
It seems like I'm older than you.
You should listen to me.
As men, let's settle this.
Let's bring in the ladies.
Let's have fun.
Hey, there!
Yes, Boss.
About the ladies...
Bring in the best you have here...
right now.
- Yes, Boss.
- Wait.
Get out.
I think we're done talking.
I'll bring them over.
I told you, get out.
You should take your time.
Did they say she married
because I paid her debt?
- Yes.
- That's right.
As a woman who was in debt
because of her ex-husband,
she must have lost her head
when she met a rich man.
But...
do you think money is all
there is to marriage?
I'm not sure if I should say this,
but she confessed later.
That she fell in love
with me at first sight.
That she never felt like that before.
I'm quite popular among women.
I'm tall and sturdy.
I have a great bottom.
Oh, my. What a waste of
an expensive liquor.
Do you want to know more?
When we lived together,
she always took care of
herself in front of me.
She woke up earlier than me.
She slept later than me.
I've never seen...
her face without makeup on.
If a woman wants to look good for a man,
I heard that's what they do.
Also,
she loved sleeping with
my arm under her head.
We never slept separately.
I heard she wasn't like that with her ex.
Drink slowly...
if you're going to enjoy yourself.
Whatever your name is,
as you said,
Jae Soon can be swayed easily,
but you should know this.
If she really wants to,
she takes control.
Hey, there.
Yes, Boss.
Do you call everyone that?
Bring your best girls in.
Mr Jeon here is going to enjoy himself.