BioskopKeren
Then how should we share the rooms?
I'll get out of this house.
Why would you?
You don't have to get out because of a newcomer.
You are talking nonsense.
Who do you call a newcomer?
Se Gye, use Gab Soon's room.
Even Dad doesn't have his own room. I feel uncomfortable.
Then the two of us will share the room.
Joong Nyeon and Se Gye can use the room together.
And why don't you share your room with Jae Soon and Ddol Ee, Nae Shim?
I'll sleep with Uncle.
I'll sleep in that room with them.
That room is too small for all of you.
And you'll get tired because your dad snores a lot.
My Dal Pa doesn't have any problem with that.
Dal Pa is different from Se Gye.
Dal Pa can sleep through a thunderclap.
But Se Gye can't because he is sensitive.
I am not any more, Mum.
I'm okay now because I used to sleep uncomfortably at the hospital.
Se Gye, use Gab Soon's room. And Mal Nyeon, come to my room.
I didn't become living proof so that I would get treated like this.
My goodness! I can't sleep now that I have to share the room.
I'm so used to having my own room.
Don't complain. You don't even have your own house.
How dare you complain while living under my roof?
You are lucky that you're in a nice, warm room in this cold weather.
Oh, Father.
What's wrong?
Dad,
can I cancel this wedding?
- What? - I don't think I can do it.
Help me out just this once, Dad.
I don't think this is right for me.
What are you saying? All these guests are waiting.
If you were going to cancel, you should have done it earlier.
Why are you being like this? This isn't like you.
Se Gye, just go through with it.
I'm saying this for your benefit.
Obey your father.
That pride, pride.
Why is it so important to show off to others?
As soon as I learned how to speak, all you said was "doctor".
I still don't know what I want to become.
For the 32 years of my life,
I lived like a robot so I don't know how to do anything.
Why aren't you sleeping?
I'm getting rid of these shoulder pads.
Mum.
You're right. Who cares if I don't have these pads?
Shoulder pads used to be in fashion, but my shoulders aren't sloped down.
I don't need them.
I don't care if shoulder pads are in fashion again. I'll never wear them.
Just be patient.
I'll make sure you will be proud of me.
It may not be because of money,
but I will make you proud of me.
Should I save these pads and put them back in later?
I will buy shoulder pads for you.
I will buy them in bulk for you.
Now that you're back home, I feel very secure.
Your dad is right.
Just having my children around me makes me proud.
I wish you were like this all the time.
Tomorrow morning,
you will go back saying, "I want to be proud of my children."
You little scoundrel.
Shall we race?
Sure. You won't be able to keep up with me.
We shall see about that.
This is the starting line.
Ready.
- No cheating. - I won't.
Go.
Dad!
Mum, this is delicious.
- Is it? - I remember the good old days.
It's your favourite, biji jjigye. Enjoy.
Now, the world will revolve around Se Gye.
My Dal Pa is in the dog house.
That doesn't even deserve a response.
I should take away his food.
I exercised in the morning, and I have a hearty appetite.
- Would you like more rice? - Sure.
I'm here.
What are you doing here so early?
I'm on my way to book a wedding hall at a hotel.
Are you having a wedding at a hotel?
Of course, he should. Did you eat breakfast?
No, I didn't. Can I eat, too?
- Bring Se Bang's rice, too! - Hey.
- Where is Ddol Ee? - He's at kindergarten.
Why would you have a wedding at a hotel?
A wedding should be done at a nice place.
What's wrong with having a wedding at a hotel with her son's father?
How can she get married three times?
Joong Nyeon.
No one's married three times in our family, right?
Sure, someone may not have married three times,
but I'm sure she's been with countless numbers of men.
Don't say such things.
She started it.
I didn't start anything. I'm just stating the facts.
I'm just stating the facts, too.
Stop it, both of you.
Why are you running into the kitchen while Se Gye is sitting still?
- We're having a wedding? - Sure, why not?
If you don't have a wedding, people might spread rumours.
Let everyone know that you're marrying Ddol Ee's father.
Se Gye, what are you doing at home at this hour?
He spent the night here.
- Se Gye got kicked... - Mal Nyeon.
There's a good reason for it.
Se Gye, let's get a drink together sometime soon.
Perhaps later.
(Director Yeo Si Nae)
Come in.
It's good to see you. What brings you here?
Have a seat.
Do you want something to drink?
Did you eat?
I ate and don't want anything to drink.
Can you lend me some money with no questions asked?
You need money? How much?
I need a lot.
Don't worry. How much do you need?
- I need three big ones. - Three big ones?
3,000 dollars.
What?
- What is this? - You said you needed 3,000 dollars.
No way. Where did you get this money?
Just look inside.
Is it really okay to take this money?
(1,000 dollars)
You don't have to pay back quickly.
Just pay me when you have...
- Why? - It's too much.
I'm thankful.
However, I would have taken care of it if the amount was this much.
There's another zero to this figure.
I guess you never handled more than 1,000 dollars.
I have.
- What's the largest amount? - 100,000 dollars.
You handled 100,000 dollars before?
I've never even seen such a large sum.
Thank you for caring.
I regretted after I told you.
I shouldn't have said anything to someone so poor.
This is very popular.
I think you will look great in this.
What do you think? Do you like this?
Do whatever you want.
I think you are deeply in love with the bride.
I will bring the paper works.
She says that I'm the only one in love.
Are you glad to hear that?
Look happy. People might think I'm forcing you to marry me.
- Did you make the reservation? - Yes.
It's not like she's getting married for the first time.
- I'm sure you're thrilled. - Why, you...
Is the hotel nice?
It's a hotel.
You got married at a hotel when you married Geum Sik.
They only had a reception there.
Why did you bring him up?
You're so tactless.
I'm leaving.
- To where? - I've been transferred to the US.
Why so suddenly?
I asked to go.
Is it because of Jae Soon?
- You're still here? - Yes.
Jae Soon, do you have time this evening?
- Why? - I'm asking you on a date.
I'll do as you say.
Cho Rong. Thank you.
I made her change her mind.
It's not because of you.
Thanks anyways.
I told her that she won't need to study hard like she does here...
or even go to private institutions.
Geum Sik, we have everything planned.
When we go to the US we're going to travel around.
I'm going to rent a car and go on a road trip.
Disneyland, Las Vegas and New York.
There are so many places to go.
I want to go quickly.
Da Rong, what did I tell you to do first?
To grow my front teeth.
Ddol Ee's teeth must have fallen out like Da Rong's.
Why are you mentioning that? You have no sense.
(Saesak Kindergarten)
Ddol Ee.
Hello.
Ddol Ee, it's been a while. You haven't forgotten me, have you?
No.
You've grown bigger.
Are you better now?
Great.
Ddol Ee, your teeth fell out as well.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Ddol Ee.
Don't be ill and stay healthy.
I'm sorry for everything.
Listen to your mother and take care of yourself.
Become a great man.
Let's meet again when you grown up.
This is too much.
Let's go to a cart bar.
I need to spend this much if I'm going on a date with an older woman.
You're going to become another man's woman soon.
You make strange jokes.
That's what Man Joo told me.
Do I make bad jokes?
You make jokes out of hurtful things.
This must be an expensive place.
I can pay for this. I kept a bottle as well.
- There's some leftover, right? - You drank it all.
Let's go.
Who do you think I am?
- I'll have the same drink. - Okay.
Stay here. I need to wash my hands.
I just arrived.
I used to come here often. It's a nice place.
I don't think it's the right place for today.
I'll find another place.
I'll call you soon.
How are things with Man Joo?
What do you mean?
When you got married,
I had my own troubles. I couldn't be more considerate.
I knew you were having a hard time but I ignored it.
I was always worried about that.
People...
need to live with those whom they love.
I hope you choose as you wish.
Of course Mum and Dad will think differently.
You have something to say, right?
Don't walk on eggshells. Spill it. I'll help if it's not about money.
Actually, I wasn't sure.
If I should tell your or not.
But still,
I think I need to tell you.
Geum Sik is leaving.
Leaving?
He applied for a branch in the US...
because of you.
To forget you.
Ddol Ee fell asleep.
I'll take him in.
I thought you went out with Se Gye.
He went to see someone.
- Mum. - Go sleep in your room.
What's this? It looks new.
- He gave it to me. - Who?
He came to my school and gave it to me.
He told me to become a great man.
He's leaving to forget you.
Who is it?
Jae Soon.
Why aren't you picking up?
- Did you call? - Are you out of your mind?
What were you thinking?
What are you saying?
I'm sorry about before.
I didn't mean that you spoiled the mood.
Is that why you were offended?
That's not what I'm saying.
Are you still drunk or sleepy?
Both.
What about the kids?
What am I?
Because of a worthless person like me,
does it make sense to take your kids to the US?
What am I that you can't forget about me?
Don't you feel sorry for your kids who don't have a mum?
How will they cope in a foreign place?
You won't be able to take care of them because of your work.
They are already shy and have been bullied.
Why did you make that choice?
You're a terrible dad.
Is that why you came to see Ddol Ee?
To say goodbye?
Don't go.
What did you say?
I don't know what to do.
To make up for what I did to my kid,
I was going to give up my life as a woman.
I was going to live my life as a mum but...
My feelings for you...
are still here.
When I wake up in the morning,
you're the first thing that comes to my mind.
That's what I thought.
I was going to date you until our kids grow up.
When we become 50 or 60 years old...
When our kids can be left out of it...
If you stayed next to me until then,
I thought of living with you.
I know I'm being selfish.
You need to remarry and settle down.
I can't hold onto you out of greed.
I can't do this or that.
Please...
give me some time.
What are you saying?
Don't you understand?
Give me some time.
To figure out what to do with you.
What is it?
I don't need this.
(It's a large amount of money.)
It's a huge amount of money.
What are you talking about?
She wants to have some time.
Time to do what?
What's the matter with you? You already set the date.
You even reserved your wedding hall.
My goodness.
You went out for drinks last night.
Hey. Did anything happen?
What happened last night?
I told Jae Soon to think about it once again.
- What? - Just mind your own business.
Since it's her life, she has to be the one who decides.
Considering her personality,
if everyone forces her, she just follows.
So I wanted her to consider it again.
It's not all because of what Se Gye said.
Please give me some time to think it over.
Se Gye, I think we should have a drink soon.
Come out for a bit.
Why are you doing this?
You weren't happy either when reserving the wedding hall. Why not?
I said I need to think it over.
Be honest. This is because you haven't forgotten him yet, right?
- What? - He told me...
that you married him because you liked him.
Your parents said you were almost forced to get married to him...
but he said you married him because you fell for him.
Because he is tall, handsome...
and rich. He even has charming buttocks, right?
You didn't fall asleep without his arm under your head, did you?
And you never looked messy in front of him?
Did you like the guy that much?
Jo Geum Sik or whatever said this, too.
You are usually led by people...
but you start to lead them when you really like them.
How far did you go leading him?
I can't talk to a jerk like you any more.
What a lowlife you are.
I'm hesitating because you're like this.
I can't trust you.
Your only merit is that you are Ddol Ee's dad.
I want to end with you right away...
but I said I wanted to consider it again because we have Ddol Ee.
Do you understand?
Hey. Shin Jae Soon!
Why did you say so to your sister?
You know very well about her.
I told her because I know her very well.
Please leave her alone now.
She's been dragged by you all along regarding her marriage and divorce.
"Think of your situation."
"You don't have money or skills."
Even I can remember your lines.
This is between you and me, but it is true about her.
Who do you think will pay attention to her if she gets older?
And we are not rich and neither are you now.
Never mind this.
I knew you would change your attitude overnight.
Mum, please let Jae Soon take care of her own problems.
She is 40 years old already.
You don't have to listen to Se Gye. Men don't know anything.
I'm not a smart person.
I have to consider something many times more than others.
I have been thoughtless so far.
In order to live off of a rich guy,
I made easy choices.
I don't want to be like that any more.
Since I have a head, I want to use it to think.
Did you realise you have a head now?
I just saw it in the mirror.
Don't look in the mirror then.
Congratulations. Here is your family relation certificate.
We finally became a married couple.
We already were.
I mean legally.
This is amazing.
Now, I'm definitely a married woman.
You don't like it? If so, I'll go cancel this.
Hey.
- Don't. - Okay. I'll put it in here.
Are you shooting a movie or what?
You were not holding hands these days.
We registered our marriage today.
Make sure to treat me as an adult.
Me, too.
Just wait. It won't take long for me, either.
You don't have a girlfriend yet.
You may be surprised soon.
I have to go deliver the food.
Does Dal Tong have a girlfriend now?
You know what he is like.
He thinks they like him when they order delivery.
Is he still like that?
Did you come here to deliver food again?
Did you come out all the way here to wait for me?
Excuse me?
They said they registered their marriage.
I don't understand them.
How could a couple date for as long as 10 years?
Do you know what my creed is?
"Before jjajangmyeon gets soggy and while jjamppong is still hot..."
Write it down when I say such things.
I got to go before this gets soggy.
(Family relation certificate)
You finally became a married couple formally.
You really did. How do you feel?
Maybe they want to run away.
A little bit.
Me, too. All my great times are gone.
Although we went out for more than 10 years,
I think marriage is completely different from dating.
It is true. Men and women can't understand each other well.
I don't know all about my husband yet.
It won't be fun if you knew it all.
If you expect a lot, you'll get disappointed easily.
So don't expect the other to do the same for you...
when you do something for them.
They said instead of taking advantage of the other,
you should think of what you can do for your partner.
That's what a couple is for.
Easier said than done because we are not saints.
It's strange that we fight more after we got married.
It's because you don't want to lose what you have.
You think you'll lose all your life if you lose at first.
So you try your best not to lose.
You can be generous to others...
but you don't want to lose to your spouse.
"I'll keep my own stance from the start."
"If I yield now, I might suffer the loss forever."
This is all because of selfishness.
We'll try not to be like that.
We're okay with other problems, but we always fight regarding his mum.
You should try to understand her as much as possible. She is lonely.
Did you hear that?
It is delicious.
This is my mum's favourite.
My mum went through a lot all her life.
Now I understand why Gab Soon gets upset.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. I sure am.
(Family Relation Certificate)
Take care of each other dearly from now on.
You are definitely a married couple now.
You're saying the exact words that Gab Soon said.
You sound like Gab Soon.
Do you know how hard it is to live a life without a husband?
I won't die young. How can I die when Gab Soon is here?
Do not interfere when I'm talking to her.
Without a husband,
a woman has to suffer a lot. So be nice to him while he is around.
I'll also have to suffer if Gab Soon is not around.
I said not to interfere.
You babble a lot.
You got talkative after you got married.
You're right. He got unattractive after we got married.
Go to your room now.
- What are you doing? - What?
Do you watch these kinds of clips, too?
Do you?
Yes. Dal Pa taught me how to watch them.
There are many interesting clips here.
- Shall I try to upload one? - Your face will be exposed.
What's the big deal? I don't mind it.
Exposing my face is not a problem.
When I was young, I wanted to become an actor.
You said you wanted to become a doctor.
You can have many dreams.
I had a lot of dreams.
Dal Pa.
I want to upload a video clip. What would you recommend?
Nowadays, eating shows and cooking shows are popular.
Eating and cooking.
I see.
You can upload anything.
Someone uploaded a clip of doing meditation while sitting still.
And some people uploaded footage of their studying all day long.
Really?
Once you are known to the public, you can't go around outside...
and you can't erase them.
It's okay if you don't do anything wrong.
Uncle, do it since you have a lot of time.
It's great to kill time.
Don't ever bring such things.
Am I a puppy or what?
If you threw food and called me,
did you think I would wag my tail and follow you?
I didn't meant that.
Let's not do something we'd feel embarrassed in front of the kids.
Tell me if you need money.
But you don't have money.
There is some I saved without your mum's knowing.
I have enough to give you pocket money.
I'm still okay.
I get money for my activities.
I can't spend a fortune, but...
I can make my living on my own.
Really?
Did you wrap up with Gong Joo?
Yes, I did.
I feel apologetic to her.
She is still young...
I feel bad that she had to go through such a hard time.
I wasn't nice to her.
Anyway, it's a shame.
How is it going with Ms Jung?
Let's be honest. She's more than just a friend, isn't she?
Do you have any plans?
He didn't answer?
He just smiled.
She's a nice girl, though.
It's not going to be easy.
I bet the whole family is going to take advantage of...
the daughter of the doctor.
I don't want to even hear it. That's not what family is like.
They're not the only one.
It seems like...
every family has at least one person who sacrifices for the rest.
What if he says he wants to marry Man Joo?
Don't count your chickens before they hatch.
What are you saying?
If they get married, who do you think would be disadvantaged?
Of course it'd be Se Gye. There's no doubt.
Se Gye is like a used product. He already married once.
Mal Nyeon.
He was married only for a year.
They didn't even register the marriage.
The package was opened anyway.
Once the package is opened, it's used.
Man Joo isn't a rubbish bin. She won't accept anyone.
Are you saying Se Gye is rubbish?
Your mouth will bring you down someday.
I'm already hopeless.
This isn't why I've become living proof.
Goodness.
What do you want to say?
Study abroad.
You're kicking me out as well?
Sit down.
Me?
No.
You can wash the dishes later.
I need to do them now.
I can never let the dishes lying in the sink.
Then could you do it more gently?
After studying abroad, get married to the guy I set you up with.
Why do you have to do everything as you like?
I'm not going to be your puppet.
Sit down.
This guy doesn't want to get washed just like me.
I'm not going to be your puppet any more.
I'll get back together with Se Gye.
Are you out of your mind?
Did you forget what his family has done to us?
Don't you get it?
We're done with his family.
No, it's not. I'll do what I want.
You live your life. I'll live my life.
Gong Joo.
I cooked some kimchi pancake.
You must be stressed from many things.
I'm ashamed that you saw it.
I've seen much worse things in life. Don't worry.
I've already seen enough of fights between...
a mother and a daughter before I moved here.
Try some.
Kimchi pancake tastes good when it's still warm.
I don't feel like it.
You don't know how tasty it is.
- Open your mouth. - I can eat myself.
Pancake tastes best when your mum feeds you.
Here.
It's tasty, isn't it? Doesn't it taste amazing?
It is tasty. It's perfectly seasoned.
What's wrong? Are you crying because it tastes so good?
It reminds me of my mum.
My mum used to feed me pancakes like this.
I didn't have a mum.
Did you grow up without a mother?
So you've never been fed pancakes by your mother.
It tastes great.
It tastes 100 times better than eating it myself.
Si Nae, how about you just wait and see how Gong Joo deals with it,
instead of scolding her?
I also just set Soo Jo free whenever he was being stubborn.
Soo Jo was also often troublesome, wasn't he?
He's even a boy.
We were rather crying together,
fighting one problem after another.
I can imagine how tough it must have been.
No, thank you. I'm done with thinking about my mum.
Sir.
Yes, Si Nae.
That day,
on such a cold day when there was a snowstorm,
why did you go to the river?
Was it because...
You're right.
I didn't want to live any more.
Were you the same?
I had a baby when I was only 18 years old.
There was nothing I could do.
I was going to kill myself and the baby,
but it crossed my mind that I had to at least let the baby live.
I left the baby and was walking into the river.
But then I heard the baby crying.
If you didn't take him then,
I would've died and Soo Jo would've died as well.
You saved two lives.
Now that I think of it,
I almost let the baby freeze to death.
I can't believe I left the baby there in the middle of the night.
This is probably how it's meant to be.
Soo Jo also saved my life.
Ever since then, I never thought of killing myself.
Whenever I was going through hardships,
I looked at Soo Jo and he gave me the motivation to live.
I've never thought it was hard raising Soo Jo.
Don't cry.
All three of us are alive now.
That's a good point.
Is it for me?
Yes.
You don't need to cool it down. It's already cooled down.
(Free medical service for the elderly)
Next pretty lady, please sit down.
How may I help you?
What brings you here?
I heard there's a handsome doctor here,
but he's not that handsome after all.
You...
What brings you here?
Be honest with me. You're here to see me, aren't you?
How arrogant.
You should take a good rest when you're tired.
We are short-handed, though.
I'm here so that you can make a slave of me.
Let me get changed.
Make sure it looks sexy.
I'll surely make a slave of you.
(Free medical service for the elderly)
Next patient, please.
Gong Joo. What brings you here?
Nae Shim, come out.
What brings you here?
- Ma'am. - What are you doing?
I don't want to see you. You'd better go.
I have nothing to talk about and I don't want to see your face.
She said she doesn't want to see your face.
Goodness. What did you expect from her?
Ma'am, please forgive me.
I want to get back together with Se Gye.
Please help me, Ma'am.
How can we help you?
I said there's nothing to talk about.
I'm not in a good mood. You'd better leave.
I have nothing to say to you.
I was too young and silly.
I got married just because my family wanted me to get married.
It must've been hard for Se Gye.
After we broke up, I realised what I've done to Se Gye.
Ma'am, I want to get back together with Se Gye.
Please help me change his mind.
It's as easy as it sounds like. He's not a child.
There's nothing I can say. Mal Nyeon, let her go.
Please help me.
I wish I could, but I have no power.
I don't have any power in this house.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. I surely am.
This is not how I expected my life to be.
My goodness.
I don't know what else to say.
Gosh.
Mal Nyeon.
How could you betray me?
Tell me. Why did you run away?
Why did you run away?
You didn't come back.
You said you'd come back in a month but you didn't.
Still, how could you get married within three months?
Do you know what I did for you?
For goodness' sake!
Stop it.
Let go!
- Did you get hurt? - I'm okay.
You got hurt.
My goodness.
My gosh.
I heard you got divorced.
Yes.
I looked for you all my life.
You must have hid well. I couldn't find you.
Did you get remarried afterwards?
You're not supposed to...
ask a woman about her past.
Did you get remarried?
I'm on my own.
Do you have children?
I don't.
Are you on your own then?
Yes.
She doesn't have a husband or children.
She's on her own.
- What did she say? - She was just crying.
I think she missed me as well.
She must have.
What are you going to do now?
I longed to see her so much...
but when she was in front of me...
- Weren't you disappointed? - No.
I was heartbroken.
She hasn't changed at all. She's the exact same height.
She was at her adult height back then. She was over 20.
How has she been?
- Is she seeing anybody? - I didn't ask too much.
She said you're not supposed to...
ask a woman about her past.
I don't know why I'm feeling this way.
I don't think she's well off.
She lives with her brother's family.
It makes me sad.
She must have suffered a lot.
She had me in her heart...
but had to marry someone else.
Only if I came back earlier...
Your family was torn apart.
You were the only son and you wouldn't marry the girl they chose.
You eventually got kicked out of your own house.
Is this what it comes to?
This is useless.
She must still have feelings for me.
My hand was bleeding and she was so upset about it.
She wrapped my hand like this...
and blew on it.
Lucky you.
I looked for you all my life.
You know I'm the only son, right?
Even after my parents kicked me out,
I couldn't forget about you so I didn't get married.
I'm getting old without children of my own.
Why do you look so startled?
Get up.
The manager's asking for us.
Hey.
What do you think?
It looks nice.
I look good in anything.
How's the jacket?
Look. I designed it.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
A designer edited it but it was my idea.
I got some prize money from the employee contest.
I used it to pay for my twin's formula.
Formula?
Yes.
I have a twin sister.
If I studied, I would have become a great designer.
Darn it.
It was my childhood dream to become a designer.
What is your dream?
To get married into a wealthy family.
Marrying into a wealthy family?
That's great.
I guess that was my dream as well.
Having a wealthy husband?
Marrying into a wealthy family.
When I was little, I imagined myself being taken by a wealthy man.
But what kind of a man would take me?
Anyhow, we had the same dream. Right?
The manager will be here in any minute. Hurry.
I was the head of my household.
If I studied, I would have become a great designer.
(It's a large amount of money.)
Is there anything bothering you?
You can tell me.
What it is? Is it money?
Sir, do you have debt?
We lived on noodles but we don't have any debt.
- Why? - It's nothing.
It's 30,000 dollars.
I'll make sure to pay you back.
You don't have to. I won't ask.
If you need money, ask me any time.
Thank you. Please don't tell my dad.
Okay.
My gosh. Why are you here?
- I'll get going, Director. - Okay.
Hey! Hey!
How impolite. He was supposed to bow.
I need to train him.
Why was he here? Did he ask you not to fire him?
Yes.
He said he has a big family so he wants to keep working.
And Ms Ban.
Why are you calling him like you're calling a country boy?
Don't say that any more.
It's fun.
It's only fun for you.
Soo Jo didn't say anything either.
Just don't do it.
Also, don't do any more training either.
- Yes, Ma'am. - He's an adult, too.
Don't talk to him as if he's a child.
Yes, Ma'am.
You won't be fired. I talked to the director.
Thank you.
My bus is here. Bye. See you next week.
What is this?
(10,000 dollars)
Soo Jo. Soo Jo!
What? Is something wrong?
Where did you get this money?
Don't ask.
I know you. This can't be yours.
I didn't steal it. Just use it.
How can I trust you?
Tell me everything. Otherwise, I can't take this money.
Did you ask for an advance from the director?
There's no way she would give you this much money.
Did you get a personal loan?
No, that's not it.
You said that loan sharks are after you.
Just pay them back for now.
Pay me back when you have the money.
This is the first time someone has lent me money...
without a promissory note.
What if I run away without paying back?
I know you won't do that.
How can you trust me?
You don't even know me well.
I know you well enough. I don't need to know more.
How can you say that?
I will take this money for now.
I will pay you back for sure.
Your bus is here. Get on.
Let's meet tomorrow.
Really?
I will treat you.
Where?
Meet me at Pyung Tae Park at noon!
What are you doing?
I'm writing an expense report. Mr Yeo wants to see it.
It's your spending money.
I don't need any money.
My goal was to find a place where I can eat and live.
Now that I've reached my goal, I don't want anything more.
I know. However, a man needs money in his wallet...
to feel confident.
That's right. I need to buy some underwear.
Many of my underwear have holes.
I saw them in your room.
Don't wear the ones with holes.
Don't dry them in your room.
Dry them confidently in the front yard.
I'm embarrassed.
Did you look for Soo Jo's potential wife?
Yes.
I hope she's pretty and kind.
I hope she at least graduated high school.
I hope her family isn't too poor.
I want her family to have their own house.
That's not enough.
Soo Jo is a very precious son.
Soo Jo is no longer Soo Jo of the past.
He's not poor any more. He's genuinely wealthy now.
I'm sorry.
I'm still the poor Geum Do Geum.
Who cares where I work? It doesn't concern you.
Don't tell me what to do.
Do you think I'm still your wife?
Do not try to control me. Be quiet.
Why do you talk to him that way?
I didn't do anything. He's the one picking a fight with me.
You changed a lot. You used to be so polite.
As I'm getting older, I'm becoming more blunt.
I'm becoming like you.
Now you're blaming me for that, too?
Since when can you afford not to work?
If he says don't work, don't work.
Why do you insist on working there?
Let's be honest.
What man will treat you like that?
A man who takes care of you is the best kind.
You sure know how to make yourself miserable.
You need to do the right thing.
What does our family have to brag about?
Let me be proud thanks to Jeon Se Bang.
Stop being so obsessed about bragging.
Didn't Se Gye say enough about that?
You never say anything nice to me.
Ms Shin. It's Dad's birthday today.
I tried to make seaweed soup, but I couldn't.
(Memorial ceremony for Gab Dol's father)
- Are you on your way out? - Yes, Mother.
- Can you come home early? - Why?
Don't ask. Just come early.
I'm sorry, but I have a lot of cleaning to do today.
I will go and make money.
How insolent.
Should I laugh or cry? Why are you spending so much time?
Just comb it. There's not much left there.
You have hardly any hair.
Don't mock me because you have a full head of hair.
Each strand of hair is so precious.
My heart aches whenever I lose one.
Hair accounts for 70 percent of men's look.
Do you want me to braid it for you?
Patience.
Should we have a spring cleaning of the house?
We should. By ourselves?
We should bring over Gab Soon and Gab Dol, too.
Let's have a pork belly party.
- You call Gab Dol. - Sure.
- Gab Soon. - Gab Dol.
Spring cleaning?
Yes, Sir.
I will bring over pork belly.
The in-laws are asking you to clean their house?
I've known them for a long time.
They treat me as if I'm their own.
Being so close to them may become problematic later.
Don't worry.
You should listen to my advice.
You don't know anything about us.
I'm here.
Welcome.
This is Se Gye's old clothes.
- Change into them. - Okay.
How is this?
- Thank you. - Bye.
This one.
Thank you.
- Bye. - Bye.
The roasted sweet potatoes looked delicious.
Make sure to eat slowly with water.
Move that.
Flex your muscles. That's good.
- It's heavy. - That way.
My goodness.
- Put it here. - Here.
We need to roll this.
There you go.
That's good.
(Mother)
The caller cannot be reached.
Why aren't they answering their phones?
Don't they know what day today is?
Hello, this is Kim Young Ran.
Hello.
This is Gab Dol's mother.
Gab Dol is not answering.
Is he really busy?
No, it's a holiday so he fixed his report...
and went home early.
He went to his in-laws to do spring cleaning.
He went to his in-laws to do spring cleaning?
Thanks to you, our spring cleaning was a breeze.
We got rid of all the unnecessary junk.
If Gab Dol's mum saw him work, she would be furious.
Gab Dol is her precious son.
It's okay. I'm a member of this family, too.
Of course, you are.
- Gab Dol, enjoy the food. - Thank you.
Here, try this.
Good.
It's great.
Chew.
Everything tastes great here.
Gab Soon is late.
- Here, have a drink. - Yes, Sir.
Here.
Cheers.
That's looks good.
(Seaweed)
- Where are you? - At the supermarket.
I'm working. Hang up.
I made seaweed soup for you.
Enjoy it with the children.
I just made seaweed soup.
Cho Rong told me that she couldn't make it.
Happy birthday.
I'll be going now.
Can you stay with me?
Just for today.
I can't let you go like this.
I know that I shouldn't say this.
Just stay with me today.
Please.
Don't fight!
Stop this now!
(Our Gab Soon)