(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 46)
Are you listening?
Let's meet right now. I beg you.
What is it?
Do you want to try on another wedding gown?
This one looks great on you, too.
I'll take this.
I have to go back to work now.
I have a meeting.
Okay. Call me later.
Hello?
Why are you calling me?
I have to tell you something in person. Let's meet right now.
No, I don't think we need to meet.
Just this once. I beg you.
I'm begging you.
Please don't ever call me again.
Goodbye.
As you allow the foam roller to roll up your calf,
you can stretch out your leg.
When you come up,
you can reverse the motion...
Hey!
You're so mean.
I thought you said you wouldn't do this any more.
You don't know what you're talking about. I'm not doing anything bad.
I'm getting ready for the US.
I have to find work when I get there.
I can't stay home without doing anything.
I don't like you doing this. This looks ludicrous.
What's going on? Why are you arguing?
We're not arguing.
Why would I argue with my niece?
I'm reprimanding her.
She was recording herself to upload on the internet.
Why are you doing this again?
Haven't you learned your lesson?
These days, people want to exercise...
at home without spending too much time or money.
I'm doing home training.
I uploaded few clips, and they are drawing a lot of attention.
Everyone's watching my videos.
If you do anything foolish again, I will not put up with it.
Don't worry.
I heard you're going to the US to check out the schools.
Yes, I'm taking the first flight out tomorrow.
Take care of the children without getting into arguments.
(Witness Interrogation)
You are being questioned as a witness, so don't worry.
Just answer our questions.
Sure.
Se Bang.
Ma'am.
Aren't you supposed to be in China?
I came back today.
That was a short trip.
China is so close.
I took care of the business and came right back.
What are you doing here?
Do you have business to take care of?
The chief of the station is my friend. I just stopped by to say hi.
- He's friends with the chief? - That's right.
I guess being in business allows him to meet a lot of people.
He knows so many people.
People who were conned are preparing to sue him.
There are a lot of people who are angry at him.
Why were you at the police station?
It's nothing to be concerned about? Are you sure?
Of course, I'm concerned.
You have, after all, criminal...
About the children...
What did you say?
What are you hiding?
I'm not hiding anything. I was talking on the phone.
You said something about criminals. Whom were you talking about?
Well...
It's someone I know. What about the children?
You know someone with a criminal record?
Of course, I know people of all different kinds.
People with criminal records and gang members.
Just hearing about them scares me.
I want to talk about the children.
Before Jae Soon gets married,
we should formally introduce Jeon Se Bang and Gab Dol.
That's a good idea.
They should be formally introduced, so they can get along.
Let's make some dumplings and invite them over. I bought groceries.
Sure, Mum.
The kimchi tastes great, so dumplings will be delicious.
Gab Dol loves dumplings. He will wake up at the mentioning of it.
Se Bang loves dumplings, too.
Now that you mention it, our sons-in-law both love dumplings.
- I'll make some fresh kimchi, too. - Okay.
She's making dumpling soup?
Make sure I get extra portions.
Okay, I will make the dumplings.
- Are you going to your in-laws? - Yes.
Is that not allowed?
Well, it's not that.
You should be careful so that you won't have any trouble.
- Please revise this report. - Okay.
What troubles could there be?
You're very good at making dumplings.
You'll have a beautiful daughter.
Is that what they say?
I'm going to eat all the dumplings I make.
I can eat dumplings all day.
I already told them how much you love dumplings.
Are the dumplings ready? The soup is boiling.
It's almost done thanks to Gab Dol.
Jae Soon, your husband is here.
I'm here.
Welcome. You're just in time.
Are these diamonds?
It's her wedding present.
You are so fortunate.
They're so beautiful.
They are beautiful.
How much do these cost?
They must be very expensive.
He gave them when they first got married.
We sold those off long time ago.
I got bigger ones than those.
Do you like them?
Of course.
He's talking to Jae Soon, not you.
She feels the same way.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Are you sure? I bet you've never seen anything like these.
Try them on.
Later.
What?
Is there anything for us?
Get some dumplings for your aunt.
Ma'am. Here's some spending money.
Thank you for inviting me over for dinner.
It's not a special occasion.
I'm so sad that I don't have a son-in-law.
Do you have anything for us, Gab Dol?
He made all those dumplings.
Sure, if you don't have the money, you have to at least work hard.
Se Bang, I will bring the dumpling soup for you.
Do you want some steamed dumplings, too? You like those, right?
Yes, please.
We may not have enough.
I can't wait to taste the dumplings.
Please give some to Gab Dol.
I will. This is too much.
Se Bang, have some more.
I made those. I can eat more.
I forgot the steamed dumplings.
You saved some for Dal Pa, right?
Yes. I saved some for him.
It's delicious.
Here you go.
The soup is delicious, too.
Now that you've been formally introduced, be like brothers.
- Yes. - Yes.
If you have any problems, come to me. Consider me your brother.
We have to get along. That'll make them happy.
Okay.
Anyway, who's going to have a baby first?
Will it be you, Se Bang, or Gab Dol?
- I will. - No, I should.
We can do it, right?
Just eat your dumplings.
Se Bang, here.
Your dumplings are the best.
Don't flatter me. I'm glad you like them.
Mother, can I have some more dumplings?
I should have made some more.
I made a lot of them.
If you didn't steam them, there would have been plenty for everyone.
There's one with the torn skin.
Give me your bowl. Eat this one. Here.
Kimchi is good, too.
So is the fresh kimchi.
What's wrong? Didn't you enjoy the dumplings?
I'm mad because of the unfair treatment.
What's your problem?
Are you arguing again?
No, Mother.
Follow me.
Tell me. What was so unfair?
What's wrong with your family?
You're at it again. What's wrong with my family?
You always criticise my mother.
Why are you mad?
Does your family enjoy embarrassing me?
Must they make me feel bad about having a fixed income?
Doe he have to give spending money...
in front of me, so that I would look bad?
Is it wrong for him to give her spending money?
You should feel bad about not giving, not criticise him for it.
Furthermore, he gave the money. What did my mum do?
Do you think I don't have anything to say to you?
Did you see Se Bang giving my sister a full set of diamonds?
Did you feel anything?
How should I feel?
Didn't you know about my financial situation?
I'm a public official.
I have a limited income. What can I do?
Why didn't you meet someone like him from the beginning, Gold Digger?
What?
As soon as you saw those diamonds, you were slobbering all over it.
You couldn't control yourself.
Do you think I was just slobbering?
If you can take care of me like he does Jae Soon, just be quiet.
Well, I worked hard instead.
I put aside my dad's anniversary.
I cleaned your house and made dumplings there.
How could you make me feel so cheap because of some dumplings?
I wasn't going to say this.
I was crying inside when eating those dumplings.
I had only three dumplings in my clear soup.
He got a load of dumplings.
I asked for some more and I was given only the torn ones.
Do I look like a beggar?
You weren't given torn ones.
You were busy eating to pay attention to me.
Do we need to get permission before we have a child?
We're the newly weds. We should have our child earlier.
I can't give this up no matter what.
I would rather speak to a dog than you.
- What? - I just copied what your mum said.
This is all because of you.
That's why women should be wise.
Do you think I'd want to be good to your family when you're like this?
Who told you that? Did she say that?
Yes, it's what Young Ran told me.
She's not even married yet she knows so much and is wise.
I take that back.
Relief Patch.
What were you up to? Did you have dinner?
I ate ages ago. It's late.
What did you eat?
I had a bite of kimchi stew.
You need to eat well.
What do you want to eat? Should I buy you meat?
Do you want some short rib soup?
Relief Patch. I miss you so much.
- Dad. - Where's the relief patch?
- I need to get some relief patch. - Relief patch?
Yes.
Here you go.
That's where it was.
- I missed you. - What?
Why did you come?
I forgot because you were looking for this.
I'll come back later.
We nearly got caught.
Be careful. Don't say strange things.
What strange things?
That you miss me or that you want to be next to me.
Mum.
Stop calling me. I'm not going to work at the restaurant.
I refused but they keep calling me.
What do you need?
I need some relief patch.
I bumped my leg. It hurts.
You're so bothersome.
Buy some yourself and have some in your room.
I heard you laugh just a minute ago.
What are you talking about?
Knock before you enter my room.
Why all of a sudden?
What are you talking about? You should. You're married now.
What does that have to do with knocking?
How about some beer?
I need to sleep early. Go to bed.
I'm a third wheel everywhere.
I told you to go. I need to sleep.
Hello.
Our director's here. Come and say hello.
Thank you for your work.
Working at the warehouse seems to be the toughest job.
Thank you for your hard work.
Please keep up the good work.
If we were discourteous before,
please be understanding.
We didn't know you were the president's grandson.
Don't mind who has power. Please act according to your conviction.
What are these? Who are all these ladies?
Soo Jo's prospective brides.
Is that so?
You won't know.
A woman knows women best.
I know women.
Someone who doesn't live in a room...
has a high school diploma and is kind?
That's not enough.
I thought you would discuss this with me. I'm disappointed.
Since I mean nothing, you don't want me to be a part of this.
Fine.
Leave out the girls who had their pictures edited.
If I'm surprised by their actual faces, I won't be able to sleep.
Also, the girl who made her eyes look bigger and lips smaller.
I need to leave out the ones who should be left out.
You understand, right?
Highlight that.
What are we having for dinner?
(Goodbye)
Goodbye.
Professor. Professor.
- Where are you going? - Let go.
I'm not needed here. I'm leaving.
You have nowhere to go. Why are you like this?
You can do everything on your own. Why did you come to get me?
You told me to butt out of Soo Jo's marriage.
There's no need for me to be here.
Let's go in. Let's go inside and talk.
There's no need for that. I'm leaving.
Come on. Before Soo Jo comes.
These are my bowls.
Here. Look. Did this make you that upset?
Women need to be observed carefully by another woman.
I was going to show you after I saw them first.
They're pretty.
She's pretty as well as her.
They're all pretty.
See. I told you that you wouldn't know.
Are you going to say you're leaving again?
I won't.
Don't tell Soo Jo. He'll get angry.
- Highlight that. - I'll highlight that.
I won't tell him.
He'll get angry at me, too.
Welcome. Please come this way.
I told you we can go to a Chinese restaurant in a hotel.
This place makes the best jjajangmyeon
Do you want jjajangmyeon?
We'll have two bowls of jjajangmyeon.
Do you want Tangsuyuk as well?
I can't eat all that. I'm fine with just jjajangmyeon.
Nothing's eternal.
We don't know how we'll change.
You or I might change our minds.
But before that happens, let's love each other...
and take care of each other.
- You're such a player. - Why?
If there's a contest in making women's hearts flutter, you'll win.
It's because I met you.
I'm not a man who usually says these things. I didn't laugh.
After I met you, I changed a lot.
What are you doing?
- Kiss. - No.
Who cares? Young people these days do it.
On the streets or in the subway. They don't mind.
We're from the Dongsan District Office.
We're on an inspection.
Please give us a second. We're in the middle of cooking.
Please let us finish.
You weren't given dumplings at your in-laws?
What?
You must have been upset.
It must hurt when you're being compared with a rich man.
My mother tries hard not to compare her sons-in-law.
That's why women need to be wise.
You came all this way.
Hello. You must work here.
You know.
You should have called me.
It feels awkward to see each other at work.
We see each other at work.
Since you're here anyway, please have a seat.
You'd better get going.
You wouldn't want to be the third wheel.
I told you we're here for the sanitary checkup.
That's what you say,
but I know you're here to see me.
My goodness.
How about...
I don't think I can ever commit a crime.
They almost got us.
It's too dangerous to hang out in this neighbourhood.
My son is everywhere.
We should go to a different neighbourhood.
I can't do this any more.
When can we stop sneaking around?
I blame my children.
(Cho Rok National University Hospital)
What's wrong? What happened?
Please help me.
I want to get back together with Se Gye.
My mum messed everything up.
I'm sorry I wasn't caring enough.
I should see Se Gye sometime.
What did he say?
He doesn't even let me see him. He doesn't answer my call either.
Please do something.
Grandpa, this is killing me.
Did you come here right after the medical service?
Yes.
Did you not even stop by at home?
No, I wanted to see you.
Don't make such jokes.
It's been a while since I ate here.
What a gentleman.
Try. It'll taste amazing.
It does taste good. It's seasoned perfectly.
I know you like it sour.
I've been thinking about what you said earlier.
Was it a proposal?
What are you talking about? I don't think I said something special.
You said you won't let me see other women.
Didn't you say you'll get jealous if I see other women?
When did I say that?
Come on.
I thought it'd sound cool,
but it doesn't at all when you say it like that.
That's the point though.
It's time to eat naengmyeon.
Oh, no. I flipped it too early.
I don't want to eat that. It looks ugly now.
I'm not cooking for you.
I wonder who that could be.
Who is it?
Goodness.
- Excuse me. - Who are you?
Gosh.
Joong Nyeon, come out.
What is it?
What brings you here?
I apologise for the sudden visit.
I know it's not appropriate, but I had to come.
I thought you wouldn't answer if I called you.
Good to hear that you know that. We have nothing to talk about.
I'm sorry.
Since you're here anyway, please have a seat.
What are you going to talk about?
- Do you want some tea? - No, thank you.
Why don't you have a seat as well?
I'm really sorry.
I should've taken better care of my family.
I was recently too sick to take care of the situation.
We're not interested. Since you're here anyway,
you can say what you have in mind and leave.
I don't want to see your family.
Could you please reconsider for our children's sake?
What do you mean?
Don't you get it? He wants them to get back together.
It's not going to happen. Please leave.
I understand you're hurt. I feel sorry for Se Gye as well.
This time, I'll get them a flat so that they can live alone.
I heard Se Gye volunteers for medical service. It must be tough.
I'm thinking of getting him a hospital business.
A hospital?
We're not interested.
It's a hospital.
They're already over. There's no need to talk more about it.
Please leave.
Please have some pity on the old man's apology.
Could you please reconsider it for the children's sake?
You'd better leave.
- Mal Nyeon. - Yes.
- Flip the pancake. - Okay.
Why did you kick him out just like that?
There's nothing more to listen to.
What else did you want to hear from him?
The reason why they had problems was...
because they were living with the entire family.
If he lets them live alone...
Stop it.
Their marriage isn't registered, but they're a married couple.
It could be better than breaking up.
Enough.
It's tempting that he offered a hospital, isn't it?
You want to take advantage of your son again, don't you?
If possible, why not?
It's better than looking poor.
Think about how desperate he was. He even wants to get him a hospital.
Stop using your son.
I never said this before,
but I have been feeling bad for Se Gye.
I've always been feeling guilty.
It's been always bothering me that we forced him to get married...
when he was so unhappy about it.
I tried to tell myself...
that it's for his own sake.
We should let him live his life.
Stop bothering him.
I just want him to choose the easier way. It's not for myself.
I'm not pretentious any more.
I'm really not.
Humans don't need to eat much.
Do we eat 10 or 20 meals a day?
If you let go of your greed,
you don't need millions of dollars.
You don't need so much money to feed yourself.
You don't need to eat meat every meal.
We need more than just some food to live. We need to wear clothes, too.
As long as you don't wear luxury goods only, it doesn't cost so much.
You need to travel abroad from time to time.
It's not that expensive either.
You think it'd cost a lot, but it's quite cheap these days.
I'm not talking about going on a group tour.
If you want a luxurious vacation, it'll cost quite a lot.
You've never even done it.
I'm saying it doesn't cost so much to live a normal life.
His license won't go away.
He can make money any time he wants.
What a smooth talker.
Why haven't you become a lawyer?
I'm more than just a smooth talker.
I can do everything. I can even cook well.
Just leave...
Se Gye alone. Stop bothering him.
I won't.
Se Gye.
- Are you here to clean? - Yes.
We're in charge of this building.
There is so much to do since spring is coming.
What a happy complaint.
I heard the news.
I heard you're back home.
It must be tough.
You look better than I imagined, though.
I'm actually doing well.
I'm finally relaxed and happy for the first time in a few years.
I'm happy to hear that.
Let's go for a drink sometime. It'll be on me.
You know, I own a business.
I know, Ms Shin.
How's your marriage? Are you doing well with Gab Dol?
I don't know. We argue all the time.
I should get going.
Make a lot of money, Ma'am.
I should get Dal Pa new clothes.
There are so many holes.
Goodness.
What a loud sigh.
Joong Nyeon, I'm worried she might get sick.
You almost got a whole hospital for free.
I have no idea what he has in mind.
I also have no idea what my children think.
Of course, you do. You just don't want to admit it.
- I'm home. - Welcome home.
- Did you have dinner? - Yes, I did.
Don't do it.
He just said, "Don't do it."
What are they talking about?
Someone wants to set up a hospital for you.
Who?
Did you meet Mr Yeo?
What do you think of getting back together with Gong Joo?
He said he'd get you a new flat to live alone...
and even a hospital.
Why did you meet him?
He just visited us without notice.
We couldn't just kick him out.
Please don't meet him again.
Since you're a doctor now,
it'll be better to live with a little pride.
I'm already living with pride.
I'm going to get changed.
Did he kick you out?
Serves you right.
Pick 5 out of 10.
How's this one?
She's pretty.
Take a good look.
What do you think about her besides being pretty?
- She looks smart... - Doesn't she look snobby?
She's disqualified.
What about this one?
She's pretty.
She looks like a nice girl.
She looks pretentious. She's disqualified.
What about her?
It's getting hot all of a sudden.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I'm not.
- Would you like some water? - I don't need any.
What's going on?
I'm so happy that you're here.
Is Gong Joo not home yet?
She's late all the time these days.
I'm waiting for the right moment to talk to her.
Don't scold her. Just watch her.
Where did you go earlier?
That's none of your business.
Did you choose one?
I can't. They're all pretty.
I'm back.
- Welcome back. - You're back.
Come here and have a seat.
I've been hearing that you're working hard.
I'm proud of you.
Isn't Soo Jo great?
So I'd like to propose that you get married early.
- Marriage? - You'll be more stable that way.
You'll be able to focus on work, too.
We looked at a few prospects.
Can you choose your favourites from these?
I'm not going on any blind dates.
- Why not? - Why not?
Are you seeing someone?
He's not. He's never dated anyone before.
He's like me.
Work is busy and I'm not ready to get married yet.
It's coming.
I'll get going. See you next week.
What's this?
- Is he asleep? - He just fell asleep.
Where's Nae Shim?
She left for the supermarket earlier.
I need to talk to you for a second.
Why were you at the police station?
Are you sure the chief of police is your friend?
I told you already.
It's still bothering me.
You said you were closing your business. Did you take care of it?
Yes.
From what I hear,
your investors are planning to sue you for fraud...
and stir up some trouble.
Who said that?
Who is it? Let me meet them.
That's not necessary.
Just tell me the truth.
Father.
I'm Se Bang. What fraud?
I'm focusing on growing my business with investment. What do you mean?
Those people can't wait so they're saying nonsense.
That's your point of view.
You haven't run a business so you don't know, right?
In business,
investments don't always turn into profit right away.
You have to reinvest your capitals and work for it.
It takes time to return the profits to the investors.
Those people are just impatient.
What if you end up in jail again?
You're an ex-convict.
What if you get sentenced again?
- What are you talking about? - When did you...
Who will get sentenced? Who's an ex-convict?
When did you get back?
Are you an ex-convict?
He's not. That's not what we were saying.
- I'm not, Mother. - Tell me the truth.
Have a seat.
Something went wrong with his business before.
He was confined...
for fraud.
Tell me exactly. Does that mean...
he was imprisoned? Is that what it is?
It is.
I knew something was wrong.
We processed Ddol Ee's documents...
when he was in prison.
Yes, Father visited me.
How can you hide it from me?
Tell me.
What were you thinking?
Don't worry. It won't happen again.
When you watch on television, company CEOs serve time.
They're all ex-convicts.
Is that supposed to comfort me?
What if Jae Soon finds out? How can an ex-convict...
Please don't call me an ex-convict. I'm not a petty criminal.
I won't end up in prison any more.
How can you be so sure?
Trust me. I'm not in trouble with the law.
I'll take care of everything.
I don't approve of this marriage.
Mother.
My daughter may be a widow for life,
but I won't make her take care of an ex-convict. There's nothing more.
I don't want Jae Soon to suffer any more.
Do you want her to send you food while you're in prison?
It's much better that she works at the supermarket all her life.
I'm finished. You can leave.
- You know... - You're no different!
Jae Soon made mistakes but did you want to get rid of her so badly?
You should have told me at least.
How could you hide it from me?
It's not his fault.
It's all in the past.
If I end up serving time again,
I'll leave enough to feed Jae Soon for the rest of her life.
That's what rich CEOs do.
I won't make her suffer.
When did you come?
Is there something going on that I don't know about?
Yes, there is.
You can stay for dinner.
I have an urgent meeting to attend.
I'm busy trying to wrap things up before our honeymoon. I'll leave.
Drive safely.
Why is it so quiet?
Is something going on?
No.
Even if I end up serving time again,
I'll leave enough to feed Jae Soon for the rest of her life.
I won't make her suffer.
Where are you going?
What do you think we should do?
Se Gye said no.
Did they convince you over buying him a hospital?
I'm talking about Jae Soon, not Se Gye.
I thought about it.
I thought about her life.
I don't know how she'll be able to survive from now on.
She graduated from college but she has no practical skills.
Nobody will hire her.
You need money to start a business.
She's not outgoing so she won't be able to approach people.
I can see her future.
She's going to work at the supermarket...
and earn just enough to feed herself with her pay.
She'll get old like that.
We won't be healthy forever.
We can barely take care of ourselves.
We can't look after Jae Soon and Ddol Ee all for our lives.
And we can't...
send her to a guy who might go to jail, either.
I'm so upset.
What do you want to do?
What about you?
How about...
telling Jae Soon the truth?
She can decide.
Since she was already looking for excuses,
she'll leave Se Bang.
And she'll make a ridiculous decision to go to see Geum Sik.
With Geum Sik and his children,
she'd probably lead an awful life.
She'd live poorly all her life.
I made a decision.
Let's send her to Se Bang.
He's not going to jail right now.
He said he won't any more.
Even if he does,
he said he'd leave money for Jae Soon.
Just like CEOs of conglomerates.
Se Bang would be better than Geum Sik who is penniless.
At least, Se Bang won't let her starve.
Se Bang is not a person who will live alone.
He'll live with any woman even if it's not Jae Soon.
Then Jae Soon will have no place to go back to.
Since he carries CEO business cards...
and has an imported car,
many women will cling onto him even if he is a swindler.
Let's make him promise that he won't do anything wrong again.
We have no other choice.
All right.
Let's think this is her destiny...
and go with that.
Mum, are you in there?
No, it's me.
Where have you been at this hour?
Weren't you sleeping?
I had a drink with your dad...
at a cart bar.
A cart bar?
Why? Is something wrong?
- No. - Just because.
Now that you're getting married, we were happy.
Since it was bittersweet, we had a drink...
and talked about you when you were young.
Go to sleep.
Gosh.
- Aunt. - What?
Is something going on with Mum and Dad?
They look weird these days and seem to hide something from me.
Whether I know or not, I can't tell you.
What is it?
Though I have a mouth, I said I can't tell you about anything.
I've been through it all.
This is not how I expected my life to be.
- That is Se Gye's room. - Oh my.
Gosh. I'm sleepy.
Hello, Father.
Where are you now?
I'm outside because I have a meeting.
Let's meet for a moment.
Can you promise that it won't happen again?
You can trust me.
If you get investigated, you can sense something.
- Investigated? - Did you get investigated?
You said you won't get investigated.
I got investigated as a witness.
You can start as a witness but may change to a defendant later.
It will never happen. I'm an expert in this.
The laws are not something you can manipulate easily.
I will be absolutely safe.
You should not take others' money easily...
or borrow too often.
If you borrow money easily,
you'll consider money in other people's pockets as yours.
I don't borrow tiny amounts of money...
but I receive investment.
Are you sure you can keep your promise before?
You said, no matter what happens,
you'd leave money for Jae Soon to use for her life.
Sure, I will.
The apartment you bought recently...
If you get married, can you...
What was it? Changing the name of the owner.
I don't remember words these days.
- Nominal transfer. - Right. Nominal transfer.
Can you do that for her?
Yes, I'll do that.
Nae Shim...
can't sleep because she is so worried.
Please make sure...
not to let that happen again.
All right. I will.
Do you want me to teach you how to make your mother-in-law love you?
Do you know how to do that?
Dal Pa. Dal Pa.
Take this with you. You left your phone at home.
It is still cold.
Keep yourself warm.
Severe cold is going around nowadays.
It's okay.
You should block cold wind.
I said, it's okay.
My goodness. Why are you here again?
I told you not to come.
Who is that?
No one.
Do you meet such a young kid like him?
You are talking nonsense. He's not someone like that.
You looked helpless in front of that young guy.
He is my nephew.
He's my brother's son.
Then why are you intimidated by him?
Did you borrow money from him? How much is it?
- I'll pay it off. - Never mind.
Considering how you look,
you don't seem to have even 100 dollars with you.
We are finished.
Never come to see me again. Okay?
What do you mean, we are finished?
We are starting from now.
I'm going to see your brother and say hello today.
Are you crazy? What are you going to see him for?
You mean nothing to me.
Disappear quickly before anyone sees you.
What if someone sees me?
Why can't you say that I'm your man?
You saw dramas too much.
Don't ever come to see me.
Sweetheart, let's begin again.
I'll take responsibility for you.
You're saying ridiculous things.
Whom do you think you can take responsibility for?
I have so many men other than you.
I've never run out of men.
You may not have gotten married because you couldn't forget me...
but I got married so many times that my family register is full.
And I've had dozens of men around me.
I can't even count exactly how many there were.
So please forget someone like me.
Gosh. It's my brother.
Go quickly.
Wait.
- Is there nobody home? - No.
I made fried rice with leftovers. Have some.
You should also forget all about her and live on your own.
You met her once and that's enough, isn't it?
Never mind.
I could even risk my life on her.
You have only one life.
You don't know anything about love because you haven't loved anybody.
That's how love should be.
You can risk all your life on it.
That's what you can call love.
I think Mal Nyeon didn't meet any other men...
because she liked me.
Although she says harsh words to me,
I know she is just lying.
I know her very well since I met her for as long as three months.
You met her only for three months.
You didn't expect she'd betray you.
Even after she got married, she got divorced immediately because of me.
Now, I should take responsibility for her as a man.
You must be living together with Si Nae like a married couple.
It's not like that. We've grown apart.
Si Nae and I are only thinking about Soo Jo.
Don't be like me and regret later.
Grab her while you have the chance.
Si Nae likes you, too.
How?
Go into her room and...
grab her.
You rotten...
Why you!
- Look! - What?
Why you rotten scoundrel!
What is this?
Open it later. I'll be leaving now.
- What could this be? - Isn't it money?
Is it?
Of course, it's not money.
My goodness.
Mother.
It's me, Gab Dol,
who can't even give you spending money or nice gifts.
I will work hard to take care of Gab Soon...
and our unborn baby well in the future.
I may not have much money,
but if you're sick, I will be by your side taking care of you.
If you want to go somewhere, I will take you.
If you crave for something, I will go and get it for you.
I promise you 3,000 percent.
I will be good to you from now and forever.
I will be a good son-in-law.
Even if it's just empty promises, I'm thankful.
What are you reading?
Read it. It's a love letter from my son-in-law.
- Gab Dol did that? - Yes.
He must be sad that he can't be more generous.
I really appreciate his thoughts.
I feel like I got a love letter.
You must be happy.
When we make a lot of money, we'll give you a lot of spending money.
We won't put it in an envelope. We'll put it in a big sack.
Bye, Mum.
I'm home.
You're the best. I love you.
My mum was deeply moved by your letter.
She said that she felt like receiving a love letter.
I love you so much. How did you come up with the idea?
- Young Ran told... - What?
It's nothing.
Be honest. Did Young Ran tell you to do it?
No way. I'm going to wash up.
Stop the car, please.
Are you going somewhere?
No, I'm coming back from the US.
The US?
I had to go for housing...
and the school for my children.
I see.
Did you have the wedding?
It's this Saturday.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry.
I will be going now.
Wait.
Well...
I don't know what to say.
Anyway, congratulations.
Hold my hand just one last time.
Be happy.
You, too.
Hello.
Do we still have a reason to meet?
I have something to tell you. Please sit down.
I ordered my favourite drink.
This one's on me.
You don't have to do this. I know your financial situation.
It's on me. I'm celebrating my upcoming wedding.
I'm not a patient man.
Tell me what you have to say.
I would like to apologise first.
I am sorry about our incident at the bar.
Also, I'm sorry about lying.
Lying?
I said things out of anger.
Honestly,
Jae Soon has never liked me.
She pretended to because of the debt and Ddol Ee.
We got married purely for financial reasons.
She's never warmed up to me.
Why did you live with her?
I got remarried purely for my children, too.
I needed someone to take care of my household.
We used each other for good reasons.
Why are you telling me this?
I felt bad after telling you that lie.
Although we met under bad circumstances,
I realise you are a real man...
who can take care of things.
I felt bad that I treated you...
in such a way. I feel ashamed.
I guess you are not a petty man...
that I once thought you were.
You can admit your mistakes.
We could have been good friends.
Since I'm older, I would be a big brother to you.
Next time we meet, let's get along better,
Geum Sik.
Let's do it.
She's harassing me.
I'm not going on any blind dates.
If you're not happy with the girl, you don't have to see her again.
You never know whom you're going to meet.
Look at me. I met your mum to defraud her...
and she found you.
Soo Jo.
Fine.
He said yes. He agreed to it.
He did?
See you tomorrow outside of work.
I'll buy something nice.
Where?
Park at noon.
Can you call me a chauffeur?
Sure, Sir.
Can I request a chauffeur? We're at...
I'm almost here.
Hello. Did you request a chauffeur?
Yes. The car's at the front.
Okay, thank you.
The chauffeur has arrived. She's out at the front.
Thank you.
Hello, Sir. Where would you like to go?