(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 47)
Hello, Sir. Where would you like to go?
Tell me one thing.
- Why did you run away? - It's because...
I can't pay that money back.
Did you intend to deceive me from the beginning?
Tell me!
No.
I didn't intend to deceive you.
Seeing the money made me insane.
I've never touched such big money.
I didn't have time to think about you. I wanted to live first.
I can barely afford my living by working all month.
Even if I don't go to a movie or buy myself a cup of coffee,
I can't save up that much money.
The cake you gave me was the first cake I ever tasted.
I was going to pay off my debt with the 30,000 dollars.
However, with that money,
I could go to a small suburb...
and open up a small store.
That's what popped up in my head.
Then why didn't you go?
I paid off my debt.
I got caught even before I ran away.
Hit me. Hit me until your rage is gone.
I deserve to be beaten up.
You should have told me.
I don't even know your number.
I was shivering like a dog all day long in front of the park.
You shouldn't play with my heart.
I'll pay back the money no matter what it takes.
I don't need it.
That petty 30,000 dollars.
Take it and don't come around again.
I don't want to bump into someone like you ever again.
I didn't mean to deceive you. Trust me.
I had my reason.
What reason?
In fact, I...
Hello?
What's wrong?
What? Hospital?
All right, I'll be right there.
Oh, dear! My goodness!
Taxi!
- Ma'am! - Ji Ha.
What happened? What's the matter with my babies?
I don't know.
I was giving them formula but they kept vomiting.
Doctor, what is wrong?
Will they be all right?
I think it's acute indigestion. I'll take a look for a while.
Since you're here, I'll get going.
I left the other kids alone.
Go ahead. Thank you.
First, pat on their backs so they can burp.
Mommy's here.
Dad, do the same thing.
You can do it gently.
I guess your husband doesn't usually help you.
Well... No...
Your call is being forwarded to a voicemail system...
He's not picking up.
They said he got off work much earlier. I wonder if something's up.
This has never happened before. It's strange.
You must be surprised.
About the reason I mentioned earlier...
I don't have to explain that, right?
This is who I am.
I don't know why I keep owing you...
since we first met.
I guess you owed me in our past lives.
You were the first person who believed in me.
I knew how things were for you.
I know how you must've gotten such a large sum of money.
You must've saved money while you gave up...
eating or buying nice things.
I'll make sure I pay you back...
such valuable money.
Please give me some time.
- I'm home. - You're late.
Where have you been? You didn't answer your phone.
Is everything okay?
I'm not a child.
I have things to do privately.
You're still a child to me.
Have you had dinner? Should I set the table?
I ate.
- I'll go upstairs. - Okay.
He seems to be fine. You should go to bed now.
I envy you.
I want to stroke his face like you do.
Have Se Bang's property under your name...
and save some money for yourself.
You should have some spare money.
You used to have no money for yourself.
Don't live like that any more.
You never know what's going to happen.
What are you talking about?
You know how it is to run your own business.
Something might go wrong or you may get involved in a bad incident.
I would leave him, then.
I'm not going to stay with him if it's too hard for me.
My gosh.
You were married to him once. You don't have to try to impress him...
with these things.
Aunt.
Hey.
Don't divorce him again and marry someone else.
Have a happy life with him.
Watch your words.
I'm already being careful with my words.
If I say what I really want to say, it's going to hurt...
many people including Jae Soon.
What is she talking about?
Don't mind her. She always spoils the mood with her words.
Do you have to do that to your niece who is getting married soon?
I really hate you.
Aunt. After I get married, it'll be just you and Mum,
so be good to her.
She's been worried about you her whole life. Don't you feel bad?
My gosh. Are you lecturing me now?
Be careful if you don't want to be lectured by your niece.
Mum practically raised Dal Pa, and you're still living in her house.
How could you be so shameless?
You two are ganging up on me.
You're the one who said unnecessary things.
If you give Mum a hard time, I won't stand it.
Your mouth always causes trouble.
Get up.
Isn't that too much?
What did I do?
You know my mum gets stressed by Aunt.
Even so, she's older than you.
Don't be so rude to her.
Your mum deserved it. You can't blame us for this.
That's enough, Aunt.
Goodness. Listen to him.
He said, "That's enough."
He didn't seem to care about her, but he's siding with her now.
Who does he think raised him?
They say you shouldn't raise someone else's child.
This is exactly why.
Stay here for a while and go back in when Aunt is less angry.
Okay.
Watch your words from now on.
Watch out for cars and don't skip meals.
Is he really your nephew?
Why did you come here again?
You didn't give me your number.
I had no choice but to come.
My neck hurts from looking up at your window for so long.
Is he really your nephew?
Aren't you dating him?
I told you I have nothing to say to you.
Let's go somewhere and talk.
Let me go.
I'll go straight to the office.
Let me go! I have nothing to say to you!
Come with me.
I said, let me go!
Hey!
That jerk.
Gosh, let go of me!
No! Don't hit him, Dal Pa!
He might ask you for money if you hit him.
He's not even worth punching.
What were you doing? Who are you?
Hurry up and go.
Hi. You're Mal Nyeon's nephew.
I'm not a bad man.
Just go.
See you again soon.
Who is he?
Nobody.
Why does he think I'm your nephew?
Do you still do this with men?
My name is Shin Joong Nyeon. I'm 64 years old.
I retired from work...
about six years ago.
If you're a middle-aged man,
you have to take care of your own meals. If you don't,
your wife will nag you.
It's hard for you to be working in your 60s.
If you don't want to be kicked out of the house,
take care of your own meals and do the dishes afterwards.
That's enough to make your wife happy.
It doesn't make you less of a man to hang around in the kitchen.
If it does, that's too bad.
From my experience,
kimchi fried rice is the easiest one to make.
You'll need kimchi, rice, ham...
and a frying pan. That's all.
First of all,
please cut...
the kimchi.
My goodness.
This is why I placed a plastic cover on the floor.
I spilled it before,
and it was so tiresome to clean it.
Also, when you open the ham,
focus on the sense of your hands.
Open it at once.
Like this.
Gosh, I was worried that I might make a mistake.
I once dropped the ham on the floor while shaking it to get it out.
Just take a knife...
and get it out like this.
Here it is.
It's so easy, right?
Dal Pa. Dal Pa!
What is it, Uncle?
Can you upload this? I made a video,
but it's hard to upload it.
Right now?
You gave steamed ones to Se Bang but torn ones to Gab Dol.
Don't treat them differently, Mum. It upset Gab Dol.
See? You're glad you listened to me, right?
Thank you.
You're not married, but you're good at this.
Feel free to ask me any questions.
Thank you.
Hi, Mother.
In the evening?
Okay.
What are you doing? Are you making dumplings again?
Yes. Someone didn't have enough dumplings.
- Who? - Just someone.
Don't you have to pack for the honeymoon?
You're right.
Mr Jeon. You can't go somewhere far for a while.
I'm going to Hawaii.
You can't leave the country.
Stay put until we resolve this matter.
I'm just a testifier. Why do you keep calling me here? My gosh.
Se Bang.
Se Bang!
(Seoul Police Station)
- Did you finish packing? - Almost.
I wish I could go to Hawaii wearing something like this.
I'm worried about Ddol Ee.
I'm babysitting him, not a stranger. Don't you trust me?
Try to enjoy your time there.
I feel bad for you.
We'll take you and Dad next time.
I have to move my things to our new house.
I'll make Gab Dol do it...
while you are on your honeymoon.
Where were you? You didn't pick up your phone.
I was in the middle of a meeting.
We were packing for the honeymoon.
- Have you finished packing? - Sorry?
Yes, I have.
Can you fix me some lunch?
You haven't eaten yet?
I was busy with my meeting.
Can we delay...
our honeymoon a little bit?
We already paid for our flight ticket and hotel.
Is something wrong?
There's something urgent at work.
What is it?
You won't know.
I think they need me.
- Do you want to go by yourself? - What?
Let's go next month...
when work situation gets better. Okay?
We're moving our honeymoon to next month.
Why?
He must be busy at work.
I packed for no reason.
You can leave it and take it after.
They delayed their honeymoon.
Do you think something's going on?
Ask Se Bang when he's done eating.
I heard you delayed your honeymoon.
Is something going on?
There's an urgent matter at work.
They need me.
Why were you at the police station earlier?
Sorry?
I saw you leaving. Be honest.
You went last time, too.
Are you sure you're friends with the chief of police?
It's nothing serious.
Somebody got involved so I had to verify a few things.
Who got involved?
It's not me. It was somebody else. Don't worry.
It's nothing serious. It has nothing to do with me.
Don't go to the police station for something that doesn't involve you.
You were at the police station?
I was there because somebody I knew got into trouble.
I had to verify something for them.
Honey, let's go for groceries.
The fridge is empty.
Let's get things to bring to the States. You can choose.
Can I buy snacks?
Of course. Don't buy too many. Pick a few.
Can I get some as well?
It's Ms Shin.
Let's go that way.
Ms Shin.
What brings you here?
I wanted to say bye to you.
We're leaving for the States.
I heard.
I saw you earlier at the grocery store.
We were getting things to bring with us to the States.
Are you not seeing my dad any more?
When are you leaving?
This weekend.
Listen to your dad...
and take good care of your sister.
Take care.
I hope you make a lot of friends.
Ms Shin.
Can you be our mum?
Once we get back and if you end up dating my dad again,
please be our mum.
Take care.
What's all this?
Weren't you disappointed last time?
You made dumplings...
and I only gave you the ruined ones.
Pick whatever you'd like.
I made steamed dumplings, fried ones and dumpling soup.
Do you want boiled dumplings as well?
- Mother. - Go ahead.
Thank you for the food.
Which one should I eat?
Let's pick one
This one. The fried dumplings.
- You chose fried dumplings? - I did.
- Is it good? - Yes.
Se Bang was getting remarried to Jae Soon...
so I made him dumplings. I wanted them to...
get along and be happy together.
You're supposed to do that even if you don't like them.
And you fed me torn ones since you like me?
Of course. We get along just fine.
I've known you for decades.
I'm not close with Se Bang.
I'm much closer to you.
I treat Se Bang like a visitor and I treat you like family.
Think about it.
If you argued with him, whose side would I take?
Should I argue with him?
Go ahead. Can you be better than him?
I can if you're on my side.
Keep eating.
I added more meat than I did last time.
It's so good.
That's what I was waiting for.
There you go.
Mum.
- Mum. - Stop calling me.
What's wrong? I was in a good mood.
Your in-laws don't even feed you dumplings.
Why are you so happy?
How did you know about that?
What?
I heard.
From whom?
I'm not sure. Who was it?
I see. It must be Gab Soon.
Do you know how awesome I am?
My mother-in-law fed me fried dumplings, steamed dumplings...
and dumpling soup. The table was full.
She said Se Bang is a visitor but I'm family.
I'm the best son-in-law.
You must be proud of yourself.
There are only two sons-in-law. You're either first or last.
It's nothing special. You were convinced over dumplings.
It's not just dumplings.
Mother made it especially for me. It was just for me.
What kind of a son-in-law gets treated like me?
What a fool.
She's feeding you so that she can boss you around.
She's not like that.
She's not your mother. She's your mother-in-law.
Don't call her Mother in front of me. She's not your mother.
What's wrong with you?
You're my mum and she's my mother.
Be wise about it.
Why do you let your in-laws treat you so poorly?
Don't act so frivolously or joke all the time.
Be more reserved.
They boss you around and make you clean and make dumplings.
You're just an errand boy to them.
They'll treat you properly only if you act maturely.
I never made you clean...
or wash the dishes. I raised you so well...
and you get treated like a servant at your in-laws?
Who called me a servant?
You have no idea.
I'm not talking to you.
My gosh. I'm sick of this.
Are you asleep, Dad?
No. Aren't you asleep yet?
I can't fall asleep.
I met Ms Shin earlier.
- What for? - Just in case.
I asked her if she could date you again...
once we come back from the States.
I guess not.
Ms Shin, please be our mum.
I wonder if something's happened.
She says it's nothing special.
Should we tell Jae Soon...
about Se Bang's criminal record...
and ask her what she thinks?
That's not going to change anything.
I just hope that the same thing will not happen again.
It better not.
Most importantly,
I want Jae Soon to stop suffering.
She's been the good daughter who did everything we told her to.
She readily obeyed us.
She didn't even touch food before we told her to eat.
How could she be ill-fated and get married three times?
I think it's my fault.
I should've kept her longer when she came home after her divorce.
I shouldn't have married her off so quickly.
It's already in the past.
Live long.
You must live long to protect your kids.
I can't do it alone.
You're still up?
Weren't you sleeping?
Why are you so surprised?
I thought you must be sleeping.
Are you hiding something from me?
What are you talking about?
Are you hiding something from her?
No.
We were getting some drinks because your mum couldn't sleep.
I like how Se Bang has changed a lot from before,
but since he's a business man, I was worried...
if he'd be out all the time.
Since your wedding's coming up,
various thoughts come across my mind.
I wouldn't just sit back if that happens.
I'm not like how I was before. I don't tolerate such things.
That's right. Don't tolerate.
This time, you should whip him...
instead of being silent like before.
It all depends on you.
Have fun.
If you don't like the girl, reject her whenever you want.
I'll be going now.
We're not hiring.
Consider that things are already over between you and him.
I can't do that.
Relationships don't work...
simply because one likes another.
What should I do then?
There's no need to cry.
That's why I told you to study abroad.
You can get over him soon if you study abroad.
He didn't treat you well anyway.
He often lied because he couldn't get over her.
I don't see why you still like him.
Simply put, she's deeply lost in love with him.
You can't help it if you're lost in love.
That's right.
She's in love with the wrong person.
Stop crying and bring medicine for your grandpa.
You're not even interested in me, are you?
All you do is care about Mr Geum and that guy.
You brat.
How could you call your brother so?
Don't be so harsh on her.
I'm being harsh on purpose.
I've been too easy on her so far.
Look at Soo Jo. He was brought up in a poor family,
but he grew up so well.
(Cho Rok National University Hospital)
This is the coffee from your favourite coffee shop.
It smelled so nice.
You even got doughnuts.
Did you come here because of this?
Compared to your side dishes, this is nothing.
Jae Soon wants you to come to her wedding, too.
To her wedding?
You can come freely. In exchange,
you'll have to be prepared.
All my relatives will be there, so you should greet them...
that you'll be the daughter-in-law.
Seriously, I told you not to make weird jokes.
I'm not kidding.
You said you can't marry me off to another woman.
You should come to the wedding and make yourself...
officially known to all my family and relatives.
You.
Man Joo.
I've got a conscience.
I got married as I pleased.
Asking you now...
wouldn't be right.
I don't deserve to love you.
- It's you, right? - Excuse me?
Incredible!
Both the sound and the colour are amazing.
It smells even better. It's sad that I can't deliver that.
You live until 100 now. Life can't be over at the first chapter.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
You should prepare for the second and the third chapters.
Start from making kimchi fried rice.
Oh my.
"Oh my."
This is you, right? How incredible!
Do you live in this building? I live here, too.
It's an honour to meet you, Mr Shin Joong Nyeon.
Let's take a selfie.
- A selfie? - In 1, 2, 3.
There's nothing wrong with my age
Did something happen?
Why are you so... Did you pick money or something?
Incredible.
Did something good happen?
A woman he saw for the first time smiled at him.
This is really incredible.
It was only recent when I posted it, but he recognised me so soon.
I even took a selfie with him.
Becoming a star isn't that hard.
You must be careful with that.
Once your profile is out, you can't go back.
I'm not doing something wrong.
What are you talking about?
You always ruin my feelings.
I'm just worried that something might happen.
Be careful just in case something happens later on.
Many people end up struggling.
What is it about?
You don't have to know.
He came home all excited. What is it?
You were rejected? Why would you be rejected?
That's impossible and unbelievable.
That's what happened. I'll go upstairs.
That doesn't make any sense. Let me ask.
I told her to highlight it. Why didn't she do it?
I've been rejected. Asking why would be even more embarrassing.
Soo Jo is right about that.
Still, let's find out the reason.
I'm too tall so her neck hurts to see me.
My goodness.
I stretched his neck when he was young.
Don't worry. I've already set up the next candidate for you.
She kicked away her good fortune...
by not appreciating Soo Jo.
Are you sure that you were rejected?
I am.
Why does a rejected guy look so calm?
Should I break down in tears then?
I better not be rejected next time.
I need to reduce my height.
It's strange.
(Director Yeo Si Nae)
Yes?
It's last week's sales and design reports.
Thanks.
It's very detailed.
I have something to discuss with you.
What is it? Tell me.
I'm scared to bump into my son again.
He won't come here to a different district.
Dating secretly makes me so nervous.
But it's fun and thrilling.
Shall we get some ice cream, too?
Let's do everything we want and not hold back.
- I'll go buy some. - I'll come with you.
No, just wait here.
I'll get them really quickly.
(Supermarket)
- Dad! - What?
Why are you here? You said you had a meeting.
The meeting just ended.
- Get in. - No, I'll walk home.
It's too far. You might catch a cold.
- Get in. - I'll take the bus.
Come on.
You had the meeting in a hotel.
What? Yes.
Chairman Kim dropped me off there on his way home.
Mean, old jerk.
(Relief Patch)
Aren't you going to answer that?
No. It's just a spam.
(Reject)
- Let's go faster. - Why?
I need to go to the bathroom.
You're going to fall.
What happened? Why didn't you answer the phone?
The battery died.
Relief Patch, where are you?
I had two ice creams and was shivering in the cold.
I just came home.
Gosh, I'm so cold.
What happened?
I came home because I had to use the bathroom.
Bathroom?
Yes.
I had a stomachache all of a sudden. I'm sorry.
Whatever.
Don't get upset. I'll go crazy if you do.
We have no time to get upset.
You should've told me at least.
I'm going to scold you.
Please do. I want to get scolded.
You're so mean.
- Who is it? - It's me.
Soo Jo?
I got formula and diapers for the twins.
Goodness. Why did you buy so much?
You should save money.
Peekaboo.
They're sleeping.
- Are they okay now? - Yes. They don't throw up any more.
- What are their names? - Il Ho and Ee Ho.
This is Il Ho and that is Ee Ho.
If you're making noodles, make mine, too.
Okay.
I only have one.
I'll go buy some.
Here, take the money.
I can cook noodles better than you.
Then cook it next time and show me how good you are.
Sure.
You know what? You're a spendthrift.
You'll go bankrupt if you spend more than what you have.
Why did you buy a whole box?
Don't waste your money.
I'm grateful...
for the formula and diapers, but I feel uncomfortable.
I know you're broke.
You've never bought a box of noodles before?
Never. You're rich if you can do that.
I've said the same thing before.
Be frugal. You can't save money if you spend it like that.
You'll have to get married.
Women don't like men with no money.
Since you're handsome, women will flock if you have money.
Hello?
Yes, I'm Ban Ji Ha.
What? Really?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Did you win the lottery?
I'll start working at a design office next week.
The secretary just called me.
They want me to start working next week. Goodness.
I think I can pay you back.
It's a contract job, but this is great.
Are you happy?
Of course. I can finally achieve my dream.
You probably don't understand how I feel.
I guess the manager put in a good word. He always nagged at me.
Wait. Was it the director?
Whoever it was, congratulations.
We'll be seeing each other often, right?
I quit working at the warehouse.
That's right. You're a chauffeur now, right?
A chauffeur?
That car was your boss' car, wasn't it?
Yes... That's right.
By the way, you look different.
You look nicer.
Did you steal your boss' clothes?
No.
They told me to wear nice clothes for the boss.
Don't drive his car secretly.
You'll get fired if you get caught.
Don't get superficial. Save up as much as you can.
I'm so happy.
What are you doing?
The noodles got too soft.
You're wasting food. It'll still taste delicious.
I make it go soft when I'm hungry.
That way, there's more to eat.
(Seoul Police Station)
Mr Jeon!
Now, we're husband and wife. You know that, right?
There's no turning back.
I heard you made Gab Dol dumplings.
He bragged about how you made so many different ones.
He would've cried if I didn't.
He ate so much because he couldn't last time.
You're the best.
- You're here. - Hi. Congratulations.
I came here to have dinner and talk with you.
- Good. - Won't you get a facial?
She went to the sauna and took a bath.
It's not sparkly Gab Soon...
but it's sparkly Jae Soon.
You really do glow.
Let me see. It's so beautiful.
This reminds me of that movie.
Was it called "Lust, Caution"?
There's a scene where the female actress gets a ring.
It's a huge, pink diamond.
That's right. I watched it in the theatre...
and when that scene came on, all the girls were in awe.
I would be like that, too.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof.
- Whatever. - It's true.
Nobody ever gave you a ring.
None of that was worth it.
Every woman deserves one of these.
It's too late for you or me.
I'll get myself one.
I don't expect one from a man.
It's not the same.
You're supposed to get this from a man.
It's true.
I don't need it. I get Gab Dol's pension.
You're a clever girl.
When are you going to raise Dal Pa's wage?
Why are you bringing that up?
I will when it's time.
Yes, Dal Pa.
What?
What happened?
I went to clean the building...
we made contract with and somebody else was cleaning already.
Does this make any sense?
I wanted to speak to their manager but they refused.
I'm sorry, Ms Shin.
We were going to sign with you,
but our boss had already signed with some other company.
We gave you three free services. You can't do this.
We already made contracts with our cleaners.
We already paid the deposits. You can't do this.
You received our service as if you were going to sign with us.
This isn't fair.
It's not up to me.
Once this contract is done, we'll talk again.
Let me talk to your boss.
We'll explain and talk to him.
The contract's been done so we can't do anything.
Let's go.
What now? We lost money.
I don't feel like doing this any more.
We should have signed the contract first.
We should have known when they waited on it.
Do you want a drink? It's on me.
You don't even have money.
Let's go clean.
Let's take today off. I'm not in the mood to clean.
It won't make a difference to take a day off.
Go home and get some rest.
We'll sign first next time.
I'm home.
That was close.
You're back.
Move over.
- Let me finish. - We have to clean and sleep.
Do you have to eat in bed?
Stop nagging.
What's wrong with you?
Do some house chores when you get back from work.
You didn't do the dishes or collect laundry.
Do you have to play games?
I just started.
I was trying to release some stress by playing games.
- I had a rough day. - So did I.
It's tough dealing with people.
You always make it sound like you're the only one making money.
If I was unemployed, it would have been much worse.
That's not what I meant.
If you come home first, you can do some house chores.
You don't have to react this way.
You keep nagging.
I can't even play games.
Stop playing dumb.
Tell us properly. We'll be done faster that way.
I don't know about it.
Give me a second.
Yes.
Why weren't you picking up? Where are you?
Did you call me? I'm in the office.
The office?
I had to take care of a few things.
What is it?
Were you worried that I'm up to no good?
It's fine.
See you tomorrow.
We're a married couple from tomorrow.
Goodnight.
Hurry up, Mr Jeon.
Who's that?
Sorry, it's the television.
Go to bed.
Okay. Talk to you later.
What kind of fate is this?
You're marrying the same man twice.
How do you feel?
I'm...
going to accept it as my fate.
You won't have to suffer because of money any more.
It's the end of your suffering. It's a happy beginning.
Let's go to bed.
You have to put make up on so that people don't think you're old.
Don't worry, Mum. I'll be happy.
You have to be.
You're my first child...
so I worry about everything you do.
I'm worried that people won't treat you right.
They do.
I'm so bold now.
Things will work out.
You're the oldest child of this family.
What are you doing, Mal Nyeon?
Oh, gosh.
Don't rush me.
Are you the bride? Don't dress up so much.
All right. Let's go.
All right.
You're so pretty.
Mr Jeon.
What's the problem? I already gave you my statement.
You said I'm only a testifier.
Jeon Se Bang,
you've officially become the suspect. You're under arrest.
- Hey! - Stop him!
Get off of me! Get off!
- Don't move! - No!
Let me go. Let me go!
Jeon Se Bang.
We're arresting you under the charge of fraud.
You may have an attorney,
and you have the right to remain silent.
I must say goodbye to you now.
Okay. I'm sad that you're leaving, but I'll see you after three years.
It's not too late for you to change your mind and stay.
We can always have video conferences.
If there is something I have to do, please contact me.
Please take care. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
To the airport, please.
A Young. Are you on your way?
No? Why?
Da Rong can't find her toy.
We're still looking for it.
We'll be there soon.
Tell her I'll buy her a new one.
You should leave right away. I'm on my way to the airport now.
Can we...
make a quick stop?
Who among his family is presiding over the wedding?
His parents passed away, so no one is.
Did Young Ran come?
Why would she come?
To see me.
I thought we could eat together.
Whom should I eat with then?
You can eat with me.
You'd better be a good host today.
Don't worry. Emceeing weddings is my speciality.
But strangely,
couples who had me as the host always got divorced.
- You should be careful, too. - You punk.
Jae Soon.
Dad wanted me to give you this.
Flying birds never look back.
Forget about the past...
and have a fun life.
I'm so sorry that...
there isn't much I can do for you.
I love you, my first daughter.
Don't cry.
Your make up will smudge.
Thank you.
Why isn't Se Bang here yet? The ceremony will start soon.
- I know. - Call him.
- He's not picking up. - He's not?
Do you want to change?
No, thank you.
Would you like some ox bone soup?
I'm fine.
You called an attorney, right?
Can I make a phone call?
(Se Bang)
Se Bang. What's going on?
- I'm not Se Bang. - Hello?
Isn't this Se Bang's phone?
Mr Jeon can't talk right now.
What?
Did he get into some kind of an accident?
Not exactly. Please hold on.
Father.
Se Bang. What's going on?
Why did he say you can't talk?
Where are you? You should be here by now.
I don't think I can marry Jae Soon today.
We'll set another date soon.
My goodness.
Tell me the truth. Where are you?
- Where is he? - Where are you?
I'm at a police station.
A police station?
What...
- What did you say? - Joong Nyeon.
Why hasn't the ceremony started yet?
It's supposed to start 20 minutes ago.
Go out and see what's going on.
I'll be right back.
Mum. Why hasn't the ceremony started?
Gab Soon. Please wait outside.
What's wrong?
I don't know what to say.
I don't think you can have the wedding today.
Tell me what is going on.
Se Bang was...
What happened to him?
Tell me already.
He was taken to the police station.
The police station?
He was arrested for fraud.
Jae Soon. Jae Soon!
- Jae Soon. - Jae Soon.
Jae Soon!
Let me explain.
Do you even consider me your family?
I'm your old and useless daughter.
Were you happy to leave me with that criminal...
as if you were taking out trash?
- Jae Soon, it's not that. - Jae Soon.
Don't say a word.
Is that why you wrote me that letter saying...
that you love me and you're sorry?
Now, I see what you meant.
Keep your successful children...
and abandon useless ones like me.
I'd rather kill myself than ask you to do something for me.
Don't you ever look for me again.
From today,
consider me dead.
Jae Soon...
Mum.
Isn't this exciting?
- It'll be so fun, right? - Yes.
I can't wait.
(Our Gab Soon)
Please forgive me, Jae Soon.
Listen to this. It says Jae Soon's number is not in service.
I think she'll sever all contact.
Maybe she went to Geum Sik.
It's an honour to have you back as our president after six months.
I will continue to work hard.
Don't say a thing to Mother.
I'm glad she didn't marry the swindler.
Do you find it that amusing?
How can you talk about it so carelessly?
Introduce yourself. He's the director of our company.
- He's my son. - Hello.
I'm so sorry for being rude. Please understand.
Let's give these flyers out to people.
Dad!
I will find her no matter what.
Where are you, Jae Soon?