(Episode 48)
- What do we do? - Where is Jae Soon?
She just left with her luggage. Didn't you see her leaving?
- What about Ddol Ee? - I'm sure she took him with her.
I brought Ddol Ee with me. She left with him as soon as she came.
I couldn't even talk to her because I was so scared.
Why didn't you make her stay? How could you let her leave?
Why are you blaming my Dal Pa?
What are we going to do?
She has no money and nowhere to go.
Maybe she went to see Geum Sik.
He left for the US.
The US? Why?
He has been sent by his company.
What are we going to do now?
Hello?
Yes, Uncle. I'm so sorry.
Something just came up.
I will explain later.
I am too ashamed to face other relatives.
I am truly sorry.
Yes.
As I told you earlier, I will explain everything later.
What are you so curious about?
Why do you have so many questions?
You were so jealous of my daughter. I'm hanging up now.
I don't want your sesame oil.
The mobile is turned off...
She's not picking up?
After the beep, you will be charged.
She turned it off.
The mobile is turned off, so you will be forward to voice mail.
After the beep, you will be charged.
I told you that she turned it off.
She turned it off a while ago and won't answer.
Why isn't she answering the phone?
She has nowhere to go.
Why would she answer?
She must be so upset right now.
Daddy, I'm thirsty.
Let's go buy water. Cho Rong, come with us.
I will stay here.
Let's go.
Do you want anything to drink?
I'm okay.
- Don't go too far. - Okay.
Daddy.
What is it?
What's bothering you?
Do you have something to tell me?
Tell me what it is.
Do we have to go to the US?
Can we not go there?
How can you say that now that we're here?
You agreed to go. Why are you saying this all of a sudden?
Ms Shin was supposed to get married today.
If she didn't get married,
you can see her again.
Don't be ridiculous.
Daddy.
What is it?
It's nothing.
- This is exciting. - Isn't it?
It gets better when the plane takes off.
Cho Rong.
Let's make the best of the situation.
I'm sorry about getting upset earlier.
They're getting ready.
My stomach hurts.
What's wrong?
Daddy, it's my stomach.
Your stomach hurts? How does it hurt?
What are we going to do?
What's wrong?
Cho Rong has a stomach ache.
We should get off the plane right now.
Let's go to the hospital. Hurry up.
- Get in. - My goodness.
Why does she have to be sick right now?
My goodness.
Geum Sik. Can I go to the US alone?
(Emergency room)
Come on out. Be careful.
Cho Rong, it's all right. It's all right.
Dad, I'm okay now.
- What? - I don't feel sick any more.
- Are you sure? - Yes, I think so.
Can you walk?
Look.
What a relief. I was so worried.
Since you're here anyway, let's get a checkup.
No, I don't need to. I'm totally fine.
You were acting because you don't want to go, weren't you?
I was really sick at the moment.
You...
- What should we do now? - We should buy new tickets.
Let's stay at a hotel tonight.
I know you didn't want to go to the US so much.
Are you sure you weren't acting?
Geum Sik, we're going to the US for sure, right?
Of course, we are. It's about my work.
I'll take you to the hotel and go to the office.
I need to email the US branch. Let's go.
Sir, didn't you go to the US?
I missed the flight. I should leave within this week.
Then could you help me?
- This could be a big problem. - What is it?
It's about the home shopping you're in charge of.
Actually, I've never dealt with home shopping before,
and I made a big mistake.
What? What kind of mistake?
I sent the wrong number of supplies to the factory.
It seems like it'd be hard for the factory to meet the deadline.
We need to have another meeting with the home shopping company,
but I don't know what to do first.
The deadline is soon, isn't it?
It's tomorrow.
This just suddenly happened. It makes me crazy.
Let's go. You drive the car.
Take some medicine and have some sleep.
I'm worried you'll get into trouble as well.
I don't even know if she's dead or alive. I can't hear from her.
She's not going to die. Don't worry.
She doesn't have money, and she's out with a kid on such a cold day.
My goodness.
Mum, here's the medicine.
Mother, cheer up.
She'll be fine.
I mean, Jae Soon.
Gab Dol, could you leave us alone?
Sure.
Mother, cheer up.
Everything will be fine.
Let Gab Dol go home. It's embarrassing.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about. He's our family.
Technically, he's not our family.
I just don't feel comfortable.
I'm sick, and having him around makes me feel uncomfortable.
And it's not like I can tell him to leave.
All right.
Why? It's gloomy in there. I should be here to help.
Leaving is helping.
You don't have anything to do here anyway.
Of course, I do. I can get her some water and do some errands.
If something happens, I'm the helpful one since...
Se Gye is slower than me.
When you're having a hard time, it's good to have many people around you.
I said, it's okay.
It's not about how many people there are.
You'd better leave. I'll follow you later.
All right. I'm hungry anyway.
Right. Don't say anything to your mum.
Fine, I won't. It's not good news anyway.
- Promise me you won't. - I won't.
I'm not a child. I won't say everything to my mum.
- Mum, I'm home. - You're late.
What kind of wedding is so long?
I want to eat.
Why didn't you eat at the wedding?
I was so hungry.
Didn't you say the wedding was held in a hotel?
You were bragging that you're going to have a very expensive meal.
Why didn't you eat anything?
Did they not want you to eat there?
That's not how it was.
Gosh, I'm sure they were like that.
I told you many times.
If you want to be treated well, you should deserve it.
They must've made a slave of you because you look easy.
Was Gab Soon doing nothing while you were mistreated like that?
I should teach her a lesson.
Don't say anything to her. This is not the time for it.
How nice.
I can't even say what I want to say to my daughter-in-law.
How dare they let you starve when they feast on all the food?
How stupid you are. You should've done better.
It's not like you can have such an expensive meal often.
You must've been doing all kinds of errands, trying to impress them.
I don't want to have a son like you.
That's not what happened.
I'm not the only one who didn't eat. The whole wedding was cancelled.
You don't know anything.
I take that back.
The wedding was cancelled? Why? What happened?
My goodness.
Why was it cancelled?
Mum, you didn't hear anything.
What are you hiding from me?
How mean. I can see that you belong to that family now.
- That's not true. - Forget it.
Promise me that you won't tell anyone.
I won't. There's no one I can talk to.
What happened?
So what happened is...
I'm worried we might have to have their funerals.
Watch your mouth.
I said that because they're all just lying down like that.
Please answer your phone.
You don't have any money. What are you going to do?
Send me your account number.
I won't tell anyone.
So please at least text me.
Dad, please have some soup.
- What about your mum? - I'll take care of her.
What have you been doing?
You're the one who needs to stay sharp...
so that we can find that witch.
I'm rather worried about...
Ddol Ee than Jae Soon.
She can put herself in trouble as she's an adult,
but that kid has no idea.
He is forced to suffer.
Dad.
She left because she's upset. Once she's calmed down, she'll return.
There's nowhere she can go with Ddol Ee.
That's right.
I feel bad for Jae Soon.
She always came to...
her parents whenever she divorced.
And now, she's abandoned by her parents.
I would've done the same.
They didn't abandon her.
Se Bang...
I don't even want to call him that. That jerk...
was an ex-convict. There were so many times...
I wanted to say that, but I didn't.
If I knew things were going to be like this, I would've said so.
My goodness.
She was betrayed by her parents.
I bet she wouldn't want to live.
There are reasons why they were like that.
They were worried about her and Ddol Ee.
Then they'd better never worry about them again.
Mal Nyeon.
I didn't become living proof for this.
I didn't know she'd be like this.
I'm home.
I feel so sorry for you.
I can't believe that happened.
Pardon?
Mum, Gab Soon must be tired today. Leave her alone.
All right. Take a good rest.
It must've been tough with the wedding.
I mean,
it must've been tough dealing with the visitors.
You haven't eaten anything, right? Gab Dol also ate a lot.
Do you want me to prepare some food?
No, thank you. I'm all right.
You'd better take some rest now.
Your parents must be very worried.
Mum, aren't you going to sleep?
I mean, it must've been hard to send off their daughter.
You should be nice to them.
It must be really heartbreaking.
It might be rather better than marrying a fraud.
- Gosh. - Well...
It was the slip of the tongue.
I didn't hear that from Gab Dol.
I heard that from someone else.
Don't say anything to him.
You must be hungry. Do you want to eat something? Rice?
- No, thank you. - Then take a good rest.
Ma'am, I'm so sorry. I fell for her tricks.
What's wrong with your mouth? You're unbelievable.
I told you so many times not to tell her.
Are we really a married couple? How could you not keep it for a day?
A married couple should keep each other's secret.
How could you blurt it out like that?
I wasn't going to but my mum kept on prying me about it...
so I had to.
It's my mum's fault. I told her not to say it.
You shouldn't have told her in the first place.
Why don't you just tell all our neighbours?
My mum is not a nobody. She's our family.
When was she our family?
My family and your family are separate.
Did you see Mother's face?
She looked very satisfied.
Why would you think that way?
She was just worried.
It might have sounded like that to you but not to me.
What if all our neighbours find out?
My mum won't do that.
She can keep her mouth shut. She won't tell anybody.
I'm not going to tell you anything from now on.
What did my dad say to you about how a man should be?
I know. You should have deep pockets and sealed mouth.
I won't do it again. I'm sorry.
What is it?
Why are you mad at him?
I was listening.
A son can tell his mum that.
It's about your family so you might want to hide it,
but there are no secrets in this world.
People are ought to find out somehow.
You shouldn't make a big deal about it. He has work tomorrow.
This is all your parents' fault.
They were greedy for money,
so they tried to remarry your sister without looking into the issue.
Please don't talk about it if you don't know what's going on.
My parents are not like that.
What do you mean?
They treated their older son-in-law nicely because he had money...
and looked down on Gab Dol because he doesn't.
They made him clean and make dumplings.
See? He may not have money,
but Gab Dol is sincere.
Stop it.
You should stop too.
Are you that happy about it?
Why are you talking like it's nobody's business?
I didn't talk like that.
Why would you think that way?
It's your parents' fault that this happened to your sister.
What's wrong with you?
If you are not genuinely concerned for me, then just leave it.
I don't know any more.
You two should deal with it.
What are you doing, Young Ran?
I'm so upset.
What am I supposed to do?
First of all, if your wife and your mother are arguing,
take your mother's side.
Gab Soon will be really mad about it later.
When the two of you are alone, take her side.
If you take your wife's side first, your mum will get upset.
You can't do anything about it later on.
So it's wise to take the older person's side in the first place.
Didn't your wife tell you this already?
A wise woman would have done that.
(Incheon Station)
Chew properly.
Where are we going?
We're going to stay here.
The two of us?
Yes, the two of us.
What about Dad?
He left for somewhere.
It's urgent so he couldn't say goodbye.
Did he go far?
Yes, he went far.
What about Mr Jo?
He left as well.
What about Grandpa and Grandma?
They have something going on so we can't visit them for a while.
We have to stay here.
Okay, Mum. You can trust me.
Okay. I'll trust you.
That makes me feel better.
Dad.
Weren't you asleep?
I waited for you.
I wanted to tell you something.
What is it?
(Motel)
(Clean rooms, VIP rooms with large televisions)
Ms Shin's wedding didn't work out properly.
I saw her in front of the police station.
Her wedding dress was ripped apart, and she was crying by herself.
Dad, you should go find her.
She might be looking for you.
What if something went wrong?
I can't sleep properly.
We always hear things on the news.
Stop talking nonsense.
You shouldn't say that about your daughter.
I don't know what she's thinking.
You didn't think Jae Soon would do that either.
We have to find her before she does something.
Once the sun comes up, let's go to the police station.
(Police)
We can't track her location.
I'm trying to look for my daughter. Why is it not possible?
It's against the law.
She's an adult and ran away at her own will.
You don't have to tell us. Can't you just check where she is?
We can't eat or sleep because we're so worried.
It'll kill her.
It's not up to us.
Even if we do know, we can't tell you.
What kind of law is this?
I'm trying to look for my daughter.
Why can't you tell us?
Does this make any sense?
We're just asking you to check...
where she is and if she's alive. Is that too much to ask?
If something happens to her, would you take responsibility?
That's the law, so we can't do anything.
My goodness.
Who cares about the law when I'm looking for my daughter?
Let's go.
(Police)
Welcome.
Sit here for a second.
I'm trying...
to sell this. It's urgent.
I tried on the ring a few times but the rest are brand new.
You're trying to sell this?
- Yes. - This is cubic zirconia.
Sorry?
It's diamond. Have another look.
We're experts. We recognise them.
It's cubic zirconia.
You thought it was diamond?
Did you get it as a gift?
That person wasn't nice.
Keep it as a memory.
(Real estate)
Is there a place that doesn't require a deposit?
It doesn't have to be nice.
Please look into the cheapest place you can find.
What do you think?
This is the only one without a deposit.
The first month's rent must be paid up front.
The heater uses coal, and the bathroom is shared.
I will take it.
The call cannot be completed. You'll be connected to voice mail.
After the beep, you will be charged for the call.
Jae Soon, it's me.
I am sorry about everything.
Wherever you are, just answer the phone.
It's hard enough being alone. You have Ddol Ee to worry about.
You don't even have 1,000 dollars. Where are you staying?
Are you eating well?
I am very sorry.
What parent treats his child like rubbish?
You have a child too. How can you say such thing?
This time,
I made a terrible mistake.
I misjudged everything.
I thought it was for your own good.
I think I'm getting too old.
I can't think straight any more.
You must be suffering so much with Ddol Ee in this cold weather.
Just come home for now.
If you really don't want to come,
at least drop off Ddol Ee here.
I know how you feel, but nothing will be solved if you're like this.
How will you support yourself?
Do you have enough money to rent a house?
I will send you some money. Just send me your account number.
Jae Soon, at least talk to me.
You don't have to go home or talk to Mum and Dad.
Just call me. Don't think too much, okay?
(Missed Calls, Messages)
(Power off)
See, even my selfies look great.
It's great to be in a hotel room after living in the rooftop.
You said that your exercises were for in-house at no cost.
It works better in the rooftop. Don't you know anything?
I do.
Whether you're at a hotel or a rooftop, you can do this.
It's time to take off those heavy, winter coats.
A great body makes your fashion perfect. Follow after me.
I adjusted the broadcasting schedule.
I contacted the US office.
I decided to leave after launching the home shopping.
Yes. I see.
- Why are you still up? - Did you take care of business?
- When are we going to the US? - Maybe next week.
We will leave as soon as the home shopping work is done.
Daddy.
Let's not talk about that again.
- About what? - You don't have to know.
Buy some gimbap.
- Buy some gimbap. - How much is it?
It's 1 dollar and 50 cents.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. I don't have any change.
I have no time for this.
Hi. Can you show me the most popular fabric?
Show me alpaca and cashmere, including imported ones.
(Director Yeo Si Nae)
Come in.
- Director. - Come in.
Thank you so much. Words cannot express my gratitude.
I stopped by after doing some fabric research at the marketplace.
Here.
You didn't have to do this.
From now on, when you do fabric research, bring it to me right away.
I need to know the fabric trend to know the fashion trend.
I will, ma'am.
I'm so excited these days.
Thanks to you, my life is full of excitement.
I can take care of my twins now.
Did you quit driving?
Yes, I'm studying at night as well.
Thank you so much.
I'm always indebted to you. Someday, I will return the favour.
I'm not the person you should thank.
I know. I will buy the foreman some bread.
The foreman?
My goodness! What are you doing here? It's nice to see you.
I guess you're here to say hi.
He must have been hired as a driver.
Don't be rough with him. You should be careful.
- It's because we're so close. - You're close?
- No, we're not. - Let me introduce him.
He's the director of strategic department.
He's my son. Are you surprised?
Hello.
I told you to be respectful to him.
I apologise.
Please forgive my lack of respect.
Thank you for helping me when I was working in the warehouse.
My son wanted to learn everything about the business.
That's why he was working there.
- Yes. I see. - Ms Ban Ji Ha.
If you're done talking to her, please go back to work.
Yes, you can leave now.
Okay. Bye.
Yes.
You are really something.
Is it your hobby to mess with people? Was it fun?
- What are you talking about? - When I took off with the money,
do you know how scared I was, thinking that it was your money?
If I knew you were this rich, I would have lied and asked more.
Whenever I gave you some bread, you must've been laughing inside.
When I told you to save money, you must've mocked me.
Was it fun to watch my misery?
You recommended me to the design department, right?
Tell me the truth.
I did make the recommendation.
However, you got the job because of your talent.
I didn't have any personal motives.
I just valued your talent.
You can go now. Don't waste your energy.
You're a player, aren't you?
Don't mess with people's emotions.
Let's be professional.
Please leave.
You can come up with another design with the time you're wasting here.
What are you talking about? You're saying that...
Soo Jo asks the ladies to reject him whenever he gets set up?
I see.
Really?
Are you sure he is not seeing anyone?
I'm sure.
He would have told me first if he liked a girl.
He would have told me...
even if he got a girl's number or saw a girl he liked.
He hides nothing from me.
Then why is he doing that?
I don't know.
Shall we eat out?
When are you done tonight?
Talk to me. Shall I wait for you at work?
Gab Soon? Ms Gab Soon?
Ms Gab Soon. Madam.
When are you going to talk to me?
What's wrong with her? She didn't even say bye to me.
- This is all your fault. - Ouch.
She looks down on you...
so she acts like that in front of me.
I begged her but it didn't work.
You begged? You...
- Mum. - Why would you beg?
No wonder she's so stubborn.
Great going.
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't do this to me. I'm already upset.
If you kept your mouth shut, this wouldn't have happened.
You told me.
If you didn't tell me, I wouldn't have found out.
Even if you knew, you should have kept your mouth shut.
I would have acted the same way if you said that about my parents.
Would you like it if I didn't stand up for you?
Stop taking your wife's side.
I don't even know.
Don't come home!
My gosh.
Why are you alone?
Aren't you going to eat lunch?
I don't feel like it.
Why are you here? I didn't order anything.
I came to pick up plates and wanted to see her.
Where did she go?
Is she your girlfriend or something?
Why would you come see her?
Doesn't she look for me these days?
She doesn't.
Stop annoying me. I'm already annoyed.
You look much older after you got married.
You don't even order jjajangmyeon.
I don't eat jjajangmyeon any more.
I want to stop seeing you, my mum...
and Gab Soon.
I think it's because I was the emcee for your wedding ceremony.
All the couples I emcee for broke up.
- What? - Look.
Our high school friend Dong Man,
my military buddy Suk Ho...
Jae Soon's wedding...
got called off at the wedding hall.
It's picking up its pace.
You guys are the only ones left.
(Missing person)
I delivered flyers before.
The owner gave me a discount.
Let's hand these out in crowded areas.
Would these work?
There must be a reason people do this.
It's quite effective. A lot of people look at them.
Let's give it a try.
What if we just wait?
If we act on impulse,
Jae Soon's privacy might not be protected.
Everybody will recognise her.
That's right.
If people start recognising her, it'll be difficult for her.
It'll be difficult for us too.
People will say,
"There goes Jae Soon's dad."
"There goes Jae Soon's aunt."
That's what it'll be like.
And even if we find her now, she won't change her mind.
She won't come back right away.
We're just wondering how she's doing.
People have their selfish nature.
What are you talking about?
Who's selfish here?
It's true we're worried about her,
but we're looking for Jae Soon for our sake.
To relieve our worries.
We don't want to be anxious any more.
Jae Soon's been hurt already...
so let's just wait for her.
She's 40. She can look after herself.
You should stay out of this.
I'm going to find her at all cost.
How could you push her into it?
You should have told her.
You should have let her decide for herself.
Se Gye.
You were like this from her first marriage.
You didn't think about her.
You made excuses...
and pushed her into getting married to make you feel better.
You did the same to me.
Father.
Fine, it's all my fault.
You can resent me. Go ahead.
But for now, none of that matters.
I have to find my daughter.
Wait.
Let's wait for her.
Let her come back on her own.
She's been hurt. She won't come back on her own.
We have to find her.
She might be waiting for us.
She won't be able to go outside if we do this.
She'll be embarrassed of herself.
Is this for you or Jae Soon?
- Pardon? - We have to find her.
If something happens to her, can I blame you for it?
Who cares about being embarrassed?
You have to think about your daughter.
Listen to him.
I gave birth to Jae Soon. She's my daughter.
I'm the one who should be the most upset.
Stop it, Mum. You should stop too, Dad.
It doesn't matter if I'm doing this for Jae Soon or for myself.
We can't hand these out right now.
That's my final word.
A married couple shouldn't go so long without talking to each other.
You should apologise to her.
Go watch a movie with her or go away somewhere not too far.
You didn't eat right, Mum?
I'll be there soon. Let me take care of my account.
You're home early.
Let's call a truce.
I don't like this silence.
Gab Soon.
Ms Gab Soon?
Forgive me this once.
Do you want to go for a movie? You wanted to go once a month.
What about a getaway? Do you want to go this weekend...
What was that for?
What about you?
What do you mean?
I was trying to make you feel better. Stop embarrassing me.
This is violence.
Do you even think?
This is going too far.
You know how things are in my family and you want to go where?
Movies? Getaway?
You didn't have to use violence.
Don't exaggerate it. I hardly pushed you.
If I pushed you, you would have wanted a divorce.
And let me say this too.
This is Jae Soon's fault.
This is not how things should be. Everybody's down.
How long would this go on for?
Your family and us two are different.
How could you... Are we really married?
Get out. I don't want to talk to you.
I don't want to talk to you either.
You're going to regret this.
Unless you go on your knees and apologise,
I won't talk to you.
I'm ready.
Me too.
I don't have to do this.
Weren't you asleep?
I just woke up.
Are you going somewhere?
Can't you tell? I'm going for milk delivery.
Did you forget I do this every morning?
And you call yourself a son.
Did they find out, Relief Patch?
They didn't. What about you?
Me neither.
It's okay.
It's heavy.
You should quit.
It is too cold and tough for you.
I don't want to idle my time away. I like it since I get to exercise.
Instead, I quit working at the restaurant.
My son didn't want me to work in a restaurant.
Great.
- Isn't it heavy? - No, it's not.
If you can do it, why can't I?
1, 2, 3. Try to cling onto my arm.
- Really? - Sure.
This one.
Aren't you eating, Gong Joo?
Leave her alone. I wonder how long she's going to be like that.
I want to teach her a lesson this time. Don't spoil her.
Don't be too harsh on her.
She is spoiled because we raised her that way.
Sir, did you go somewhere at dawn?
Excuse me?
I came down to cook and...
you came in quietly like this.
What... What are you talking about?
At dawn?
He didn't see anything. I didn't go anywhere. I was just sleeping.
I did see you.
You are mistaken.
I really did see you.
I don't want to be treated unfairly. I really saw him come in.
I said I didn't. Why do you insist that you're right?
He is a sleepyhead early in the morning so he can't go out.
Are you sure you weren't dreaming?
You have weird dreams often.
Since when?
I think there was a time before.
The soup is cold now. Give me hot one, please.
I could swear it was him.
The number you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number again.
The number...
The number you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number again.
There is something wrong. They say the number is not in service.
What?
They say Jae Soon's number is not in service.
Call her. Call her right now.
The number you have dialed is not in service.
I guess she changed her number.
I think she'll sever all contact.
Abandon a useless child like me.
I'd rather kill myself than...
ask you to do something for me.
Don't you ever look for me again.
From today,
consider me dead.
She might be waiting for us to look for her.
Since we're her parents, we should go look for her.
The number you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number again.
If you see her, please call me.
This is my daughter. Please help me find her.
Please take a look.
Please help us.
- Please help us. - Please.
Please.
Please help us find her.
We're launching our product for the home shopping channel tomorrow.
We tried our best to prepare, but we should wait and see.
Please prepare them as so.
(Hope Daycare Centre)
You got off work early today.
Yes. Did my twins have a good time?
Yes, they did.
Il Ho, you're cold, aren't you?
Ee Ho, you must be cold too. So am I.
Let's go home quickly.
All right. We're almost there.
He's my son. Are you surprised?
Let's be professional.
If you're done, please leave.
- Who is it? - It's me.
Why did you come here?
Your babies called me to say they're out of formula.
All right.
Peekaboo. Hello.
What? Did you miss me?
I missed you too.
I'll hold you after washing my hands.
I don't understand why you keep doing this.
Do you think it's funny?
A frog could get killed by a stone you threw for fun.
It's not warm enough for frogs to come out.
Don't talk to me formally. I feel awkward.
Okay. I don't want to talk to you formally any more either.
Let me be simple.
How do you...
think of me?
Do you see me as a woman?
If so, please give up.
I need to succeed.
Do you know how hard it was to get this chance?
I even quit chauffeuring and am now focusing on my new job.
Ever since I was born,
I've never been happier.
I get paid, I can study about design...
and I can see my kids.
Though I'm a contract worker now, I can be a regular one if I try hard.
I can go to work in the morning and come home in the evening.
You can't imagine how happy I am to sleep with my babies in my arms...
since you are a child of a rich family.
I don't want to...
lose them all because of you.
You're exaggerating.
What does my seeing you as a woman have anything to do with this?
Can't you understand?
I should be grateful to your mother forever.
If she finds out that we meet like this, she'll kill me.
A little sympathy for me...
and your help for my babies...
I'll take them until today.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
You make a conclusion all by yourself.
I'm hungry. Shall I make noodles?
I don't want to be swayed.
Who would refuse a man like you?
It'd be right for me to seduce you.
But I should not do that. I don't want to be so ungrateful.
I couldn't forgive a woman like me, if I were your mother.
I'm uneducated and have two kids.
And I'm old. Who would like such a woman?
Once I feel attached to you, it'll be harder to break up.
Don't try to sway or shake a poor woman.
Just keep on going your way.
Then,
I'll see you at work, sir.
I understand what you mean.
The things you're worried about will never happen.
Trust me.
I'll take care of everything.
I like her the most.
She has a favourable impression.
What's the use for us to like her? Soo Jo has to like her.
But I think he really hates going on blind dates,
considering he told the girls to reject him.
- I'm home. - Did you eat dinner?
- Yes, I did. - Could you come here and sit?
Come here.
Speak honestly. Do you not want to go on blind dates?
Do you have a woman you like?
I heard you told the girls to reject you first.
I'm sorry. I don't want to go on blind dates.
Why not? Don't you want to get married?
I'll get married someday, but I don't want blind dates.
Do you have a girlfriend?
If your mother finds out, she'll kill me.
If you have a girlfriend, just tell me.
I don't.
Hey, Mal Nyeon's nephew.
I can't see your aunt for the past few days.
Is there something wrong? Is she sick?
Wait.
This is my number. Please give it to her.
Thank you.
Tell her she can call me day or night.
You brat. Hey!
Please don't make any trouble.
- What do you mean? - You know what I mean.
It is true that you sound cold sometimes.
We can get hurt by the words others say.
- Am I like that? - Yes.
You should comfort your parents well at times like this.
They are probably suffering a lot...
since their child disappeared and is not in contact at all.
I don't understand my sister.
How could she disappear with her child?
She is hopeless.
People are sometimes hopeless.
See? You just said she is hopeless and that was cold.
It is true.
I'll be careful.
I'm worried since she has no place to go.
Today, we'll give you seven boxes.
There are six tablets in a box.
You'll have a chance to get seven boxes in total today.
(901 people are ordering over the phone.)
Mr Jo. This is awesome.
The sales are increasing incredibly.
Thank you.
The theme of the broadcast was great too.
We scheduled for the next broadcast too.
By when can you get the products ready?
- I'll let you know. - All right.
Don't lose the chance for the samples.
We'll be back as soon as we get enough products.
Mr Jo. You are great.
Let's go to the meeting room.
The shareholders' meeting is just over.
Let's go.
(Welcome back, President Jo.)
President Jo, you came back in six months with glory.
Let's give him a big hand.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
These are your house deed and your stock.
Your entire properties.
As I told you already, the company didn't lose anything.
We bounced back more than enough.
Thank you for working as a salesman so far.
I'll try harder in the future.
We'll get going now.
(President Jo Geum Sik)
I want to go to the US though.
Be quiet.
Dad, I'm so happy.
I'm thrilled.
It is so good to be back home.
I feel the same.
I didn't know we could come back here.
Dad, congratulations on becoming the president again.
I want to congratulate on it too.
I knew you could do it.
But I'm a little upset. I was looking forward to going to the US.
Let's go there for a trip later.
Whatever.
Cho Rong, take a look at your room.
Everything's the same!
Honey.
Please go ahead.
It's awkward. I've never said that.
Repeat after me.
"Honey."
Honey.
Dad. Let's go out to buy Da Rong's backpack.
Okay. Let's go.
Dad, what do you think of this?
It's pretty.
Cho Rong, I like this one.
Okay. Let's choose this one.
Cho Rong, choose one too since you're becoming a sixth grader.
I'm okay.
It'd be great if we bought Ddol Ee a bag since he's entering school.
(Incheon Education of Office)
Gimbap again? I'm tired of gimbap.
We can't help it since it is the leftovers of what I sold.
There is beef in here.
This is delicious. It's delicious to me.
I don't want it. I want to go to Grandpa's.
I miss Grandpa.
He looked like Geum Sik from the back.
He is in the US.
(Missing person)
Dad!
(Shin Jae Soon, 40 years old, 166cm)
Let's stop it.
I can't see people step...
on my child's face any more.
Let's pick them up and go.
What are you doing here?
I thought you were in the US.
I didn't get to leave.
I heard that the wedding didn't happen.
How could this happen?
I told you so.
You should have taken action.
How can you let this happen?
It's all my fault.
She must be suffering so much.
She has Ddol Ee with him too.
What is there to say?
Life is more miserable with a child to take care of.
Please, Geum Sik. Find Jae Soon for me.
At least find out if she's alive.
I will.
No matter what, I will find her.
(Our Gab Soon)