(Episode 49)
Come on in.
I've been waiting for you. Have a seat.
It's her.
I don't care how much it costs.
Please find her. I beg of you.
All right.
Gimbap for sale.
I made them myself.
Gimbap for sale. Gimbap for sale.
- I'll take one. - Thank you.
Enjoy.
Gimbap for sale.
I just made them, so they're still warm.
They're all homemade gimbap for sale.
- How much is it? - It's 1 dollar and 50 cents.
Ddol Ee.
Get up now. You must eat and go to academy.
You'll attend it as of today.
Here you go.
Gimbap again? I don't want it.
I couldn't sell them all, so you have to eat it. Just today, okay?
Buy me pizza. I want pizza.
I'll get it for you once I make a lot of money.
Please take good care of my son.
Don't worry.
Ddol Ee, listen to your teacher carefully.
Study and play. I'll come pick you up in the evening.
In case something happens, call me right away.
I will. Let's go.
I'm sorry. I'm a bit late.
Hurry up. Clean up here first.
Place some ice on these fish...
and sprinkle salt over there.
All right.
We can't just sit back like this.
I can't distribute flyers.
Let's do something else.
Should I do it alone or will you do it together?
(Missing person)
Excuse me,
have you ever seen someone like this?
She turned 40 this year.
Her name is Shin Jae Soon. Have you seen her?
She's my daughter. Take a close look.
I might have seen her.
At where? Where did you see her?
Please think carefully.
Maybe not.
If you remember, please call me at this number.
Whether it's day or night, please call me. I beg of you.
- All right. - Please call me.
You didn't even find a clue yet?
We're tracking her through the surveillance camera...
from the police station that day.
All right.
Please find her quickly.
I beg of you.
Have you seen her?
(Looking for someone)
You couldn't find her?
It's already been several days now.
You might be ill.
She must be hiding well. She was determined when she left home.
I think it's best to wait for her until she returns home.
How could I just sit back and wait?
I'm going insane from anger.
Going out and looking for her is better than staying home.
Ddol Ee has to start school in March too.
He needs to come home to attend school.
What if he ends up not going to school?
Jae Soon will take care of it.
Wherever she may be, she'll send him to primary school.
Shouldn't he go to a school nearby?
He can go to any school near his address.
Jae Soon wouldn't be able to send Ddol Ee to school.
We could find out their whereabouts if we visit Office of Education.
They will probably not tell you.
Why not?
Even the police won't track her...
although we're family.
It's the same logic.
Besides, he didn't enter school yet, so they wouldn't know either.
Still, I better go and give it a try.
(Seoul Dongjak Gwanak Office of Education)
It's their first time going to school, so I don't know what to get.
Would a backpack, pencils and notebooks be enough?
You should get some new clothes for them too.
Their going to school makes my heart flutter.
Me too. I'm amazed.
They've grown up so quickly to enter primary school.
Please throw away the garbage in the kitchen.
I don't want to go out.
When the family is like this, at least you should help out.
You haven't done a single chore so far. You might as well do it now.
Or get out.
Gosh, I don't want to see anyone.
I'm irritated.
I'm the pushover.
For goodness' sake.
Gosh, this isn't why I'm living proof.
You are so busted!
What are you doing?
I have nothing to tell you. What's the matter with you?
Let's go somewhere and talk.
Talk about what? There's nothing to talk about between us.
We're destined to have met after decades.
It was the divine being's will for us to have met after decades.
I only want to take care of you in your later years.
That's enough. I don't need you to take care of me.
Please don't come to see me any more.
Your nephew was so rude.
I told him to give my number to you,
but he tore the paper right in front of me.
Why is he so rude?
Don't say he's rude.
How dare you speak badly about my nephew?
I don't need your phone number.
If my brother finds out about this, he will kill both of us.
My goodness.
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
- Go away now. - Hello.
- Who are you? - I don't know him.
Let's go.
Who are you?
I'm sorry I have to introduce myself on the street.
Stop.
Mal Nyeon has told me so much about you. I am...
I said stop.
I don't know who you are, but I don't want to hear or say anything.
I don't think I would see you again, so I'll just go now.
- Come on, Mal Nyeon. - All right. Let's go.
Please wait!
My gosh.
Are you in your right mind?
Who is he? Is he the guy you met at the dumpster?
No.
You met him at the dumpster before, right?
Why are you seeing him? When did you two meet?
We're having enough trouble, so behave yourself.
How can you be seeing a man when your niece is missing?
You're her aunt. My goodness.
I know you like men, but don't fool around near the dumpster.
What are you going to do if Dal Pa finds out?
He just started to settle down. It will stir him up again.
I didn't... I didn't know you were home.
Did she get caught by you too?
Did he catch you as well?
Yes.
Gosh. What a lonely life.
Just let her be.
You shouldn't care if she sees a man or not.
I don't care either.
Uncle.
Have you heard anything from Jae Soon yet?
I don't know where she is. No one has seen her.
Do you want to post it?
Where?
(Missing person)
You can begin.
I am...
Shin Joong Nyeon. A few days ago, I posted...
"Feed Yourself without Walking on Eggshells: Kimchi Fried Rice"...
of "How Shin Joong Nyeon Lives".
The reason why I'm taking this video is...
Uncle, let's do it again.
What should I say?
Just say whatever you want.
I'm Shin Joong Nyeon. I posted an episode of...
"How Shin Joong Nyeon Lives" a few days ago.
You don't have to say that. Just get to the point.
This is my daughter.
She has gone missing.
She recently disappeared and hasn't come back.
Please look closely at her picture,
and if you see her by any chance,
please call me.
I need your help.
Please help me find my daughter.
Who is it?
- Is it Jae Soon? - It's...
It's me.
I was on my way home, and I thought I'd drop by.
I'm glad you did.
I brought some bread and fruits.
You shouldn't have. You're not a guest.
Don't bring us anything next time.
You don't have much money. You should save every penny.
I'm doing my best to find Jae Soon, but I haven't gotten much news.
I'm sure she's fine. Don't worry.
We don't know what to do,
so we're just looking for her on the street. It's frustrating.
I don't know where we should begin.
We're only getting strange phone calls.
Strange phone calls?
We're getting some prank calls.
Joong Nyeon can hardly sleep at night because of it.
We wrote his cell phone number on the flyers.
I will find her no matter what.
I've been asking around, so I should hear from her soon.
Ddol Ee will start school soon, so she will come back.
Thank you for saying that.
Hearing what you said, I feel much better.
I'm sorry.
I should've known that life isn't all about the money.
If Jae Soon had married you, none of this would have happened.
I'm regretting it so much.
Jae Soon loved you so much.
I pushed her to marry Se Bang because I wanted her to have...
a comfortable life. I didn't mean for things to turn out this way.
It's all water under the bridge.
Is your heater working okay?
Pardon?
Your heater at the rooftop broke down,
so your daughters had to stay here for the night.
Well... That's...
I feel so bad for them too.
If it's too hard, you can let them stay here for a while.
No. It's okay.
- A bottle of soju, please. - Okay.
Hello?
Is that true?
Where is it?
Fish market?
Okay. Thank you.
I will give you a reward for this later.
What is it?
Someone saw Jae Soon. We found her.
Really?
Where is she? Where did the person say she was?
She should be around here.
Jae Soon!
I can't take this any more. This isn't a joke.
It's terrible to play a prank on someone having such a hard time.
Maybe it's not a prank, but he was just mistaken.
He says the name of the store was "Jae Soon's".
We'll find her eventually.
It's better than receiving no calls at all. It gives us hope.
No, it doesn't. It just exhausts us.
You should check before going out to find her.
I don't have time to do that. I have to go and see it for myself.
That's your problem.
I told you to look into Se Bang's business, but you didn't.
You didn't listen to me.
If you had looked into it, things wouldn't have turned out this way.
Why are you suddenly blaming me?
My goodness.
Gosh.
- Excuse me. Please... - I'm sorry.
(Missing person)
Please look at this.
You know the fish stew restaurant, right?
- Take this to that place. - Yes, Sir.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me. I'm from the fish store.
- Yes. Put it down in the kitchen. - Okay.
They're really fresh. My boss picked only the best ones.
See you later.
Hello?
That's not her.
My daughter is not 22. She's turning 40 this year.
Hello?
It's not her.
That's not it.
Thanks, anyways.
I'm mad at you for how you treated me.
When you first saw me, you said I smelled like relief patch.
I didn't say that.
I fell in love with you from the first time I saw you.
- I'm hanging up. - No, I'm sorry. Don't get mad.
Now, when I smell relief patch on other ladies,
I think it's you and start following them.
But you're quite stubborn.
I should have known.
So? Do you not like me for it?
What do you mean?
That's your charm.
That's why I'm so attracted to you.
I don't like women who are easy.
I like women who are hard to get.
Nobody's ever told me I was hard to get.
- Aren't you embarrassed? - I am.
How long have we been on the phone?
It's been over three hours.
We're going to stay up all night.
Time flies by when I'm talking to you.
It only takes an hour...
to say a few words and laugh a few times.
You don't have delivery today so let's sleep.
Okay. Goodnight.
Relief Patch.
Why do I miss you so much?
We can meet.
Right now? That's a great idea.
Where should we meet? Should I go pick you up?
Do you want to go to the sea?
Of course.
Let's go to the sea and watch the sunrise.
We can eat raw fish.
It's too far. Let's just go to the Han River.
It's the same sun.
Should we get rings?
Rings?
Young couples get these rings.
We can get them too.
Mum.
I'm at a funeral.
Do you like it?
This is my first time putting on a ring.
Me too. I'm happy.
It feels like you and I are one.
What if your daughter finds out?
That's fine.
Don't even lie.
If she finds out, you're going to push me away...
and run away.
I won't.
Can you promise that you'll keep it on?
Of course.
I'm going to keep it on all the time.
It means I'm yours.
You're also mine.
I'm mine.
Only wear it when we meet.
Don't make things complicated.
If your daughter finds out, we're both done for.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
It's Sunday. You should stay home.
I have a few things to take care of at the office.
- I have some toast. Have some. - I'll eat out.
Hello.
You don't have to be so polite.
See you later, Dad.
I don't know what's wrong with her.
Don't.
What's wrong with you?
You should reply back when someone says hi.
She's your brother.
Don't you understand?
You're not a teenager. Why are you being so rude?
You know why I'm acting this way.
Can't you be more understanding of me?
Understand what?
He appeared out of nowhere and ruined my life.
You kicked out Se Gye because of him.
That's not true.
Se Gye and you weren't for each other.
He married you with a motive.
Can't you still forget about him?
I don't get it. Anyhow,
make sure you treat your brother nicely.
I won't change my mind.
Look at you.
Il Ho. Ee Ho.
Yes?
It's me.
Why did you come? I told you not to.
I didn't come to see you.
Il Ho. Ee Ho.
You're Il Ho, right?
Bring Ee Ho with you.
Let's try the strollers.
This is Il Ho's.
This is Ee Ho's.
What are you doing? Let's go for a ride.
Let's go.
The boys are so happy.
You look happier than they do.
I never did this for them.
I always had to carry them so they never got to look around.
Look, Il Ho.
Look, Ee Ho.
It's so pretty.
It's seafood. We'll cut it up for you.
It's seafood.
I'm going to make soup so don't cut the head or the organs.
Can you cut this one up?
Is this fresh from this morning?
- The colour... - The colour?
Your husband is very knowledgeable about fish.
He must be a good housekeeper.
He is, indeed.
I've never been to a place like this. Isn't it expensive?
Your wage is enough.
You've been to places like this a lot, right?
I don't like places like this.
The boys have a good appetite.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir. What is it?
Hang on.
I'll check it right away when I go to work tomorrow.
Yes.
Why? Did you see something?
Never mind.
I'm upset because of Soo Jo.
I want to marry him off quickly and have a grandchild.
You feel the same way, don't you?
Of course. I've been waiting for my grandson since 30 years ago.
He wouldn't even have a chance to see a girl.
I wonder why he refuses to meet...
a girl from a nice family.
I'm home.
Hi.
- Where have you been? - To work.
Be honest with me. You met a girl, didn't you?
What?
I saw you in front of a restaurant on my way home.
You saw her? What do you think?
I saw her briefly, so I'm not sure.
How could you be so disloyal?
I was going to tell you.
What kind of a girl is she? Where did you meet her?
How old is she? There are so many things I'm curious about.
Ask me one by one.
I'll tell you one thing only.
I met her while working at the warehouse.
She now works at the head office at the design room.
Is that so? What about her age?
How many people are there in her family? What's her name?
- That's all for now. - Come on.
I'll tell you later.
This is a secret.
Tell Mum that you're seeing someone,
so she won't ask you to go on blind dates.
I'll tell her when the time is right.
- But until then... - All right.
Let's do grocery shopping together from now on.
It's a great way to refresh myself. I liked it a lot.
It is, right? I must tell you a bit about Soo Jo.
Go ahead.
He doesn't want to go on blind dates. Why don't we leave him alone?
We better marry him off quickly.
Soo Jo prefers love over arranged marriage.
Are there many pretty women at the warehouse?
Why?
Forget it.
Gab Soon, we're in trouble.
Two ladies didn't come to work today.
Why not? We're supposed to clean the building today.
I think another team has hired them discreetly.
They're the best ones. What should we do?
I told them that the cleaning will be done by today.
Let's go.
- What's up, Se Gye? - Are you busy?
Mum and Dad can't eat anything.
I hope you can come by.
I'm volunteering for medical service, and I can't go home today.
All right.
Dal Pa, please take care of the work here. I need to drop by home.
We have a lot to do.
Mum, I'm here.
Going around for several days got me sick.
My entire body is sore.
Poor you.
Stop going outside. You won't find Jae Soon that way.
I'll make some food.
My gosh,
it's been a while since I smelled good food.
Daughters are better...
since they make food for their parents.
You might as well come here and do some housework...
until your parents recover.
I work too. You should do this kind of stuff.
You can make kimchi stew at least.
I came here although I have so much work to do.
Gosh.
You're just like a mother-in-law.
Even your mum gave up on me. Why are you nagging?
I want you to take care of the house when the family is like this.
Does your mother-in-law know?
About what?
That Jae Soon's marriage was broken off and thus left home.
She doesn't. How would she know?
Please contact us if you see her.
Excuse me, have you seen this woman?
(Missing person)
Oh, dear.
Have you seen this woman?
You're going through a lot.
Yes, well...
I feel bad for you.
Your wife must be ill in bed.
Yes, she is ill in bed.
You were going to marry her off to a swindler?
You should've known carefully.
Didn't you notice?
You're so smart when it comes to other things.
What a relief that the marriage didn't work out.
I hope you'll find her no matter what.
I'll try my best as well.
Mum, I cooked rice and kimchi stew,
so eat later.
I came in the middle of work, so I'll get going.
It must have been hard for you to work and cook all together.
What is it that you do?
Excuse me? I just made some food.
That's not what's important.
How could you say things about your family?
I just met your mother-in-law. She knew about everything.
- Dear goodness. - I'm sorry.
There are things you shouldn't say even if he's your husband.
Don't you know Gab Dol well enough?
Gab Soon doesn't know that her husband is a big mouth.
Gab Dol is a big mouth,
and he doesn't make much money.
There's nothing trustworthy about him.
If Gab Dol knows, he'd tell his mum right away.
I'm sorry I didn't get him to keep his mouth shut.
He slipped it by mistake.
There's nothing we can do about the broken marriage,
but I didn't want her to know about Geum Sik's being a former swindler.
It may be okay for others, but I didn't want her to know.
Goodness.
I was so embarrassed that I wanted to hide.
Speaking bad of your own family will eventually come back to you.
It's true.
I'm sorry.
What on earth are you doing?
Why? It's Sunday. I can take a break.
This room is a mess.
Clean up before you rest.
Come on, Mum.
I came here because I didn't want to hear Gab Soon nagging.
Go dust off your blanket.
My goodness!
You couldn't even whip your wife and got kicked out of your room.
I wasn't kicked out. I moved out on my own.
Gosh, I shouldn't have gotten married.
You're newlyweds. Good for you.
If you got married, you should live happily.
You're already sleeping in separate bedrooms. It's your fault.
You've been whipped by her since you were young.
Now that she's making money,
are you even more discouraged?
It's not like that.
What do you mean? Don't be discouraged.
Most women work these days.
It's not like she makes a lot of money.
I'm going to let her have it.
She makes more than I do.
What?
She has no respect.
How can she act so spoiled in front of her mother-in-law?
How can she not talk or say hello?
It's because her family isn't doing well these days.
Where did you get that ring?
I found it in the drawers, so I'm wearing it.
You don't even like them.
All women like them. If they had one, they'd wear one.
What do you think I am?
Jjajangmyeon is here.
Put it there.
Why do you look so down? You're a newlywed.
I guess you must be worried about Gab Dol.
What do you mean?
I think Young Ran keeps asking him out...
because of me.
Do they meet outside?
Sometimes, I think.
I think she's asking him about me.
Don't worry too much. I'll take care of it soon.
Please follow the precautions. Good luck with the restaurant.
Okay. Thank you.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
It's really busy today.
Let's check one more place.
Okay.
Isn't that Gab Dol?
Why is he with a woman this late?
It's not a woman.
She's just a co-worker.
They'll become attached if they hang out too much.
I hope you hire someone soon.
I hope so, too.
You put up an ad online, so you'll find someone.
You must be really stressed these days.
You should go home and sleep.
You should go home and rest, too.
See you early in the morning.
Okay.
We need to talk.
You didn't even say hi when you came in.
I was just about to. I'm home.
I made you say it.
- When will you use the same room? - Pardon?
You're newlyweds. Why do you sleep in separate rooms?
How can you kick your husband out of your room?
Whose house is this?
I didn't kick him out. He left.
I nagged at him because he left crumbs all over the place...
and kept playing games.
Men don't like to hear someone nag at them.
You should talk to him nicely.
Who likes to hear someone yelling at them?
I'm tired too.
We both work. Gab Dol should do house chores too.
He never cleans the room. He never does the dishes.
You're tired because you're making your money.
You aren't earning money to support me or your husband.
You weren't like that when you were jobless.
You're on your high horse because you make money now.
When was I like that?
I was never like that.
You said you couldn't do any chores because you worked.
That's what you said on the first day you came here.
That's being on a high horse.
You make more money, so you look down on your husband.
Most importantly,
I'm your mother-in-law.
You should at least say hello and goodbye.
Did your parents teach you to be that way?
I would've asked your parents to discipline you...
if they weren't having problems.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't say hello because I couldn't control my feelings.
I'll be careful next time.
But Mother,
I have to ask you this.
Did you have to mention it to my dad?
- Mention what? - My sister.
I saw him wandering so I said something because I was worried.
What's wrong with that?
You shouldn't have said anything.
He must've felt...
really bad after hearing what you said.
Put yourself in his position.
How would you feel if my dad said something like that to you?
It's not like I said something bad.
He's like family, so I showed my concern.
I guess he felt bad because he has an inferiority complex.
What?
My dad doesn't have an inferiority complex.
Why are you like that?
My goodness.
You should listen quietly to someone who's older than you.
How dare you talk back?
You've never once listened to me obediently.
Are you looking down on me?
Because I have no husband?
It's not like that.
I just explained the situation.
How is that talking back?
I don't want to say I'm wrong when I didn't do anything wrong.
What?
I should explain myself when you misunderstand me.
I was never on a high horse for making more money.
I never kicked Gab Dol out.
I'll keep my mouth shut forever if you think I'm talking back.
But you'll scold me if I don't talk.
What should I do then?
You said we were family.
Can't you be considerate of my feelings when I'm down?
Gab Dol and I both work the same, long hours.
Would you have treated me like this if I were your daughter?
I came home after working all day.
Do you have to sit me down and nag at me like this?
What are you doing?
Look at her.
You heard what she said, right?
She never once apologises but she talks back to me.
Even when I say something wrong,
you should just nod.
Why do you always talk back?
Do I have to put up with you?
Do I give you a hard time? Am I a bad mother-in-law?
You two sleep in separate rooms.
So all I said was "You shouldn't do that."
When I tell her one thing she talks back for several minutes.
Come out.
I'm okay with everything else.
You say whatever you like to me.
You can swear at me. That's okay.
But...
I don't want you to do that to my mum.
She had a tough life.
I'll put up with everything.
I'll agree with you on anything.
But I don't want you...
to talk back to her.
If you do this one more time,
I won't stand it.
- Goodbye. - Did you sell a lot?
Yes, I sold all the mackerels.
I told you to put ice in that box.
They all melted.
They'll go bad. Do you know how much they cost?
I'm sorry.
Goodness.
It smells like pizza.
It's pizza bread.
That looks yummy. Can I have a bite?
No.
No! Why did you eat mine?
Teacher!
What's wrong?
He ate my bread.
Why did you do that?
You shouldn't eat other people's food without permission.
I wanted to have some.
My son is in the first grade.
Which one is the best college savings plan?
Have you seen this person?
Please take a look.
Here. Please help.
Please give me a call if you see this person.
- I hope you find her soon. - Thank you.
Jae Soon.
Jae Soon!
- Jae Soon. - What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You look just like my daughter.
You're crazy.
I'm sorry.
She looked exactly like Jae Soon from behind.
Jae Soon looks exactly like you from behind.
Here.
Be careful. You aren't young any more.
If you hurt your knee, it'll take a long time to heal.
I'm sorry, Mum.
I can't believe I hurt my leg.
Why is my life so twisted?
What did I do wrong in my past life?
Why are my kids giving me so much trouble?
You're better off not having any children.
This is my daughter.
Have you seen her?
Please take a closer look.
(Missing person)
I think I've seen her before.
Where did you see her?
I'm not sure.
Please try to remember. Where did you see her?
I don't know.
If you end up remembering,
please call me.
- Thank you. - Sure.
She must have had an affair.
It's obvious.
I feel sorry that her dad has to look for her.
What did you say?
She didn't have an affair. You can't talk about people like that.
We were just talking to each other.
My daughter is not like that.
There are other problems so we can't reach her.
You can't gossip about her like that.
What's wrong with you?
You're so inflexible. No wonder your daughter ran away.
She probably couldn't take it any more.
My gosh. Even if I knew where she was, I wouldn't tell you. Let's go.
What did you say? Say that again.
Why do you keep following us?
She couldn't take it any more?
Have you seen her? Have you?
You're so weird. Let's leave.
Why are you getting mad at us because your daughter ran away?
- I think he's mad. - My goodness.
What did you say?
You shouldn't say that.
Stop drinking. That's enough.
Leave me alone.
You're going to fall ill like this.
- Let go. - Stop doing this.
My goodness. Really? Stop.
Nae Shim.
Oh, dear. What's wrong?
My gosh, Nae Shim.
- Oh, dear. - Let go.
- Oh, dear. - Why did you do that for?
You treated Jae Soon like trash.
Did you want to get rid of her that badly?
Stop it.
- Did she drink? - She drank the whole bottle.
Yes, I drank. So what?
You think this is good enough?
This wouldn't have happened if you took care of things properly.
I told you to look into Se Bang.
You made the final call.
You stopped me from telling her.
When she came back after getting divorced,
you forced her to remarry because you couldn't stand it.
That's when it all started.
You were all excited because Se Bang had some money.
What about you?
You knew he was an ex-convict,
so why did you still hide it?
You say I'm materialistic but you're no different.
- Father. - Am I wrong?
You have no right to blame me.
If you didn't waste your retirement pay,
I wouldn't have married Jae Soon off.
Are we getting started again?
Is it about the retirement pay again?
I can't hear it any more.
Let's get back to your room. You should stop too.
She's drunk.
What are you going to do now?
- Tell me what you're going to do. - I don't know. I don't know either.
How could she do this to her parents?
Watch when I find her.
You need to find her first.
Let's call it quits.
Let's get a divorce.
Sure. I'm not scared.
I was planning to do that earlier.
Let's fill out the documents...
and sell this house. We can each get a small place.
I can't live with you any more.
Same goes for me.
I can't live with you either.
Where's Jae Soon?
She doesn't even have a friend.
She doesn't even have 1,000 dollars.
She has nowhere to go with Ddol Ee.
She has nowhere to go.
Father.
- Oh, dear. - Is this why...
I became living proof?
She doesn't even have 1,000 dollars.
It's so cold outside. Where is she going to take her boy?
I have something to talk to you about.
What is it?
Ddol Ee stole his friend's bread.
It might not be something serious,
but I don't think he should get in the habit of stealing people's food.
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure that doesn't happen again.
Don't do this.
I don't want to go.
- Pull up your pants. - No!
Hurry.
No! You're going to hurt me!
Listen to me. Pull up your pants.
I don't like you. I wish you weren't here.
I told you you'll get punished if you do something wrong.
Who said you could steal other people's food?
I told you, you can't steal or take other people's belongings!
I hate you!
Don't dodge.
I wanted pizza. You wouldn't buy it for me.
Even if you want something, you can't take other people's things.
I want to go to Grandpa's.
Let me go to Grandpa.
There you go. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Take care.
(Pharmacy)
What's that noise?
Where are you, Ddol Ee?
Let's go to school.
Where are you?
Jae Soon.
You can't do this to me.
Where are you, Jae Soon?
I'm sorry.
You're up early.
Where are you going?
I have to go outside. I have to keep looking.
You probably aren't feeling well.
I made some bean sprouts soup. Have some before you leave.
I don't feel like eating.
I'm going to check farther places.
I've been looking for her in this neighbourhood.
I'm going to take the subway and go out farther.
Eat this before you...
(Missing person)
This is the last stop.
It's still morning. How can you be so fast asleep?
- Where am I? - You're in Incheon.
My goodness.
Please buy some gimbap.
Buy some gimbap.
- Can I have one? - Thank you.
- Here you go. - You forgot the change.
You can keep it.
(Incheon Station)
Come on in.
I'm sorry. You must be busy.
It's okay. I have some spare time today.
Take care of my mum. She hurt her leg. She can't move around freely.
Gab Soon is busy,
and I couldn't change my appointment.
I can't make the elders waste their time.
Why are you talking so much?
Don't worry and just go.
I just feel bad asking you. I'll see you later.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
I know I shouldn't say this at a time like this,
but this feels strange.
What does?
You're seeing me off...
and wishing me a good day.
Just go already.
You look like you belong here.
My gosh. Looking at you here in our kitchen,
it feels like you're one of our family.
It would've been perfect if you had married Se Gye.
You didn't have to come. I know you're busy.
I made some kimchi soup.
I'm not sure if it'd taste good, but please have some.
I can't eat.
I know I should eat some since you made it for me,
but I really can't eat anything right now.
You should eat to recover faster. You can't find Jae Soon like this.
Don't worry.
Jae Soon wouldn't think about doing something silly.
She has Ddol Ee. She'll return.
She's right. You should eat.
She's a doctor, and she made that for you.
Thank you for coming here when you're busy.
Are you really?
My gosh. You ruined...
all your children's lives because of money.
You told Se Gye to break up with such a nice girl like her...
because her family is poor.
You pushed Jae Soon to marry that swindler because of money too.
Did you have to say that?
Am I wrong?
You just don't like to hear it because I'm right.
I guess it's the same for everyone.
Get out.
You've made my brother's life so much harder.
You do something terrible, and he takes care of it.
I said, get out.
Look what's happening now.
You're lying down in your room because you hurt your leg.
Joong Nyeon is the only one looking for Jae Soon,
shivering out in the cold from the morning. My gosh.
Goodness. Poor Joong Nyeon.
Where would he be wandering around right now?
This isn't why I've become living proof.
My gosh.
Who is it?
Mother, it's me.
Why are you here?
Please be quiet.
Mother.
She can't see you right now.
Talk to me.
Why can't she see me?
I don't know the details,
but she's very sick.
You're so shameless.
You wrecked our marriage.
Se Gye and I are not done yet.
Stay out of it.
Please be polite to me.
I've been putting up with it, but I won't any more.
You disrespected me first.
You're the one who seduced Se Gye.
You started it in the beginning.
Se Gye was my boyfriend.
You have no idea how I felt when I let him go.
I didn't say anything because I knew it wasn't your fault.
Even when you were rude to me, I tolerated it.
I won't put up with it any more.
How ridiculous.
I'm not going to put up with this either. Let's see who wins.
The number you dialed is not in service.
Please check again.
Finish up for me, okay?
Yes, sir.
Hello?
I won't be able to pick up Ddol Ee today.
Please drop him off at home after class.
- Hello. - Hello.
Ji Yeon.
Goodbye.
All right.
Ddol Ee. Your mother will be here soon, so wait here.
You have to stay here.
Hello.
My son is starting elementary school.
Please show me a nice and cheap backpack.
I'll take this.
Grandpa!
Ddol Ee!