(Episode 51)
Soo Jo?
What are you doing?
Si Nae, I have...
I have something to confess.
Confess? What is it?
Right here?
Yes.
I've been desperately waiting for this moment.
I really wanted...
to say this at a supermarket.
What is it?
- Let's buy some spoons. - What?
What's that medicine for? Are you sick?
My body aches from fatigue.
Poor you.
You should take it easy. Don't overwork yourself.
Health is more important than money.
Come over for a second.
What's all this?
I made it for you. It's braised cutlassfish, your favourite.
Come on and eat.
Thank you, Mother.
It's delicious.
That's good to hear.
I know you're young, but don't work too hard.
You'll get sick when you get old.
I should make money while I'm still young.
Aren't you going to eat?
I had a late lunch. I'm not hungry.
I should've made food that you like more often.
I know you're busy too.
Things must be hard for you these days.
You must've thought you'd be happy after you got married.
But Gab Dol doesn't see how hard you work,
and all I do is nag you.
It's hard, right?
Gosh. How did you know? That's exactly how I feel.
Do you want to annul your marriage?
I'll have to think about it.
Things are actually hard at my company these days.
My business isn't going well,
but Gab Dol doesn't listen or talk to me.
I've been upset and exhausted.
Of course, you would.
Gab Dol should be careful about his behaviour outside.
He shouldn't do things you might misunderstand.
Even if he can't do the things you like,
he shouldn't do the things you hate at least.
That's right.
I don't need him to get me a diamond ring,
but I hope he won't do the things I hate.
I feel...
ashamed for everything.
I showed you things you shouldn't have seen.
I'm ashamed and embarrassed.
You shouldn't be.
He likes you because you're beautiful and charming.
Don't be timid and date him proudly.
You shouldn't let him pay all the expenses on dates.
Young people these days always split the check.
If he buys you a meal, you should buy him a meal next time.
Thank you for saying that.
Ms Yeo is not a nice person.
You're right. She is so rude.
She gave your brother such a hard time.
She treated him so harshly, but he was always polite.
I was wondering whom his parents were.
You really cheered me up today.
I feel embarrassed to you,
but I also feel so relieved.
Gab Dol and you are the best.
Aren't we?
Don't be intimidated. I'm a good fighter too.
I know you are.
But you shouldn't...
tell Gab Dol about this.
Maybe it's okay to tell a daughter, but he's not.
I understand what you mean.
I'm home.
Why are you so late?
I got off work late.
What are you doing?
- What? - Why aren't you greeting your wife?
She's not greeting me either. We don't even talk to each other.
That's not something to be proud of. Don't sleep in separate rooms.
Listening to your wife only brings you fortune.
You can't find a woman better than Gab Soon.
She's pretty, successful,
smart and a good fighter.
You don't realise how lucky you are.
- What's wrong? - Why do you sleep separately?
- You didn't even do well in school. - You're right.
Why would you bring that up?
I still passed the exam for 3,000 percent.
Gab Soon didn't.
You had studied for 10 years while doing nothing,
but Gab Soon had part-time jobs while studying. It's different.
No one except Gab Soon would have supported you for 10 years...
when you were jobless.
You couldn't even get her a house on your own.
Mum. Look at her being all smug.
That's enough.
If Gab Soon were still single,
guys who already have apartments would line up to marry her.
Mother, you're the best.
You're only a public official.
You wouldn't even have become one if it wasn't for her support.
You should treat her a lot better than this.
What's the matter with you?
Did you hear that, honey?
Get the blankets and go to your room.
Sleep in a separate room again, and I'll give you a good scolding.
What on earth did you do?
I didn't do anything.
- Did you give her money? - No.
Gosh. I'm totally surprised.
You turned the tables around completely.
Mother has worked hard her whole life.
Now that you're married,
don't make me upset...
and be good to your mother.
What's up with you?
You always got angry when I said my mum has worked hard.
Come here.
My dear wife.
You're finally being nice.
Don't you think...
Mother would be lonely if she lived alone?
Why would she live alone? She has us.
It's a different matter.
What are you trying to say?
My mum won't be lonely.
She's living with us. Why would she be?
You're saying silly things now that you're close with her.
Hello?
What were you doing? You didn't answer your phone.
Let's talk later.
Why? Are you busy?
I can't really talk now. I'll call you later.
Can we talk?
Why did you take this out?
You keep it in your drawer and wear it when you go out to see Ms Nam.
Do you really want to do this? It's disgraceful.
What does grace have anything to do with dating?
Were you graceful when seeing a guy?
I don't want to talk about this with you.
Sit down. Don't pretend to be naive.
We're both old enough to talk about anything.
I said sit down.
She deceived you once. Do you want to be deceived again?
How can you still be seeing her? You even kept it a secret.
We only get one life,
and there is not much to it.
Nothing is better than living each day happily.
You can't take money with you when you die.
Please come to your senses.
I already have.
I'm not going to marry her. I'm just going to date her.
There is no problem with dating her, is there?
You're just saying it now that you won't marry her.
Does she really want to date you even if she can't get your money?
Why would she want to do that?
- What? - To be honest,
I don't get why someone so much younger than you...
would want to date an old man like you.
Do you think...
an old man can't be loved by a woman?
Don't argue about my age.
You can go now.
You think I'm just worried about your money, right?
What is it then?
What are you going to do if she betrays you after you put...
all your trust in her?
This isn't just about your money.
How are you...
going to endure it if you get hurt and betrayed by someone at this age?
Have you thought about that?
When you're young,
you can just get over it and move onto someone else.
But you don't get another chance when you're old.
If she betrays and hurts you, you won't be able to bear it.
Why are you outside?
I was waiting for you.
Did you miss me that much?
You should've waited inside. It's cold. Let's go in.
Soo Jo.
Let's go somewhere and talk.
What is it?
I don't wish for much.
I just want you to be happy.
- The woman that you're seeing... - Give me a little more time.
I'll introduce her to you soon.
You don't need to.
I won't meet her.
Why?
If you like her, I will like her too.
But it can't be the woman you're seeing right now.
I went grocery shopping and saw you at the supermarket.
Whose babies were they? They looked like twins.
They're her babies, right?
- Soo Jo. - Listen to me first.
I have nothing to hear from you. I don't want to hear anything.
I was going to tell you first once I have everything figured out.
She's a nice woman.
She became a single mother due to unfortunate circumstances,
but she never thought about abandoning her children.
She struggles to make ends meet, but she's so good to the boys.
Everybody might disapprove of us, but I need you to take my side.
She makes me laugh just like you do.
I don't like how you said that.
Are you putting me on the same level as her?
That's not what I meant.
End it off before it gets too far. Before the others find out.
You know how it'll go if your mum and grandpa find out.
I can't take your side.
Ms Nam.
Who is it?
It's Do Geum.
Can you let me in?
What's going on? It's late.
Ms Nam.
Let's have some soju.
Come in.
She's seeing a girl with two children?
They're twins.
There are so many women out there. Why her?
Look at him. After all you did to raise him.
He doesn't even care. What's wrong with him?
I'm so upset.
Once Soo Jo makes up his mind, he doesn't get swayed at all.
He's heading straight for trouble.
That's what I'm saying.
Does he lack something?
You said he works at the office.
His mum will go nuts once she finds out.
How's the family?
I'll tell you about it another time.
Gab Dol married a girl you disapproved of.
What am I supposed to do?
Now that I think of it, I don't know why I disapproved of it.
You must be very satisfied with your daughter-in-law.
That's not even the point.
It's either you disapprove until the end and split them apart,
or pretend...
as if you like them from the beginning. It's either of those two.
I initially disapproved, but I let them marry.
We already hurt each other. It's not ideal for neither of us.
- See you later. - See you again.
All right. Goodbye.
She's been missing for over a month.
Can't you just check whether she's dead or alive?
You don't have to tell me.
It's been over a month since we got in contact with her.
She could have gotten into an accident or something.
She ran away due to family problems. You have no choice but to wait.
I just want you to check whether she's dead or alive.
We can't do that.
Are you her husband?
I'm not.
Why are you looking for her then?
We can't do it.
We can't do it even if you were her parent or husband.
We can't tell you even if we knew.
Ddol Ee.
- Grandpa. - Oh dear.
My baby. How are you?
My baby.
Is it good?
It's been a while since I had meat.
Mum only gives me gimbap.
She says I have to eat the leftovers so that they don't go to waste.
Did you eat gimbap every day?
Mum hit me.
She hit you? Why?
I stole my friend's bread.
She hit me here.
I'm living proof, it's true.
Don't say that.
Did it hurt?
It did. I want to live with you.
Okay. Live with me.
Let's go to my house in a few days.
But don't tell Mum.
It's a secret between us.
Goodness.
Hello. It's delivery.
You can leave it there.
You must have a lot of customers.
Everybody says your dishes are tasty.
Really?
Is it expensive to open a business like this?
You can start off in a small space so it's not expensive,
but you need to be a good cook.
If it tastes good, customers will come.
Home-cooked meals are the best.
Don't find me again.
I want a refund.
Welcome.
- I want a refund. - Why?
- They don't taste good. - Sorry?
You bought two yesterday. You can't just return these.
I tried it, and it was so bad. I can't eat it.
I want a refund.
You only brought two pieces back. I can't refund this.
What? Are you saying no?
No, I can't.
What's wrong with you? You're just a part-timer.
You're supposed to listen to the customer.
Haven't you heard, "Customers are the kings"? What a fool.
I may be a fool, but I know enough.
Look at this woman. You don't know what you're saying.
Think about it, ma'am.
You bought 2 cutlassfish and you only brought 2 pieces back.
Does it make sense that I refund you for it?
I can't do that.
Are you out of your mind?
I need to report you to Consumer Protection.
Go ahead.
I don't care if you report or accuse me.
I can't give you a refund.
You're not going to sell fish today. Close the shop.
I'll report you to the police for interrupting business.
What? Hey, come here!
What is this?
Behave yourself!
Let go!
This is nonsense!
- Let go! - Let go of her!
Let go of her! I can't believe this!
- You! - Let go of her!
- Let go of her! - My goodness!
You can't treat me like this!
Is this the police?
- Is this the police? - You can't...
- talk to me like that! - I'm calling from a market.
- Let go of me! - A woman made a complaint,
- and it turned into a big fight. - Stop it!
Gosh, really!
You're bad luck.
You better run your business well.
- For goodness' sake! - She's running away.
Get up. Get up.
You shouldn't have come here.
I abandoned you.
Whether I live of die is none of your business. Go back.
Why didn't you take Ddol Ee along with you?
What did Jae Soon say?
I couldn't even start.
She didn't even look at me.
She has changed so much.
She doesn't feel like our child.
I think we made her become that way.
How can we make her feel better?
Goodness.
A woman asked for a refund after buying two whole fish.
She only brought two pieces back.
What are you talking about?
She sells gimbap in the morning...
and works at a fish store during the day.
Oh my.
Mum.
Weren't you sleeping?
I'll tell you a secret.
Grandpa came to see me at school.
I know.
Cho Rong, weren't you sleeping?
I was waiting for you.
I can't fall asleep.
What if something happened to Ms Shin?
I think she changed her number. I can't reach her.
What if something went wrong?
No way. We'll find her no matter what.
Are you hungry? Shall I make you some noodles?
I'll cook it myself.
Get some sleep. You have school tomorrow.
When did you come home?
Were you looking for her again?
Do you not even eat?
Do you know what you're like these days?
You're struggling to find a woman like that.
Watch what you're saying.
What will you do when you find her?
Will you live with her?
She dumped you for her ex-husband. What will you do?
I don't get you.
You deserve a much better woman. She's not worth it.
You have such low standards for women.
What did you like about her when you were married?
- Stop. - You should stop.
She left you because you lived on the rooftop.
You're so annoying.
Relief Patch, we were supposed to meet today.
Didn't you get my text?
I can't see you for a while.
Why not? What happened?
Aren't you feeling well?
There's no need to worry, but I can't go out.
Did my daughter go there?
No.
Then what is it? Shall I go to your place?
Don't come.
I had a little argument with my son.
Why?
He talks about how much he respects you for all your struggles in life.
Why did you argue with him?
Hang up. I'll call you later.
Relief Patch. Relief Patch.
Sir, people under you are supposed to carry things like this.
Hello.
Let's eat fish cakes.
What was that?
What if people find out?
It's okay. We're working.
- Just working? - I was.
Why? Did you have other intentions?
Gosh, you're so good at this.
I told you I'm good.
What is this?
Hello, ma'am.
Why did you get off from the same car?
I told Ms Ban to come see some fabrics together.
We just came back.
Is that so?
You worked hard today. You may go now.
Yes, sir.
I'll see you later, ma'am.
It's nice that you're working hard,
but people may misunderstand, so don't get along with her.
I'll be careful.
You're ready to bathe the boys, right?
I'll go now.
You can go home now, right?
What brings you here? You didn't even call.
I met someone nearby. I came to go home with you.
I have an appointment.
I came all the way here. You're asking me to go alone?
All right.
Something came up suddenly. I'm sorry.
Il Ho and Ee Ho.
Soo Jo can't come today.
Let's just bathe without him.
You miss him, don't you?
I do too.
Come here.
- You came on purpose, didn't you? - Yes, I did.
That won't change anything.
All right.
Dal Pa,
open the door. Somebody's here.
How dare you come here? Get out.
The adults are here, right?
I said get out.
What's wrong with you?
How disrespectful.
I'm here to see the adults. How dare you do this to me?
Get out. How dare you come here?
How dare you?
Get out!
Come on out.
Let go of me!
- Hey! - Don't do that.
Don't meddle in our business.
This isn't right!
How could he visit the house?
Get out.
Why do you care?
I care because I can.
Let go of him.
You can't do this at my house. Let go.
My gosh.
You shouldn't behave like this to an elder.
Don't ever do that again. You may go now.
Gosh. I'm so dishevelled.
Hello.
I don't want your bow.
Sit down. Let's hear what you have to say.
Mal Nyeon isn't even home. Just tell him to leave.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Kim Sam Sik.
Bring us some tea.
What tea?
Please give me a cup of tea.
Bring it out.
This...
- Sit down. - Okay.
Why does Mal Nyeon meet a man who's just like herself?
Why did you come to our house?
My nose hurts.
I thought my nose broke,
but it's a tiny fracture.
I would've sued you if you were someone else,
but since you're Mal Nyeon's brother, I'm letting it go.
Did you hit him?
Yes.
I believe Mal Nyeon and I are meant to be.
We are made for each other.
I looked for her for 30 years, and it was worth it.
- My nose. - 30 years?
Mal Nyeon and I met 30 years ago.
Didn't you hear?
Wait.
Then you didn't meet her by the dumpster recently?
You were the...
I can't believe this guy.
How can you shamelessly follow her here?
Just keep quiet.
What do you mean? This is ridiculous.
Mal Nyeon even set the wedding date. Because of him...
I'm right. He's the...
Pardon?
It's nothing.
Fine.
Let's say you've been looking for her for 30 years.
What will you do now?
I'll live with her.
I'll right the wrong I did to her...
even though she did me wrong too.
What did she do wrong?
I never knew she set up a wedding date.
I was the one who was fooled.
I wouldn't be a man if I said this now, but I'll say it.
I told her I'd be back and asked her to wait for me.
I went to her after I was discharged,
but she was already married and gone.
My life became a mess after that.
My nose hurts.
Mal Nyeon is trouble.
- Where is she? - She went to the sauna.
By the way,
you didn't get married?
I never did because I couldn't forget her.
You must've saved up quite a bit then.
Since you didn't have any children or wife to support.
What do you do now?
- A club... - Do you own a club?
No, I don't own it.
I console the hearts of the lonely elderly people.
I help two lonely hearts spend the rest of their lives...
What is he saying?
Are you like a matchmaker?
You can say that.
He's a waiter at a club.
Do you have a house?
I'm not greedy for a house since I'm single.
So where do you live now?
Have you heard of...
goshiwon?
- Leave. - Goodness.
I can't help but say, "Goodness."
Is this why she became living proof?
My goodness. I'm sorry but leave now.
What?
Why are you coming out from there?
I introduced myself to your brother...
and told him everything. My nose...
What everything?
You lied and seduced me when I was in the army.
You had someone you were going to marry.
You...
You're crazy! You're mad!
You're crazy!
Hey!
Joong Nyeon. I heard Sam Sik was here.
How can you meet a man like that?
You twisted your own fate.
How could you do that when you even had a wedding date?
- Did you tell him about Dal Pa? - No.
You should tell him. He's the real dad.
Dal Pa should know his real dad.
It isn't something you should hide.
Whether he's good or bad, he's the father.
No way. If Dal Pa finds out, he'll kill me.
Well, he had nothing to show for his life.
He lives in a goshiwon...
and works as a waiter at a club. That's absurd.
Don't even mention that.
Tell me what you'll do to Dal Pa.
I don't want to hurt him any more.
He's a member of the Go family no matter what.
I even had a wedding date set,
but I had Dal Pa with some other guy. If Dal Pa finds out,
he won't treat me like human.
Of course.
Sam Sik won't stay quiet either.
If he finds out that Dal Pa is his son,
he'll follow Dal Pa around right away.
I would've supported Sam Sik if he had anything.
How can he live in a goshiwon?
Plus, he's a waiter who does this at a club.
That'd be the customer. A waiter says,
"Welcome," and "do you want me to find you a partner?"
(Taehwa Store)
Jae Soon!
I don't want to see you.
Don't be like this. Let's talk.
I'm busy. I need to pick up Ddol Ee.
I'll come with you.
I have nothing to say. I'm leaving.
Jae Soon. Please don't do this.
If I did something wrong, scold me.
Don't be so cold. You're scaring me.
Jae Soon, I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry? It's all because I'm useless.
Don't say it like that. Why are you useless?
I'm the firstborn. I feel ashamed.
I don't want you to see me like this.
I was living with my parents after the divorce without any money.
My parents and siblings looked down on me.
It wasn't like that.
People are all the same.
That hurts.
I depended on you whenever I had hardships.
Why didn't you call me?
Don't I mean anything to you?
- Ddol Ee is waiting for me. - I want to see him.
No. Just go home.
Jae Soon. You should at least keep in touch with me.
You'll be too lonely living in an unfamiliar place like this.
You need a person to call if anything goes wrong.
- Why would I call someone? - Don't say that.
I'll come running if you call me.
I think our parents went overboard.
They should've told you even if it was for you.
If you hate them, don't meet them for a while.
Nobody will scold you.
But let's keep in touch, okay?
- Did you get her number? - Yes.
Tell me.
I promised I wouldn't tell anyone.
Only I should call her.
Don't worry too much. I'm sure she'll come around.
She's not a mean person.
She's the meanest one in the family.
It's a relief.
She opened up her heart a bit, and that's good.
You should visit her often.
Okay.
What do we tell Geum Sik? Shouldn't we tell him?
You can't.
Jae Soon told me not to say anything.
She won't see me if I do.
I can understand her.
She probably doesn't want to see Geum Sik the most.
Are women like that?
- Of course. - Of course.
Men aren't like that?
I'd feel sorry.
If my ex isn't doing well,
I'd feel bad and want to help her.
I guess he has someone like her somewhere.
You shouldn't say that.
Geum Sik wouldn't look for her like we did. He's not family.
Is it over between him and Jae Soon?
We can't do anything.
If that's their fate, so be it.
Go home. You said you were busy.
By the way, it's the same family.
What?
The old man my mother-in-law is dating.
It's Se Gye's grandpa-in-law.
- What? - What?
My mother-in-law used to work for that family.
They must've fallen in love while she worked there.
That woman came and made a huge fuss again.
Didn't they break up?
They've been dating secretly.
His daughter is too much.
Why doesn't she just let them date?
What does she know about life?
It's because of money.
If he was a penniless, old man,
she would have jumped for joy.
But there's something strange about it.
What is it?
I don't know if I should say this.
Say it. What is it?
Don't tell anybody else.
I saw a man...
coming out of her room late at night.
Goodness.
That old man dropped by late at night?
My goodness. In the same house where you guys live?
It wasn't him.
It looked like a younger man.
He looked about Mother's age.
She's cheating on him.
That's indecent.
Play dumb.
I did.
He slipped out at night.
Is she dating the old man for money...
and seeing another man at night?
That's skill.
I've been through it all.
I'm living proof. It's true.
Stop it.
This isn't why I've become living proof.
She must have energy left over.
How can she see two men at once?
She's incredible.
(Dongsan District Office)
Why are you going home so late? Everybody else left.
Pardon?
Hello.
Are you always this slow?
I don't like women who are slow.
What do you mean?
I waited for you because I had no options left.
I gave you enough chances. You should notice by now.
Are you clueless or what?
- I can't wait for you any longer. - For what?
- Why aren't you proposing to me? - Sorry?
I would love to do it,
but it looks like you did too so I waited.
I took care of all the other women.
I erased all their numbers and stopped flirting with girls.
I had over 300 girls on my phone, and I erased them all.
Don't forget that this man before you...
is an incredible one.
Why are you doing this to me?
- What's going on? - Tell her.
I don't like women who cry or don't pay for jjajangmyeon.
You always cry.
The food's getting cold.
What's going on with him?
He told me to propose to him.
He's out of his mind.
You shouldn't have listened to him. Just cut him off.
He lives in the community.
That doesn't mean you should listen to everything they say.
You're too hardworking.
Yes, Father.
All right.
I'll deal with him.
We haven't spent time together recently.
Our family's been going through a lot, so we didn't get to drink.
I should have cared more, but I was too busy.
I heard you found Jae Soon.
I feel better now.
It's nothing big.
- It's about your mum. - Okay.
She worked hard all her life.
She must have been lonely.
It's true. It probably bothers her every night.
You must know about it, and you have your own family now.
I can be honest, right?
Of course. He must know.
Your mum should have this in her mind.
She probably couldn't date anybody because of you.
Don't look at her just as your mum...
but a person. She's a woman.
I don't know about others but my mum is not like that.
That's because you only look at her as your mum.
Everybody's like that.
After my father passed away, she hasn't thought about seeing anyone.
She only cares about her children,
and I'm proud of her. I respect her.
You must be proud and respect her.
But do you think that's happiness to her?
She struggled enough. It's time for her to live for herself.
You should let her see that man.
I don't think she's seeing him any more.
That's not what I heard.
She's still seeing him.
Her daughter came to confront her about it,
and Gab Soon had to kick her out.
- Sorry? - You should take your mum's side...
and make her feel at ease.
If they say something rude to her,
you should defend her.
That's what children are supposed to do.
You're home.
What's wrong with you?
Are you still seeing that old man?
What's wrong with you? It's her life.
Let her take care of it.
I told you enough times.
Were you seeing him discreetly?
You promised me you won't see him again.
And what?
What are you really thinking?
What's wrong with you? She can date whomever she wants.
My mum's different.
Come out.
You can do whatever you want.
If you like him so much, leave!
I won't care any more. Do whatever you want.
What's wrong with you?
What about you?
How can you tell your family?
You said I talk too much,
but this is different.
Your dad invited me over. He totally embarrassed me.
It's not like my mum is desperate for men.
It was like I was standing naked in front of them.
Why does your family care whom my mum sees?
Why do they care?
It's for your mum.
You're not letting her date anybody.
What? Date?
Why would she date?
You should accept it. She's a woman too.
Is it because you don't want to live with her?
You want an old man to take her away?
Sure.
It's not like he's poor.
He's rich, so we can benefit too. What's wrong with that?
She can date and eventually marry him.
I don't want her to!
Seriously!
(Mr Yeo)
The person you're trying to reach...
The person you're trying to reach is not available at the moment.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Jae Soon.
I made some side dishes.
The door was locked,
so I waited for you.
I wanted to come every day, but I knew you wouldn't like that.
I don't need them. Please leave.
I'll leave if you take this.
I made some for Ddol Ee.
Please leave.
Don't do this.
Jae Soon, I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
It's entirely my fault.
Please forgive me just this once.
Don't look for somebody worthless like me.
Don't say that.
Why would I think you're a worthless daughter?
You're the most important child to me.
Se Gye and Gab Soon are nothing compared to you.
You're so precious to our entire family.
Your dad and I never thought about you that way.
Jae Soon.
Don't touch me.
Don't do this. Let me hug you.
I said don't.
Please leave. I don't want to see you.
Don't speak like that.
It doesn't sound like you. You sound cold.
You feel like a stranger.
I sound cold?
I feel like a stranger?
I already lost any type of affection for you.
We've been strangers for some time now.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have done that to you.
If it's too hard for you, do you want me to raise Ddol Ee?
No. I will raise my own child.
Please go and take these with you.
You're only giving me more trash to take out.
Leave her alone for a bit.
We know she's okay. It's all right now.
We should live too.
We should eat and laugh.
Come out to the living room. There's a funny show on TV. Come on.
- What are you doing? - Hi. You're here.
What is that?
It's nothing.
(Promissory Note)
Again?
Did your father do something again?
It looks like he borrowed money from his friend.
I even asked him not to lend money to my dad before.
Tell him you can't pay it back.
It's 10,000 dollars.
You haven't even paid off the debt from last year yet.
My dad came and begged me, saying he doesn't know what to do.
He said I should be a good daughter and give him money.
He knows your salary is under distraint, doesn't he?
How can he do this?
Stop it. This is too hard for you.
He must think all doctors make loads of money.
Hello. You're here again, Dr Shin.
Hello.
Let's go.
Don't come here any more.
I'm not afraid of the rumours, but I don't want people...
to talk badly about you.
What do you mean?
Hi, Se Gye.
Now?
Okay.
Se Gye.
I knew you would call me eventually.
My heart was pounding the whole way here.
Let's go out and eat something delicious.
It's my treat.
Gong Joo.
I called you today because I have a favour to ask.
What is it?
I'll do anything.
I heard you posted something on the website of Man Joo's hospital.
That's the meanest and most cowardly thing.
Let me ask you.
Is Man Joo a home wrecker?
She is.
She's not the reason why we got separated.
You know that.
I don't care what people say about me,
but that is where she works.
She has a social life.
You can't ruin her like that.
What would the patients think?
How can she face her fellow doctors and nurses?
You didn't just insult her dignity. You ruined it for good.
You still say she is not the reason,
but you've just made it clear that she is.
Gong Joo. When someone tells you something...
Stop it.
I'm right in front of you, but you only worry about her.
I'm disappointed in you.
If you do something like this again,
I won't stand it.
Se Gye.
I just got off work. I'm on my way home now.
What about the babies?
I worked late today, so I told the nanny to put them to sleep.
I'm hungry, and I miss you.
Give me a minute. I have a solution for both.
- The problem hasn't been solved. - What problem?
I'm not hungry any more, but I still miss you.
Here. Look all you want.
This won't solve it.
I'm looking at you, but I still miss you.
What should I do?
Should I leave my face with you?
Do you like me that much?
How arrogant. I was nice to you, and you got all smug.
When I'm with you, I feel guilty these days.
I don't know if I can do this...
or if I'm doing the right thing.
But...
I want to be with you until the end although I don't know...
what is waiting for us there.
Promise me one thing.
If you meet a woman you want to marry,
leave me.
Leave and don't look back.
Promise me that.
I will stay by your side...
only until then.
Why are you home so late?
You didn't pick up your phone.
You said you'd only have dinner.
Why do you care so much?
We agreed not to do that.
We said each of us would live the way we like.
Did you forget that?
My gosh. I even smell some bad cologne on you.
What have you been doing?
We had pork belly meat and soju,
and went to a karaoke.
Gosh.
We sang and danced.
Everyone was so excited to have an elementary school reunion.
How many people came?
There were five girls and me.
You must've been popular.
Of course.
It was amazing
My goodness.
Dear me.
You do all kinds of things now.
The girls haven't changed at all.
What do you mean, girls? They're all old now.
How could they not change?
They must be all old with wrinkles.
No, they're not.
They're just like before when they were young.
It was so amazing
He's totally excited.
If you're going to disapprove, you must do it until the very end.
If you don't firmly disapprove and have them get married,
you'll both end up getting hurt.
You weren't sleeping?
I was waiting for you.
Have a seat for a while. Everyone's sleeping.
Why drink in the middle of the night?
Soo Jo,
this is wrong.
I don't care if the girl is old without much education.
It's okay even if she's an orphan. However,
having kids is a different story.
You raised me too.
That's why I'm disapproving of her.
I'll live happily.
Honestly, I'm confident enough to be their dad. It's true.
You're not afraid of anything now because you're blinded by love,
but there's nothing more cunning than people's feelings.
How long will that love last?
What will you do when you become sick of her?
Will you abandon them?
That will never happen.
You can't help it when your feelings change.
The babies will be hurt too.
Raising others' kids...
isn't something anyone can do.
I know.
I respect those who raise others' kids more than anyone else.
I don't care. I'm not going to see you do that.
This isn't why I raised you all this time.
What's the matter?
I couldn't fall asleep, so we had a talk.
Let's go upstairs. I'm sleepy now.
Goodnight.
Hello?
What?
She died?
Gosh, it tastes really bad.
I can't do this any more.
Oh my. It's Mr Jo.
Should I call him Geum Sik instead?
How should I call him now?
Hello, Geum Sik. What brings you here?
Come have a seat.
Thank you.
Didn't you go to work?
I guess he came in the middle of his shift.
Have some.
I think he's funny.
It's my first time seeing him. He's hilarious.
He's very popular these days.
You're all really mean.
You don't even know what happened to Jae Soon,
but you're all laughing.
Do you know where I've been?
I went to the morgue at a hospital.
I went there to check the dead body.
I was relieved that it wasn't her,
but my heart raced, and my legs shook.
What if she gives up on her life from struggling so much?
How could you be so calm?
I didn't think you'd be like this.
I'll find poor Jae Soon myself.
What should we do?
I thought he'd given up looking for her after several days.
Oh dear.
Geum Sik, Geum Sik.
I don't want to talk to you any more.
Geum Sik.
I'm really disappointed in you.
It may be possible for others, but you can't do this.
How could you be so happy right now?
We found her.
Sorry?
We found Jae Soon.
You did?
When? Where is she? Is she alive?
She is alive.
Where? Where is she?
In Incheon.
With Ddol Ee?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You should've at least told me.
I'm disappointed.
I wanted to tell you before anyone else.
However, Jae Soon didn't want me to tell you.
She said that she'd run far away if you came to see her.
Why?
She said that she's the most embarrassed to see you.
She said that it hurts her pride...
to let you see her like that.
Where is she? Where in Incheon does she live?
Where does she live?
- We have a delivery order. - All right, sir.