(Episode 8)
It has a nail on it.
Joong Nyeon. Stand up.
My goodness.
You...
Dad. No. You'll kill him.
Today will be his last day as well as mine.
How could you?
- You ruined my daughter's life. - Nae Shim.
- You deserve to die. - Mum.
Nae Shim.
Let go.
Mum.
Stop.
Please stop.
Dad. I'm sorry.
Mum. I'm sorry.
Gab Dol didn't do anything wrong.
I asked him to live with me.
You must be out of your mind.
- Wait. Gab Soon is... - Nae Shim.
Don't.
I'm sorry.
Please don't be angry with Gab Soon.
Hit me instead. Gab Soon is...
I said don't.
What are you saying?
Don't.
Don't say it.
Gab Soon's pregnant, Mum.
The dream was about a baby.
You had a dream.
A dragon flying up to the sky and falling into Gab Soon's arms.
How could you do this to me?
- How could you do this? - Mum.
- Mum. - Mum.
- Don't. - Mum.
Nae Shim.
- Nae Shim. - How could you...
How could you do this?
If you got a girl pregnant,
you should have got approval from both parents.
Do you think that's manly?
Do you still think you're a man?
You're not even human.
How could you...
Do you know what Gab Soon means to us?
Gab Soon.
I know I was wrong.
She stayed with me for 10 years though I'm penniless.
I wanted both our parents to approve...
and have a blessed wedding in front of everyone.
I also want us to have a beautiful wedding, a beautiful house...
and raise a beautiful baby.
But you know why I can't.
I haven't even gotten a job yet.
I don't know when I'll pass the exam.
I can't even rent a room on my own. How can we have a wedding?
To get married in this country, men should provide the house.
I don't even have 10 dollars in my pocket.
I can't afford to get a place. It costs over 100,000 dollars.
We can't have a wedding.
Gab Soon and I are not...
from a family who can support us financially.
This was...
the best I could do.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
You're crazy.
You're a terrible person.
Do you like him that much?
What are you going to do?
Your life is ruined.
Mum. Let's sit down and talk.
She's with child.
I don't want to hear that.
She's not even married yet.
- Get her some water. - Water? Okay.
Goodness.
Mum, drink some water.
What are you going to do now?
I'm sorry, Mum.
Forgive me, Dad.
You should've listened to me sooner.
- I knew you'd be wailing someday. - Aunt.
Say something.
I feel so lonely.
I'm disappointed in you.
I don't want to hear that. Come up with a solution.
Mum.
My gosh.
Goodness.
Dear me.
You're 29 years old already. Was that the best you could do?
I didn't raise you to be like this.
You brat.
You know how much we adored you because you're the youngest.
What do you know? You broke our hearts.
How could you let us down like this?
Dad, I'm sorry.
Goodness. You crazy girl.
Don't take it so seriously.
These days, people often live together before marriage.
No, they don't.
If they could look after themselves,
I wouldn't care if they live together or not.
They're both still jobless.
They just got a place to stay together.
Nobody can accept that.
That's not important. What's important is their happiness.
Now that...
you know she's pregnant, how about letting them get married?
I can't let her marry that jerk.
What else can we do? She's pregnant.
Why does it have to be him of all people?
It's because they're alike.
You should've thought about the consequences.
He's a slacker who can't even get a job. Why would you...
have his baby?
I told you to stop seeing him.
What are you going to do?
This can ruin your life.
Don't be too hard on her.
I'm sure she didn't want this, either.
It must've just happened.
Tell me. What's your plan?
I'm going to have the baby.
What?
I'll hear the wailing soon.
What will you do after that?
Are you going to raise it alone?
What can I do?
Even if it's all my fault and my mistake,
I'm already with child. What do you expect me to do?
I'm so sorry to you and Dad, but there is nothing I can do.
She's starting to become a living proof.
Be quiet.
When did you know about this?
Why didn't you do anything?
You're her brother and sister.
You're going to have the baby?
If you do, how are you going to raise it?
Do you think raising a baby is easy?
He said he will pass the exam no matter what.
Pass? Him?
Wake up. He hasn't been able to pass for the last 10 years.
I'll get a job.
Are you saying you'll get a job, make money,
support his study...
and raise his baby?
You little...
Gosh, Nae Shim.
We worked so hard to support you through university.
Then you tell me you'll have that jerk's baby...
and support his study.
It's all her fate.
She brought this on herself.
Just go out and die.
Get out of my sight!
You never know. She might win a lottery or something.
Aunt.
Do you have to cause trouble to our family all the time?
Why are you getting angry at me?
This happened because of you.
Joong Nyeon. Did you hear that?
Gosh. She can't be serious.
Why is she blaming me for her daughter's mistake?
Would you expect me to do nothing about...
her living with her boyfriend without her parents knowing?
Frankly, you even had a dream about her having a baby.
You saw a dragon going up to the sky and falling into Gab Soon's arms.
I can't take this any more.
Where is he?
Call him. Tell him to come over.
Stop it, Mum.
You beat him up already.
It's both Gab Soon and Gab Dol's fault.
I can't let it pass like this. Let's go.
I need to see his mother who raised him...
so poorly.
Mum.
I need to talk to her, too.
Lead the way.
Dad.
Goodness.
Are we there yet?
We're almost there.
It's too far. You said it's only five minutes away.
Are you kidding me?
You're just going around.
Dad, I'll take care of this.
This won't do you any good.
I have things to say. Where is it?
Where is it?
Excuse me.
Is anybody home?
Who is it?
Go home.
Dad.
Go.
It's between adults.
Who are you?
I'm sorry to bother you at this hour.
Is this where Gab Dol lives?
Yes.
You raised such a pathetic son.
Who are you people?
I'm sorry.
You know Gab Soon, right?
I'm her father.
I'm her mother.
What brings you here?
Gab Dol isn't home.
Can we have this conversation inside?
Hold... Hold on.
I'm at a loss for words.
You're saying...
your daughter got pregnant with Gab Dol's baby,
and they've been even living together.
You think it's his fault and he should be responsible. Is that it?
That's not my son's fault.
Whose fault is it, then?
She's almost 30 now. She should take care of her own body.
Are you saying it's her fault that she got pregnant?
Don't talk like that.
She's being rude.
- What are you going to do? - What?
Your son ruined my daughter's life. You should take your responsibility.
You have to at least compensate for the damages.
Damages?
I don't know what you came here for,
but I didn't like your daughter in the first place.
She's not pretty or smart. She doesn't even have a job.
I can't believe this woman.
How about your son? Is your son so great?
Even if he isn't,
everyone knows that your daughter is the one chasing around my son.
She's not good enough for Gab Dol.
She's the one who helped you when Gab Dol was in the army.
You called her in to do your laundry and cook for you.
You treated her like a maid. You can't say she's not good enough.
If it wasn't for your daughter, Gab Dol would've passed already,
had a teacher wife, enjoying his happy life.
Your daughter seduced my innocent son.
Look at you talk.
You should be thankful my daughter even stayed with your foolish son.
Who seduced who?
Gab Soon stayed with him because she's so naive.
Go ask anyone.
Nobody would go out with a jobless guy.
Why? I need to say the truth.
Now that you're old and don't have anything,
you must have planned to make a fortune through you daughter.
Dream on.
Who are you to blame? She should have taken care of her body herself.
Watch your tongue.
- Calm down. - What are you saying?
You heard her.
Keep still.
You keep on blaming my daughter.
Don't you think that's too harsh?
It's 2 against 1.
Am I wrong?
I was wondering who your son took after. It must be you.
You have no common sense. You ignorant woman.
Yes. I'm an ignorant woman. So what?
Who do you think you are?
Are you looking down on me because I'm living on my own?
Why are you saying that?
Don't you look down on me because I don't have a husband.
Don't you think I have anyone else?
Call anyone. Whoever you want.
(My son)
This phone is turned off. You will be directed to voice mail.
(My daughter)
If nobody's watching,
you'll blame us for hitting you.
Come home quick.
I can't hear you. Speak louder.
What?
Okay. I'll be there soon.
Wait.
What are you going to do?
Do what?
Don't you make my son do anything. I won't let that.
He needs to take responsibility.
Why should we?
Who knows whose baby it is?
Did you check if it's my son's baby?
What on earth are you saying?
Watch your tongue.
Am I wrong?
Get up. Talking like this is useless.
Same here.
Do you think I wanted to come here?
I hate your son too.
Like mother like son.
That woman. I should have grabbed her by her hair.
Being a mother of a daughter makes you powerless.
I was worried what will happen to my daughter carrying a baby.
It annoys me I couldn't say everything I wanted to say.
You should have come quick to back her up.
I couldn't help out.
Mum.
My goodness.
How could they look down on my mum?
I won't let this slide.
Be quiet.
I'm annoyed that you had to take that.
Why did Dad pass away so soon?
If you feel annoyed about this, get a hold of yourself.
Think how things would have been if Geum Sik was still with you.
How reassuring would that have been?
This phone is turned off. You'll be directed to voice mail.
Please speak after the beep.
Where are you?
Turn you phone on right now.
How can you go out drinking after making all this fuss?
I knew it.
Mum had to take it on her own.
They came in a group.
You were out drinking?
Just keep out of this.
Is she pregnant?
Mum, I'm sorry.
I did wrong.
You're sorry?
Do you know Mum's going through all this for you?
Mum's knee...
What do you call the bone again?
You worked at the restaurant.
- Knee cartilage? - Yes, knee cartilage.
She wakes up at 3am and walks up the hilly area to deliver milk.
She goes to tend to the old man in the afternoon.
At night, she can't sleep because her body aches all over.
Then at 3am she wakes up again and delivers milk.
In the afternoon, she goes to care for the old man.
Then lie down with her aching body.
Then at 3am she wakes up and...
That's enough.
No need to repeat it three times.
Think how disappointed Mum would be.
You pull yourself together first.
The fish always stinks from the head downwards.
What would he have learned from you?
I don't want to see you. Get out.
- She wants you to get out. - You too.
Aren't I right?
Look at his eyes. It looks dull.
That's why every time he said he's going out to study,
it sounded like he's going out to live together.
- Soo Jo. - Yes?
You're nothing like them.
Don't you get close with him. You'll walk a different path.
I won't.
What if this affects us?
That reminds me.
Why?
Hold it in.
You need to eat something and take your medicine.
Don't get stressed.
What are you doing?
She's making porridge for Joong Nyeon.
She's making a lot of porridge these days.
You look terrible.
You've aged overnight.
Now you're like my brother.
Watch your tongue today. Don't get on my nerve.
All right.
Get dressed.
Get ready. Before she gets angry.
- Mum. - I told you to come out.
No. I won't.
Let me do this.
I'll manage on my own. I won't let you worry.
I'll do it on my own.
She'll take care of her life.
I told you to come out.
Listen to your mum.
You can't raise a kid on your own.
Mum.
Mum. Just this once.
Just this once. I'll do it my way.
I'll do it my way.
Come here.
Mum.
You can't solve it like this.
- Let go. - Mum.
The hospital won't even do it. It's illegal.
What is this?
Shouldn't we do something before it shows?
Are you going to watch her raise the baby on her own?
Mum. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Mum.
Mum.
I emptied the room.
It must've been tough for the past few days.
Gab Soon is going through more.
What can we do?
It was only natural that both parents were enraged.
I know.
Wait just a bit more.
We need to persuade them and let you get married.
You need to make a move today.
- I know. - Easter egg.
Throw the net.
Then reel it in.
Wait and see.
Hello.
You look sad.
Is something wrong?
What will you have, Sir?
Go away. I don't have an appetite today.
We have high-quality beef that...
Didn't you hear me?
You shouldn't skip a meal, Sir.
She must be hungry.
This is all the change I have.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Let's share your problem.
I don't want you to go through with it alone.
My father wouldn't budge.
What do you mean?
It's my marriage. I told you before, right?
Everyone in my family marries young.
He wants me to go on a blind date this weekend.
A blind date?
Do you have to marry that person?
Our family has been close.
She's 23 years old. She attends Harvard University.
I heard she entered some beauty pageant.
It's giving me a headache.
I should go home early today.
Wait.
I want to take you somewhere.
Welcome.
Pick one.
I want to give you a present.
You pulled me in here for this? I hate it.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
I just wanted to give you something.
I have many of these at home,
but I just don't bother to wear them.
I know you have them piled up in the storage.
It will lighten up your mood.
Just let me buy you one for fun.
This one looks good.
- Try it. - Hey.
What do you think?
Father. I won't go on a blind date.
Don't accept things in a haste.
It will make you look dumb.
No!
Hey. Soo Jo!
Thank you, but I can't accept this.
My father wants to see me. I'll call you.
Soo Jo.
I can't get him even with a luxury watch.
What should I do?
Gab Soon. Are you feeling well?
Don't skip meals. You should eat.
I miss you.
I'm fine.
Let's get through this together. I miss you, too.
He's sitting in front of a book, but it doesn't look like he's studying.
Don't let him go outside.
Don't worry.
What are you doing? It's your working hour.
Nothing.
It's time for my meal.
Man trouble?
He's a man, but not that kind of a man.
Watch out for the men who know you're alone.
You should behave yourself so they won't look down on you.
Don't just grab any men.
Stop it.
I'm sad enough that I'm all alone. You don't have to make it worse.
Don't look down on me because I'm alone.
What's wrong with her? Relief Patch!
He's asleep.
(He's asleep.)
That's mine.
- Why are you crying? - He hit me.
Why did you hit her? You shouldn't hit people.
I didn't hit her.
She threw my toy.
It's not yours.
My dad bought you that.
You still shouldn't have hit her. Are you a bully?
I'm not.
What are you crying about?
You wouldn't like being hit, either.
Be quiet. I can't sleep.
What are you doing? Can't you hear them fighting?
After he moved in, it's always so noisy.
I need to get some sleep before my flight.
You don't know how hard working is, right?
A housewife wouldn't know.
I'm sorry.
Teach him a lesson.
He shouldn't use violence.
You should be good to her.
You shouldn't hit her.
Go to your room.
Are you okay, Da Rong?
- I'll scold Ddol Ee later. - Okay.
They're poor kids without a mother.
He must be acting cheeky because he has you. You should manage him.
Come in.
He wants us to come in.
No.
I can't do that.
No!
She's pregnant.
I know he's not good enough, but we should get them married.
I can't let Gab Soon live with his family.
How can I let her marry him when I know he's incompetent?
He's almost 30, but he's a slacker without a job.
I know Gab Soon will have to work hard to support him.
Besides, you saw how his mother talks about Gab Soon.
It's just her fate.
Does she have to marry him just because he's the father?
Don't just think about the present. Think about the future.
You said you can never have her raising her child by herself.
You couldn't even bear to see...
Jae Soon raising Ddol Ee alone, so you got her married again.
It's different for Gab Soon.
Jae Soon didn't go through much trouble growing up. She's soft.
But Gab Soon is strong. She will survive anything.
She's strong. It's true.
She's so strong that she did something others won't do.
Still, it's better to have an incompetent husband...
than raising a baby on her own.
He's right.
It's better to have a husband.
I expected so much from her.
That wretch.
She was so smart when she was a student.
How could she ruin her life so easily like this?
That's how life is.
Gab Dol isn't a bad guy.
Call Gab Dol's mother and let me talk to her.
What is it?
You already said what you had to say.
I have something important to talk to you about.
I'll wait until you get off work.
I'll see you there.
You don't have to grovel to her.
You two already said what you wanted to say.
I'm sorry about that night.
It took me by surprise.
I didn't realise that it was rude to barge in like that.
I'm so sorry.
That's right. Here.
I visited your house empty-handed.
I bought some chestnuts on my way here.
They're delicious when steamed.
I don't need it.
If you wanted to apologise, your wife should be here, too.
She's sick in bed right now.
Anyhow, I'm sorry...
for what my wife said. I'm sorry.
What do you want to talk about?
Would you like some tea first?
It's okay.
- Well... - If it's about...
marrying the kids, don't even start.
She's already pregnant.
I won't allow it even if they have a couple of babies together.
What shall we do, then?
If it's too much for you right now,
we'll try our best...
Are you planning to ruin my son's future?
Let's not try to make things work. It's pointless.
I feel sorry for my daughter.
She wants to have the baby.
Your daughter is so stubborn.
It's not like I didn't know.
I guess she'll take care of herself.
This is all I have to say.
Please, take this.
I don't need it.
Yes, Mother.
Don't call me mother. I need to see you.
I have a daughter myself...
so I understand your parents' point of view.
Their unmarried daughter is pregnant...
so obviously they want to get her married.
But this isn't how it's supposed to be.
I told you this ahead of time.
You two can't be together.
I'm not doing this for myself.
I'm doing this for my son and you.
If you get married now, it'll be good for nothing.
You'll get divorced within a year.
Even if your parents come and beg, I won't bat an eye.
You're going to have the baby?
Go ahead. It's your baby so you can do whatever you want.
I'll pay half of the child support.
That's what the law says so I'll follow it.
You have an ill-fated relationship with Gab Dol.
Don't even think about continuing this relationship over the baby.
I don't want to see you ever again. You may go.
Gab Soon.
Gab Soon! Gab Soon!
Gab Soon!
Hello! Is anybody there?
Save Gab Soon!
Bring her here.
(Emergency Medical Centre)
Gab Soon fainted.
We're at Se Gye's hospital.
Se Gye.
Gab Soon. Gab Soon!
Move over. I'll do it.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Oh, gosh. - Oh, dear.
- What happened? - Is she alive?
She's fine.
I'll have her here for a day.
It's malnutrition and shock.
And... You see...
She's not pregnant.
What do you mean?
She's not pregnant?
It was a false pregnancy from excessive stress.
It happened because she had fear of getting pregnant.
Plus, her menstrual cycle was irregular due to stress...
and she wasn't having a regular cycle for two months.
Once she's treated for malnutrition and becomes stable, she'll be fine.
I'll get going.
Then was this all fake?
What's the dream about the baby?
Gab Soon.
You heard, right?
I don't even know what we were doing.
I saw two lines for sure.
They say it happens sometimes.
I don't know what to do but laugh.
I'm speechless.
How could this be?
You know what I thought about while I was running with you on my back?
What did you think about?
It's a secret.
I was heavy, right?
No.
You were light.
You were so light...
that it broke my heart.
Gab Soon.
Let's make a promise.
Do you know what it's going to be?
"Get better soon, Gab Soon."
"I'll pass this exam 3,000 percent."
Let's start over again from the beginning.
You're right.
We're such a great match.
When we have a baby in the future,
let's make sure...
we get everybody's blessing.
You're going to get married?
Are you still half asleep?
I'm not talking about right now but after passing the exam.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
You've got the timing all wrong.
Did you have to say that in this situation?
Pass the exam first.
You must be hallucinating.
She wasn't even pregnant and she faked it.
She was trying to drag you down!
How could you talk about her in that way?
Gab Soon almost died because of you.
I'm going to marry her...
regardless of what you say.
That's the end of us, then.
You think I'm really smart and clever, right?
I wasn't as smart as Gab Soon and there's nothing great about me.
Only she would date a guy like me.
No other women in this world would date somebody like me.
Let's be honest.
I'm jobless...
and it's not like I have assets to inherit or a rich father.
On top of that, there's you and Da Hae.
I have to look after both of you. Who's going to want me?
This is the reality, Mum.
You think I'm handsome?
There are loads of guys on the street that look like me.
- I agree. - Gab Soon is a good person.
You know as well as I do that she took care of me for 10 years.
She'd work on part-time jobs to the point that her legs are sore...
so that she can buy me gimbap and tteokbokki.
She even gave me money.
Hey.
How can you say that to Mum?
Think about everything Mum did for you.
She had you in her womb for 10 months,
fed you, clothed you and sent you to school without Dad.
Don't you compare that to gimbap and tteokbokki
She was hospitalised because of you so you should have asked about her.
How could you be so heartless?
Is this the kind of person you are?
I'm so disappointed in you.
What a jerk.
After all I did to raise you, you get swayed by a girl...
and go against your mum?
Is she more important than your own mum?
She lived with me for a while.
Can you accept a daughter-in-law who used to live with another guy?
If I betray her after living with her, I can't be considered a human.
I'm going to take care of Gab Soon...
and I hope you and Da Hae accept her for who she is.
Stop talking rubbish. Get out!
How stubborn. She must have talked him into it.
Go inside.
Mum.
I'm sorry for yelling at you.
Sit down.
What's this?
Mum, this is not right.
Gab Dol.
There's nothing I can do for you.
Like you said, I have no asset for you to inherit...
and once I get old, I'll be a burden to you.
I haven't saved up for my later years.
I go out to work early in the morning...
so that I don't leave you debt but I'm always in this mess.
Your sister will be in mess all her life.
In the end, both of us will burden you.
Gab Dol.
I want you to be happy.
I don't care what anybody in this world says...
as long as you're happy.
If I was better off,
I wouldn't have said no to the woman you love.
If you had a stable job, I wouldn't say no.
But...
you both have nothing so it won't make things better.
You're still young so you may not know...
but I can see through it.
I know how you two will live.
Just because you're young and you like each other,
it doesn't mean that things will work out.
You are not well off...
and you're not good enough so you have to meet a better woman.
You can't survive in this world as the sole provider of the household.
You need to meet a rich, competent woman to have a better life.
Are you going to live worrying about feeding yourselves and your baby?
I don't want that. I don't want you to live like that.
If you had to marry her at any cost,
go ahead.
Rather than watching you marry her...
- Mum! - Mum!
Mum.
Mum!
I asked the boss to pay me in advance,
but he said he could only give me 100 dollars. What should we do?
Where are you going?
Gab Dol!
(Sokcho)
I don't know if it's this house...
or if we're just unlucky.
I feel bad for Gab Dol.
I feel bad for his mum, too.
Not Da Hae, though.
What is it, Professor? Can you not think of an idea?
- Sorry? - That's what you said last time.
You said women must be inspired...
and men must have ideas.
I can't think about anything today.
My soul feels complicated.
My head gets complicated.
You're different from a normal person.
Let's sit quietly and meditate.
Close your eyes.
Who are you thinking about?
I'm not thinking about anybody. What about you?
King Sejong.
I'm thinking about King Sejong the Great in the green background.
I'm thinking about Shin Saimdang as well.
Shin Saimdang in the yellow background.
The Great Shin Saimdang.
Shin what? Is she that famous?
Of course. She's the best of the best.
Next are Yulgok Yi I and Toegye Yi Hwang.
They're strangers to me...
but I miss them dearly.
I miss the coins as well.
The coins?
Admiral Yi Sun Shin.
Open your eyes.
King Sejong, Shin Saimdang, Admiral Yi Sun Shin.
You know where they appear, right?
I've heard of them.
Think carefully.
We can't live without them.
King Sejong, Admiral Yi Sun Shin. And who was that again?
Shin Saimdang.
The yellow background.
King Sejong, Admiral Yi Sun Shin...
and Shin Saimdang.
I got it!
Do you get it?
You think I wouldn't know that?
They're all lead characters of historical dramas.
I got it right.
Is this reality or a dream?
Is this for real or not?
Who's your mum seeing these days?
I don't know.
I need to do a secret investigation on her.
Give her some freedom.
She has a lot to do at work.
Your mum doesn't handle freedom well.
Gong Joo. You know I trust you, right?
I know.
You can't make me angry like your mum.
If I get into an argument with your mum, you have to take my side.
I'm home.
Where were you going about?
Listen to me while you're at my house being fed by me.
Stop going around dating any fool.
He's not a fool.
He watches a lot of historical dramas. He knows a lot.
He's a professor so he's different.
Ddol Ee.
Grandpa!
Oh, dear. My Ddol Ee.
Have you been well?
Didn't you miss me?
I did.
Grandpa. Were you really sick?
I'm all good now.
I had this in my pocket. Do you want it?
Yes.
Are you close to your sisters? Are they nice to you?
I'm not close to them. They hit me.
Why?
They take my toys.
You should take theirs, too.
Don't let them hit you.
Why would you? Hit them back.
Mum cried.
Why? Why did she cry?
I don't know. She cries once in a while.
There was no smoke.
Hello?
Is it Geum Sik?
It's me, Joong Nyeon.
What's going on?
Do you have time for dinner?
Let's have soju together.
I already have dinner plans.
That won't work, then.
Are you free any other time during the week?
This week is a bit tough.
I'll call you another time.
Okay.
I'll wait for your call.
Talk to you later.
Gosh.
- It's me. - Yes, Geum Sik.
I changed my dinner plan. Let's meet today.
Thank you, Geum Sik.
I'll make an appointment at my favourite restaurant.
No, it's okay. We don't have to go to a Japanese restaurant.
We don't have to go to an expensive restaurant.
We can go somewhere I know well.
Sure. See you later.
It's a bit shabby, right?
You don't belong to a place like this but their food is good.
Your clothes might start smelling.
It's okay. I like places like this.
- Have a drink. - Let me pour you a drink.
Sure.
- Give it to me. - Thanks.
Let's drink.
They say businesses are difficult to run. You're incredible.
You have to take care of your health for your family.
Let me do that.
There are ways of doing this right.
You won't know if you haven't done it before.
Here. It's ready. You can eat it now.
Eat up too.
Geum Sik.
Ddol Ee is a boy,
so he might not get along well with the girls.
When boys grow up,
they tend to be more understanding.
But he's young now.
I think Ddol Ee is scared of his sisters.
Hello, Mr Jang.
Hi, Mr Jo. What brings you here?
I'm having dinner with someone.
I'm a regular here since 30 years ago.
I see.
Things got settled well last time thanks to you.
That's good to hear.
How is your wife doing?
I never saw her since the wedding.
How many kids do you have?
I have two girls.
You should have a son.
Yes, maybe.
- We should get together soon. - Sure.
- Go in. - Okay.
- I'll call you sometime. - All right.
I'm sorry.
He's an important client.
It's all right. Don't mind me.
What were you saying earlier?
Nothing.
- Go on and eat. - Okay.
Thank you for making time for me today.
Don't mention it. Take care.
Geum Sik.
Please take good care of...
Ddol Ee and Jae Soon.
Would you like some fruit?
No thanks.
You know...
Please don't report everything about our family.
What are you talking about?
You must have said something for him to say it.
He said Ddol Ee is scared of his sisters.
Did you meet with Dad?
If you have things to say, tell me directly.
We should fix things together.
I don't like the idea of getting other people involved.
Put yourself in my shoes.
Wouldn't you feel the same?
I'm sorry if it upset you.
I'm not upset.
I don't want others talking about our family.
Dad is also our family.
Did something happen?
We haven't talked in days. I'm worried.
Are you stuck at home?
I'm grounded too.
Did you get your phone taken too?
Please text me.
I miss you, Gab Dol.
Are you busy, Mum?
I miss you. Do you have time?
It's me.
Let's meet up.
I'm going to see the kids.
Is that what you had to say?
Why are you not letting me see them?
You even missed the open day. You're not doing it right.
Things just happened.
I won't make you worry. You stay out of it.
They are my children. I have the right to see them.
- What right? - Don't get worked up.
- I'm their mother. - You're so shameless.
Did you forget why we divorced?
Did you forget what you did?
What's that got to do with me seeing my children?
I had no idea I'd get divorced.
It became a trauma, I can't trust people any more.
I got remarried for the kids,
but nobody knows about my divorce or remarriage.
I'm too embarrassed to even tell my friends.
I don't want to talk to you any more. Leave me alone.
I know I did wrong.
I admitted when we divorced.
And I let you divorce me.
But you made me like that.
You left me lonely, busy with your work.
I worked to make money.
Was that for my sake?
Money is just money. Don't make excuses.
You stop making excuses.
You drank and spent money like water because you were lonely?
I don't even want to mention it.
I was always like that.
You were the one chasing around me. Why are you complaining now?
I thought you'd change if we get married.
I even suffered from postpartum depression.
Is that why you did that?
Jerk.
Must you hurt me like this?
Whatever you say, I'll meet them.
- Don't. - I will.
Go on. Hit me.
I'll give you a piece of advice.
Don't forget I won't stay still.
- You haven't changed a bit. - You think you have?
Please leave me alone, and live quietly.
You are a shameful mother to show my children.
I beg you.
(Jae Soon)
- Hi. - Will you be late tonight?
How about dinner?
I'll have to work late.
Don't mind me and go to sleep.
Shall I pack some food for you to share with your employees?
It's fine. Don't worry.
Gab Dol.
Did you go somewhere?
I couldn't reach you for so long.
It was so hard to get out. They're keeping a close eye on me.
What's wrong with your face?
Gab Soon.
Let's...
break up.
What are you saying?
You must be stressed.
I'll be better.
It's too hard for us both.
Before we are ruined even more,
let's put an end here.
Gab Dol.
I won't ever forget you.
You were the best love of my life.
It was only you.
Ever since elementary school.
Meet someone good.
You deserve better man.
There will be no other girl in my life.
You are the last woman.
I can't break up with you. I can't end it like this.
Gab Dol, I'll treat you better.
I won't yell or nag any more.
I'll pass the exam first. I won't be a burden to you.
I'll pass the exam soon, and buy you nice food...
like samgyeopsal. No, I can buy you rib eye.
I'll look after you.
If you don't want to study, don't.
I'll be nicer to your mum.
I've missed you so much.
Don't leave me, please.
Don't do this. You're tiring me.
You don't mean it, right?
I mean it.
Look me in the eyes.
Can you forget about me?
You said you need me.
You said you can't live without me.
How can we break up?
We have so many memories.
We even lived together.
I can't do that.
I can't break up with you, Gab Dol.
Stop being so clingy.
Have some pride.
No. I don't have any pride.
I don't need it if it's you.
I've dated you for 10 years,
but I never felt this way before.
I've never said this.
I love you, Gab Dol.
Can I be honest?
I got tired of you a long time ago.
I just couldn't say it.
You annoy me.
Frankly, I don't like your ugly face and voice.
It gives me goosebumps when you call my name.
My mum's right.
You only bring me bad luck.
You're unlucky.
Unlucky?
Did you say I give you goosebumps?
Yes.
You're unlucky.
One for each year.
Go.
(Our Gab Soon)
What do you think you're doing?
Why do you spend Jae Soon's money? Return all of them.
Return them.
I just wanted to earn more money for my children's sake.
Si Nae!
Give the money back now.
You stole it.
Geum Sik invited us to his house.
Jae Soon didn't fall in love with the guy.
She married him for the money. There is no affection between them.
Why are you slacking off from work? Where have you been?
What if you get fired?
Gosh, you're annoying!
Mind your own business. We don't need you. Get out!