(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
You think I can do it too, right?
What do you think are my chances?
Maybe 0.00001 percent?
(The beginning of one's...)
Forget it then.
I was going to give up on piano anyway.
Thanks to you, I'll be able to give it up easily.
(road to a world-renowned pianist...)
Jin Mok might lose the bet after all.
He's in a slump.
He even looked into switching majors.
(It's the story of the two people...)
You're far from it. You have a long way to go.
(who initiated his start.)
At this rate,
I'm sure both of us will be made fools on stage.
(Episode 3: Let Us All Sing Songs of Joy)
(Jeong Cha Sik)
My goodness.
(You should have made a sound.)
(I knocked and I even coughed.)
(I even tapped on your shoulder.)
(Here are some letters and gifts from your fans.)
(Thank you.)
Another one?
(Who is it from that it makes you so happy?)
(It's a letter from my son.)
(You had a son?)
(Yes.)
(I didn't know, but I have one.)
(He's in Korea.)
Dad, I decided to participate in the "Two Piano Competition".
What? "Two Piano Competition"?
(This is impossible.)
Everyone tells me it's impossible,
but I'll make it possible.
Do you remember Yoo Seul whom I mentioned in my other letter?
We'll be going to the competition together.
Please come to the competition with me,
Yoo Seul.
Okay, I will.
Thank you.
Great.
You think I can do it too, right?
I'm trustworthy and reliable, right?
I knew it.
What do you think are my chances?
Maybe 0.00001 percent?
Wait, then why did you agree to play with me?
I probably have similar chances...
to become a pianist with these eyes.
So I decided to gamble.
If we win the competition by beating the impossible,
I'll trust those numbers...
and start over again.
Are you going to start playing piano again?
Only if we win the competition.
Hey, I'm going to work really hard.
I promise. I'll put my life on it.
I will. I'll make it happen no matter what, just for you.
Let's do this!
I'm not going to put in much effort.
I'll just teach you the basics.
We won't make it anyway, so I don't want to waste my time.
"Roll your hands as if you're holding eggs."
Come on, you stupid.
That's a rule for toddlers.
Your hands are too big to guide with an egg.
For you, this much is perfect.
It's okay. Everyone struggles in the beginning.
Just don't lift your wrist when changing your hands.
It's not bad.
If you lift your wrists, the sounds will jump.
So do it gently.
Okay.
Wrists.
I said, don't lift your wrists!
I didn't lift them.
Don't lie.
You lifted them when you switched from 3 to 1!
How did you know that? Are you sure you're blind?
If I couldn't do it, she would yell and pinch me.
She told me she wouldn't...
put in much effort since we wouldn't make it anyway.
But she was still so scary.
How is it? Don't you think I'm getting there?
As much as a drop in the bucket.
Really? How big is the bucket?
I'm saying, you didn't get much better!
She gets upset and screams.
Are you straining your wrists?
I'm so amazed by you.
How can you only get worse? What's your secret?
You have the most useless hands I've ever known!
Relax the wrists for trills.
You have to play with your fingers. Do I have to tell you again?
Your index finger is too weak.
Can't you do this? Why can't you?
This is so easy, but why can't you do it?
And Yoo Seul gradually became a monster.
And in the end...
Hey! If I could do it, why would I learn it from you?
Forget it. Forget it!
I blew up.
Hey you, index finger! Are you really mine?
Why won't you listen to me? You useless thing!
What should I do?
What a jerk.
- It's my fault for trusting him.
-  Yes, Soo Jung.
I'm sorry, but where am I?
Here? It's Saeim Park.
If you go straight, there is the post office.
Thank you!
Jerk.
If he mentions lessons or the competition one more time,
I'll staple his lips together.
Thank you!
It's me, Cha Sik.
What?
You can't see me, but I'm on my knees.
It's all my fault.
They say one shouldn't go back on their words.
I'm sorry I keep changing my mind...
and also for screaming at you.
Please forgive me.
Do you think such a stupid method...
will make me forgive you?
- Are you smiling?
-  No.
- No, you did.
-  No, I didn't.
I didn't...
Do something about that voice!
Hey. This is funny, right?
I can even sing a song for you.
The sky is pouring out light
Stop it, stop it. It's not funny at all.
And there's a kid standing underneath it
Up, down, up, up, down
Seeing Yoo Seul laugh...
was prettier than I had imagined.
Her smile is so beautiful.
But why did she always keep that stern face of hers?
I can't wait to play with Yoo Seul...
at the competition on stage.
I'm curious to find out...
what her face would say after we finish performing.
I think "Two Piano Competition" is supposed to be in February.
(Do I have any schedules in February?)
(No. Are you thinking of going to Korea?)
(I'm getting more curious...)
(about my son.)
You know that registration deadline for the competition is today, right?
- Yes.
-  Yes.
Seo Jin Mok.
Why haven't you applied yet?
You used to always be the first in line to register.
I'm not participating this time.
Why not?
You should try and participate in all the competitions...
to build experience before your senior year.
I want to build other experiences, too.
What are you doing?
It's snowing.
The snow is acidic these days. I don't want to go bald.
Hey, you look really funny right now.
Everyone is staring at you.
That's fine.
Since I can't see anything, it doesn't embarrass me.
Are you waiting for Larva?
Yes.
Are you sure it's going to be fine joining the competition with him?
What do you mean?
I just hope you're not being forced to go because of him.
It'll be embarrassing if you make a fool of yourself.
I told you.
Since I can't see anything, nothing embarrasses me.
And on top of that, I won't be making a fool of myself.
Cha Sik is improving by the minute.
I began to believe that he may really be Hyun Myung Sae's son.
He's improving so fast.
Am I? Really?
I heard you and Cha Sik made a bet.
It's too bad. I think you'll lose.
You are the one...
who should be scared of getting humiliated.
Yoo Seul!
Then, bye.
Let's go. We have to practise.
Okay.
So it wasn't just me.
I thought that my improvement was like a miracle.
I wonder if this is why people call me a genius.
Is there anyone around?
No.
Hey...
What are you doing?
You're far from it.
You have a long way to go!
At this rate,
I'm sure both of us will be made fools on stage.
I don't want to be humiliated.
Especially in front of Jin Mok.
I dread it.
Are... Are you threatening me?
I'm pleading you.
I'm asking you...
to please make it work.
Don't worry.
I won't humiliate you.
I hate it as much as you do.
I don't want Dumber to look down on me.
- All right.
-  Okay.
How about we put it up a notch?
What do you think about practising until late at night?
Good.
Since the school practice rooms will be empty at night,
- we can practise there.
-  Great!
I'll pick you up at 10pm!
Okay!
- Let's go.
-  Okay.
Hello, it's Jeong Cha Sik.
Did you come to pick up Yoo Seul at this hour?
Yes.
But please don't misunderstand.
We're meeting this late only in order to do something healthy.
I never asked.
You didn't?
How do I look today?
Do I still look like a gangster doing rounds?
No.
You look like a burglar who's about to jump a fence.
What?
What does that mean?
You look cheap and indecent.
What's your secret?
What? What do you mean?
Yoo Seul never played the piano while smiling.
But when she's playing with you, I saw her smiling.
What did you do?
How did you know that?
Why did you think that I wouldn't know?
I'm her mother.
Cha Sik.
Jeong Cha Sik. Are you here?
What?
Yes.
Hey, be quiet. You might wake up my mum.
Okay.
Hey, well...
How about we tell her about your playing piano again?
I think she'll be happy.
No.
She'll have expectations if I tell her.
And I'll be too pressured and mess up.
But still...
Did you bring your bike?
No.
I thought it would be dangerous at night, so I didn't.
It would be bad if you got into an accident and hurt your hands.
That's true.
Let's go.
Okay.
(Used upright piano for sale)
It sounds boring to me, too.
I think this part is the highlight, too.
I like this part the best,
but it's the hardest to play. The feeling's like...
I didn't get the right feelings for it yet.
But you have to feel it to play it.
If you mess up here, you'd be messing up the whole song.
That's how important it is.
Okay.
It's the most dramatic part.
How should I explain the feeling?
Okay, Cha Sik.
We're at the tracks.
- We're in the practice room.
-  I mean, imagine it!
Okay.
There is a really high crossbar in front of you.
You're nervous.
And you're not sure if you can go over it.
But everything becomes calm all of a sudden.
You have a good feeling about it.
You think you might make it.
Your heart beats faster.
In pianissimo...
And then,
you take everything in you to pull it to a crescendo.
Then you jump in a fortissimo.
And you jump over it.
What do you think? Do you think you can do it?
You and I have to split this up and play it.
Of course.
But it might be hard for me to play right away.
Give me some time.
How fast do I have to play it?
It's about 135 BPM on a metronome.
135...
My heart is beating.
And as I start to run...
It's slow. I'm too slow.
How can I bring it up to 135 BPM?
Give it up. You'll never make it.
Hey, can you stop popping up randomly?
I thought you had something going on with that big mouth,
but you've got nothing.
It's so bad, you won't make it even if it kills you.
I agree.
- Keep going.
-  What?
I said, I agree with you, Dumber.
- So keep on talking bad about me.
-  Larva...
I'm not Larva, they call me Raging Bull.
Because I go insane when people talk low of me.
If I see people looking down on me, my blood starts to boil,
and I get so energised from the anger.
That's how I made the national record.
So did you get angry by what I said?
No. Not yet.
So keep on making me mad.
Just stomp on me, will you?
I think if you can make me mad, I could bring it up to 135 BPM.
Do you really think you have talent?
Of course.
That's how everyone starts.
Then they realise how mediocre their talents are,
and they start to wonder if they should continue.
Then they get nervous about becoming a nobody.
That's too weak.
- What?
-  Can't you try harder?
That won't make my blood boil.
- You're an idiot.
-  Try me, stomp on me harder.
Make me as mad as a bonnet.
It's supposed to be a hornet, not a bonnet!
A bonnet is on a car,
and a hornet is the insect.
Don't you know the difference?
"Bonnet" or "Hornet", it's all the same.
Why are you so picky?
You're not an entomologist like Pastre.
It's not Pastre, it's Fabre.
It's all the same.
And I'm not stupid.
(Yoo Seul Piano School)
"Yoo Seul Piano School"?
This Yoo Seul must be that Yoo Seul.
That must be the woman who likes to criticise.
Excuse me.
I saw the poster outside about the used piano.
Gosh, were you drinking?
Don't bother getting up. I'll just take a look.
After you look around,
let me know if you like anything.
My son just started playing the piano.
I wonder which one would be good.
He's improving so fast.
I'm hoping to get something that's not just for beginners.
That might be good for him...
although it's a little expensive.
That's okay. I can just withdraw from my funds.
Rather than investing in something I don't know,
it would be better to invest in my son.
He wants to buy me a building and is working really hard.
Your son is really sweet.
Yes.
So I plan on putting my everything on him.
Don't do that.
What?
Don't put your life...
on such a good son.
I've already done it.
And...
it's like spraying water...
on a kid dragging a cotton blanket.
I was worried that my kid might be having a hard time,
so I saved up the water I'd drink and sprayed it on her.
But when the cotton blanket drank up the water,
it must have been really heavy.
It must have been so hard for her...
to carry all that weight on her small shoulders.
I didn't know this...
and continued to spray more water on her.
The cotton blanket that was so nice and soft...
probably became disgusting.
While the mother suffers from being thirsty,
the child is suffering from the weight.
I'll give you the piano for free.
So don't withdraw your funds...
and don't put your life on him.
He'll die from the pressure.
Our children are full of hopes,
but us, mothers, shouldn't turn it into a nightmare.
So how much faster can you play?
I went up to 95 BPM,
but there's still a long way to go.
I have to bring it up to 135 BPM.
But it's not easy.
Cha Sik.
I've been thinking.
I don't want to own a building.
What? Why not?
I don't know if it's because I'm used to paying rent.
But if I become a landlord, I'd feel like I'm robbing people.
It would make me feel bad.
Really?
Then how about a barbecue place?
You can be the owner of a huge barbecue restaurant.
No.
I'm shy. I don't like having too many people around.
Then what do you want?
Nothing.
I just want to participate in a writing competition...
and become a writer.
A writer?
All right, you can be a writer. I'll help you publish...
and open a party for your book at a hotel.
That's better than being a landlord.
Are you this clever because you're a writer?
You are so classy.
Even if he only played one song,
isn't that really good for three months?
Do you think maybe he really is Hyun Myung Sae's son?
The competition is in a week, right?
He might even win at this rate.
Jin Mok might lose the bet after all.
He's in a slump.
Slump? No way.
- He's not.
-  He is.
He even looked into switching majors.
Is he behind me?
Yes.
Let's go.
Look at him.
What's wrong?
Why did you stop?
What?
Well...
I just got a text from my mum.
She asked me to come home right away.
What is it?
I don't know.
I think I should go.
Can you go home on your own?
Yes, of course.
You should go.
I'm sorry. I'll come pick you up tomorrow.
Okay.
Dumber.
Can you help me?
Help you with what?
Make me mad or teach me. Whatever you can will do.
I have to win this competition.
Gosh.
Why would I help you?
Don't you remember our bet?
Yoo Seul said...
that if we win this competition,
she'll continue playing the piano.
What if you don't win?
She'll really give up on it.
You don't want that too, right?
Why wouldn't I?
We're enemies and she's always looking to put me down.
I'd rather have her quit.
I heard this cut...
was from you beating up a kid who was taking her photo.
Let go.
What kind of crazy person,
especially a pianist,
decides to beat up someone else...
for their enemy while getting their hand hurt?
The number you're calling is currently not available.
What? Why isn't he coming?
Larva.
"Larva". Please record your message.
Why aren't you coming?
Is everything okay?
Is your mother okay?
When will you pick me up tomorrow?
Why aren't you coming?
Answer the phone now! Are you sick?
You didn't give up on the competition, did you?
Are you playing hard to get?
Do you want to die?
Have you seen Cha Sik?
No, I haven't.
He hasn't been around for a while.
I guarantee you...
that you will look for me when I am not around,
and you will be happy to hear my voice.
- It's not like that!
-  Goodness!
What a jerk.
- Gyu Seon.
-  Yes?
What is it?
Can you send Cha Sik a text message with my phone?
Okay.
- I'm listening.
-  Jeong Cha Sik.
This is your last warning.
If you don't come...
to our last practice at 10pm tonight,
I will assume that...
you ran away like a coward, and I won't enter the competition.
Do as you please.
This is driving me crazy.
Why can't I do it?
I should be able to play at this point.
What do I do when tomorrow is the competition?
Please help me, Father.
Come on.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the academy.
What academy?
I'm going to the academy for college entrance exam.
Good, you made the right decision.
Even if you become a good pianist,
all you can do is earn money as a piano instructor.
But it isn't worth it to give up everything...
just to become an instructor.
Don't you agree?
I agree.
I'll be going now.
Current time is 10:10pm.
Fine. Forget it.
This is good because I was going to give up playing anyway.
Thanks to you, I will be able to stop playing without any regrets!
Thank you, Cha Sik!
However, I'll wait five more minutes considering our friendship.
Just five more minutes.
We haven't known each other long enough...
for you to consider our friendship.
Cha Sik.
Why did you come so late?
Why didn't you answer my calls?
You told me you would always protect me!
So did you want to see me?
Did you miss me?
No, not at all.
I didn't miss you at all.
You sounded very desperate in your text messages.
You desperately looked for me.
I am not in the mood to joke around.
Did you finish practising?
Well...
I...
Did you finish practising?
Weren't you able to play it? Is that why you didn't show up?
Tell her, no.
No.
I did it.
Okay, I knew you would make it.
- Play it.
-  What?
Okay.
Why don't you sound confident?
Play the highlight first.
You know where it is, right?
Of course.
You mean this part?
The part that plays in two beats?
Yes, play that part.
Okay.
Listen.
The part that you're playing is the orchestra,
and the part I am playing is the chorus.
You must play the orchestra part loudly and clearly...
for this piece to come to life.
Still,
how can I manage to produce the sound of an orchestra?
You must do it.
You can't miss a note or get any of them mixed.
You can't be offbeat either.
If you play right, you can play...
the scale of an orchestra.
How was it?
That was perfect.
It was perfect. It was overwhelming.
Even I wouldn't be able to play like that.
Really? Was it that good?
Yes. I think your decision to become a pianist...
was the best decision you've ever made.
No matter what happens, do not give up playing the piano. Okay?
Can you repeat...
what you just said?
What?
I was actually thinking of giving up.
I wondered if I was overestimating myself.
I was worried that I would only become an average pianist,
so I kept questioning myself.
Don't question yourself.
Don't worry and don't give up.
You definitely have the talent.
I usually don't approve people,
but I approve of you with all my heart.
Do you want me to repeat what I said?
10 times?
No, I can repeat it 1,000 times.
That is enough.
Thank you, Yoo Seul.
Dumber.
Thank you for today.
If you want to thank me, do whatever it takes...
to make it either by going crazy or by practising.
Win the prize at the competition tomorrow.
Also,
stop calling me Dumber!
Goodness, hello!
I am Cha Sik's mother.
I see.
I should have said hello...
when I bought the piano.
When do you mean?
Isn't this our first time meeting?
You drank soju...
out of a wine glass.
You got drunk and said you'd give me a free piano...
and told me not to put everything...
- on the line for your child.
-  It wasn't me.
You must have mistook me for someone else.
Pardon me? It's definitely...
First, I don't drink and behave that way.
I wouldn't have acted that way drunk.
Second,
I would never give away a piano for free.
- Third,
-  You...
You have a third point?
I would never say...
not to put everything on the line for your child.
Wow, that evil woman...
I'm the one who was dumb enough to pity her.
What's... What's wrong? I didn't say anything.
Don't tell my daughter that I'm here.
She will feel pressured and run away.
Okay, I won't.
The invited judge is Hyun Myung Sae?
How is this possible?
It's more impossible than Cristiano Ronaldo being the referee...
for our soccer game in the neighbourhood.
Why would he come to Korea of all places?
Why would he come all the way from Austria just to be...
the judge for...
a preliminary piano competition?
Why would he...
- come here?
-  I am not sure.
Isn't it one of the two?
Either he has lost his mind,
or he came to see Cha Sik.
Is Cha Sik really Myung Sae's son?
Have you seen Cha Sik?
Goodness.
Do you know where Cha Sik is?
He must be in the waiting room.
But who are you?
Cha Sik!
(Two Piano Competition)
(Guest judge, Hyun Myung Sae)
(A special guest, Hyun Myung Sae)
Are you Jeong Cha Sik?
Yes.
Father, did you come all the way here to see me?
I am also curious to know why you're mistaking me...
for your father.
Cha Sik! Cha Sik!
Have you seen Cha Sik?
- No.
-  No.
- Have you seen Cha Sik?
Goodness, where are you, Cha Sik?
Cha Sik.
Cha...
Cha Sik, did you...
Was it all a lie?
Then it must also be a lie that I'm a genius.
What do I do now?
That's the only thing I believed in which brought me this far.
Cha Sik.
Looking back, I think I was too naive.
Right, Mum?
It was just a photo.
Just a photo.
Cha Sik.
I am sorry.
I am really sorry.
What should I do,
Yoo Seul?
Do you want me to help you?
No way. That's perverted.
Gosh.
How do you feel?
I am fine. How about you?
Aren't you nervous that your father is coming?
What? My father?
I thought you didn't believe he was my father.
No. I believe it now.
Based on your performance yesterday, I'm sure of it.
You are definitely his son.
Right.
What?
You don't sound confident at all.
Gosh. Come to your senses.
Just play like you did yesterday.
Then your dad will approve of you.
You might even get lucky, and he might find you talented.
Wouldn't it be unfair...
if he finds me talented instead of you?
I might get a little upset, but I wouldn't find it unfair.
I told you, I approve of you.
Okay. Thanks.
This doesn't mean I am giving up on myself.
I'm also going to play my best.
I know.
You wait and see.
My performance will be beyond your imagination.
I've improved immensely.
Gosh, your lies are getting worse every day.
I am not lying.
Today is one of the few days in a year when I'm normal.
Keep the promise you made last time.
If you win, you won't give up...
playing the piano.
Okay.
I guarantee you...
that you will smile like this...
after the competition.
I will make sure of that.
Didn't your trip to Korea take too long?
It was okay.
I beg your pardon,
but I have something to tell you.
- Pardon me.
-  Thank you.
I can't believe there are reporters at this competition.
There are even cameras.
They aren't here for the competition.
They're here for Professor Hyun Myung Sae.
Cha Sik and Yoo Seul will win today.
Win?
How do you know that?
It's based on my sixth sense.
Come on!
Why are you here? The competition is starting soon.
Jin Mok, I beg you.
Please play instead of me.
- What?
-  I will be honest.
You were right and I was wrong.
I am neither Hyun Myung Sae's son...
nor a genius. And I couldn't even play up to 135 BPM.
At this rate,
Yoo Seul's performance will be ruined.
This performance may be once in a lifetime chance for her.
I don't want to ruin it for her,
so I beg you.
Please play instead of me.
You're crazy.
Competitions aren't a joke.
How can I play when your name is on the list?
I put up your name instead of mine.
It wouldn't be possible for the final competition,
but they let me since it's the preliminary.
I still can't do it.
I haven't memorised the piece...
Can you play it if you have the music sheets?
Try it.
I will turn the pages.
And this piece is composed by Beethoven arranged by Liszt,
so it's the perfect piece to show your strength.
Ma'am.
Don't run away.
And go on stage.
I will help you.
Okay.
Will you be okay?
Yes, I will be fine.
Of course, I am.
Cha Sik.
I am sorry,
but I want to be alone right now.
Cha Sik, Cha Sik.
I am sorry.
I am really sorry.
I told you already...
that I want to be alone.
I understand, but please listen to me.
I understand how you feel right now.
You understand?
How would you understand?
You don't know...
how many silly things I've done while believing in your lies.
If you had known, you wouldn't have lied to me in the first place.
Do you know...
how excited I was practising with Yoo Seul to become a pianist...
while dreaming of something impossible?
Of course, I do.
Do you? Then you must've known my dream was impossible.
And you must've known how miserable I'd be after realising it.
- Cha Sik...
-  Why did you lie if you had known?
Why?
Why did you go...
to the rooftop of the hospital building?
You were...
thinking about doing something terrible like Yoo Seul did,
right?
I am so scared.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
I wanted to make you feel better.
I wanted to tell you that you are better than anyone,
but I felt so pathetic.
Is that why you lied?
If...
If I told you the truth,
would I have made you feel better?
Would you have felt better if I told you...
that you will be fine because you take after me?
You shouldn't take after me.
What's the use of being...
like me who's a ghostwriter?
That's why I lied.
I thought it'd give you strength if I said you took after someone great.
Gosh.
Cha Sik.
What you just said...
makes me extremely upset.
I've never felt this outraged in my life before.
- What?
-  Follow me!
Next is participant number 17.
The piece is a piano transcription arranged for two pianos...
of Beethoven's "Symphony No. 9 Fourth Movement"
Aren't you going to tell...
Yoo Seul that you're here?
No.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be her choice to be here.
I know this won't happen,
but if you make a mistake intentionally like last time,
you won't ever perform again.
I will pull out all of your hair.
What are you going to do for me if I don't make a mistake?
A compliment.
Did you ask if I would have felt better...
if you had said that I took after you?
Listen carefully. This is my answer.
I am playing...
as your son...
and not as Hyun Myung Sae'.
Father.
I am going to continue playing the piano.
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
You may be right.
I might become...
an average piano instructor because I'm not talented.
But...
I love playing the piano.
So I am okay...
with becoming an average piano instructor after 10 years.
You are okay?
You want to waste your time to become an average instructor?
Yes, I don't care.
It's more important for me...
to think in bed every day that I had an amazing day.
- Jin Mok.
-  It'd be nice to be...
a successful pianist, but even if that's not the case, it's okay.
My next 10 years will be enjoyable...
because...
I'll be doing what I absolutely love.
What happened?
That psychopath is smiling while playing.
I know. I can't believe it.
Bravo.
Wow.
Bravo!
That was the best, Jin Mok.
(Bronze, silver)
(Silver, silver)
(Seo Jin Mok)
(Grand prize of Two Piano Competition)
(Page Turner)
(This story is about a world-renowned pianist...)
(Thank you for watching Page Turner.)