(Episode 19)
Joe Deul Ho will make you a promise.
I will make sure...
Mr Shin Young Il does not drink champagne,
but rather, a cold soup.
- What's his problem?
-  What is he saying?
What is his problem?
Who's that?
May we help you?
We're from the prosecutor's office. Arrest them.
Arrest whom for what?
Wait. Wait. Come on, we're eating here.
- Wait.
-  Hold on.
What are we being arrested for?
Hwang Ae Ra, for violating the Personal Information Act.
What about me?
Did I violate the National Security Law or something?
You're under arrest for usury.
Why are you treating us like terrorists...
for little crimes like that?
I'm their attorney.
- What evidence do you have?
-  Take them away.
Fine! I'll walk on my own!
Please call Mr Joe!
What?
Dae Soo and Ae Ra were taken away?
Okay. Go after them.
I'll be right there.
I need to go somewhere.
What's going on?
It was expected,
but Mr Shin...
arrested my team.
He's becoming more and more childish.
His subordinates are probably overly loyal to him,
and he's probably enjoying it.
I bet he's making more plans right now.
You will face...
mountain after mountain going forward.
Can you handle it?
I expected as much.
Please look after yourself.
Be careful,
at least for Hae Kyung...
and Soo Bin's sake.
Spill it!
My heart...
I'll do it. Step outside.
You'll do it yourself?
I should handle evil villains like him myself.
You're dead now.
Mister. I mean, Sir... What do you mean, a villain?
Why are you doing this to me? I don't understand.
I only run a small private loan business in my neighbourhood.
I'm just a citizen...
You look like a thug.
Pardon?
How do I look like a thug?
People always ask if I'm a hair stylist.
Shut it!
You scared me. I have a weak heart.
I've been a prosecutor for over 20 years.
I've seen many punks like you.
You work with gangsters, don't you?
What do you mean?
I avoid alleys because I'm afraid of gangsters.
The only fault I have is receiving a higher interest than banks...
Hwang Ae Ra. You went to Detective Song and asked...
for someone's personal information without police authorisation.
- I...
-  What are you scheming?
I was only looking for someone.
Who?
I can't tell you.
Why not? Are you sure you didn't sell that information...
- for a voice phishing scam?
-  What?
What are you saying? Would I do that?
I'm so naive that I was scammed out of 3,000 dollars by them.
I got a call three years ago,
and they said something about personal information protection.
So I switched accounts and lost it all.
Sir.
Your investigation is out of line.
Why do you keep working with Joe Deul Ho?
Sir.
Did you drag me here because I work with Mr Joe?
What now?
I can't stand to watch...
your underlings acting out, now that you're the nominee for Minister.
Is this revenge for last night?
Move.
Are you getting ready for your confirmation hearing?
Don't do anything.
Stay out of it.
I'm already in it.
I thought you may have too much assets for a minister,
so I got rid of 30 million dollars for you.
Sure. Thanks.
But that's enough.
My patience is running thin.
There's no need to be patient.
I won't...
go easy on you either.
Do you want to take this all the way?
Do you want to try me?
Sure.
Let's take this all the way.
That's why I started anyway.
What will you do?
If you kick Deul Ho out and cut ties with him,
I'll let go of all your acts of usury, illegal debt collection...
and threatening businesses.
Sir.
I don't know what Mr Joe did wrong that you're doing this,
but all I did was let him use my office.
Then rot in jail for 4 or 5 years.
Why are you doing this?
You have your clients sign over the rights to their bodies, right?
Are you filming a movie?
I told you, I've never done that.
- Good afternoon.
-  Get out!
What are you doing down there?
Why aren't you sitting on the chair? Sit up here.
- May I really?
-  Come and sit.
I'm his attorney.
Explain in detail just how he violated usury laws.
What makes you so confident?
What else? I believe in the laws of this nation.
If you're upset that you couldn't eat the expensive cake last night...
because I poured champagne on it,
let them go and arrest me.
I won't forgive you.
I don't care. Do whatever you want.
If you brought in law-abiding citizens,
you should explain exactly what they did wrong.
Or you should apologise for bringing them in improperly...
and buy them ice cream or something!
You lunatic.
Lunatic? What?
I'm losing my mind.
I'm going crazy.
Are you all right?
Of course. This isn't my first time here.
Sorry about that.
I never knew I'd be back here.
It's been a while since you were here. Do you want to sing a song?
My gosh.
What is it?
Did you order them to arrest...
Deul Ho's employees?
Do I look that bored to you?
We have no reason to arrest them.
I spoke with Mr Kim and told him to let them go.
What do you plan to do with Deul Ho?
Will you let him run around like that?
The higher up you go,
the more jealous people get...
and try to attack you from left and right.
If I were afraid of them, I wouldn't be where I am.
Did you...
do something bad...
that Deul Ho is holding over your head?
What could Deul Ho hold over my head?
I saw Ms Myung Soon.
You saw whom?
Ms Myung Soon, who used to work at our house.
Did Deul Ho bring her?
Yes.
He must've talked about my fake accounts.
Is it true?
Do you believe me or Deul Ho?
I don't believe Deul Ho. I believe Ms Myung Soon.
Don't let Deul Ho manipulate you. You know how he is.
Fine. I used her account.
But it isn't the type of money you think it is.
Tell me the truth.
- Don't you trust me?
-  No.
I want to trust you, so please help me understand.
Goodness.
Did you do something bad...
that Deul Ho is holding over your head?
Let's take this all the way.
That's why I started anyway.
It's me.
Let's meet.
How have you been?
Well.
You need to do something else for me.
Just say the word.
I need you to kill someone in a car accident.
If it all goes well,
I'll make sure you're not dragged into it.
Don't make any mistakes.
Il Goo.
Il Goo, are you okay? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Help!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about that.
What are you sorry for?
This happened because of me.
That prosecutor said he'd send me to prison...
if I don't cut ties with you.
I'll go to prison then.
This is too dangerous.
I've thought about it, and this won't work.
Let's stop here.
Go home.
No, what's better is...
for me to leave the office.
Just a minute.
Are you firing us?
This is extremely dangerous.
When wasn't it?
Run to the roof of a building, steal a patient from a hospital...
and I was almost killed by a hitman.
- You know that.
-  Seriously.
We're almost there.
We need to work together...
Don't be discouraged.
We're following you because we believe in you.
Anyway,
I can't leave.
You can't move out of the office, got that?
I can't leave. No.
And I won't leave.
I won't go either.
Me, neither.
I'm afraid you need to resign...
from your current position as managing partner.
It's not just my opinion.
All the attorneys with a share in Geum San agree on this.
Resign...
for the sake of Geum San.
- Please, resign from leadership.
-  Please, resign from leadership.
Dad.
Are you going somewhere?
I need to go to the office.
Not yet. You can't.
I can't just take this lying down.
I'm meeting the partners one-on-one and talking to them.
Leave it to me.
It won't be easy.
I'm sure it won't,
but I'll convince them somehow.
I'm sorry, Hae Kyung.
I don't want to see you...
being weak.
It'll be impossible if the chief prosecutor...
becomes Minister.
We must take him down before then.
- That's right.
-  Dae Soo and Eun Jo,
move Ms Lee Myung Soon somewhere safe.
I know someone who has an orange farm in Jeju Island.
How about we move her there?
You should avoid airports, train stations and bus terminals.
I know someone who runs a bed-and-breakfast in Ganghwa Island.
What about there?
- Is it safe?
-  Nobody goes there.
Okay. No one can know where Ms Lee Myung Soon is...
before the confirmation hearing.
I got it.
Ae Ra, please work more on locating Shin Chul Soo.
If you can bring him in, that'd be even better.
- You can do it.
-  Okay.
- Let's go.
-  Go on.
Where are we going this time?
Don't worry. We're taking you somewhere very safe.
I'm not sure if I'm doing the right thing by going with you.
Please be patient.
You just have to testify at Mr Shin's confirmation hearing.
Testify?
I don't know anything.
Remember your account that you let him use?
Just tell the truth about that, that's all.
What happens to him...
if I testify?
I don't know.
The citizens will decide.
(Mr Shin)
Is it Mr Shin?
No.
Turn off your phone.
They may track us.
If you don't mind, may I hold onto it for a while?
No, I'll turn it off.
Your call is being forwarded...
Please say a word about becoming the next minister.
I'm not the minister yet. I'm merely a nominee.
We still have the confirmation hearing, too.
The citizens have high hopes for the prosecutor's office.
Would you please say a word?
The prosecutor's office...
will thoroughly investigate and punish...
people of the law who desecrate the law...
because they are paid off or asked for a favour by the wealthy.
Thank you.
After his confirmation hearing, Chief Prosecutor Shin Young Il...
will be sworn in right away as Minister.
Congressman Kim Seung Hyun will preside over the hearing.
This is Chairman Jung Geun Moo's list of people he bribed.
I understand how you feel,
but this alone is insufficient...
to prove the relationship between Shin Young Il...
and Chairman Jung.
Please call me...
as a witness at the confirmation hearing.
That is the only way to stop Mr Shin.
Are you sure about this?
If things go wrong, you'd be handing him...
an exemption instead.
My political career may take a hit as well.
I will obtain...
fool-proof evidence and witnesses before the confirmation hearing.
I've sent a car.
Come out quietly.
She said she wanted to take a walk. Where is she?
Ma'am.
Where are you?
Mr Shin is my saviour.
- I can't testify.
-  Ma'am!
- I'm sorry.
- I'll live in hiding somewhere.
-  Ma'am!
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
What?
- Her phone was definitely off.
-  It was.
How could he have tracked us?
How did he know she was there?
- You weren't followed?
-  No. I'm sure of it.
You should've stuck to her like glue.
I need to eat. I went grocery...
Were you on vacation?
- No, I...
-  I'm sorry.
- We made a mistake.
-  I was gone for a minute.
That Mr Shin is scary.
How did he find her there?
Was anyone here when you left?
- No.
-  No.
- Was anyone by Eun Jo's place?
- Were you tailed?
-  No.
I was very careful.
There was no one.
How did he know?
Mr Joe.
A bug.
Dae Soo, you messed up.
What is wrong with you people?
I'm sorry. It was all my fault. I'm so sorry.
She was an important witness.
It was your fault.
This is so hard.
This is too hard.
Hello? Is this Min Joo Gwan?
Their deliveries take too long.
Order from somewhere else.
Should I?
Why is life so hard?
That's life.
When is the food coming?
I'm sorry, Sir.
Why did you say that to Ji Wook?
I wasn't thinking.
I shouldn't have listened to that lawyer, Mr Joe.
Three years ago,
he lost his job as a prosecutor for taking a bribe.
He has a grudge against me.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you leave the country for a short while?
It won't take long.
I'll make sure you can return once things quiet down.
Yes, Sir.
I made sure your oldest son will get a promotion this fall.
Thank you, Sir.
Thank you.
Mr Shin is not an easy adversary.
I have the slush fund ledger, but that is not enough.
The sole witness for his account under a borrowed name...
has disappeared.
Chairman Jung is unconscious,
and it'll be difficult to find any additional evidence.
The confirmation hearing is drawing near.
Seoul Central District Court.
Case Number 2016-311.
Defendant Jang Shin Woo,
you are found guilty of tax evasion,
Attorney-at-law Act,
and are sentenced to 14 months in prison.
Dad.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
The doctor says I need my rest.
I'll rest soundly in prison.
I'm sorry I couldn't help.
No,
it's what my dad wanted.
How are things going for the confirmation hearing?
I'm working on it.
I need to make sure he doesn't get confirmed.
Do you have a sure-fire plan?
No.
Then what will you do?
I'll have to figure something out,
Whatever happens,
be careful.
Hold it.
What brings you here?
I just came.
I thought he'd be lonely,
so I figured I'd keep him company.
He cant express himself yet.
I know.
I'm not here to do anything,
so don't worry.
Chairman Jung.
Do you recognise me?
It's me, Joe Deul Ho.
Seeing you lying there like that...
This isn't you.
Aren't you lonely and frustrated?
I came because I'm frustrated.
You ran the world...
like it was your toy, with your slush fund and lobbying.
Why are you lying there?
I'm bored because you're just lying there.
Mr Shin is succeeding and going full speed ahead.
Doesn't it make you angry to just lie there?
Aren't you angry?
Aren't you angry that Mr Shin...
stabbed you in the back?
If you're angry, get up and say something.
"I will not go down like this!"
"I refuse to go down like this!"
Or even yell at me and tell me to get out!
You also want me...
to take Mr Shin down, don't you?
We really don't have much time.
Conclusive evidence.
I need conclusive evidence.
Mr Shin will deny...
everything during the confirmation hearing.
I need conclusive evidence.
I must find conclusive evidence.
Il Goo gave me this key just before he died.
(Belongings that are not claimed within 7 days will be removed.)
I'm sure there was an important clue in that locker.
But...
there is no way for me to find out where the locker...
for this key is.
Hi, Soo Bin.
Daddy.
Sorry, I've been too busy to come see you. Sorry.
It's okay.
I know you and Mummy are busy.
How have you been? Have you been busy?
Yes. I went to school,
then piano school, art school...
and even English school.
Why do you have so many classes?
Today is my busiest day.
That's still too many.
Should I ask Mummy to send you to just one academy from now on?
No, I like it. It's fun.
You should rest on your day off.
I'm swamped with cases.
I'm super busy.
I'm going to become really busy, too.
With that? Playing?
I registered for an academy to take my GED.
- Do you mean it?
-  I mean it.
Really?
- Guess what the academy is called.
-  What?
Il Goo Academy.
Are you joking with me? I'm busy.
I mean it. It's in Noyrangjin.
This is fate.
You're joking.
You passed the bar after taking the GED.
You did it, so why can't I?
Fine. Study hard and pass first.
If you pass, I'll do anything you ask.
Do you mean it?
Daddy.
- Daddy!
-  Yes, Soo Bin.
Sorry. I'm really busy now, so let me call you back.
(Il Goo Academy)
(Kang Il Goo)
(Shin Young Il)
What's the matter?
I heard you'll be a witness at the hearing tomorrow.
So what?
Does that concern you?
If you cancel your presence,
I'll reduce the sentence of Mr Jang.
Did I ask you to reduce the sentence?
One who has committed a crime...
must be punished for his deeds.
Is this supposed to be a deal?
This is your last chance.
Same here.
You will end up losing everything.
And...
you will regret it.
You won't be able to prove anything.
You'll end up in court on charges of defamation.
Do you remember Kang Il Goo?
He's my little brother from the orphanage.
You were going to put him in prison...
on Michael Jung's behalf.
What about him?
I was just reminded of him...
all of a sudden.
Isn't there anything you'd like to tell me...
regarding Kang Il Goo?
Is there anything you'd like to confess?
Where are you? Let's talk in person.
Sure.
Today is the day.
Get the job done.
Mr Shin...
will push ahead his plan until the very last moment.
The more he rushes, the easier it will be to trip him over.
However, if I can't trip him,
I might be the one who's tripped.
Nonetheless, I want to meet him...
and ask him...
why he had to do it...
and if it was really necessary.
Hello, Dae Soo.
Mr Joe, won't you come out and drink with us? We're all out.
Sorry. I'm a bit busy at the moment.
Have fun.
We're also busy ourselves.
Come on. We haven't had fun in a while. Come out.
Dae Soo.
Yes?
Thank you.
I really appreciate...
all your help.
Look at you.
Are you saying your goodbyes or something?
- Where is he going?
-  I don't know.
Tell everyone that I'm grateful for all of them.
I can't believe you.
He wants me to tell you both that he's grateful.
What's wrong with him? Come quickly. Right now.
I miss you.
You heard him, right?
I'm sorry. I'm really quite busy.
Have a good time.
All right. Call me if you change your mind.
We're drinking at a bar near the office.
I really have no idea...
what Mr Shin is...
about to do.
Do you think I have the ledger...
or not?
If you have it,
you're going to die.
Do you want to take this all the way?
Do you want to try me?
Hello?
Hae Kyung, it's me.
How are the preparations going for tomorrow?
I'm still preparing for it.
I'll do my best.
I'll look forward to it.
Hae Kyung,
you should never...
be weak.
Take care of yourself first.
All right.
Daddy!
Soo Bin.
Daddy, can we go to an amusement park?
I really want to go with you.
I really want to go with you as well.
Let's go to an amusement park...
and ride a pirate ship.
Let's ride all the rides.
Really?
I'm so excited!
You should finish all your homework before then,
so that Mum won't get mad.
Don't worry. I'm a good girl nowadays.
You are a good girl.
You're the best, Soo Bin.
You need to listen to Mum, all right?
Dad, you have to keep your promise, okay?
Okay, then.
I will keep my promise no matter what.
Help! Help! Il Goo!
I'm sorry!
Good job.
Leave the country for a while.
I don't know why I do that whenever I get drunk.
I woke up, and I was at your place.
I slept well thanks to you.
Today is finally Mr Shin's confirmation hearing.
We'll do fine.
Why am I so nervous and anxious?
Maybe it's because Mr Joe is going to testify.
He wasn't answering his phone this morning.
He didn't answer my call, either.
- Should I try him again now?
-  Yes.
No, no.
He's probably concentrating on doing something big.
Bring this to him.
Let's split this.
Let's be strong. Let's eat and be strong.
(Witness)
We will now begin...
the confirmation hearing...
of Minister nominee,
Shin Young Il, the present Chief Prosecutor.
First, we will hear Shin Young Il's speech.
I am Shin Young Il, the chief prosecutor of Seoul Central.
It is an honour for me to be here...
as the nominee for the position of Minister.
For the past 30 years,
I've fought against corruption and brought about...
justice in society as a prosecutor,
and for that, I am proud of myself.
I will...
do my best to ensure the people of this nation...
can trust in the prosecutors.
Did you know that there are rumours saying you received sponsorship...
from Chairman Jung Geun Moo since you were a junior prosecutor?
Some even call you "Chairman Jang's man".
I've never heard that before.
What do you think about the assertions...
that you took bribes from Chairman Jung and covered up...
Daehwa's various illegal activities?
During my 30 years as a prosecutor,
I did my best and did nothing that I would be ashamed of.
I did nothing illegal.
Where is the witness, Joe Deul Ho?
Did he not show?
He's not here yet.
Since the witness did not appear,
we will have to...
The witness is right here!
The witness is right here.
Here I am.
Joe Deul Ho.
You claimed you could prove the joint corruption between...
the nominee and Daehwa, correct?
Yes.
What I have in my hand...
is the list of people Jung Geun Moo paid...
with his slush fund.
This proof that Chairman Jung Geun Moo...
had been lobbying people in politics and the judicial system.
Let's look at the screen.
Lee Myung Soon, Shin Chul Soo, Yoon Hyun Jong.
As you can see,
these three names are repeated over and over.
These three people...
are not in politics...
or anywhere in the judicial system.
These people...
all have personal relationships with the nominee, Shin Young Il.
More specifically,
they are people who lent Shin Young Il...
their names to make bank accounts.
Shin Young Il,
do you have anything to say about this assertion?
I don't know them.
If there is any doubt,
I'm sure the prosecutor's office will investigate thoroughly.
Furthermore, Joe Deul Ho...
was dishonourably terminated from his position as a prosecutor...
for receiving a bribe from Chairman Jung Geun Moo.
I prosecuted Joe Deul Ho back then...
for taking a bribe.
I believe that is why he is making...
these unfounded accusations.
Joe Deul Ho.
Can you prove your assertions?
If you cannot,
you will be punished for perjury.
Congressman Kim,
and honorable members,
I'd like to call another witness...
in order to prove my assertions.
Please permit it.
As the presiding officer, I will permit it.
The witness is waiting right outside.
- I will bring the person in.
-  Okay.
Oh, my.
Isn't that Chairman Jung?
Can you...
really get Chairman Jung to testify?
Yes, but I will proceed...
with the testimony as his legal agent.
Jung Geun Moo.
Are you able to swear in as a witness?
Sir.
Jung Geun Moo recently had brain surgery for a brain aneurysm.
He is incapacitated both mentally and physically.
That is why the charges against him have been dropped.
I question whether or not he can testify properly.
This is an evaluation from the medical association.
It says Jung Geun Moo...
has a slight handicap in speaking,
but his mental state is perfectly sound.
This evaluation is trustworthy and dependable.
Honourable Sir,
please permit me to assist Chairman Jung Geun Moo...
with his testimony as his legal agent.
Do you approve?
I will permit it.
Mr Jung,
do you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth...
and nothing but the truth.
Are you aware that perjury will be punishable under the law?
You may nod...
or make other movements.
If what I say is true,
please blink once.
If I am wrong, please blink multiple times.
You also want me...
to take Mr Shin down, don't you?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
What's my name?
Is my name Jung Geun Moo?
Will you go with me...
to the confirmation hearing?
Do you want to go with me...
and strip the mask off of Mr Shin and destroy him?
Does 2 plus 2 equal 36?
Okay.
Jung Geun Moo.
Have you ever bribed the nominee, Shin Young Il?
Jung Geun Moo, have you bribed the nominee, Shin Young Il...
by depositing money...
into those accounts under borrowed names?
Nominee. Do you have anything to say in response...
to the witness' statement?
Sir.
Jung Geun Moo...
is resentful of me...
since I arrested him.
That is why he is lying under oath.
Three years ago,
the witness' son, Michael Jung, caused a car accident...
and set fire to the body of the homeless man...
who died in the accident.
Back then,
the witness asked the nominee,
who was the chief prosecutor, to bury the case.
In return, he deposited a million dollars...
into the account under a borrowed name.
Do you admit...
this is true?
Shin Young Il...
instructed me,
a prosecutor a the time, to bury the case.
I withdrew the case...
and buried it.
Sir.
The witness is making statements that cannot be substantiated...
and is making a mockery of the hearing.
I'll prove it now.
Plus, I did not make a mockery of the confirmation hearing.
I have a video...
which I'd like to submit.
Hold on.
Take my hand.
It's the security video of Michael Jung.
I'm sorry...
for giving it to you now.
As you can see, the witness' testimony is true.
I want to make it clear that Shin Young Il,
who hid and manipulated the truth and took money for it,
should not be appointed Minister,
but should be arrested instead!
Shin Young Il.
Do you have anything to say?
This is...
slander and...
a conspiracy against me.
This is...
a serious challenge...
against not only me,
but against prosecutors as a whole.
I will take legal recourse...
against both Chairman Jung Geun Moo...
and Joe Deul Ho.
Fine.
Let's watch the bonus video.
After that, you can take me to court.
- Have a seat.
-  Okay.
My gosh.
That kid, Il Goo...
is a big headache.
Is he still calling?
Several times a day.
Didn't you pay him to go to prison in my son's place?
He didn't even go to prison,
so why should I give money to his orphanage?
He didn't have a proper upbringing, so he must not be trustworthy.
Don't you think we should do something about it?
He's threatening...
to tell the media if I don't pay.
Wouldn't that put you in a pickle?
We should make sure...
we don't have any problems in the future.
Can you take care of it?
We'll fake a car accident.
Would you take care of it?
I'll give you a solid million this time.
Thank you.
- Is that real?
-  Oh, my.