Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Minions Reloaded Team @ Viki
- It seems that person's child is at Moorim School.
- Is it the child?
I heard that you, Chairman Wang Hao,
have one of the parts of the key with you.
The headmaster did not
allow you any free time.
I want to go outside.
I'm sorry.
♫ Now I'm controlling you. ♫
I don't care about what
happened between both of you.
Don't run away. I haven't started yet.
Aren't those Hwang Seon Ah's?
I'm Seon Ah.
♫ I'm fast, I'm fast. Now, feel this. ♫
Hey! Sim Soon Deok! Hey! Sim
Soon Deok!♫ I'm the king. ♫
This punk.
Just a little more...
Wang Chi Ang... Wang Chi Ang!
Soon Deok!
Sim Soon Deok.
♫ Yeah I'm alive,♫
Are you okay? Are you hurt?♬
Look straight at me.
For dozens of times I
will get up once again. ♬
♬ Yeah I am alive. Watch me.Now
close both eyes and feel me ♬.
That's a relief.
It's truly lucky.
♫ Yeah I'm alive. ♫
Wang Chi Ang!
It seems like Soon Deok changed clothes
with Seon ah. Soon Deok is fine, but.
Chi Ang is having surgery.
Hwang Seon Ah!
You're okay, right?
Yeah. What about Chi Ang?
What happened?
He lost a lot of blood...
He's having surgery right now.
Moorim School- Episode 9 -
How can you do work like this? Just
hide until everything calms down.
Perhaps it's good that it happened.
Definitely. Because Chi Ang was hurt,
they probably wouldn't think
it was us that did it.
There was a lot of blood loss,
but due to a friend's quick
help (WHO STOPPED THE BLOOD), we
passed the critical condition.
For now, it's great for him to just rest.
Thank you.
What kind of person would do this?
Let's all think it's a relief
that everyone is fine.
These people definitely knew about Seon Ah.
By chance, do you have any suspicions?
But, there was a reason as to why my dad
didn't allow me to leave the hotel.
Anyway, all the other
children should go back
to the school, this is
the headmaster's order.
Teacher Yoo Di, you'll stay with Chi Ang.
No, I'll stay with him.
There is no duty for me.
I'll stay here as well.
Because of me, Chi Ang got hurt.
I'll take care of him.
It's not your fault. They thought
you were me, so it's my fault.
So I'll take care of him.
If it were like that, it's even
more not okay for you to stay here.
Alright. First, Sam and
Soon Deok will stay here.
- Okay. - Yes.
Let's not make rash decisions.
To be honest, while I was being held as
an hostage, I heard something strange.
What about the kid? Should
I take her to that person?
"That person"?
"Person"?
They definitely said "that person."
Do you have any suspicions?
No... None at all.
About this issue, I think the
headmaster is suspicious.
What?
Just like the exams, the field trip
was a mission. Chi Ang was injured.
And who is Chi Ang? He's the
son of the school's sponsor.
So because the problem might get bigger,
they are trying to blame someone else?
There you go!
If the sponsorship is gone,
there is no more Moorim,
they are trying their best
to cover this problem-
Hey!
Yeah, the headmaster is not such a coward?
Yes. Why does that make no sense?
Yeop Jeong, what do you think?
Stop making assumptions. Why don't you
use this time to practice instead?
Have you already forgotten
what happened to you?
The school is in chaos!
Can I even practice?
You have been in Moorim Institute for 3
years, you can't even handle those jerks.
He's starting again.
Didn't you enter Moorim because you
didn't want to be bullied anymore?
But then, what changed
between then and now?
Back then I... didn't want any trouble...
I'm sure you are embarrassed.
While letting them see how
you have not changed being
weak and useless and letting
us find out about your past.
Me too, I would be embarrassed.
Hey! Yeop Jeong!
Anyway, amateurs like you won't
even think about such things.
Ahoo, this jerk.
Yeob Jung was dissing
you, but I sure am upset.
What are those? Aren't those Seon Ah's?
Seon Ah received the order
from the headmaster
not to leave, so I'm
pretending to be Seon Ah.
Do you know who it could be?
They definitely talked about "that person".
Moorim is facing a serious situation.
A board meeting will surely start soon.
Prof. Beop Gong, the only people who
knew that the kids left school,
are me, the teachers, the students,
and Chairman Wang Hao sponsoring us.
The culprit has to be one of these people.
But rather than asking who did this,
I'd rather first ask myself why.
If, perhaps, you share my perspective,
won't you think this would
lead to the solution faster?
I do not want to suspect
anyone from Moorim.
Sometimes an enemy
can hide in a very close place.
Just like how eighteen years ago,
when Chae Yoon's family was attacked,
some people were suspecting you
were part of the destructive force.
But I believed you until
this day, and here we are.
That has not changed.
However,
I do have some unresolved suspicions
regarding Seon Ah.
- About that... - You said you would
tell me when the time would be right.
Has that time not come yet?
As you have said,
the enemy might be in the closest spot.
Please find out more details
about Chairman Wang Hao.
Yes.
Oh, are you up?
I stayed up all night nursing you.
How is it? Pretty right?
It is pretty.
Si Woo just called. He
asked if you were okay.
I'm fine.
I find you quite burdensome.
Receiving this kind of help from you
you offered me such help.
I'm sorry.
Have I done something burdensome again?
Wang Chi Ang!
- Are you up? - Can you walk alright?
Doesn't your head hurt?
Don't worry, I won't die.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm Wang Chi Ang! Of course I'm okay.
Hey, Sim Soon Deok.
Stupid.
You couldn't avoid that
even now that you're in
Moorim's advanced class?
Well, why couldn't you just avoid
getting kidnapped by those guys?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
Can't you stop apologizing already?
I really am sorry.
As long as your in security, I'm good.
That will do.
They say Chi Ang can be transferred
to our hospital in about a week.
Did the police call?
They don't know where to start.
Since the hotel supervisors
were persuaded too,
it looks like it will be hard to find them.
Will the headmaster just keep silent?
- Maybe if he could explain to us...
- There must be
some kind of meaning to this.
Let's learn the art of
hapkido self-defense.
How should we defend ourselves
when suddenly attacked?
Let us demonstrate.
The situation must be serious.
I know right. All of the
professors are taking part.
Don't tremble. To use this
technique in real-life situations,
The body must respond first.
- Are you alright? - Yes, it's fine.
Professor?
What should I do to advance to
the higher class before finals?
I don't think there is a way
to do it before the finals.
Seeing your speed of development,
I think even advancing after
the finals would be a stretch.
Please get a grip.
- How's Chi Ang? - He's good now.
He's eating well
and just acting like the
normal Wang Chi Ang.
- When are you coming? - Tomorrow.
He'll be alright after he rests at his
mother's house and takes some medicine.
- My son! Chi Ang! Chi Ang!
- I'm hanging up. Hello, Madam.
Soon Deok? How's my Chi Ang?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Minions Reloaded Team @ Viki
Are you really alright?
I perfectly protected my handsome face.
I'm doing great.
What kind of school only contacts me
now after my son's wound up like this?
I told them not to call you.
Look at yourself. You're
overreacting like this again.
But what happened?
Your professors said you were
trying to save a friend.
I am so sorry to interrupt,
but since it's a slight
injury, you shouldn't worry.
Who are you?
I am the security guard responsible
for the safety of Moorim students.
As the school's
representative, I would like
to extend our profound
and sincere apologies.
Well,
what kind of a school has its headmaster
hide away and sends the security guard?
- Mom...  - I should've
looked better into this
weird school your father
wanted to send you to.
You are quitting this school
and coming home right now!
Mom, stop it. You're embarrassing me.
Soon Deok, have you been
here all this time?
Bang Deok called.
- What? - Your dad caused a ruckus on the
cruise. He wanted to turn the ship back.
What?
How can someone stop
in the middle of a
cruise because their
daughter hasn't called?
I even had bad dreams. I worried so
much, so how could I endure that?
But how could it be so bad
for you to yell at them
to turn the boat in the
middle of the Pacific?
Do you think this was some kind of bus?
Stop being so loud and
call Soon Deok again.
What is the use in calling again and again?
Huh? This damn girl...
- Hey? Why won't you just answer
your phone? - Give me that...
Hello? Oh, oh...
I lost my phone, but now I found it. Sorry.
Are you alright?
Dad, what are you talking about?
I'm having so much fun right now.
Really? That's a relief.
What? Pfft, relief...
Nothing's wrong, so don't worry
and have fun sightseeing.
Okay, okay. I'll have lots of fun too,
so you be careful too.
Having fun, my foot.
Where are you going now?
I want to feel the sea breeze some more.
I'm going to borrow that boat from Mr. Kim.
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
Wait... how annoying.
The sun will set soon!
Well, what would we do in
the middle of the sea?
How romantic!
You won't even tell me?
Why so formal? It doesn't suit you.
Wasn't the restriction order
on going out because of this?
You knew in advance
there was a possibility that
something bad could happen to me.
You've always had a lot of secrets.
Things about Mom... and the
reason why I'm afraid of fire.
You were always worried
that something would
happen if I ever went
out of the school.
Tell me. Who in the world
wanted to kidnap me?
Everyone has a weight they have to carry.
To someone that could be responsibility.
To another, it could be a past
that can't be turned back.
To another, it could be a
relationship between people.
Like the amount I can't take on, are
you saying that your secret is heavy?
No,
You'll be able to endure it.
Because you're my brave daughter.
But, what I carry, I do not want
you to take on that baggage.
What you have as a secret,
which one of them is it?
Responsibility, the past... or.
Is it about the relationship between us?
If you can't bear this by
yourself anymore, tell me.
I'll be able to do as much as you can.
Just like you said, I'm your daughter.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Minions Reloaded Team @ Viki
Looks like this powerful energy you're
unable to control is inside your body.
If you can't overcome
this energy by yourself
the pain might never go away.
I heard that 18 years ago, there was a
Jeokpoong member in the Moorim Association.
What do you mean? A lone martial artist?
Yes.
Someone saw a man leaving
with a young child.
How did the person look like?
No, which child did he hold? Boy or girl?
I have not found out to that extent.
Do you know if this witness maybe
saw Hwang Moo Song?
Let's go! Let's go!
As expected, you were there.
Oh?
To play the lullaby?
Yeah.
You knew that I was the
one playing the piano?
Why weren't you playing?
Just because... I didn't
have the energy to do it.
Why aren't you sleeping?
Maybe it's because I haven't
heard the piano playing,
Or because I don't have no one to talk to,
I can't sleep.
Was it Bramhs? (GERMAN COMPOSER)
Yeah, when I was little, it's a
lullaby my mother sang to me often.
Although I haven't told my
father that I remember it,
But I reminisce it sometimes.
To be honest, this is the only thing
I know how to play on the piano.
What's wrong?
Me, too...
You too what?
When I was young, I also liked
hearing this kind of melody.
Oh! Hey, where are you going?
I feel confined. I can walk by myself.
Hold my arm. You can still be dizzy.
When I'm dizzy, I'm going to fall
into your arms. Is that okay?
Yeah, it's better than your
head falling onto the floor.
Are you feeling sad for me now?
You pity me? Or is it compassion?
"You got hurt because of me,
I'll take it all" is that it?
I'll let you help me when
I'm in physical pain, but
what are you going to do
about my emotional pain?
This wound is much deeper.
Hey, this...
I can take a walk alone.
Is it going well? Hurry up
and come back to your bed.
♫ A handful of tears, ♫
♫the meaning was in darkness. ♫
♬ Even when steps are taken ♬
♫ even when I let out a long breath
For the first time in my life,
I thought I had a friend.
♫ Where does this lead to? ♫
This is what I thought.
Sorry.
I don't want to hear this.♬
Goodbye, goodbye this word. ♬
♬ Goodbye, please don't say goodbye. ♬.
Are you okay?
You say you woke up. Let's see each other
soon.♬ Baby, I must've been too young. ♬
♬ Baby, I must've been
too much of a coward. ♬
♬ If I knew it'd end up like this, ♬
♬ I thought only sweet
things were in my hands ♬
♬ Goodbye, please don't say goodbye. ♬.
That's believing a delusion.
Get your head straight, Hwang Seon Ah!
I'm coming back home today! Expect a lot!
Yoon Si Woo! Soon Deok and Chi
Wang are coming back today.
- Really? - Yeah.
Hey...
Slowly, careful, careful!
Omona, omona. You're here?
I told you I was okay.
I'll go back to school.
You want to see me die?
Yeah, even for a few days, just stay here.
I'll visit often.
Omona, your face got so much smaller!
I'll make a very special dish for you!
Let's have lunch.
Careful, careful...
Are you waiting for your friends?
I feel safe in this school, weirdly enough.
I feel like the barrier isn't
restraining me, but protecting me.
I wish they would just come back faster.
I was hesitating in saying this,
but when Soon Deok was
kidnapped, I saw a man.
My head and ears hurt like
they haven't in a long
while, but that man just
showed up and healed me.
Just like you did.
I asked him if he
was from the Moorim.
Association, but even
before hearing the answer,
he disappeared.
Could he have a part in all this incident?
Can you describe what he looked like?
What is wrong?
I went to find the Moorim School, but
I couldn't even locate the barrier.
Where are you?
Are you the one who was looking for me?
I'll get back to you.
Eighteen years ago... oh, when
the Moorim successor died.
I heard that back then, Guh
Ji was involved in this.
That is true. But those
involved in the affair
were obliterated by the
destructive force,
the 5 other members left,
fearing for their lives.
You know them and how they love to talk.
Does anyone from those
who are now scattered
know more about the
incident in detail?
Now that I think of it, there is this man.
I don't know much about
him, but there is someone
who was watching everything
from a distance.
Soon Deok's mother...
How can you leave your
kid with someone else?
What will you solve by drinking all day?
Just give me more drinks!
It's been ten days since your wife died.
You should think of Soon Deok
and get back on your feet.
There come these guys again.
What do you want?
We'll just have the usual.
By the way, why is the destructive
force gathering its people?
So what, huh? We'll just go
with the flow and make money.
If it goes well, they're
giving so much money.
What do you mean, go well?
I hear they want to steal
the key to Cheon Ui Joo.
Cheon Ui Joo? What's that?
If you have that, you gain all
the strength in the world.
What kind of nonsense is that?
It's true!
There has always been
earthquakes, plagues, flooding,
a lot of people suffered a painful death.
It's all because of the
owner of Cheon Ui Joo.
After getting it, I've heard people
can become invincible or even immortal.
Should we just sneak and take it?
Hey, do you think they're so easy?
But the one from Moorim who has
it shouldn't be easy either...
Cheon Ui Joo?
What's that?
What are they doing?
What do they want to do with the Cheon
Ui Joo? I should just go home...
No.
If only I can get it, my Soon
Deok will never have to suffer.
Who are you?
Where's the Cheon Ui Joo?
Look around.
Go find it!
I have found the key to the Cheon Ui Joo.
But it's only a part.
If you're hiding it, I will kill you.
I swear it's only this one part.
No one leaves until we find
the entire thing. Find it!
Hey!
Mommy, Mommy!
Come on, kid.
What is this?
Mommy!
Oh my... stop crying, stop crying!
It's all in the past, all in the past...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Minions Reloaded Team @ Viki
You startled me.
Sim Soon Deok! Why are you only coming now?
I stopped by my place and work too.
Were you waiting for me?
"Were you waiting for me?"
You weren't? Haha...
Yes, yes I was.
Have you eaten anything?
♬ Today ♬
I knew it. I told you not to skip meals.
I haven't.
I'm just hungry again.
Wow.
It's good!
Don't forget the rice!
And the vegetables too.
Alright.
♬ Like a child who hasn't grown enough ♬.
You're not eating?
I already ate.
Two bowls. ♬ Just
walking with only you ♬
♬ When I look at you ♬
♬ When I hold your hand ♬
- This is a bit salty.
Drink some water while you eat.
Eat a lot.
♬ Love is ♬.
You're eating well.
♬ The love I've learned ♬
♬ Even in my small room ♬.
Why are you looking at me like that?
♬ You are my love ♬
I'm scared.
♬ You don't have to say it,
you can just embrace me ♬
I was scared I might not see you again.
Yoon Si Woo.
Don't disappear from now on.
Don't
♬ My days pass so easily ♬
ever leave me behind again.
♬ The love I've learned ♬.
Why are you looking at me
like you would at a stranger?
How long have you been standing there?
What are you thinking
about so deeply that you
don't even notice when
people sit in front of you?
Isn't it obvious?
Thinking of me?
That's crazy talk.
So it's not that.
I was thinking of a
really interesting story.
Want to hear?
Your sense of humour is
very different from mine.
I'll listen for now.
Once upon a time,
like, in the eighteenth century,
there was this German guy called Schumann.
- What kind of a story is this?
- Will you listen or not?
That guy got a story book from
his dad when he was little.
A story about a golden treasure
which burned in a fire.
The kid actually thought
the treasure was real
and promised himself he'd find it one day.
It was only a short while, but.
That man's eyes looked very sad.
Have you looked into it?
Yes. There's nothing on the records
of our ONP Holding building.
That can't be. I clearly remember it.
You must have been mistaken.
But why are you asking?
It's nothing. I must have
really been mistaken.
Thank you, Secretary Jang.
When he grew up, he became
a very rich businessman.
He wanted to see the world that
he imagined in that story,
and decided to go find the treasure.
He held on to that even as an adult? Jesus.
They all said he was crazy.
That it was just an
absurd, fictional story.
But then? Did he really find it?
What do you think?
There really was a golden treasure?
No one had seen it in real life.
They all thought it was just
a legend, but he found it.
A golden crown, golden chalices, etcetera.
All the things you'd
like too, in abundance.
That doesn't make sense.
What doesn't make sense?
The thing Schumann found and
now the whole world knows
are Trojan artfacts.
Wait a minute. Wasn't that Schliemann?
Heinrich Schliemann?
That's why this...
Look at this. If ask you to
look at the moon the only
thing you'll look at will
be the dirt under my nails.
I am talking about the Cheon Ui Joo now.
Oh, the Cheon Ui Joo that
lets you rule the world?
Even when you were in
school you always said
you'd find it and went to
Moorim Peak and stuff.
Have you still not given up?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Minions Reloaded Team @ Viki
ONP Holdings.
How will I remember all of this?
Even if you don't join
it right now, you
should at least remember
our sponsors, right?
ONP Holdings?
Why do they suddenly want a deal with us?
You don't have to be concerned with that.
It's a paper company.
What is the CEO thinking about
that he sent up a ghost company.
So annoying.
It certainly was there.
Certainly. They're hiding
something from me.
Could my father have something to
do with Soon Deok's kidnapping?
Son, it's time to take your medicine.
Mom. When my dad told you
to send me to Moorim.
School, didn't he
mention anything else?
Something else? What?
Nothing. My dad visited
recently, didn't he?
I thought he'd be staying
for a while, but I
only got to see him a
few times and he left.
I heard things aren't well at the company.
The rumors must be true.
But, why are you asking?
No, it's nothing.
Here.
It's a child called Hwang Seon Ah.
If it's certain that she is Chae
Yoon's daughter, Chae Yeong...
Chae Yoon's lost key
is very likely to be with her.
I heard you have one of
the pieces to the key.
I do have some suspicions
regarding Seon Ah.
- About that... - Is it still not time?
As you said, the enemy can
hide in the closest places.
How long were you guys here?
Since a little while ago.
What brings you here at this hour?
Haven't you seen anyone
suspicious around here?
A suspicious person?
Is something wrong?
Oh, Professor.
What's going on?
Nothing bad happened to you two, right?
Yes, nothing really happened.
Is it morning?
Nothing happened, right?
We're only bothered you came at this hour.
Hello.
I thought I'd sleep in my room, but
I came here to borrow something,
and I just fell asleep.
What the heck?
Professor.
I got it. Go back to sleep.
All right, go on to sleep.
What's going on?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Minions Reloaded Team @ Viki
What is all this?
What's going on?
Who did this to the Headmaster's office?
Has the barrier been broken?
As if kidnapping a student wasn't enough,
now someone wants to harm the headmaster?
This is not an ordinary situation.
Even as this continues, are
you going to keep your
mouth shut about the key,
Chairman Hwang Moo Song?
The key! The key to Cheon Ui Joo!
So to sum up, the rumors about
Cheon Ui Joo are actually true?
Not only that. If we're
to believe Prof.
Beop Gong, the headmaster
has the key to it.
Oh my God.
It was unusual he cared for the school
this much, now the answer is coming out.
Hwang Seon Ah, you don't know anything?
Hwang Seon Ah, wouldn't you telling
us about it correctly be faster?
I'm hearing it for the first time.
Does it make sense that the Chairman's
daughter doesn't know about it?
All this time weren't you working how
to take over the Chairman's place?
That's right. Weren't you going
to become the successor?
It's not that. I just...
You're really pathetic.
What about you? Have you known
all about the Cheon Ui Joo?
Listen up carefully. This is the
difference between me and you guys.
Yeop Jeong, if there's anything you know,
say it. Don't beat around the bush.
That was not something to be brought
up in front of the children.
It was going to be known
by everybody someday.
The barrier has certainly not been broken.
It isn't an outside force.
Then that means it was an inside job.
Isn't that worse?
As expected... to find the Cheon Ui Joo...
Professor Beop Gong. We cannot know
if the Cheon Ui Joo was their goal.
Do not make reckless assumptions.
The voice of doubt, claiming
that eighteen years ago,
you were the one who stole the key
from Chae Yoon, is ever stronger.
Of course, you wouldn't have...
Please stop!
Professor Beop Gong, weren't you one
who wasn't swayed by unfounded rumors?
I am only saying that if you
have one part of the key,
I would like to help you
find the others as well.
Do you really not have it?
So the Cheon Ui Joo that gives you all
the power in the world really existed.
To think that the key
was with the Chairman.
It isn't guaranteed that
the Chairman has the key.
What is with that key?
Why is it so important
that the Headmaster's
office was ransacked?
Eighteen years ago, the Moorim Association
was assaulted by the destructive force.
Assault?
The victims were the Moorim representative
guarding the key and his family.
But something happened that night,
and the key just disappeared.
So then, the destructive force took it?
What's the destructive force?
It's an organization within Moorim.
Instead of protecting
the Cheon Ui Joo, they
intended to use it for
selfish purposes.
It seems like their true
identity has yet to be revealed.
Then, if the missing key
is with the Chairman,
the Headmaster is...
The man who died then was the
Headmaster's best friend.
Within the family, there
were young children too.
There's no way... The Headmaster
isn't someone who would do that.
That's how the rumors go.
But if the key to the Cheon
Ui Joo is in this school...
The rumor would then be true.
If the destructive force
wants to terrorize us,
shouldn't we do something about it?
This isn't something we can
just cover up, Headmaster!
The students should be
informed and well prepared.
I have an idea.
Are you sleeping?
No.
The thing is...
Let's sleep.
Okay. Sleep tight.
Headmaster.
Everyone is very confused.
Of course, I am too.
I was about your age when I
heard about the Cheon Ui Joo.
Do you really have it?
Better than saying that I have it,
this school having it would be right.
Because the reason I wanted to establish
Moorim School was because of that friend.
The one you've told me about last time?
Yes. Actually I am only
substituting that friend.
Also, in order to be the
owner of Moorim School, the
student that has the abilities
to safeguard the key,
is still trying to be found.
Wait.
It seems like we are not
the only ones awake.
Are you feeling better now?
I am all good. Thanks to your help.
Could the ONP Holdings you mentioned.
That's what I want to ask.
I know the company has
many buildings and
partners in Seoul, but...
It's strange that this
happened exactly there.
Soon Deok was kidnapped and I
was hurt there of all places.
That company has been done
for since a long time ago.
Does my father know about this as well?
I haven't told him. Why?
I did not want him to be
disappointed in you again.
The Chairman has been
making great efforts to
push you forward as the
official successor.
What?
But the lack of a sound justification
was always the problem.
A justification?
The perfect reason for him to
confidently name you his heir.
Are you going to keep silent
about the key, Headmaster?
The key to Cheon Ui Joo!
If someone find Cheon Ui Joo but isn't
worthy, the world will be in uproar.
Should anything happen to me...
Become a strong son to the Chairman.
A man qualified to take
the greatest position, who
always wins over his enemies,
a powerful man who can
lead such a great group.
Moorim isn't an ordinary school.
This is why the Chairman sent you there.
First, become acknowledged at Moorim.
The Chairman wants a strong heir.
Actually, I am only
substituting that friend.
And I am still searching for
the student who would be able
to lead this school and
protect the Cheon Ui Joo.
Moorim SchoolPreview
I'm getting scared. What if I can't
handle the past that I've forgotten?
What should I do then?
I won't give up on you. I
will become a strong person.
Have you found the culprit?
I'm waiting for it. Thus,
we need one more teacher.
Tae-kwon-do!
He's really trying to see
our school's number one.
- Moorim Competition?- He's letting
people from the outside in.
Judge well if you're on the same side.
Don't fall behind later.
A friend has died. Why are
you looking for Soon Deok?
You have hidden something
from me all this time?
Something might happen to Soon Deok.
Will that really be okay for you?
Do as you wish. I'll do it my way.
You do you, and I'll do me. Are you
going to take part in the competition?
Don't imagine anything.
♬ Yeah I am alive♬