Subtitles by DramaFever
[My Wife's Having An Affair This Week]
[Episode 10]
Dear Toycrane,
I have a question for you.
Can you forget that your wife
was held by another guy?
Of course.
I can forget it.
I can forgive her.
No. I have already forgiven her.
Forgive her?
I told you not to forgive her.
All right. Forgive her, and live as
a moron for the rest of your life.
- Geez.
- What? What is it?
- Let me see.
- That's great. Great.
- What do you mean that's great?
- Oh my.
You...
Toycrane, you can't do this.
You should never forgive her.
You will be the only one that will
get hurt. A traitor has to go to hell.
It has been a while.
Just the two of us, drinking together...
You're right.
How are things going at work?
I don't do identity work that
much these days.
I'm focusing on making brochures.
So I'm not that busy.
It's been a while. Let's toast.
I got some information about
that flirtatious wife.
She's a graphic designer.
Joon Soo, what are you looking for?
Where did you put my crayons?
- Crayons?
- Crayons...
I'll find them for you.
It's right here. I found your crayons.
Ta da.
Oh. Isn't this a telescope?
Wow, he still has this?
Wow, it looks so fancy.
That's right. Producer Do was part of
the Telescope Team in college, right?
Yes. Soo Yeon was part of the Telescope
Team, and Hyun Woo followed her.
Wow. I can see your pores very clearly--
Oh my.
Hold on.
2008. 11. 27?
November 27 is Mom's birthday.
Is tomorrow your mom's birthday?
Were you drawing that to give it
to her as her birthday gift?
It's all done.
Your mom will be so happy
when she sees this.
It would be great if your dad,
mom, and you
could celebrate her birthday
together tomorrow, right?
Yes, that would be so nice.
Are you going to put that
up on the wall?
Why would you say that?
Joon Soo might get disappointed.
- So we can't disappoint him.
- How can we not disappoint him?
You and I have to work together.
Joon Soo, let's go to bed.
Is he sleeping?
It's much better to not have you around
when I'm putting him to bed.
This is what I learned from
babysitting Joon Soo.
I can see why people say
moms are the greatest.
That's right. They are the greatest.
- Don't you want to be the greatest too?
- In my next life maybe?
- Hyun Woo is here.
- You're here.
Yes, I'm here.
- What about Joon Soo?
- He's sleeping.
Is he sleeping? Thanks guys.
Babysitting for two days...
- Are you guys tired?
- Do you know what day tomorrow is?
Tomorrow? What about tomorrow?
- Do you really not know?
- What?
This means you missed it every year.
Tomorrow is Soo Yeon's birthday.
Joon Soo remembers it. He even drew
something to give to her as a present.
That's right. Today is the 26th.
Buy some flowers and a cake
when you come home tomorrow.
We're not living together.
Do you think she'd come here?
She'll be here. For Joon Soo's sake...
Since you're here, we'll get going.
Let's go Writer Kwon.
I'm sorry, and thank you guys.
I will buy you guys a fancy meal later.
- Take a rest.
- We will get going.
Thank you so much.
Aren't you hungry?
Should we go grab something to eat?
It is a perfect day to eat
roasted clam with soju.
But I'm too tired. Let's just head home.
- Why? Let's go eat.
- I'm tired.
Please wake me up when we get home.
You are being disrespectful
to the driver.
Why would you call this
a passenger seat?
You have to talk and run errands
for the driver--
Why? Why? Why?
Hey, Writer Kwon.
Are you happy now?
Wake me up when we get home.
She never gives me a break.
Okay. Let's go.
Writer Kwon, wake up. We are here.
The wind tastes salty?
It feels like we're at the beach--
What is this?
- Where are we?
- I had hard time driving here.
- Did you just kidnap me?
- Kidnap?
You said you want to eat roasted clam.
You said we must eat it at the beach.
That's what you said on our way here.
Forget it. If you don't want to eat it,
I'm going to eat alone.
- How could you change your words...
- Producer Ann.
There's a famous restaurant.
It's this way.
Oh my. It's hot.
This is the downside of
eating roasted clam.
I'm in a war, trying to save
some roasted clams.
- Is it done?
- Wait.
You can't eat that yet.
I can just sterilize it.
What would you have done
if I hadn't brought you here?
Don't even try to trick me
again like this.
Trick you? This is what you said earlier.
You have to eat roasted clam at the beach
if you want to really enjoy it.
- Did I say that?
- Gosh.
All right. Let's be honest.
Why did you say that to me?
I don't even remember. I guess I was
just talking to myself.
Don't pretend like you don't remember it.
You were clearly trying to say
"Joon Young, take me to the beach."
That's what you were trying to say.
Ask anyone out there...
"Joon Young, I want to eat roasted clam
so let's go to the beach together."
- No.
- Yes.
- I said no.
- I said yes.
- No.
- He is right.
I think what he says is right.
Doesn't that mean
"Let's go to the beach together?"
Right?
Based on what you guys just said,
she likes him.
How could you take it that far?
When I was dating my wife
She wanted to go to the beach.
That's how we got married.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I will put an end to this.
I had a bad cold.
And she bought me medicine.
It's done. That's my favorite part.
It's the best when she takes care of
you when you are sick.
That means it's okay if I'm sick,
but I can't watch you suffer.
I'm not sure why I have to
explain to those guys about
that incident.
I got tired of him sniffling
during our meeting
so I gave him the medicine.
It was the one that I took before.
You wouldn't give it to him
if you don't like him.
That's right.
You guys speak the truth.
Look at her. She is a bit aggressive.
I think you guys are
a match made in heaven.
Sir, even if he was the only man in
in this universe
I couldn't date him. Because--
Men are all garbage.
Sister, men are all garbage.
After he sleeps with you,
he will change his mind.
I finally found someone
who can understand me.
- Can I join you?
- Come here. Join me.
- Let's have a drink.
- Great.
Drink.
- Cheers.
- Do you really think I would do that?
Oh, he is handsome.
You're the worst.
Be careful.
Hey, do you guys think I'm a garbage?
- No.
This is what the life is all about.
- Cheers.
Drink it.
I used to be pretty too.
How did I become...
so lame?
You were pretty back in the day.
You're still pretty, but
you seem like an old single man.
But you can change that.
Pig? Did you just say I'm a pig?
Sir, can I order some pork rinds?
What is going on here? Why would you eat
pork rinds at the beach?
Pork rind?
Sir, do you have pork rind here?
We sell roasted clam here,
why would we have pork rind?
You guys are all drunk.
You guys should go home.
Let's go. Go.
- Drink some more.
- No, I'm not going.
- I'm not going.
- You are--
You scared me.
Honey, when did you get back?
A while ago.
Why did you come back all of sudden?
You should have called me.
I would have waited for you.
I told you I would be back
by our anniversary.
Oh.
It's past 12 o'clock already.
Congratulations.
You and I.
Our wedding anniversary.
Honey, let's blow out
the candles together.
Wow.
What is this? Can I take a look?
Honey. Isn't this the building
in Seochodong?
What is this?
The owner of the building is...
It says Choi Yoon Ki.
That's the building that my grandfather
gave to me himself.
Honey.
I don't think I can take this.
I know that you love me.
I will just take your heart.
I can't take this.
I was planning on giving this to you.
- Take it.
- Gosh.
This is what your grandfather
gave to you.
I have to take good care of this.
You will do great.
Come in, come in.
Why did you come to our house?
I came to drink, drink, and drink.
What kind do you want to drink?
I came to drink everything.
Drink, drink, drink.
This is great.
You drink coffee as if it is
hangover soup.
I had a drink with Writer Kwon.
What? Did she abandon you
on the street again?
I was at my house when I woke up.
You're growing up.
Talk with Bo Young and pick a date.
I have to buy you guys a meal
for babysitting Joon Soo.
I guess you really drank a lot.
I'm sorry.
I was thinking about something.
Thank you. I can just eat
instant cup ramen.
It can hurt your stomach
if you eat ramen.
I didn't mean to do this,
but sorry for causing you trouble.
I'm the one causing trouble.
- Thank you for babysitting Joon Soo.
- Oh.
It was tiring, right?
Joon Soo is a bit picky.
That's right.
I think he's like Producer Do.
Oh, happy birthday.
How did you know that?
Joon Soo. He was totally ready
to celebrate your birthday.
I think it might be best
to go see Joon Soo today.
I know I have no right to say this...
But if you guys stay like this, it will
make things harder for both of you.
And more than anything,
I feel bad for Joon Soo.
I'm not saying this because
I'm tired of babysitting Joon Soo.
That's not it.
I know. Thank you.
Oh my. It's hot.
I'm going to finish this.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Can I buy a flower basket?
- A flower basket?
- What is it for?
- It's a birthday present.
Do you want to take a look
at this pamphlet?
- I can take it today, right?
- Yes.
- Can I include a card too?
- Of course.
Ms. Jung Soo Yeon.
- Yes?
- Here's your flower basket.
- It's so pretty.
- She must be so happy.
Did your husband send it?
- He must be a great guy.
- She must be so happy.
I can't ever forgive the one
who betrayed her family.
Your husband might have forgiven you.
But I can't forgive you.
What's wrong, Team Leader Jung?
It's nothing.
- We should go back to work.
- Okay.
[I got some information about
that flirtatious wife.]
[She is a graphic designer.]
Mom.
Joon Soo.
This is not my cell phone.
I asked her to call you for me.
Good job.
Are you coming home today?
It's your birthday.
Of course, I will be there, Joon Soo.
Okay. See you later, Joon Soo.
Bye.
Do you remember that guy's post
about his wife cheating on him?
- Was it Toycrane?
- Of course I know. It was a hot issue.
- Someone found out what she does.
- Really?
- She's graphic designer.
- Isn't Joon Soo's Mom
- a graphic designer too?
- Then she might know her.
Isn't she all done if they found her?
It will be a mess once they get
a picture of her.
She won't be able to live
in that neighborhood.
I feel bad about the kid. Everyone will
talk about them behind their back.
Honey. Joon Soo.
- Happy birthday.
Dad, cake.
Happy birthday to you.
Dear Mom.
Happy birthday.
This is my present.
You have a present for me?
Wow, did you really draw this?
Thank you, Joon Soo.
Dad, give her your present too.
Here.
It's nothing special.
- Thank you.
- It's nothing.
You haven't eat dinner yet, right?
- Should we eat out?
- Great.
Let's go. Let's take this.
He was excited about your
birthday party all day.
He must have been tired.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for always leaving you behind.
Don't say that. I will get going.
Okay.
What should I say to Joon Soo?
He thinks you came back home
to stay here.
I'll call him and talk to him tomorrow.
Okay then.
By any chance...
Huh?
Never mind.
What? Did something happen?
No. I will get going.
I sent a flower basket
to Toycrane's wife today.
- Don't lie to us.
- Prove it.
[Receipt]
You are totally making it up.
- Really?
- Show her address.
Post a picture of her.
Are you throwing your garbage--
Did you receive a flower basket today?
The message board...
I think so.
Why? Who are those people?
- How is that possible?
- There's a way if you look into it.
Some people only use one ID
for all websites.
When you search for a ID on
a search engine
you can find shopping history
and question search history.
You can find what people wrote
on some website.
They might have found personal info
on one of those random posts.
They could have gotten some hints from
the posts you posted earlier.
If it's not that...
It's illegal.
But you can find out who
that is by searching his IP.
What am I supposed to do?
I think Soo Yeon was very surprised.
Soo Yeon.
I'm so sorry.
I was a fool. If I didn't post
those things there
this wouldn't have happened.
But you don't have to worry too much.
Everything will be okay.
I will take care of everything so--
What should we do with our Joon Soo?
It's my fault.
People can point fingers at me.
But Joon Soo...
Honey, they can't do that
to our Joon Soo.
Not Joon Soo...
No. Nothing will happen.
Nothing will happen to
either Joon Soo or you.
I promise you. Okay?
Don't worry.
Why is this on here?
You must have posted it on the internet.
And everyone is allowed to see it.
So you just searched for my ID
and this is what you found?
Yes.
- On the flip-side...
- Yes.
If I know someone's ID, I can
find out who that person is, right?
Yes, if you get lucky.
Then search for this ID.
[Adultery Patch]
It's clean.
I googled it, but nothing popped up.
Search on the message board. Hurry.
The message board? It's the same.
It's clean.
My stuff is all over the internet,
Why isn't any of his stuff popping up?
It seems like he just made a new ID.
What? Can you track IP?
- That's illegal.
- Just try it.
- It's illegal.
- Just do it. Give it a try.
Why are you trying to search
for this ID?
Never mind.
Oh, okay. Okay.
What did Cyber Crime Department
people say?
Since the actual personal information
did not get leaked
they can't start investigating
with only assumptions.
They are not going to tell us who he is?
That's what I mean.
This is driving me crazy.
Why are these people doing this?
I heard it seems like he made a new ID.
Yes.
I think it is one of the people who used
to post things on the message board.
You know how thieves wear masks
to hide their faces.
I think he made a new ID
to hide himself.
What is he thinking?
He might want to become a hero.
Or he could be doing this for fun.
Since he is getting people's attention,
he might be enjoying that.
Social media can give people
god complexes.
Someone you don't know asks for answers.
And the person asks for a word
of encouragement.
That person think of you as if
you are his or her god.
It has nothing to do with him.
It's my business.
Some people listen to someone else's
story and put themselves into it.
At one moment, they forget who they are.
They become Toycrane.
They become Producer Do.
Honestly, what did Toycrane do?
What did he do wrong?
It's all, and only the wife's fault.
At least Toycrane didn't cheat on her.
I got some information on
that flirtatious wife.
She is a graphic designer.
I sent a flower basket to
Toycrane's wife.
Your husband might have forgiven you.
But I can't forgive you.
Good thinking. You can't ever forgive
your wife if she had an affair.
Let's punish her.
Dear Toycrane, you can't forgive her.
A traitor has to go to hell.
It's wife's fault. She's worse than a man
who had an affair with a married woman.
Please find out who those jerks
and bitches are.
Post the guy's picture.
We have to bring him down.
This irritates me. Is she saying he is
more important than her husband?
Screw Toycrane.
All the ones who get divorced and leave
their children behind are all selfish.
Don't have children
if you can't be responsible.
Anyone can be Adultery Patch.
No one can be Adultery Patch.
Hello, I'm flower artist Moon Sun Hee.
Hello, this is Toycrane.
I have decided to forgive my wife.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I hope you will stop illegally spreading
personal information about my wife.
Please let us start our
new life together.
- It's Toycrane.
- What? Did he really spread that?
- That's why he's asking him to stop.
- Wow, amazing.
- Amazing, god Adultery Patch.
- Reveal who she is.
- We have to reveal who she is.
- Let's let Toycrane live a happy life.
Who's trying to teach whom?
You be quiet.
Adultery Patch: You can never
forgive her. She has to be punished.
If you are not going to do it
I will punish her.
Tomorrow night, I will reveal her
personal information.
Crazy bastard. This is driving me crazy.
I put a point on the handle
just by using a ribbon.
This piece portrayed an elegant bride.
The next piece reflects
our current color trend.
What is this?
This is driving me crazy.
The person cannot be reached--
What is this?
What is going on?
I will track his IP or something
and find out who he is.
- You said that's illegal.
- Illegal? That's not our problem here.
When Soo Yeon's personal
information gets leaked
it's going to hurt both you and Joon Soo.
Can't you see why people commit suicide
or leave the country?
I'm going to stop him no matter what.
I'm going to do everything and use
all the connections I have to stop him.
- Thanks.
- Writer Kwon.
Soo Yeon shouldn't stay alone now.
Bring Joon Soo and stay with her.
Okay.
- Please do me that favor.
- Okay.
Mom.
Joon Soo.
My wife regrets this incident too.
So please stop it.
- Adultery Patch, let's stop it.
- Just sit back and enjoy the ride.
Reveal who she is.
That will solve all the mysteries.
- He has no right to do this.
- Stop it, Adultery Patch.
Can't wait until tomorrow.
Reveal it now.
- Let's have some fun. Reveal it, okay?
- Reveal it.
- Don't reveal it.
- Don't reveal it. I feel bad for her.
- That's not nice.
- Reveal it.
[Send a message]
Don't reveal it.
Please stop it now.
My wife clearly made a mistake
and it is her fault.
But that is also my mistake
and my fault.
I'm not forgiving her.
We are forgiving each other.
So please stop it.
[Send]
[You did nothing wrong.]
You did nothing wrong.
It's all your wife's fault.
Your wife has to be punished.
[Reply]
Did you say it's my wife's fault?
If her information gets revealed,
both my kid and I will get hurt.
You are not just punishing my wife.
I feel sorry for you.
But that is the best punishment
for your wife.
Stop it you bastard.
Are you a pervert?
What do you get for doing this?
Let's just say it's for justice.
Sir, I'm sorry.
I think I was going insane.
If my wife has to be punished,
I will do it. That would work, right?
I'm very sorry for swearing at you.
What should I do? What can I do?
I will do everything you tell me to do.
I will talk with the producer in charge
and call you back.
Yes. Do you have time today?
Director Yeo Un Hyuk wants to
have dinner with you.
I'm sorry.
I can't have dinner with him tonight.
- Really?
- Yes.
Okay then. Let's pick a different day.
I'm sorry.
[To Tuna Mayo]
It seems like my wife is going to
get hurt again.
If I did nothing and stayed quiet,
nothing would have happened.
It feels like it's all my fault.
Go tell your wife.
If I did nothing and stayed quiet,
nothing would have happened.
Why are you doing this to me too?
These perverts!
Why are you doing this to me?
My guess was right.
I was going to visit you.
Ma'am.
I became a bitch because of you.
My career is over.
But, Ma'am.
I'm not going to die alone.
I'm sure you thought about this
when you were planning to bring me down.
Right?
Huh?
I'm asking you if I'm right!
Are you done?
Why don't you slap me some more?
If you are done, it's my turn.
You have five more to go.
Madam.
How is it going?
Are you with Soo Yeon?
- Yes.
- I will take care of it.
- Tell her to not worry.
- Okay.
Do me a favor. Please, please, please...
[Send]
[My wife is regretful about this
as well. Please forgive my wife.]
[My wife is regretful about
this as well.]
[You have one new message.]
[Delete]
This is driving me crazy.
I will reveal information about
Toycrane's wife soon.
[Post]
[I will reveal information about
Toycrane's wife soon.]
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Geez.
This is Toycrane. I will forgive my wife.
This is Toycrane's wife.
I don't mind getting my
information revealed.
But please don't harm my
husband and my kid. Please.
- Huh? Is it really her?
- Are you really Toycrane's wife?
This is disgusting. You are scared of
getting your information revealed.
So now you are acting like
a mom and a wife.
This just made me more mad.
I will reveal it sooner.
Why did you post it?
I said I will take care of it.
How can I not do anything?
I don't want you or Joon Soo to get hurt
because of me.
I will reveal it now.
Honey, I will talk to you later.
[Write]
What is wrong?
[Low battery]
Why all of a sudden...
Cable. Where is the cable?
Crazy.
Toycrane's wife is...
What now?
This is driving me crazy.
Please. Hurry.
Please. Hurry, hurry, hurry.
I forgive your wife.
- I forgive your wife.
[I forgive your wife.]
I forgive your wife.
- I forgive your wife.
- I can't forgive Adultery Patch.
- Adultery Patch, let's stop it.
- I forgive your wife.
I reported it to the
Cyber Crime Department.
- I forgive your wife.
- [I forgive your wife.]
So is this what you guys want?
Okay.
What are you doing?
Do you know that's illegal?
- I know.
- You know? And you're still doing that?
- Do you want to get arrested?
- How can you just let this slide?
I have to find Adultery Patch.
So are you trying to hack the website?
This is what I learned. I should use it.
You were an internet security
programmer. Not a hacker.
If you are not going to help me
go away. Don't distract me.
If you get caught, I'm going to say
you did everything by yourself.
They use the security program
that you made.
That's why I can't hack it.
- It's too perfect.
- What do you mean you can't hack it?
There is a reason when someone fails.
What? Anyway. We can't hack this.
They are using a secure coding system.
Then what are you going to do?
Something like Zero Day Attack
RSA Algorithm, or DDoS?
Their firewall is DPI. We can't do that.
Then what are you going to do?
Let's use the old method.
Like how we used to collect IP addresses
when the person opens the email.
We are not living in 1988.
Do you think that will work?
So we have to lure him
to open the email.
Okay. Then I will make the program.
We don't have time. Hurry up.
Done.
What should I say to Adultery Patch?
We have to lure him so that
he has no choice but to open the email.
So what should I say to him?
Hold on a minute.
[Honey]
Thanks to other people,
we got some time.
I will somehow stop him.
- I'm sorry.
- Nothing will happen. Don't worry.
Okay.
Go to this address.
This is Adultery Patch's address.
I'm here to check a gas leak.
Are you there?
This is driving me crazy.
- Was it you?
- What are you talking about?
I'm Toycrane.
What?
Why in the world did you do that?
Let me hear it.
I thought it was unfair.
I thought it was unfair because
I was the only one suffering.
When I saw someone else
suffering from the same thing...
I lost my mind.
To raise my kid well
I sent my kid and my wife abroad.
I was living in a room that looks like
a coffin. I sent all the money I had.
What's left for me in the end was...
A wife who didn't want to
come back to Korea.
And my kid who was more indifferent
to me than a stranger.
Last time my kid was here
I was saying goodbye at the airport.
I was the only one crying.
I was the only one...
I'm sorry.
Gosh.
I was lying about revealing the personal
information about Toycrane's wife.
I just wanted to get your attention.
I didn't think that
it could complicate things.
I apologize for causing trouble.
I'm very sorry to the people
who got hurt by this.
It's a huge relief, right?
Yes.
Honey, you are here.
Oh, you went to your
parents place, right?
Honey, about that flower
arrangement instructor...
It was just a coincidence.
Like a car accident...
It was not a head on collision.
I was not moving.
It was a rear-end collision.
And that happened only once.
Once? That's a lie. Twice.
Twice is true.
This is true. And you know how
that flower arrangement instructor
always smiles when she sees a man.
I didn't do anything, but
she clung onto me. This is true.
Honey, I'm so sorry.
Can you forgive me?
Let's get divorced.
Honey, I said I'm sorry.
Well.
I think you are too upset now.
Let's talk when you calm down at bit.
I'm not upset.
I think it has been a year since
I stopped getting upset looking at you.
So listen to what I say.
Let's get divorced.
Honey.
You don't have to worry about
that building in Seochodong.
It's under your name anyway.
I'm not doing this because of that.
- I'm not that type of person.
- I will send the papers tomorrow.
That's right. Even if we get divorced,
the building is still mine.
This is not a bad deal.
Manager Kim.
You may begin.
You told me to not worry.
You will do everything to stop him?
I did everything I could do.
I went to see a specialist in that field.
- Specialist? Who?
- There is a specialist.
So who is it?
The owner of the internet cafe
that I go to.
But it wasn't that internet cafe owner
knows all about the computer.
That's how Producer Ann does things.
Hold on.
- Do you want go grab something to eat?
- I just want to go home.
Let's eat together. I'm hungry and
I don't want to eat alone.
This is why you don't have friends.
Okay, I will eat with you.
- What are you doing? Let's go in.
- Huh?
Let's go to a different restaurant.
Why? You said you want to
eat spicy chicken stew.
Your wife.
Let's go in. It's okay.
Go ahead and order. Let's go.
Don't you want to know
what I said to my wife?
I finished things with her.
Just eat some chicken.
No feelings left for her.
I said just eat some chicken.
Okay.
Wow, it's hot.
It's not fully cooked yet.
Really? It's not cooked yet.
- Try it again a little later.
- Gosh, you.
[I was lying about revealing information
about Toycrane's wife.]
Huh? What is up with that face?
Are you jealous of Toycrane
working things out with his wife?
That's not it.
What do you mean that's not it?
Since you brought it up,
let me ask you something.
Why did you keep telling him
to get divorced?
You seduced my husband and
had my bedroom all to yourself.
You need to have a conscience.
You wouldn't have done that
if you had conscience.
Be nice.
You won't get better because
someone else fails.
You won't fail because
someone else got better.
That's really not it.
If it's not that, tell me.
Why did you keep telling him
to get divorced? Why?
You had a hard time.
You had a hard time because of
me and your flirtatious husband.
If you divorced him...
At least you would have felt better.
That's how things work.
It's not like you can forget it
when you say you are going to forget it.
Just like how the wind blows in when
you open the door.
It will come back to his mind
once in a while.
It might seem difficult now.
But it will help him smile later.
I thought
getting divorced is better.
It's like the cat is being
considerate of the rat.
- I will get going.
- Bye.
Hey, hey, drink this one.
Hold on.
Drink it.
What? Writer Kwon likes espresso.
What's up with you guys today?
You guys used to fight every day.
Let's have a team dinner
after meeting today.
I will pay for it.
- Is today a special day?
- He always pays for it.
It's not that surprising.
Guys.
- I got divorced.
- Huh?
You shouldn't buy a meal
for that. Don't you think so?
Why did you get divorced...
Is it impolite to ask these things?
No, you are fine. To be honest
it has been a while since I got divorced.
I got divorced because of a lame reason.
We broke up because of
the personality difference.
So from now on
think of me as
a single man.
"Brother" Ann Joon Young, okay?
Bo Young, is it because of me?
Let's start the meeting.
I said let's start the meeting
Mr. Single Ann Joon Young.
Okay.
What is this?
Let's throw Mom's birthday party.
Mom's birthday was yesterday.
Mom forget to make a wish yesterday.
- So we have to do it again,
- Really?
You have to do it again if you forget
to make a wish, right?
We have to throw
the birthday party again, right?
Dear Mom.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you for everything today.
Okay.
Then I will get going.
You are really a bad woman.
Jung Soo Yeon,
you are really a bad woman.
You know that, right?
You are selfish. You're the worst.
But.
I'm way worse than you.
After we got married...
No, even after we had Joon Soo
I never tried to
fully understand you.
I'm sorry for just passing by you
whenever you are aimlessly looking
out the window.
I'm sorry for leaving you alone
during the time you had to get rid of
your high heels to wear loafers.
The past eight years,
we've never had a fight.
I thought we were doing well.
I boasted about that too.
There were a lot of things I didn't know.
There were too many things I didn't know.
Don't be like that.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I left a big scar on Joon Soo and you.
I'm so sorry for making you
be like that.
Soo Yeon.
Let's forget everything...
and start fresh.
I will do better.
From now on, I won't leave you alone.
Me, you, and Joon Soo.
Let's live happily together.
I will do better.
Wait. Soo Yeon, that's not it...
I know.
I understand you.
Can you forget that your wife
was held by another guy?
Subtitles by DramaFever