Subtitles by DramaFever
- Let's get divorced.
- Honey...
No need to worry about the building in
Seocho-dong. It's under your name anyway.
I'll send the papers tomorrow.
Manager Kim, start the process.
You're really bad, but...
I'm much worse.
Let's forget everything and start over.
I'll do better.
[My Wife Is Having an Affair This Week]
[Episode 11]
Wait.
No, it's not that...
I know.
I understand.
That question... I wrote that one.
What?
Can you forget the fact that your wife
was held by another man?
Of course I can forget that.
I can forgive her.
No, I've already forgiven her.
It's just...
I'm just a bit confused right now.
I can forget it!
I mean, it'll be difficult right now.
But if I make an effort, of course I...
We can go back to this!
Soo Yeon, look at this!
Should we go on a trip?
We took this
when we went on a trip, right?
How about this?
Why don't we go to Europe?
You said you wanted
to go back to Prague.
I'm sure Joon Soo will like it. Right?
I finally realized today...
that you and I...
we cannot go back to the past.
We won't be able to do it
no matter how much we try.
I don't want to burden you anymore.
The more you try to forgive...
the more you try to forget--
How do you know
when you haven't even tried?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to yell at you.
I am really sorry.
What about Joon Soo?
We need to consider Joon Soo.
He's only seven years old.
If he finds out that we'll separate...
it'll be such a big shock for him.
Then why don't we live apart?
Why don't we stay apart for a while?
Give me some time then.
Then I'm sure...
I was sure that I forgot...
I already forgave you, damn it!
It's driving me crazy!
It's driving me nuts...
Honey... let us...
Oh, right.
I have an early recording.
I'm going to work now.
Take care of Joon Soo today, will you?
I'm leaving now.
- You're here early.
- Yeah.
- Good morning!
- Hello.
As soon as everyone's here, come to
the meeting room. We'll have a meeting.
So... everyone should search for stories
that fit the theme of the week.
Let's get back together at three.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Writer Kwon, when will you have a plan
for a new program?
Writer Kwon.
He wants the plan.
It's not ready yet.
I'm sorry.
I'll finish it today and show it to you.
Oh, okay.
Okay then.
Ji Hoon, let's go to the editing room.
- There is a part that bothers me.
- Oh, okay.
What's with you?
Are you not feeling well?
You've never been late on assignments.
We've worked together for eight years,
and it's never happened.
No, it's not that.
I'm glad that Hyun Woo came back.
He wasn't able to focus on work at all,
but he's working really hard today.
I guess it was meant
to turn out for the better.
The incident became the critical turning
point for them to make up.
Are they back at the old place...
or are they trying their hardest
to return to their old place?
What? What do you mean by that?
I already got the building.
Should I take off?
Should I beg?
I can't even make the calculation.
Honey.
I guess you haven't heard yet.
Haven't heard what?
I've decided to close this office.
Why would you close my office?
Not anymore.
If you need anything, pack it up today.
I have to get another tenant soon.
Honey...
I'd like you to also
leave me with the car key.
You're a professional, aren't you?
Let's finish this like professionals.
Okay.
Well, Honey...
You bought the cellphone before...
Did you have a problem with it?
I'm not capable
of paying for the cellphone.
I keep having lingering thoughts.
I can't have lingering feelings.
I'm sorry.
The returning window is over.
And you can't cancel the contract
because you signed up for three years.
I'm sorry!
[Employee Wanted No age restriction,
man or woman welcome]
Hyun Woo.
Hi, Ah Ra.
Did you come here to see Yoon Ki?
So you've known it all along?
I don't know what to tell you.
You don't need to console me.
I don't need to be consoled.
I know it's out of line, but why all of
a sudden did you decide on divorce?
You've kept it well even though
you've known it all along.
So why all of a sudden...
I felt like I was becoming a monster.
Pardon?
I've been lying to myself all along.
And to him.
When I smelled another woman's makeup
on his shirt
I thought, "a female client
must've come by his office."
Even when I saw a friendly conversation
on his phone
I thought, "she must be a good friend
of his that I don't know."
That's how I lied to myself
and looked the other way.
Because I loved him, because I couldn't
go on without him.
I pretended to be a better woman.
"Since I'm really good at cooking"
"let me make more delicious foods
and make him happy."
"And... make myself happy, too."
But no matter how much I pretend,
it jumps out unexpectedly.
Even as I was trimming vegetables,
cutting meat, boiling a soup for him
"He must be holding another woman."
"He must be undressing another woman."
"He must be kissing
another woman's neck."
When those thoughts pop up suddenly...
I cursed my heart out at him.
I loved him,
and I wanted to be loved by him.
But I cursed at him using the words
I can't even bring up here.
Sometimes I was smiling as I was
watching him eating my food.
At the same time, I wished him
to die right there and then.
He did wrong, but I obsessed over him
and doubted him endlessly.
I feel like I'm turning into a monster
as I curse at the man that I love.
And I hated myself for...
becoming that way.
Don't blame yourself.
I don't blame myself.
I don't regret it either.
Because I don't love him anymore.
You should get back to work.
I took too much of your time.
Not at all.
Be well, Hyun Woo. We won't have
an occasion to see each other.
Yes, I guess you're right.
I made a mistake
about what I said before.
Excuse me?
That you could've also
done something wrong.
Whatever wrong you did,
it can't be an excuse for cheating.
I realized it's a separate issue.
What do you mean?
But I still feel
that love can be a weapon.
I loved him much more
so I was able to make a clean break.
Didn't I tell you?
You may be able to forgive her
but you'll never be able to forget it.
You're already in a swamp.
Even if you try your hardest to forget
you will only be sucked down
to the bottom.
Accept that reality, Toycrane.
- Is Producer Do not eating lunch?
- No, he went out with a visitor.
Is he coming back after lunch?
We should get him a sandwich
on our way back.
Oh my. My friend is getting divorced
after only six months of marriage.
What's the reason for divorce?
She says it's a personality issue
but it's not like she didn't know his
personality when they were dating.
I think she's lying.
There are a lot more reasons for divorce
than we can come up with.
Based on my database,
the number one reason for divorce
is irreconcilable differences.
Followed by economic reasons,
followed by the partner's adultery.
Oh, and based on an unofficial database,
the sex life is also a reason.
Wow, could that be my friend's reason?
What?
How could there be a sex life issue?
You're right.
I didn't drink it.
What could be such a serious issue
to cause divorce?
In my opinion, the man's --
Isn't that right?
Producer Ahn.
Stop acting like that
in front of other people.
Huh? What?
I told you that we're not going out.
I can't even take care of you?
Did I ask you to go out with me?
It's awkward in front of other people.
It's uncomfortable, so don't do it.
It means you've noticed.
I was good at things like that before.
Why do you care now?
You should admit it now.
If you started noticing me,
it's game over.
No. So don't do it
when I tell you not to.
Tell me.
Did your heart flutter
when I cared for you?
Can you forget the fact that your wife
was held by another man?
Didn't I tell you?
You may be able to forgive her,
but you'll never be able to forget it.
You should accept the reality now.
I thought it would be possible.
I thought I would be able to do it.
But...
I don't think I will ever
be able to forget it.
[Divorce Agreement]
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm the one who is sorry.
[Divorce Agreement
Do Hyun Woo]
"Registration base"?
What's "registration base"?
Oh, my family hometown?
One proof each of the husband's
marriage and family.
One proof each of the wife's marriage
and her family.
In case of a child,
an agreement of custody
and parental rights and two copies of it.
Or three copies
of the family court's decision.
A copy of identification...
What the heck. Why is it so much?
This is driving me crazy.
Okay...
So I can get this from the internet?
[Do you allow the following program
to change this computer?]
[Will you allow the XecureWeb module
to work on all websites?]
I already completed this.
[Will you allow the XecureWeb module
to work on all websites?]
How many times do I have to do this?
Divorce is such a complicated thing.
I bet a lot of people give up on divorce
after they find out
how complicated it is.
You're right. There are a lot of
things I have to submit.
And it's a headache
to complete the forms.
There is a reason
that divorce planners exist.
Divorce planner?
Just like a wedding planner
a divorce planner
takes care of the complicated process.
Just like the marriage,
it's your first divorce.
[Agreement on Custody
and Parental Rights]
You are both working full-time
and your child is seven years old.
Who is going to raise the child?
- The mom should raise the child.
- I'd like to do that.
Mostly moms raise the children.
And the parental rights...
In most cases, the one with custody
takes the parental rights.
- Parental rights as well?
- Yes.
Of course, both of you can choose
to share parental rights.
In that case, if the child goes to school
or he has to get emergency surgery
or even when he opens a bank account,
he'll need approval from both of you.
What you're saying
is that it's better for the child
if the mom takes the parental rights?
That's right.
I'll do that.
This is not usually easily agreed on.
You're easy-going.
This is the suggested child support
cost table by the court.
Given the combined income of the two of
you and the child's age
the average child support cost is
about 1.4 million won.
Given the husband's income...
it's 740,000 won.
I get about 740,000 won.
- Okay, I will.
- Pardon?
I'll pay the amount you said.
Yes, I understand.
You do understand, right?
After you submit the papers, you can't
retract on the child support amount.
Yes.
"Visitation rights." It is a decision on
when your husband can visit the child.
When would be convenient for you?
You should rest a bit on weekends.
I'll see Joon Soo on weekends.
Would that be all right?
You won't be able to rest on weekends.
No, it's okay.
It'll be a lot harder
for you on weekdays.
I'll see the child on weekends.
And I'll leave the house.
You should live there with Joon Soo.
No, why would you?
I'll leave with Joon Soo.
No, his kindergarten
and school are there.
So you should just live there.
Please let me.
Okay. Then I'll find a place
for you and Joon Soo.
Don't mention it anymore.
Are we done now?
Oh, yes. We are done...
but are you really
going through with this?
Pardon?
Never mind.
The court looks like a borough office.
Let's go.
You don't want to get divorced anymore?
What the heck are you saying?
I changed my mind! Divorce?
I'll never do that for you!
I won't do it for you!
- She keeps looking away.
- Shush, you're loud.
What are you doing
in front of other people?
Do you have to talk back
at your husband every time?
Excuse me. How may I help you?
Oh, yes.
Are you here
to submit divorce papers?
Yes.
Please let me have it.
- I need your ID.
- It's inside.
Okay, it's submitted.
That's it?
Take your course and submit it
during the waiting period.
Here you go.
[Child Rearing Guide]
We have to take a course like this, too.
There's one at 4:00 p.m. Should we
attend it since we're already here?
- It'd be better, right?
- Yes.
[Classroom 207]
[The class has already started,
so you cannot enter the room]
Mom, Dad, don't get divorced.
In a lot of cases, a child expresses
her anxiety through physical pain.
I believe the child was anxious
and had a very hard time.
I believe she expressed her feelings
through stomachache.
Children in kindergarten feel guilty
over whether the parents
got divorced because of them.
At the same time,
they're wrapped in fear
that they may get abandoned some day.
Thank you for your hard work!
- Sir.
- Please sit, please sit.
Enjoy your meal and please do
a good job on the interior.
Don't worry!
By the way, I heard
you're the owner of the building.
Yes, I am.
Wow, you look so young,
but with such a big building...
You must be so happy.
And your wife is so pretty.
What would you like?
I'd like a bottle
of Chateau Cos d'Estournel.
With two glasses, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Would you like anything else?
Please call the owner.
I'll put shelves on this wall.
I'll put a partition here and
make it a foot massage room.
If you put a partition, it'll look small.
You should just break down the wall.
- It'll be nice.
- Then we can do it.
Wow, this is nice.
I don't know what you're thinking...
but I believe this
will change your mind a bit.
What is this?
If I'm going to expand the store, I need
to get more assets from my husband.
You're greedy.
How about it?
Do you have the will to fight?
Where are you going?
Huh? Just going.
Where?
Well...
As I went through Toycrane's incident
I thought of a good business idea.
What is it?
People leave their records here and there
while they're on the internet.
Because of their records
their identities are revealed
and get on the news...
So I thought it would be a good business
to help them erase those records.
Wait.
Wear this one. This sucks.
This was from such a long time ago.
What happened to Toycrane?
I hope everything worked out for him.
They must've made up by now.
Tell us what happened afterwards!
I'm dying to know!
I'm sure they got stronger
after the hardship.
I hope our effort of plastering the board
with our comments.
I'm proud of myself.
Blocking the revealing of the ID
is the best thing I've done recently.
I'm putting together a group
in support of Toycrane.
Let's meet up on a beautiful day.
It's come to this after all.
I'm at a loss.
When I was preparing for divorce,
I wondered why it was so complicated.
But once I was done, it's all in vain.
I wonder why I worked so hard
to make a living.
I feel like my life is over.
Right...
divorce makes people feel really empty.
What did Joon Soo say?
I haven't been able to tell him yet.
Doesn't the divorce planner
do things like that for me?
Telling my friends and family
that I'm divorced.
That is really an issue.
When and how would you notify whom?
Don't drag it out.
Do it quickly and get it over with.
The longer you drag it out, the harder
it is to bring it up.
I should get going now.
Where are you going? Have dinner with us.
You guys eat. I'm late. I'm leaving now.
By the way...
we're eating together,
playing games together
and drinking together
whenever we have time.
Aren't we dating?
No no no. Okay, okay!
I won't bother you, so just eat.
I can't even say anything.
I like you, Producer Ahn.
How can you say things like that
while you're eating radish kimchi?
But I don't want to date you.
Then what?
Do you want to get married?
Are you crazy?
I do like you...
but it's hard for me to have
a relationship with another person.
I've also failed at my marriage.
So I do understand it's hard for you--
I'm not doing this because I'm divorced.
Then what is it?
I told you already
that I have a problem with relationships.
I can't give you
a normal feedback on emotions.
And I don't really know
what to do with my own emotions.
And...
I'm tired.
I'm annoyed and tired
to waste my feelings
so I don't want to do it anymore.
Are you tired when you're with me?
When we talk, when we eat together...
are you tired of those?
When I was pretending to be married
I thought to myself,
I'd never love anyone again.
Like you said, I was tired of everything
and didn't care for anything.
But with you, I'm okay, Bo Young.
I was hurt, and I closed my doors.
But it healed.
I remembered again
how nice it is to like someone.
I want to find those feelings
for you as well.
No, don't do that, Producer Ahn.
Aren't we already heading
to some sort of relationship?
It's not like we don't
have any relationship.
Let's date, Bo Young.
Don't say that while you're eating
radish kimchi. It's annoying.
Why?
You don't like it
because I'm eating radish kimchi?
Okay okay, then...
Let's date.
I said, let's date.
I don't want to.
You don't want to
because of radish kimchi?
You're leaving because
you don't like radish kimchi?
It's because of radish kimchi!
- This is what Joon Soo likes...
- Wow, it's chocolate cake!
- Joon Soo, say, "thank you"!
- Thank you, Grandma!
I didn't know what to get.
So I just bought some cake Joon Soo
likes at the bakery nearby.
Did you have fun at the hot spring?
Wow, this was my first time there,
and it was really nice.
Next time, let's all go together.
Mom.
We have something to tell you.
Mom, we are--
You haven't seen this picture, have you?
I took this near the arboretum.
Mom.
Hey, it was amazing.
If you walk up a bit,
there is a view of a reservoir!
Mom.
We...
We decided to get divorced.
I'm sorry, Mother.
You can't.
I will never approve of it.
Just what is the reason?
Did Hyun Woo say he can't forgive you?
Is that it?
- Do Hyun Woo, are you really--
- Mother, it's not like that.
Then why are you getting divorced?
He will forgive you for everything.
He will let it go for you!
Soo Yeon...
I understood you.
Do you really have to consider
only yourself all the way?
What about Joon Soo? What are you
going to do about Joon Soo?
What did that little one do wrong?
Change your mind
even just for Joon Soo's sake.
Please.
We've already made up our minds.
You can't!
I cannot accept it.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry.
Why would you be?
I'm the one who is sorry.
No, Father.
I'm responsible for most of it.
I... wasn't able to make her happy.
When I took Soo Yeon...
I pledged that I'd make her
the happiest person.
But I wasn't able to keep the promise.
I'm really sorry.
- Mom, I'll go ride the bike with Dad.
- Okay, be careful out there.
- See you later.
- See you.
Joon Soo.
I have something to tell you.
Dad and Mom...
we've decided to live apart now.
Why?
Because we'll be happier that way.
You will live with Mom from now on,
Joon Soo.
But you can see me anytime you want.
Even if we live apart,
I'm always your dad.
What have I always told you?
When I'm not around, Joon Soo is...
Instead of you, I have to protect Mom.
I have to stay apart from your mom now...
Joon Soo, you have to protect Mom.
Mom's working too hard by herself.
Don't cry.
Okay? Men don't cry.
You'll go to elementary school soon,
right?
I'm sure you can do well.
I'll ask you to take care of Mom.
Thank you.
For these reasons, we believe
the requested property division
and alimony are justified.
That's all I have.
Defendant, anything you'd like to say?
Yes, we do.
I think it'll go well.
I think we'll get more alimony.
Yes, we have evidence that the plaintiff
had no will to raise children
or to do housework.
Most of those claims are bluffing.
Please look at the submitted photos.
What are these photos?
Those photos prove that the plaintiff
provided reasons to break up the family.
If you look at the presented photo
the plaintiff has had a relationship
with Attorney Choi Yoon Ki
for the past few months
before the divorce.
The photos show the status
of that relationship.
Your Honor, we have other photos as well.
What do we do?
Based on the evidence,
it shows the plaintiff
had no will to continue the marriage.
And that her contribution
to the property is very low.
Does the furnace work well?
No, the house is not facing south.
It's facing east.
Isn't it too close to the next building?
It looks like they can see everything.
And the walls...
Is it molded inside the walls?
Is this a cockroach?
How can there be a cockroach?
If there is one, more will keep coming!
The mom will flip out
when she sees the roach...
The security cameras are here,
here, and there?
Yes.
There shouldn't be
any blind spots, right?
You're really detailed.
Oh, how many people are moving in?
Did you say it's three of you,
with your wife and the child?
It will be two. The mom and the child.
Relax. Don't worry.
I'm so upset, it's my money!
I will buy everything you want
and get everything you want to do.
Don't you worry!
- Really?
- Of course!
Did you forget? I have a building.
Here.
Thank you, Yoon Ki.
The shoes are so pretty.
Aren't they? Wait, is it okay for me
to buy the shoes for you?
Would Bo Ram run away from me
wearing these shoes?
Then you can buy me another pair. So that
I can come back to you wearing those.
Choose one more pair.
For you to return to me.
Take a look!
Mr. Choi Yoon Ki!
Mr. Choi Yoon Ki, are you inside?
Who are you?
- Are you Mr. Choi Yoon Ki?
- Yes, I'm Choi Yoon Ki.
Please take this.
And sign here.
What's this?
I'm not sure.
It looks like it's from the court.
Why would I hand over my building
and my land to you?
It's not your land.
I'm asking you to give it to me
because it's my land.
There are the land registry
and property tax record
during the Japanese occupation period.
Are we making up stuff?
You saw the certified copy of
the land registry, didn't you?
My name Choi Yoon Ki is written on there!
This is definitely my building, my land!
During the Japanese occupation period?
Why bring up, "once upon a time"?
Even if you can't accept it,
you don't have a choice.
We'll just follow the law.
What does this all mean?
Demolish the unlicensed building
built on my land, and get out!
How can I demolish such a big building?
We have tenants there!
Tear down the building? You mean,
we should get rid of our building?
It's not our concern.
Since you've used our land
so far without our permission...
we will request for compensation for it.
What does he mean? Is he going to
take away our building?
Please stay calm.
Writer Kwon! What a coincidence!
The food here is great,
so I come here alone often.
You waited for me, didn't you?
I told you not to do this!
What do you mean, I waited for you?
I happened to run into you
as I was leaving after drinking.
It's a coincidence.
Your nose is red.
If you were going to wait for me,
you should've waited inside!
Why are you so foolish?
I guess you're not
feeling well these days.
You haven't come here to drink at all.
- Let's go.
- Where?
I'm hungry. And you should warm up.
If you tell me to go, of course I will.
Here.
Were you out somewhere?
I thought you were home.
You waited for me without knowing
whether I'm home or not?
Yes. I thought you might not like it
if I rang the door bell.
I thought I'd be thankful if I happened
to run into you. If not, that's fine.
I just walked around
the neighborhood a few times.
You're working out?
You must be on a diet!
Now that I think about it, you've been
nibbling small bites these days.
Producer Ahn.
You want to date me?
You were embarrassed to say it,
so you haven't been able to say it!
If you want to date me, eat the noodles.
Otherwise, drink water.
What is it then?
Why do you take so long to say it?
If you don't want to date me
you've already told me several times,
so you don't have to say it.
Don't tell me
not to come here and wait for you.
I'm not bothering you or anything--
I'm pregnant.
Pregnant?
I'm not bothering you or anything--
I'm pregnant.
Pregnant?
Who is?
You heard me.
Don't make me say it again.
I can't believe it.
Who is the father?
Me? Me?
It's me?
No no, I don't remember--
The day we had grilled clams...
- Cheers!
- Here!
Let's go have another drink at my place.
Why did you come to my place?
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
I thought about it...
I'm going to have it.
That's why I'm telling you.
Wait, wait. I'm not getting this.
I know.
That's how I've been
for the past few weeks.
Okay. There is nothing more
to think about.
Let's get married.
You don't need to take responsibility
for the child.
I was afraid you'd think that way.
That's why I haven't told you until now.
Whether we have a child or not,
I want to be by your side.
To be honest with you,
I have no feelings
for the baby
that just popped up suddenly.
It doesn't even feel real, but...
If you decided to have it...
I'd like to be by your side
for both of you.
No, I don't want to get married.
Why not?
I can't. The baby and marriage
are separate issues.
How can you say that?
People get married in this situation!
- Let's get married.
- I won't get married!
How can you say
that you can't get married?
You can't do this.
I'm getting married no matter what.
- Did you pack up the books?
- Not yet.
- Then I'll pack your books.
- Okay, thank you.
Wait. You can't leave things like this.
It will break.
I'll leave this here.
What's this?
You'll see Joon Soo anyway, but still...
This...
- You should.
Your birthdate is written on it.
Are you okay without my help?
I'm okay.
The movers will take care of everything.
- Still...
- It's okay.
You should go. You'll be late.
Okay, I'm leaving.
We're done. You can leave right away.
Okay.
Joon Soo, you'll grow this tall. Okay?
Honey, is it ready yet?
Yes, I'll be done soon! Hold on!
I'm hungry. I'm hungry...
Honey, hold on for a minute.
I'm hungry!
Honey, I'll be done soon.
Wait for a minute!
Wow, it looks good.
- So, this is everything.
- Yes.
It took three hours...
It must be really good since it took
three hours to make it.
Thank you!
I think I'm pregnant.
Huh?
What?
I think I'm pregnant.
My gosh, are you all right?
Is everyone ready?
Lighting is good.
It's been a long time.
This is Toycrane.
We will begin recording.
Camera Two, standby. Ready, cue!
I'm currently in the process of
the divorce procedure with my wife.
But I'm okay with it.
Because I came to the answer
after thinking hard about it.
In that regards, I would like
to sincerely thank you.
If I didn't have you who held onto me
when I was going through
the toughest time
I would still be blaming my wife
and wouldn't have been able
to look back on myself.
This will be my last post.
Thank you for everything.
Although I've never met you
I wish all of your happiness
from my heart.
Goodbye.
It's really clear.
Don't make me worry about you!
Hurry up and come inside!
You're well over 60, and you still have
things that you're afraid of.
You're still young!
Sister, can I sleep here?
You and I don't have a relationship
to share the bed.
So sleep over there.
Yes, Sister.
Sis. I'm curious about something.
Can I ask?
What is it?
He's dead, and you can kick me out.
So why do you have me around?
I'm going to keep you around and take
revenge on you for the rest of my life.
I'm going to return all the sadness to
you until the day you die.
Then you should live for a long time.
Because I'm going to live
for a very long time.
Shush! Sleep already.
That's fast.
Toycrane, now I've lived to this age,
I came to this thought.
The times that I miss
hurt because I can't get them back.
The times that I don't want still hurt
because I can't forget them.
But I wonder, the time that's floating by
in front of us now...
I wonder if I will miss it tomorrow.
That's a reason I can go on today
with a smile.
Damn, I'm hungry.
Vegetables will go bad quickly,
so eat up the vegetables first.
If you are not going to eat the
marinated meat, freeze the meet.
I portioned one serving of rice and
soup each and froze them.
Take them out half an hour before you eat
and microwave them.
Should I have a luxurious meal
for the first time in a while?
Should I get new wallpaper?
The rice cooker is too big
for one person.
I should give it to her next time.
Why is it not getting cooked?
Right, kimchi. Kimchi!
Subtitles by DramaFever