Subtitles by DramaFever
[My Wife's Having An Affair This Week]
[Final Episode]
Where should I start?
Yes.
I'm that flirtatious wife.
It seems like a lot of people read
my husband's post.
I have read it too.
My husband was considerate of me.
He wrote good things about me.
My husband is a warm-hearted person.
What is that moron
Toycrane doing these days?
He pretended to be a gentleman.
Is he getting divorced?
We were fools. Why did we support him?
That guy is a fool.
No wonder the wife had an affair.
Toycrane gave hope to all
the women having affairs.
I'm not writing this post
to make excuses.
It is just too difficult for me to watch
everyone blaming my husband
for everything.
I thought it is my job to tell my story
to everyone else.
Please only point fingers at me.
My husband and I met in a
Astronomy Club in college.
Just like everyone else
- we had slightly boring dating years
- I love you Soo Yeon.
And we got married.
With our child, our precious gift,
we became a family.
After my maternity leave ended
we decided to send our
one year old baby to daycare.
We felt sorry for our baby
but I didn't want to follow
my coworker's footsteps.
Most of the time, having a baby meant
the end of the career.
Please take good care of Joon Soo.
Bye Joon Soo.
I left my baby, who was
still in diapers, at the daycare.
I was doing my best for my baby
but I guess that was not enough.
Joon Soo, your school bus is going
to be here soon.
I knew my child was becoming a loner
but since I was already doing way over
what I was capable of doing
I could have left him alone.
I wanted to be perfect at everything.
But in the end, I think I failed both
as a mom and as a career woman.
Some people say if the mom is
a loner among moms
the kid becomes ta loner also.
It could be a bit late, but I have
decided to join other moms for my child.
But it wasn't as it sounds.
You said you want this, right?
I bought yours as well as Joon Soo's.
To help him get along with other friends
I ran around downtown Seoul
to find that toy that was
difficult to buy.
Whenever he goes on a field trip
I prepare box lunches for
his friends as well.
[Ye Won's Mom]
[Joon Soo's Mom]
[Ye Won's Mom invited Jung Soo Yeon.]
That simple chat invitation message
felt like it was okay
to not feel guilty.
On weekdays, as soon as I was
done working, I headed to the daycare.
On the weekends,
I went to my son's friends'
birthday parties and to kid's cafes...
On holidays, I went to kid's musicals
and to amusement parks
I was trying hard not to get kicked out
from the mom's group
that I hardly got in.
During the time I was focused
on spending time with my son
my short hair became long
and it got past my shoulder.
Don't you think my hair is too long?
It looks fine.
It's okay.
When he said it's fine,
I thought that's enough.
I thought that was fine by me too.
Even if I get up before six o'clock
before my alarm goes off
I had to receive bad looks from
the coworkers who work
past six o'clock at night.
Still, I had to be
the first one going home.
Riding through 16 bus stops
and running like a short track runner
in my formal shoes...
I thought it was still okay.
I thought it was okay until I met him.
That day was the day
that my shoes wore down.
It had been like that almost a week.
But I couldn't make time to fix it.
I had several meetings with him
before I knew him fairly well.
I will be there in two hours.
In those two hour that he gave me
I could almost finish reading my book.
As I was reading the book
I realized that it only took
two hours to read this book
and that I haven't had a chance
to spend just two hours for myself.
Yes.
When I was with him
I stopped thinking about my husband
my son, and my work.
Feeling sorry, being guilty...
Those things didn't come
to my mind either.
Like a kid who is chasing after a balloon
that is flying toward the open road
I was just chasing after the balloon.
If my husband did not
come to the hotel that day...
I must have been wandering around
the streets.
The relationship between him and I was
like reading a book that you know
how it is going to end.
The ending was decided already.
And that ending seemed
too obvious and too plain.
The story after that...
It's exactly the same as
what my husband wrote.
I asked him to divorce me.
And I left the house.
And I gave up on him first.
But there is something that
he didn't post.
My husband didn't give up.
He tried his hardest
to protect our family.
Even though I left my family behind
My husband still tried
to forgive me.
I know that the reason he decided to
divorce me instead of
protecting our family is to
make me feel comfortable.
Even at this very last moment
I'm a selfish wife.
Mr. Do Hyun Woo, and Ms. Jung Soo Yeon.
I have to ask you guys this question.
Do you guys want to get divorced?
- Yes.
Are you guys going to follow
everything it says
in the Parental Rights Document
that you guys submitted?
- Yes.
Since both of you agree
to get divorced...
I was surprised a bit
by the fact that
things don't change much
even after you get divorced.
Joon Soo, you have to go to school.
Wake up and go brush your teeth.
It is just that he now goes
to an elementary school, not preschool.
We are still having that
same busy morning battle.
Hurry. Let's go brush your teeth.
It's a relief that my husband is
also adjusting well
to being alone again.
I think my post became too long.
I'm sorry.
- Hello.
My husband might seem slow and naive
but he was always true to his feelings
when he was with me.
It's all my fault.
Please stop criticizing my husband.
I hope you guys will cheer him on.
Thank you for reading my lengthy post.
- What is that? You got one again?
- Huh?
Well... No.
- I think I should stay out of this.
- Gosh, you.
Someone piled all the stuffed animals
to one side of the machine so I just...
- Mom, I'm going to take a bath.
- Okay.
He takes baths by himself?
Yes. He bathes himself now.
He said it's embarrassing to
have me bathe him.
Really? Oh my.
I guess he is a guy too.
What is wrong with that?
It has been like that for a while.
You have to get a new one.
It could hurt your eyes.
Is there anything else that I can do?
No.
- My next door neighbor said I'm lucky.
- What?
She said we are lucky to be
a "weekend couple."
Since you come here from time to time,
she thinks we are a "weekend couple."
I heard "weekend couple" is
the "thumbs up" among moms like me.
Then just tell them we are
a "weekend couple."
It's better than them
pointing fingers at you.
Is that so?
What do you mean by "thumbs up?"
Joon Soo taught me.
Thumbs up.
I will get going.
Leave the kimchi out
for two to three days.
And you have to put the other dishes
in the refrigerator right away.
Don't worry about it. I will take
care of it from now on.
If I don't do this, you are going
to buy things
at the convenience store again.
Do you know how great
their box lunch is?
I will enjoy it. Thanks.
Let me go talk to Joon Soo.
- Bye, Joon Soo.
- Dad.
Wow, Joon Soo. You're all grown up.
You are a man.
Joon Soo, thumbs up.
Bye, Joon Soo.
Smile please. One, two...
Yong Sik, sorry to keep you waiting.
- Thank you.
- Smile please.
One, two...
One more please. One, two...
Okay, thank you.
Congratulations on your wedding.
The bride shouldn't make a face.
You will get to keep this picture
for the rest of your life.
Smile.
We will take the picture. Smile please.
One, two...
Bride? Your wedding is about to start.
You have to go.
Please open the door.
Wow, it's so dusty here.
You are here. When did you get here?
Didn't you say you are going to
pay your rent today?
I was going to give it to you today
but my client said he will pay me
in a few days--
What do you mean
your client is going to pay you?
I haven't seen anyone come here
since you've opened this office.
You said you are an attorney, so I was
hoping you'd make my building thrive.
Forget rent. You can't even
pay your electricity bills.
I'm going to pay it.
If I can get a crime case,
I can pay you for sure.
If you don't pay me by tomorrow,
I'm going to throw all your stuff out.
Please don't be like that.
I have to go work.
He's here. I heard he is a
"garbage attorney."
- What do you mean?
- He's as bad as trash as an attorney.
He had an affair with his client who
came to prepare for a divorce law suit.
He got kicked out by his wife.
So he has the attorney title,
but he is just like a beggar.
Ma'am.
I'm not a beggar.
- I guess he heard me.
- You talk so loud.
How could I not hear it?
- Are you married?
- What?
Let me know if you get divorced.
Is he flirting with me?
No.
How did this happen?
Didn't you know that I'm here?
How come you don't even look at me?
Let's stop it now.
I didn't see a girl.
Look. You didn't see a girl?
People lose hundreds of hairs in a day.
But I lose thousands a day.
Look.
I have alopecia areata.
I was just wandering around
and those stuck on me.
But why does it have to be
long female hair?
That's not it. That is just not it.
And I don't have money.
I don't have money to date a girl.
If I had money, my office...
- Never mind.
- What?
Do you mean you would date
someone if you had money?
Do you think I have money?
You constantly buy stuff.
Those things don't cost that much.
If I got all my alimony from
my ex-husband
I wouldn't have lived with you
like a beggar.
Beggar? Who do you think
caused all this mess?
- If we didn't go on that trip...
- If I didn't meet you
people would still treat me well.
I could have been a rich madam.
- Then leave.
- Hey!
Hey, don't throw that.
I'm going to return-- Hey.
I can't return it if it breaks.
Gosh. Hey, this is--
Amazing.
I guess some foolish guy
in the neighborhood was here.
Is he really a fool?
That's mine.
- What?
- I piled it up.
I went inside to get some change.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
But I just put in 1,000 won.
That's my 1,000 won.
Well, 1,000 won...
Yes, I got it.
What is this? Did it get stuck again?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
There's no need to do that.
The owner wouldn't give it to you.
- He won't give it to me?
- No.
I got stuck several times,
but he didn't let me take it.
How could he not let me take it?
Geez.
- Wait. Pull my hand.
- What?
Pull my hand.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
The owner is mean. Why would he not
let you take it? This is so pretty.
Thank you.
You live one floor up, right?
- I've seen you several times.
- Oh, yes.
- You can take it.
- No, you don't have to give it to me.
It was your 1,000 won.
I'm okay.
I'm not that narrow-minded.
I have the same one at home.
To tell you the truth,
I have the same one too.
Claw machine lovers like us
won't stop playing because
we have the same one at home, right?
Right. Claw machine...
Gosh, she is funny.
Oh my goodness.
What are you doing?
You are sitting there as if
you are at your house.
I should change
the password or something.
You still can't get a hold of Bo Young?
What is wrong with you two?
You have to tell me why so that
I can console you or
help you guys get back together.
You and Bo Young are fools.
I picked out good items
that we came up with.
You don't have to worry about
searching for new items for a while.
- Are you going to the army?
- What?
You sound like you're going away.
- I want to take a break.
- What?
"Why do you need a break?
Where are you headed to?"
"When are you coming back?"
I hope you don't ask me those things.
I might never come back.
Just pick one. Detergents are all same.
Joon Soo has sensitive skin.
You can't just use a random one.
Honey, do you like the one that has
lavender fragrance in it?
I have no idea what
"lavender fragrance" is.
But I liked your fragrance.
- That's the lavender fragrance.
- Oh, really?
It's me.
What kind of detergent should I buy?
It all looks the same.
Oh, really?
Okay.
If you are going to be like this,
why did you divorce him?
You cook, he changes the light,
and you pick detergent for him.
You guys meet up and eat together
from time to time.
It seems like you guys are going to
get back together soon.
No way.
You guys look better together
now than before the breakup.
- Am I right?
- No.
You say no, but you are laughing.
That's really not it.
I said no.
This is the one.
Why are they only
selling this in a pack?
Two bottles is too much for me.
Take your time.
- Thank you. Here.
- Yes.
Thanks to you, I could just buy one.
Otherwise I would have had no choice
but to keep all that to myself.
Oh, do you live alone?
I got divorced. Did you not
hear the news yet?
Wherever I go,
I never talked about it myself
but people always find out
that I got divorced.
Oh, me too...
Somehow they find out.
That's right.
- By any chance...
- Huh?
There's a frying pan claw machine.
Have you seen one?
I just need a cheap frying pan,
but I don't want to go buy one.
Oh, there's one that has all the
appliances in it.
This is the chauffeur service.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm here.
Ma'am.
Where is all my stuff?
Your wife moved out.
What do you mean she moved out?
She said she has to leave now.
So I gave her security deposit back too.
- Security deposit?
- Yes.
The person cannot be reached.
The person cannot receive the call.
Hello? It's me.
I told you I'm going to pay you the rent.
You got a new lock?
Can't you wait just a few days?
Then just for tonight...
I have nowhere to go.
I'm the dad.
I'm responsible for the baby.
You don't have to be responsible for
the baby. I decided to have the baby
- so I will take care of the baby.
- What am I then?
- Biological father.
- Okay, I'm biological father to the baby
- then what am I to you?
- Don't put me in a corner.
I might run away.
This is great. I was going to go
back to Seoul anyway.
Eun Jung is going to be happy.
Eun Jung had a hard time
covering for you.
The CEO and Hyun Woo were anxious
because you were not there.
- This is great.
- I'm going back to empty my house.
I shouldn't leave it like that too long.
The real estate agent said the house
has been sold.
Come back to work.
You don't have to be that careful now.
If you are doing this because of me,
you don't have to do this.
Since you don't want me to, I'm not
going to try to stay by your side.
I just need to be the biological father.
Isn't that all?
It was so nice to hear birds singing
here in the morning.
I have to say bye to that now.
Gaeddong, Let's go to Seoul with Mom.
How could you call the baby "Gaeddong?"
There are many other pretty things.
Sky, wind, star, flower...
Why? Gaeddong sounds friendly.
But you shouldn't call it "Gaeddong."
You can never call the baby that.
Change it. You must change it.
Did you forget what you said?
You said you won't ask me for anything.
You are a writer.
Let's think of a name in a documentary
perspective. This is not a variety show.
This is a belly baby nickname. It's okay.
The baby looks like a pretty dog
in the ultrasound.
So I started calling the baby "Gaeddong."
You have a picture of
the baby's ultrasound?
Do you want to see it?
- No way.
- Show me.
- Is this our baby?
- Do you know where the baby is?
Isn't this the baby?
Right. That's the baby.
Doesn't the baby look more like
a peanut than a dog?
Let's go now.
You can never call the baby that.
Can't I ask that as a biological father?
Let's go to Seoul. You said you are
going to go to Seoul.
We are going. Let's go.
Gaeddong. Gosh.
- Oh, hello.
Do you want some coffee?
The claw machine over there has a short
claw. So you can't just pick one.
The owner loosened the one next to that
so you can't really pick things up.
- And the one on the back street--
- Oh, that one...
There's a toast claw machine there.
- Did you try that already?
- Yes.
The owner put a ton
of erasers in the box
so I couldn't pick up the box.
The one in front of the convenience
store is the best one.
If you really want to do it,
use the ones on the back street.
There was a drone there.
I picked it up.
Oh my. I went there early morning to
get it, but someone already picked it up.
I went out to exercise and...
Since it's the rare one...
- Does it work?
- Yes, it works.
But I'm not good at flying it.
The wing scares me.
It's very sensitive.
You have to be very careful.
Your wife hated you picking up
stuff at the claw machine, right?
She didn't hate it,
but she gave me looks.
My husband always complained about it.
Well. It was nice to have someone
complain about that.
That's right. If it wasn't for her
I might have spent all my money there.
- That's right.
- It's over there.
- Frying pan claw machine.
- Oh, okay.
You are a pro. You easily
picked up the frying pan.
I'm not a pro. I just play it a lot.
Do you want to go on a date?
- What?
- Your reaction was very special.
The worst thing about living alone is
that you have to eat alone.
But for a divorcee to say
"Do you want to eat lunch with me?"
I think that sounds like I'm trying
to latch onto you.
"Do you want to go on a date?"
I think that sounds better.
Now that I think about it, that's true.
- So your answer is?
- What?
Let's eat dinner together then.
Did you clean the house?
I didn't know when you would come back.
I didn't want you and the baby
to stay in a dusty room.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
That has a lot of meaning to it.
Thank you for respecting my decision too.
You are going to go back to work, right?
Well. I haven't decided...
What is that?
You might be okay, but I thought
the baby might want to see dad.
Do me a favor. Please keep it there.
I will get going.
Bye.
It's so tiring.
I'm so tired.
Oh my. Gosh, Ann Joon Young.
How sneaky...
Do you have some good news?
Huh? No, why?
You were humming.
Was I?
When was I humming?
Are you dating someone?
- A woman?
- It has to be either a man or a woman.
She is a woman.
Who is it?
She lives one floor down.
She;s divorced.
She is talkative.
But we understand each other very well.
And we both like claw machines.
I guess she is not just a person
who lives in the same building.
It's not that.
But I'm surprised that I got close with
a woman who I don't really know.
Should I tell you a surprising story?
What?
Bo Young got pregnant.
What? Bo Young got pregnant? Really?
And it's my baby.
I'll get going.
Welcome.
Try it.
It's good, right?
If I want to season it and eat it,
how much should I buy?
How many people will be eating it?
- Three.
- Okay.
This will be enough.
- I will take it.
- Okay.
Let me do it.
Don't you think I'm very strange?
What?
I don't really know you,
but I asked you to go out on a date.
I don't think you're very strange.
A little maybe.
I was just kidding.
I don't like eating alone either.
It's 9,000 won.
- Do you need the receipt?
- No, that's okay.
Excuse me. Please be happy.
What?
Okay. Good luck to you too.
It has been a while since
I've had a beer. It's good.
It has been a while since I drank
beer with someone else.
Don't you have a close friend?
Or someone you know?
I don't have many friends.
It's just that my husband and I broke up.
I didn't like people looking at
me thinking
I have a long story to tell and
I did something wrong.
There are times when people try to
not talk about getting divorced
and things get awkward.
I haven't run into those kind of
situations yet. So I'm not sure.
Oh, you said it's fairly recent.
You should learn a lot from me.
- We are close friends, right?
- What?
Yes. We ate dinner together
and we are drinking together.
Then you are my best friend
in this neighborhood.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who
got divorced in this neighborhood.
But there won't be a nice guy like you.
What?
You like compliments, right?
I'm very emotional.
Do you want to go on a real date?
- Are you okay?
- Napkin.
I'm sorry. What is wrong with me?
I shouldn't say these things when
you are drinking something.
Father.
This is the new proposal. Please take a
look at it and edit it if you need to.
- Writer Kwon.
- Bo Young.
- Have you been well?
- I missed you.
To celebrate Writer Kwon's comeback,
I will pay for the meal.
Drink.
I'm okay. No, thank you.
It's okay. It's not that much anyway.
You will come up with better ideas
after you drink some.
I'm really okay.
- Don't worry about me.
- She said no. Gosh.
I guess it's because I'm an old guy.
You fill her cup.
I will fill your cup.
Stop it. She said she doesn't want to
drink today.
Guys, I'm pregnant.
- Oh my.
- The baby might hear that.
So please don't ask me to
drink alcohol, coffee, and other things.
I don't think I can work late at night.
Instead, I will try to work
harder during the day.
It might be hard to eat with you guys
because I'm having morning sickness.
So please eat lunch without me.
I feel sorry to make you guys change
your menus because of me.
I will take care of myself.
I think everyone is curious...
But we are all hesitating. I will ask.
Who is the baby's dad?
Don't be curious about it.
Even if you guys are curious,
you guys will never find out.
Eat.
I feel so connected to you already.
You still have the key to open my heart.
Bye, my love.
Ah Ra.
I will miss you a lot until
the next time I see you.
I miss you even when
I'm looking at your face.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Who are you?
What are you saying? Hey.
I'm her husband. Husband. You know?
- Are you her ex-husband?
- I'm her husband!
Excuse me, excuse me. Please, please.
Do you want beer?
I will buy the conditioner
and the treatment.
I have to buy milk.
- Here?
- Little more.
You got it.
- Bye.
- Hold on. Could you hold on a minute?
- What?
- Hold on a second.
Wait, this is...
These are some side dishes.
I followed the recipe.
It won't taste that bad.
- You don't need to--
- Enjoy it.
I will enjoy it.
I think this is the place for you.
You look great when you are here working.
What do you mean all of a sudden?
What's the matter?
Where were you?
I went to the post office.
Is today a special day?
Gosh. You forgot your husband's
"death anniversary?"
Oh, it's his "death anniversary."
Why don't you make some pancake?
Make him feel better.
I was his favorite person in the world.
He would be happy just to see me.
Wow, it's so good.
We are going to the graveyard.
Why are you taking the shovel?
I need it. Let's go.
What do you need it for?
You said our old man liked you the most.
Since you are all dressed up
and look nice
to make him happy
I'm going to bury you with him.
You are so funny. You are kidding, right?
It's a bit expensive, right?
If you sign two year contract, we can
lower the price to 380,000 won.
Just a moment please.
Team Leader Jung is going
to get promoted no matter what, right?
Of course. It would be weird if another
person get promoted.
Right?
What does your husband do for a living?
Ms. Jung Soo Yeon.
Do you need that information to
decide if I can get promoted or not?
Oh, you got divorced?
It's not because of that.
I'm a single mom.
But I always did my best
as a Team Leader.
So please make a decision only based on
my job performance and my capabilities.
Team Leader Jung.
That's okay.
I can get promoted next time.
We will start the meeting in five
minutes in the office downstairs.
- What are you doing?
- One of the guests can't make it.
Why? What happened?
No, it's nothing.
Do you want to have
a cup of coffee with me?
Something did happen, right?
I didn't get promoted.
They are so mean.
They made you work so hard.
I think so too.
- Should I go to your office?
- Huh?
Well. I have a dinner meeting tonight.
No, that's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Bo Young.
- Did you not hear the news?
- What news?
- Producer Ann Joon Young resigned.
- What?
Why is not answering his phone?
It's me. Joon Soo's Mom.
Joon Soo wanted to play with Yoon Woo.
I will be there soon.
Yes.
Yes...
Oh, you are here.
Why did you not go inside?
The password is the same.
Just...
Let's go in.
Just leave it.
Can't you report
to the Labor Administration
for denying your promotion?
That's okay.
I was just feeling a bit down.
Did you wait long?
No...
- At the restaurant--
- I will get going.
Joon Soo is at Yoon Woo's house.
I have to go pick him up.
- Should I bring him?
- No, I will go home with him.
What should Mom do?
[Bo Young]
Why are you here, you bastard? Huh?
Your ex-husband is garbage.
Go in. I will take care of him.
Why are you going that way?
Why are you going to our house?
Hey... Ah Ra. It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
From now on, I won't cheat on you.
I'll only look at you
for the rest of my life.
I will only think of you.
I can understand you seeing him.
Let's say we both paid our price.
Let's start fresh.
I love you.
You have one minute.
- What?
- I will give you one minute.
Disappear. Get out of my house.
I just told you what I want.
I... Hey.
Why do I have to disappear?
I will wait here.
That red shirt looks great on you.
You look pretty today.
I'm not going to disappear.
I'm going to wait for you here forever.
I'm not going to move.
Just watch if I move.
- Ah Ra...
- I said disappear.
This time, I will count to three.
- One.
- I'm not going to move.
- Two.
- You are counting too fast.
- Three.
- Okay, okay.
Hey, Aa Ra.
Excuse me. Please save our Bo Young.
She was unconscious when I got there.
Bo Young, I'm sorry. Open your eyes.
[First annual "Toycrane Lovers" Meeting]
[We support Toycrane.]
I guess the person in charge is the CEO.
I think so too. He prepared everything.
Guys, I think he is not here.
Let's introduce ourselves.
I'm "Monk Over Hairpin."
I'm not a real monk.
I'm "Loner."
I used to be a loner
but I'm not anymore.
Hello, I'm "Let's go to the Han River."
- Did you really go there?
- Yes, I went there but
the water was too cold, so...
Hello, I'm "Odd Man Out.".
But I don't feel lonely anymore.
I'm "Eye to Eye."
I left a lot of malicious comments,
and so it's a bit embarrassing.
I'm Lee Byung Jin.
- Lee Byung Jin.
- You can't say it like that.
Hello, I'm "Mr. Unknown."
Hello, I'm "General Toothpick."
- I'm "Harvard Farming Major."
- Hello, I'm "Fried Ham."
I'm "First and Only Wife."
I'm "What's that important?"
I'm "Mom, he's eating dirt."
Hello, I'm the person in charge.
I'm the "Tunnel Man."
Are you wearing a microphone?
This is my own voice.
Even though Toycrane does not
post anything anymore
I have created this group
to gather together
and remember Toycrane.
Since we all said our greetings,
let's have some drinks.
Excuse me, would you
please take our order?
I work here.
I will bring some right away.
Sir, please bring 11 cups of draft beer
and one cup of coke.
We will start with half fried and
half seasoned spicy chicken.
Sir, it's half fried and
It's half fried and
half seasoned spicy chicken.
That's so cool. Half fried and
I was scared.
Whenever we fought, I brought up the
things he did wrong in the past.
We kept on hurting each other
over things that
had happened in the past.
When I realized that I was not nice
enough to forget about the past...
that's when I decided to divorce him.
Whether you force yourself to forget it
or you eventually forget about it...
That's what divorce is for.
If I think of it that way,
I'm happy that I got divorced.
So did you get him
completely out of your mind?
It doesn't matter.
That has nothing to do with me anymore.
I got divorced because I didn't want
to go back to the past.
So there is no need to bring that back up
and try to forget about it.
Look straight ahead.
So  a divorced man and woman like us
just need to look straight ahead.
- What do you think?
- What?
Do you want to start a relationship?
I'm actually asking you out on a date.
It's not because
I don't want to eat alone.
- Hello?
- It's me. Are you home?
- What about Joon Soo?
- He took a bath and went to bed.
Is Joon Soo doing well in school?
Yes.
Are you handling everything okay?
There's more things to
take care of in elementary school.
I'm ready for it.
Soo Yeon, if it's too tough for you--
- Joon Soo's Dad?
- Yes?
You don't have to feel sorry to me.
What?
I just wanted to tell you that.
I feel sorry to you whenever I see you.
So let's stop being sorry to each other.
Let's be happy in our separate ways.
Okay.
Mom, the bathroom light went out.
It's dark in there.
Oh, really?
I will call Dad and ask him
to get a new one.
No, Joon Soo. I will do it.
You can't do that.
Dad changed the living room light too.
No, I can do it.
I think I will have to do it from now on.
Hello, this is Toycrane.
I have an important meeting tomorrow.
What should I wear?
Do you have a meeting with a woman?
- Of course it's a woman.
- He said it's an "important meeting."
- Did you ever date anyone?
- Toycrane? That flirtatious wife?
Since Toycrane is single again,
he can date another person.
It's Toycrane.
It really is him. Is he going on a date?
- I hope things work out for him.
- I envy him.
Should I ask him to upload
pictures of his clothes?
This is so lame.
She said it's lame.
Do you think those clothes
match your face?
Do you know Toycrane?
No way.
He said you look like a countryman.
She wants you to try wearing the
shirt you wore before
and the third pair of pants.
Tell him to post his address. I will go
buy some clothes and send them to him.
Your eyes look like fish eyes.
He says let's go to the Han River.
What do they want me to do?
What about the baby?
The baby is okay.
He said you don't have to worry.
Is the baby really okay?
Yes.
It's for real, right?
Of course.
That's a relief.
Then what was wrong with me?
Due to the stress from being pregnant
and the sudden changes in your body
you couldn't pass feces.
That's why that happened.
He said make sure to take laxatives
when you go home.
Due to the stress from being pregnant...
- You couldn't pass feces for a long--
- Okay.
You couldn't pass feces
for a long time...
I can't live without you.
I'm just going to die here.
Gosh, you didn't shoot me this time.
At least you don't die
from getting hit by a brick.
Father.
I know you don't want me
to stay by your side.
I admit it. I was being selfish
asking you to marry me just because
we have a baby.
Still.
I have parental rights too.
We could go to the hospital together or
something, let's raise the baby together.
But how could you resign from work?
What should I do then? You said you are
going to quit work
and move to a new place.
I know you like your job
more than anything.
I don't want you to give up
because of me.
I will quit. There are a lot of companies
that want to work with me.
I stayed here because of you.
Producer Ann, let me ask you a question.
What is it?
Do you have no feelings left for me?
Yes.
My house has been sold. I think I will
have to move out tomorrow.
Please help me move out.
Could you do that for the baby?
Of course.
Because I'm a biological father.
- You can follow me.
- Okay.
- Where should I go?
- I will tell you.
Turn right here.
We are here.
This is where I will be living.
Do you really mean it?
Sir, please start putting stuff in.
Well.
- Are you really going to live here?
- Yes. Can I?
I will leave if the owner says no.
No. You can live here.
But why all of a sudden...
It's not all of a sudden.
I have been thinking about it.
You should have told me ahead of time.
I could have got things ready for you.
It's so sudden... What should I do?
We have a lot of time.
- I should clean the house.
- You talk too much.
Where should I put my stuff.
Should I put it in that room?
No, not that room. Not that room...
What do you mean "it's so sudden?"
There is a baby store across the street.
I started piling cute baby stuff up
and put them all here.
- That's how this happened.
- Then you should have just bought one.
We don't know if we are
having a boy or a girl.
- It's a girl.
- Oh, it's a girl.
- Yes.
- It's a girl?
It's a girl?
- Wow.
- Are you that happy?
I thought about this all the time.
If I have a daughter, I will get
pretty dresses for her
and the two of us could sneak out
and eat ice cream together.
And teach her how to ride a bike...
I'm going to give her
rides to school every day.
I will be so jealous
if she finds a boyfriend.
Just thinking about that...
You are going to be
a daughter's daddy for sure.
I'm jealous of her already.
Wait.
Let me ask you just one favor.
Okay. What is it?
Don't ever say you are going to
hide or run away from me.
- Okay.
- You promised me.
Okay.
- Yes, I promise you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Can I test you if that's true or not?
What?
Every time you do this,
it is going to get worse.
You might not be able to be her
biological father.
This is going to be a problem.
We have different tastes.
- We have to redo the interior.
- Don't touch it.
I have my own taste and style.
I could not leave my wife behind.
Because I was scared to forget her.
Because I was scared that
she will forget me.
So I left my wife behind.
And I was always looking back.
Now, I have courage to leave her there.
I'm just going to leave her there.
I'm not going to care about her.
Because the most important
person for me now is...
Mom.
Have you been well? You got prettier.
Be careful.
Study hard, Joon Soo.
I will make corn cheese and
wait for you at home.
Her. It's her.
I hope that she could also
leave "me" there in the past.
The one who was foolish and lame.
I hope she could forget "me."
This week...
our new story begins.
Subtitles by DramaFever