BioskopKeren
[This Saturday, at Hills Hotel. 3 o'clock.]
[I miss you.]
Affair? Do you think that makes sense?
A lot of men think that their wives wouldn't cheat on them.
But it's just that they don't get caught because they are more careful.
When a woman is having an affair
her underwear and makeup become more noticeable.
If she wears flashy underwear or makeup, it's for sure.
Do you know why women cheat on their husbands?
Another man's skin, body, and passionate love.
Don't you think women yearn for those things too?
My wife is having an affair this week.
Guys, please give me an advice.
I have three days left.
[My Wife is Having an Affair This Week.]
[Episode 2]
Honey.
What is this?
Soo Yeon. I'm here. Hey!
Who is he?
Hey, Soo Yeon!
Hey! What are you dong?
Honey!
Jung Soo Yeon!
Soo Yeon.
You're up early.
Yes.
Huh? Did you sleep here?
Yes. I was working and...
I guess I fell asleep.
You must have been cold.
I will make some hot coffee.
This week...
my wife is having an affair.
When a woman is having an affair
her major spending changes from
groceries and necessities to makeup and other beauty related stuff.
Drink it while it's still warm. You could get sick.
Thank you.
I don't know who that man is yet.
Her whereabouts
tell me that she is looking forward to spending the night with him.
She is looking after me as if nothing is going to happen.
And I'm getting ready to go to work.
Good morning, Dad.
It seemed like you had a drink last night, so I made dried pollack soup.
I just can't understand her theory.
Is she trying not to get caught cheating?
- Honey, please finish feeding him. - Okay.
- See you later, Joon Soo. Bye. - Bye.
- Let me feed you. - Okay.
As her husband, I don't even have the courage to ask her about it.
I'm just standing here, not knowing what to do.
[Until my wife's secret love affair D-2.]
Ask her about what?
Now that things turned out to be like this, we are getting divorced.
Gosh.
Gosh. You know I'm here.
What? Why are you here? What about day care?
How would I know? I just followed you. You brought me here.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I do this all the time these days.
I will take you there soon. I'm very sorry.
It's a perfect day to skip day care.
What?
Joon Soo.
If Mom and Dad...
So if Mom and Dad...
Am I getting a younger sibling?
Never mind.
What am I saying to you? Let's go. We are late, right?
How about working on our detective agency concept?
- Detective agency? - So our plan should be--
What do I lack?
What's the reason?
After they abolished the adultery law
I heard detective agencies are actually getting more work.
So I think we should make it more realistic.
Wouldn't people say we are just try to make fun out of it?
- We should think about that a bit more. - We are done. Think about what?
I like that concept.
Since we will only be filming outside, we won't need an MC or a studio.
Based on my data, I think we can handle that with our current budget.
Okay. Great.
With a detective agency concept in mind, we are chasing after a forbidden love.
- Oh, great. - What?
Forbidden love?
What is "forbidden love?"
You call having an affair a love?
Hurting other people, is that love?
Then what should we do about our ending?
What if we find out that they are actually having an affair?
We should first listen to what his wife says--
What do you mean listen to her?
Do you think she would say I'm the bad person?
Why do we have to listen to her excuses?
We are getting divorced no matter what.
She will only make excuses.
But we can't make all our clients get divorced.
To solve the problem, we have to find out why his wife had an affair.
If you have a reason, can you stab someone with knife?
- What? - What is wrong with you?
Are you going through menopause?
Having an affair is the same.
Those people who think cheating is a love and a romance
screw them.
Having an affair is a crime. Whoever does it, it's a crime!
Oh my goodness.
Yes, sir.
Oh, Hyun Woo? We are having a meeting.
Oh, okay. Okay.
- He said your phone is turned off. - Tell him I will turn it on.
- Gosh, batteries. - Battery, battery. Give me that.
Hurry.
Here.
Well.
The CEO said he wants to see the project proposal as soon as it is done.
The moment he heard the title, he said he liked it.
He said it's great.
Comments?
[My wife is having an affair this week.]
[I have three days left.]
Gosh.
What have I done?
[My wife is having an affair this week.]
My stocks are down, and I'm feeling down. And this is dragging me down.
How lame are you to make your wife cheat on you? Divorce her.
Isn't he making this up? I think he is trying to get some attention.
Divorce her right away.
Having an affair is not something that can be forgiven.
I'm going to divorce her anyway, you bastards.
Women cheat because of men. It's because of you.
You must be having a hard time. Cheer up.
Is Han River's water cold these days? Let's go there together.
You are married? I envy you.
That's great. You should cheat on her too. That's fair.
I think you should calm down.
The fact that she booked a hotel room, doesn't mean she cheated on you.
If this is her first time, you can stop her ahead of time.
And don't let her actually cheat on you.
That's right.
But if she has been cheating on you
based on how serious their relationship is, your response should change.
Anyway. Calm down, and find out who is she having the affair with.
Don't you think you should look more into their relationship first?
That's right. Be calm.
Be calm.
Okay, then.
Our scenario is we are going to follow our client's wife.
Secretively.
The wife who said she is going to exercise
gets in a suspicious SUV that was parked in the park.
In the car, they have light skinship
and the car leaves.
They drive a long way.
And they stop at a quiet motel in the countryside.
They tenderly get out of the car, get in an elevator, and go into a room.
When are we going into the room?
Why do we have to go into the room? The car stopped at a motel.
The wife got out of the car with a stranger.
They walk into a motel, and we film that exact moment.
Huh?
What is up with this response?
- They didn't go into the room yet. - They are going to get in.
Since they are going to get a room they went to the motel.
Even if they are in a room, they have to "do that" to say...
They didn't go to the motel to eat.
Isn't it obvious?
Hold on. Then what's men's standard on cheating?
Even if they went to motel to sleep together, they haven't yet.
That's nonsense.
The person is "out" for just going to the motel.
As a husband, the fact that my wife went to a motel with a stranger can
be upsetting. But. Things can change if she didn't get into the room yet.
- Right? - Right.
That's a possibility.
Okay. Okay then.
Let's film them when they get into a room.
That's still a little...
Gosh. They are in a room together. Is that still not enough?
Even if they are in a room together, that's not enough.
We have to know for sure that they slept together.
That's how all men are.
After seeing his girlfriend holding someone else's hand
he asks her if she slept with her.
Then let's say they are 10 seconds away from sleeping together.
They don't have anything on. Is it still no?
- No, that's not enough. - Everything will be over in 10 seconds.
- They haven't slept yet. - So you mean what's important is
whether your wife has helped him make offspring?
I just can't understand man.
That's what you guys want to believe.
I want to believe that. And I believe that.
Then.
They have luxurious clothes here.
I think it will look good on you.
Look at this one. What do you think? Doesn't this look nice?
- Huh? - I think this is too much.
Really?
Well. How about this one?
This is a bit loud.
No way. You will look elegant.
Look. This looks nice on people who have face shapes like ours.
Wow, this looks very elegant.
I think you will look very elegant in this.
It's okay if it's a bit loud. You are sexy.
Gosh, you.
- We will go eat lunch. - Are you not going with us?
I don't feel well. You guys go ahead.
What is this?
[One hour ago.]
What should he do? Gosh.
Excuse me.
What should I do if I want to leave a comment like them?
You can make a ID and leave a comment.
ID... What is that?
Myun Mok Dong Yok.
Being nice can also be a problem.
Being nice...
Ouch.
Who is this?
Didn't I say finish it up and come eat?
That's not it.
What do you mean that's not it?
Follow me.
First, be calm and find out who she is having an affair with.
Don't you think you should look more into their relationship?
It's an affair because they are hiding from me.
How can I find out who that bastard is?
How was your blind date?
- I didn't go. - Why?
I searched for his social media. He's not my type.
He was sitting down in all of his pictures.
That means he is short.
I can forgive everything, but I can't stand short guys.
There's nothing much.
Jung Soo Yeon. Jung Soo Yeon.
Okay.
Micheal.
He's not here.
Why are their so many Micheals?
Micheal, Micheal.
- Steak, date with husband, love you. - Why do women take these pictures?
Are you going to show it off to your friends?
It's fun. And it makes my heart flutter
when I post pictures of us on our dates.
It's fun for me too.
But, more than taking pictures...
Doesn't this make your heart flutter more?
Thank you.
I have a meeting with a client. You can go first.
Oh, good luck.
- What about dinner? - Of course, I have to eat at home.
You know that white blouse? Let me buy that.
It's this one, right?
It's my gift.
And this is a freebie.
By the way. Your wife's shoes and bag... She has all the luxury items.
Those are worth two years of my rent. Amazing.
Is our baby having trouble paying rent?
I will have to look for a lease.
Really? Really?
Are you on your break?
- Let's go eat something delicious. - Didn't you eat lunch with your wife?
It was just an appetizer. Now, I will be having the main dish.
Let's go to the countryside.
Okay, sir. I will find a size four and get it ready for you.
Yes. Please get it ready.
Red looks good on you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Bye.
Use this to pay for everything.
Did you win the lotto or something? Why do you pay for everyone?
I'm paying because I'm capable.
- Doesn't your wife get upset at you? - No.
She's very cool.
She's not cool. She is just abandoning you.
Ma'am, please pay for everything except hers.
That's okay. I'm cool.
Please give me the receipt.
You buy meals and drinks every day. You have a family.
Do you think you are an angel?
We don't care about our personal expenses.
We care only about what we share.
By the way. Aren't we a bit awkward?
Wasn't that why you didn't accept my friend request?
We weren't close enough to ask about each others husband or wife?
I should send a friend request to PD Ahn's wife.
- You won't be able to find her. - Why? She will be on social media.
You must be her friend. I'm going to search for her.
Hey, hey, why are you searching for her?
A husband and a wife are not friends.
Why are they not friends?
Why do they have to be friends on social media?
- I see her every day at home. - Hold on. What about me?
You see me every day at work, but you nagged me to accept your friend request.
How are those the same?
How are they different?
Oh.
Isn't that PD Do's wife?
- Where? - There.
Oh, you are right. It's Soo Yeon.
Right. Didn't he say his wife's company is close to here?
Yes, I think so.
Hey, Jung...
Oh, what is that? They are looking good. Hold on.
He smells nice.
What? Smell...
I should take a picture. I'm doing my job right today.
What are you doing? Don't do that.
Micheal. Micheal.
Who is this bastard?
Is he a foreigner, or a Korean-American?
What is this?
Your wife is having an affair.
Yoon Ki. Yoon Ki.
Hey, hold on, hold on.
- Why? - Hold on.
- What is that, Yoon Ki? - They sometimes have hidden cameras.
They have hidden cameras? Are they filming me?
I don't think they have it here.
- They don't have it here? - No.
What could you have done without me?
- I would have been in big trouble. - Right?
Oh, Hyun Woo.
I saw Soo Yeon for the first time in a while, and she was still pretty.
Okay, I know she is your wife.
The man she was with. He was very handsome.
- That's enough. Let's start the meeting. - Was he that good?
I want to see him too.
Guys can tell from 100 meters away how a man matches up.
Think about those animal documentaries. Hyenas never fight lions
and always crouch when a lion is around.
That's an instinct for survival.
Oh. Didn't Writer Kwon say he smelled nice?
Yeah... he did smell nice.
- See? - I saw this on a blog before
that if a man has a nice scent, that means he's in love.
Is Soo Yeon having an affair?
Gosh. He's not funny, and he does not have any creativity.
What should we do?
He's upset again.
Hyun Woo, I was just kidding. Gosh.
Where are you going? Are you going out to buy cologne?
Why are you so... upset?
Get back to work.
What? An affair?
Soo Yeon?
- Not you, but Soo Yeon? - Yes!
Why did you fuss about it?
Wait. Let's get things straight here.
Soo Yeon is going to a hotel. This Saturday.
So it's in two days.
Soo Yeon is going to a hotel with a bastard?
So. What you said during yesterday's meeting was your story.
What are you going to do?
It's in two days. Are you going to let her go to that hotel?
Of course not.
But I have no idea what I should do.
Let's just break in.
Let's catch them at the scene, beat that guy up, and make a mess.
And let's throw divorce papers at Soo Yeon.
Divorce papers?
Hey, hold on.
Let's calm down and think about this.
We can't be sure if she is actually having an affair yet.
What do you mean yet?
Yet? Do you think that makes sense?
Listen carefully.
The moment she let him book a room, she is "out."
There's a difference between a man's and a woman's affair.
A man's affair is like having measles.
But in a woman's affair, feelings are involved.
Psychologically, it's way more serious.
But she's not having an affair yet.
You guys said no. You guys said that during meeting today.
Okay then. Just let it slide. Don't ask her about the details.
Cheating is not a big deal these days. You are being positive. This is good.
You bastard. How could you say that?
Then go ask Soo Yeon.
You should have talked to her when you first saw that text.
I'm doing this because I feel bad too.
If you can't ask her, go ask a detective agency for help.
Get Soo Yeon's caller history.
And find out how she responded to that bastard's text message.
If she said no to him, we don't even have to worry about this.
So look into this.
- Honey, I'm sorry I'm late. - You are here.
- The traffic is so bad right now. - I will get your meal ready.
Okay.
- I will go wash my hands. - Okay.
Something smells very nice.
Go ask a detective agency for help.
Get Soo Yeon's caller history.
And find out how she responded to that bastard's text message.
I have a question.
- By any chance, do you-- - Is your wife having an affair?
No. Yes.
Then go wait inside. It smells over there.
What?
I don't feel well.
Go wait inside. I will be there soon.
Oh, yes. Okay.
- Have a seat. - Okay.
I'm very busy these days, and I didn't get a chance to go to bathroom.
I have constipation.
- Drink it. - Okay.
There's nothing special here, right?
It surprises everyone. In movies, detective agencies seems very scary.
This is our business venue. Just like everyone else.
Yes. That's true.
- When did it start? - Huh?
When did you start questioning her?
Oh, yes. On Monday.
A guy sent my wife a text and asked her if they could meet at a hotel.
- Oh. - How did she respond to that and...
- if she called him... - Hm.
How long have you been married?
- Eight years. - Eight years.
There's a high possibility.
People start having affairs a lot during those years.
I have something to show you.
This picture was taken today.
Hm. I don't need it. It's not that helpful.
We will find out right away once we start working on it.
Wow, your wife is very pretty.
Right? Thank you...
It's okay. Not everyone comes here to end their relationship.
Okay then. There are three main tactics that we use often.
Tailing, phone tapping, and a call history check.
The one we use the most is call history check.
It is because it is hard to get caught, and we don't waste money.
Then, sign this agreement form.
Put your wife's phone number, carrier
and first few digits of her social security number.
- What? - You want to know
how serious their relationship is, right?
- That's right. - Yes.
Once we get paid, we will start working on it right away.
We can tell how serious they are by just looking at two texts...
No, we can tell just by looking at two emoticons.
I miss you.
Me too.
Eat this while you are working.
Why did you bring so much?
You need all these things.
Try it.
It's a black currant. It's a good antioxidant.
It also helps your eyes to relax.
Are you not going to check it?
- What? - Your message. It's something urgent.
I was too focused on working. I didn't hear it.
I should check my message.
Who is it at this late hour? Is it Attorney Kim?
Gosh.
It's Hyun Woo. Do Hyun Woo.
Oh my goodness.
Look. It's Hyun Woo.
Why is he texting me at this hour?
- Is it Hyun Woo? - Yes, look.
"What are you doing? Let's have a drink. I'm in the neighborhood."
Why did he send me a text? He should have called me.
Really?
That works? Do they sell it?
Oh, you are here.
Nice to meet you. I'm Attorney Choi Yoon Ki.
I'm PD Do's best friend.
As heard, you are very beautiful.
You must be very happy.
Give us some beer please.
Beer please.
Give us the most expensive snack here.
I'm embarrassed because of you.
I thought you were dating her.
Are you crazy?
By the way, you have changed a lot.
You called me out to make excuses.
I said that's not true. I'm not you.
What are you doing?
Everything is high-tech now. It's scary.
This picks up any hidden cameras, phone tapping, things like that.
Gosh.
Recently, when I see my wife, something just doesn't feel right.
It seems like she knows something.
Yesterday, I was checking everything at my house with this.
What are you doing?
Oh, it got turned off.
Gosh, I was so surprised.
Hey, isn't phone tapping against the law?
Take your hands off. Hands off.
It's illegal.
You can't even use it as evidence in court.
But you can still check if your spouse cheated on you or not.
I still don't think it's something a human should do.
I think so too.
The ones who do those things are way worse than the ones who cheat.
So you don't want to get caught by your wife?
Of course.
Why?
Does that mean you still have feelings left for her?
Why would I have feelings left for her?
Didn't I tell you? Marriage and dating are two different things.
My office, and that building. Those are all my father-in-law's stuff.
He owns many of them.
My wife?
She's an only child, good at cooking cleaning, sewing. She's perfect.
She is perfect as a maid who works for free.
You bastard.
That was a compliment.
Isn't she pretty?
Hey, what do you think?
When a woman is having an affair
do people always get divorced?
A wife's affair is not a matter of
a husband forgiving her or not.
It depends on whether the wife is willing to go back to the family.
That's more important.
When people get charged for adultery
nine out of the ten man say he didn't cheat.
They say "that woman is a player."
- Do you know what the woman says? - What?
"I loved him. Arrest me."
That's what they all say.
When you have to give up something that's in your hand
women become braver than men.
[I wish someone could drink with me.]
[If I was in the area, I could have went there.]
[Where are you?] [I'm in Chung Dam.]
[Oh, it's close from here.]
- I have to go. - Go where?
Why do you ask? You know where.
You know this, right? I drank with you all night.
I drank with you until eight, okay? I will get going.
Gosh, he is...
He's a strange bastard.
When you have to give up something that's in your hand
women become braver than men.
Since when?
When did you become so brave?
You are here. You are late.
Yes.
What about Joon Soo?
Joon Soo? He must have been tired. He went to bed early.
I guess he ran a lot today.
Oh, really.
What are you doing?
Laundry.
I'm behind in laundry.
Who is it?
The moms from the day care. It's Yoon Woo's birthday.
Oh, really?
Oh, that's right.
Joon Young said he saw you today.
Oh, really?
Where did he see me?
He said it was a cafe in Gangnam.
Then why didn't he say hello?
You were with somebody. So he couldn't say hello.
Oh, it was a business meeting.
Oh, really?
Who was it? Someone from work?
Yes. I told you before.
I got selected to work on a new project.
It's vague.
You got selected to work on a project? You are amazing.
Who else got selected?
From our company, two designers got selected.
And from headquarters, people from planning and marketing got selected.
We have several people from all departments.
Even more vague.
I have a filming schedule this Saturday.
Didn't you say Joon Soo is doing something at his day care?
Can you pick him up?
Saturday?
I have to work on Saturday.
Never mind. It should be fine.
It's okay? You booked a hotel room.
The meeting starts at 1 o'clock.
I will be done by 6 o'clock.
Oh.
From 1 o'clock to 6 o'clock?
The meeting is so long. It must be very tiring.
I do that all the time.
Where is the meeting held?
My client is going to decide and let me know.
Wake up--
What are you doing?
I couldn't sleep because of Dad.
- Honey. - Dad is not here.
Where is he?
He went out a while ago.
I'm too tired. I don't think I can go to day care.
[Until my wife's secret love affair, D-1.]
[Pretty Wife]
[Wife]
Good morning, Hyun Woo--
What happened?
Are you okay?
Did something happen?
Why do you ask?
Do you think something happened? Do you want something to happen?
No, I was just asking to be nice--
Since when are you nice?
- Hello. - You are here.
Hello.
- Are you sick? - What could you do if he was sick?
Are you going to use your fancy data to introduce him to a doctor?
- If not, keep your mouth shut. - Be quiet.
Hyun Woo.
What is wrong with him?
He's just like a dog that barks when a stranger comes near him.
PD Do, can we talk for a minute?
I will go.
What?
I will talk with the CEO instead of Hyun Woo.
- What are you talking about? - I will--
It's nothing. I will go.
I will go.
What is going on with you these days?
You are zoning out.
Even a lonely father like me is doing just fine.
Actually, I'm not doing just fine.
By the way, Hyun Woo. How is the proposal going? Is it going well?
Yes. We are doing okay.
We are going to start filming first.
Just bear with me.
If this goes well, things will get easier for me.
I will support everything you want to do.
Whether it's a TV program or a movie...
I will finish writing the proposal some time today.
- What's wrong? - Because of PD Ahn
- we can't start our meeting. - What did PD Ahn do?
I'm sorry.
Let's continue.
So the husband is going to catch his wife having an affair on the scene
- and we are going to-- - Hold on.
- Hold on. - We can't continue like this.
I thought about this a lot... I don't think this is right.
Let's forget this item.
What are you talking about? We're filming it tomorrow.
This is not something a human can do.
What is wrong with you?
- Gosh, Hyun Woo. - Hey, come here.
- Come here. - It hurts.
What is wrong with you?
When you were being hesitant during the last meeting
I made fun of you and said you are an old man now.
I feel bad for making fun of you. My heart aches.
I'm a bad guy. I'm very sorry.
Hey, that's okay.
But we have to make our program.
I'm not going to do it.
Hey, Joon Young.
Let's keep working on this.
I'm okay.
By the way...
If you keep fussing, I'm going to kill you.
Get some fresh air.
Joon Young needs to get some fresh air. He will be back.
He has some family issues.
- Okay. - Okay.
Please be considerate of him.
Okay.
Even though our new program is important
- we should finish our previous project. - Oh, that's right.
You have to meet Director Park today.
- What? - You said you were going to
- apologize to him in person. - That's right. I was going to do that.
He doesn't even know that our program is getting cancelled.
Today is the pre-meeting day. You should explain it to him.
- Okay. - Okay.
Hold on a second.
We received the money. We will let you know as soon as we find him.
I'm not sure if I'm doing well.
- Hello? - Happy anniversary.
Hyun Woo, congratulations on your anniversary!
Oh, sister-in-law.
- Anniversary? - Oh my.
Hyun Woo, did you forget?
No, no, I know.
If we were there, we would have thrown you guys a party. We are sorry.
Since we're not in the country, it's not that easy.
Tell Soo Yeon that I said congratulations.
You have to make her the happiest person in the world today.
A wedding anniversary is like a dream for a woman. You know that, right?
Oh, okay.
Thank you. Bye.
She is so loud.
Is today your wedding anniversary?
Wedding anniversary.
There are so many stars.
Wow, really...
- It feels like it's going to fall on us. - Yes.
How about this one? Don't you think Director Park would like it?
Yes.
Are you going to get that for your wife?
As an anniversary gift?
No.
She'll remember it forever if you just let it pass.
- Bo Young. - Yes?
I'm sorry. But could you go meet Director Park for me?
I could do that...
Yes, I could do that. I will go meet him.
Thank you.
I put a sketch behind it. Tell her to put her sketch too.
I will go to the printing shop and check colors. I will go home from there.
Okay. Do you have anything special planned for today? You look happy.
A family gathering. I have a lot to prepare. Please do me a favor.
Okay.
- It's all done. - Thank you.
[My Wife is Having an Affair This Week.]
Are you heading to court?
Let's find proof, and get everything, including alimony.
Apologize for everything you did wrong and beg her not to leave.
He would get so many stars if he did a live broadcast.
It would be so much fun.
Having an affair is like an option these days.
I will be waiting for you at the Han River tonight.
I understand you.
Cheer up.
Catch them at the scene and put an end to it.
- Hey, let's go. - Okay.
Why is she going to a hotel the day after our anniversary?
You don't know why?
She wants to enjoy her anniversary, and when you are caught off guard
she is going to have an affair.
That's how clever women are.
What is this?
I thought something urgent came up.
Oh, I met someone.
Did you meet Director Park?
How did I end up seeing you here? This is driving me crazy.
My studio is close by.
You helped me move in there, don't you remember?
You're too young to forget those things.
Hey, it's okay. You don't have to drink with me.
I drink alone often.
When I have to get a new light bulb but there's no man in the house.
I can't open a jam jar, but there is no man in the house.
There was a thief in the area but there's no man in the house, et cetera.
What is up with that look?
It's like you want to say "you need a bodyguard more than a man."
No, it's because you never talk about those things.
You've never asked.
- I didn't meet Director Park. - What?
I called him ahead of time, and he said let's meet next time.
He said he is on a trip. It's a celebratory trip.
Oh, really?
Yes. He went there as a couple.
That trip is to...
Celebrate their 25th wedding anniversary.
They are amazing.
25th anniversary. That is...
- Producer Do. - Yes?
Do you know that the first wedding anniversary is called a "paper wedding"?
It's not that well known.
But starting with the first wedding anniversary there's a special name to it.
Starting with paper, it goes cotton, leather, wood...
So it goes from something soft to something as hard as silver or gold.
Really? Does that have any meaning to it?
As time goes on, the couple gets more intimate.
Isn't that what that's trying to say?
"As time goes on, the couple gets more intimate."
Then what is eighth wedding anniversary?
- Eighth wedding anniversary? - Yes.
It's rubber.
Rubber?
"A couple that can never be untied."
I think that's what that means.
Director Park and his wife had so many problems.
But they are celebrating their 25th anniversary. They are amazing.
You have more than enough time to buy a gift, Producer Do.
What?
- Thank you, Bo Young. I will get going. - Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Cheer up.
Talk? What do you mean you're going to talk with her?
I'm going to buy her a gift and celebrate our anniversary.
And we are going to be honest and talk.
The cake is ready.
Be honest?
Are you going to forgive Soo Yeon?
I have to listen to what she has to say to decide if I'm going to forgive her.
Anyway. I'm going to get serious and talk to her.
We are a "rubber couple."
Rubber? What is that?
It's a thing.
Since I discussed this with you, I'm just letting you know.
How can he just hang up like that?
Whatever. He will take care it.
It was buy one get one free.
It's Jeon Ju Bibimbap. I like spicy pork.
- What's yours? - Don't eat it then.
Why are you taking it back?
Did you argue with your wife?
You looked like you were feeling down all day today.
We don't argue.
Is there a couple who does not argue?
We respect each other.
We don't mind each other's business.
You respect each other, so you don't  mind her business.
Aren't you just leaving her alone because you don't care about her?
Are you saying my wife is leaving me alone?
If you feel bad, don't eat these things here.
Go home and be nice to your wife.
She took my kimbap.
I want to eat what you made.
Yoon Ki, are you going home? Ah Ra, Yoon Ki is going home now.
I have more work to do.
He said he has more work to do. I will call you later.
Honey, wait just a moment. I will be there soon.
Are you not going home?
- I have things to do. - Oh.
I didn't ask you to do anything. You have things to do?
- What about you? - I have a dinner meeting.
- With who? - With producers.
Producers?
Wow, it's unlucky.
- It's unlucky. - What is unlucky?
Just something.
- Let me hang out here. - We are having a meeting.
Keep going. Don't worry about me.
- Keep going. - So do you want to
record the talk between the wife and that stranger?
- It's clearer that way. - Wait.
Huh? You guys are going to get arrested.
Protection of Communications Secret Act. Article 14-1.
No one can record or phone tap
someone else's private calls.
Breaking that law could get you between a year and ten years of jail time.
- It's illegal? - Does it sound legal to you?
What about hidden cameras?
It's called "hidden camera" because it is not legal.
Filming with a hidden camera is illegal
and using the tape without agreement is also illegal.
And when you get portrait rights problems in the mix, it gets very complicated.
What about the black box in the car?
Other than special circumstances, it's okay.
Then we should use the black boxes of their cars.
If you're not planning on living in the car, you won't get anything.
Then what should we do?
You fool.
You can just look at the odometer.
Those odometers don't lie.
"Honey, where were you?" "I went to a meeting in Chungdamdong."
Chungdamdong is 15 kilometers away from home.
But when you look at the odometer, it says 50 kilometers.
What does that mean?
She went somewhere farther than Chungdamdong.
And another thing. When people go to a motel
there's that mark on the front of the car.
Careless people always miss those things.
But since we are pros
we look at the back of the car. The plate.
When you go to a motel , they hide your plate.
Then everywhere expect for the plate is covered with dust.
But you can just wash your car.
That's why you never improve.
My wife washes my car before I go out.
But I wash the car my wife already washed.
It's 100 percent.
One last thing.
- Rock. - Rock?
All the motels cover their entrance with pebbles.
Why would you have pebbles stuck in your tire?
It's proof right there.
"He went to a motel."
Why are you looking at me with those admiring eyes?
Those are all from his experience. He's different.
Writer Kwon. I have never done that. I'm not that kind of person.
This is why I wasn't going to say this.
Isn't this fun?
It's like Sherlock's affair case.
It would be fun if we could do something like this at the scene.
Do you guys want me to appear on TV? At the scene?
But he probably doesn't have time.
I don't think it's a bad idea.
We can also get legal advice.
I'm not busy.
That's right. We are a "rubber couple."
A rubber couple.
Like how she always does on anniversaries
she will be cooking something delicious and waiting for me.
Okay. Let's take this as a chance
to remind ourselves how much we love each other.
Then the wind will stop.
And we can be happy again.
Right, Soo Yeon?
I'm home.
What is this?
Is this a surprise?
I'm going to turn the light on.
Okay?
No one's here?
Honey.
Joon Soo...
Where did they go?
We are going to Joon Soo's friend's birthday party.
We will be having a sleepover there.
I'm sorry about the short notice. Let me know if you have any problems.
Dear Yoon Woo
Happy birthday to you.
Yes, Honey.
What is this? You're not coming home today?
Joon Soo's friend is having a birthday party. We're going to sleep over.
I will be there before breakfast.
- Hey, Soo Yeon. Today is... - Today? What?
I was going to have dinner with you.
I made dinner for you.
Okay.
My wife forgot our anniversary.
Happy birthday, Yoon Woo.
- Happy birthday, Yoon Woo. - Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday. - It's a lot.
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
"Rubber couple"? Forget that.
Intimacy? Forget that.
I can't talk to her even if I want to!
[Mr. Do Hyun Woo, we sent Ms. Jung Soo Yeon's]
[call history and text messages to your email.]
Okay.
Let's end this today.
[Jung Soo Yeon. Call and Text History.]
[Delete] [The message has been deleted.]
I'm going to grab that bear no matter what today.
What's going on?
Hey.
Hey. Give it to me.
Give it to me.
Be quiet. Give me my bear.
Hey, give me that.
Give it to me.
- Give it to me. - Excuse me.
What are you doing?
- Oh, are you the owner? - Yes, I'm the owner.
Oh, sir, please look at this. The bear is stuck here.
How could you kick it like that?
It's because I can't get it out. Give it to me now.
What do you mean, give it to you? I will give it to you if it drops down.
Sir, I spent a lot to get it out.
I don't know that.
- I said no. - Give it to me now.
I said no.
Sir.
I'm a regular customer. It has been a while.
Since eight years ago, I have been a regular customer.
Who does these things nowadays? It's old-fashioned.
Sir.
Did I kick it, or poke it with a stick?
I was just being diligent and worked hard.
If I knew thing would turn out like this, I would have lived like a mess.
What is this?
If I bought beef with the money I've spent on this machine
I could feed 100 people.
Give me what's mine!
- Okay, okay. Go. - You can't do this to me!
You can't do this to me!
You can't do this to me, sir.
Why are you doing this to me?
What did I do wrong?
What did I do so wrong?
What did I...
Today. Will my wife cheat on me?
This afternoon. At 3 o'clock. I'm going to catch her at the scene.
I'm going to barge in there and beat up that man.
Guys, my actions are justified, right?
[10 hours left until my wife's secret love affair.]
B I O S K O P  K E R E N
- Do you really have to go? - It's just one day for me.
What? My wife is having an affair today.
Barge into that hotel and beat that guy up.
And end everything.
If Mom and Dad separate, who are you going to live with?
Dad is okay.
Thank you.
I'm scared and anxious about what is going to happen in the future.
If Yoon Ki is cheating on you, what are you going to do?
I think it's okay as long as he doesn't get caught.
The fact that he is trying not to get caught means
he still has feelings left for me. There's still a chance.
I want to believe that.
About Attorney Choi's wife.
I couldn't do that.
- What? - I have some experience.
My partner cheated on me.
If I really loved him... I shouldn't have stopped.
Even if I end up breaking up with him, I should have made it clear.
Jung Soo Yeon, don't come here. If you come, we are done. So don't come here.