Subtitles by DramaFever
I believe you should be calm.
Shouldn't you find out who
she's having an affair with
and the nature of their relationship?
Stay calm.
Isn't there something at Joon Soo's
kindergarten on Saturday?
Can you go pick her up?
I have work to do on Saturday.
But it should be fine.
It should be okay?
But you booked a hotel room.
Why do you have to go to the hotel
the day after our wedding anniversary?
What? You're not coming home tonight?
My wife forgot about
our wedding anniversary.
[My Wife Is Having an Affair This Week]
[Episode 3]
And the D-Day finally came.
[8 Hours until my wife's secret meeting!]
You're right. You shouldn't forgive
your wife who cheats on you.
The monk should speak
after he experiences marriage.
He has no wife to help him out.
It's no big deal once it passes.
So cheer up. I'm rooting for you.
There is only one answer. Let's go to
Han River. Don't miss this last chance.
You should attack first. If you miss
the first move, you'll lose.
It's okay if this is a lie.
Can you tell me which hotel?
I'll just watch.
Can their be a solution to catch her?
If you barge in emotionally
and punch the other man
you may feel better for a moment,
but nothing will change.
What would your wife think of you
who behaved that way?
Are you really ready
to end it with your wife?
If there is still time,
try to convince her not to go.
You should think of your child
and find a way to recovery
right up until the moment.
Right up until the moment...
What's the point of conversation
at this point?
You don't have evidence. Sure, she'll
confess that she cheated on you.
She won't admit the affair
even if you jump into the hotel room.
Yes, catch them in the act and
make them admit it.
Make a clean break. Then meet with me
and have a drink with me.
Awesome. This is not
a made-up story, is it?
When I read things like this,
I don't want to get married.
You won't be able to get married anyway.
Since it's past midnight,
isn't it happening today?
What a pity for the child.
- Dad!
- We're home!
All the moms got together last night
for Yoon Woo's birthday.
I was going to come home, but all of
them said they'd have a sleepover.
I felt awkward to be the only one
who would say no.
It's not like a dinner with colleagues.
It's also about Joon Soo's school.
Would the moms go to elementary school?
Are you upset?
Don't be upset.
Eat up before the food gets cold.
Oh, the stew!
- Did you have fun at the party?
- It wasn't bad.
Not bad? Why do you say it wasn't bad?
Kids' birthday parties are all the same.
Oh my. Look at the time.
Joon Soo, you can eat
the tofu by yourself?
- Yes.
- I'm running late.
Joon Soo, should we go out and have fun?
You don't want to go
to kindergarten, do you?
- Dad, don't you have filming?
- Huh?
- No, I don't.
- I have to go.
I'm supposed to be
Ye Na's partner today.
Oh, I see.
Is your work not going well?
Don't overwork yourself.
You're dressing up today.
Most of the advertisers will attend
the meeting today.
I shouldn't look like I always do.
You look like you have
too much makeup on.
My makeup? This is how I usually do it.
Do you have to go?
You're not the only one working there.
Why do they have to drag out someone
with a family on the weekend?
I planned this, so I have to take charge
and make it happen.
It's the weekend. Whether we go
camping or to the zoo...
We should get time to be with family.
Why do you have to be dragged out
on a day like this?
- It's only for today.
- What?
I'll clean up here,
so please take Joon Soo.
Today... my wife is having an affair.
But I still don't know who the man is.
I'll get going.
Soo Yeon.
Yes?
- You really have to go to this, right?
- What?
I'm making coffee soon.
Your favorite coffee. The one from Nepal.
Why don't you go after you have coffee?
We haven't talked much recently...
I have a lot of time.
Can't you take your time?
I'd also like that, but I'm really late.
I'll take the garbage.
I can throw out the garbage...
I'll be back.
Soo Yeon...
I planned to barge into the hotel...
but I'm scared and nervous about
what's going to happen now.
[Will my wife
cheat on me today or not...]
You scared me.
Is some honey smeared here?
Why do you keep coming back?
It's because--
Just come and eat when it's time to eat!
Just for an hour!
I'll be back after one hour.
When will you grow up?
An hour, really?
You only wrote three words,
"I would think" in one hour.
I don't know what this is about
but can you write everything
you want before you die?
Let's go eat.
By the way, what's wrong with this guy?
His wife is going to meet
with another man.
Do you like your dad or your mom?
Dad...
do you like grandpa or grandma?
By any chance...
if Mom and Dad lived apart
who would you live with?
I'm just going to live together,
all three of us.
Yes, you're right.
The three of us will live together...
- Dad!
- Yes.
- Cheer up.
- Huh?
Aren't you too stressed out these days?
Are you worried about me?
- Here.
- What's this?
I brought this to give to Ye Na,
but I'll give it to you.
Really?
Are you sure you can give this to me?
What about Ye Na then?
I'll need to earn points
with something else.
Really?
Okay. Thanks for this.
When things get tough,
we should help each other.
Okay. I'm fine.
Joon Soo.
Thank you.
I'll cheer up.
I really can't stand this.
Do they have to film on the weekend?
That's what I mean. I was planning
to have lunch with my father-in-law.
- But Hyun Woo begged me.
- You can't help it then.
What about your lunch?
Should I make you lunch
and bring it to you?
No no... all of us will eat together
at a restaurant nearby.
Then what about dinner?
Of course I should eat dinner at home.
With you!
- I'll have your favorite ready for you.
- Okay. I'll get going.
Have a good day.
Is it out? Let me see.
Writer Kwon, you look so pretty
when you're working.
I should take a picture of you.
- Don't frown. Here I go, one, two--
- Attorney Choi.
Then this way.
You look prettier this way.
- What are you doing right now?
- Just smile.
Honey, I'm sorry, but I'm really busy.
I didn't know you called.
- Did the recording start?
- No, not yet, but we're about to start.
Wow, everyone here is super busy.
Do you want to say hello to everyone?
Here is Writer Kwon. Say hi.
Writer Kwon, this is my wife.
Hello! Hello!
That's Producer Ahn.
Producer Ahn, this is my wife!
Look at everyone. This is no joke. Wow...
Wow, everyone has a busy life.
It's really tough for me, too.
Shouldn't I bring you
something to drink at least?
No! If you come here now,
you won't even be able to say hello.
Huh? Producer Ahn? Why, why, why?
We're starting now?
Honey, it looks like I have to go now.
I'll call you later.
- Good luck!
- Good luck! Okay.
Writer Kwon,
what time is the recording today?
Two o'clock.
Two o'clock? I have errands to run,
so I'll see you later.
Wait. Aren't you coming with us?
I'll be back in time, so don't worry.
- You're coming now?
- Everyone's here early today.
- Hello.
- Why are you here?
He's filming today. Why are you here?
Why? Is this a place I shouldn't come to?
Sorry, but I have to get going.
See you later.
I'm asking why you're here.
Is everyone getting ready?
Hyun Woo, really!
Let's talk.
Are you crazy? Why would you come here?
Aren't Soo Yeon and Michael or some guy
meeting today?
Yeah.
"Yeah"? Yeah?
Why are you here? What about Soo Yeon?
Did you have a good talk with Soo Yeon?
Is she not going to the hotel today?
No.
She left for work before I did.
She forgot about yesterday.
It was our wedding anniversary.
She completely fell
for Michael or whoever.
This leaves you with no choice.
Barge into the hotel, beat him up,
pay for his injury, and end everything!
Don't say it so easily just because
it's not your business, punk.
Don't you worry about Joon Soo?
I haven't made up my mind yet.
You're right...
But why did you come to work so relaxed?
You're not in a situation
to behave this way.
My wife's meeting is at three.
I'd go crazy if I had to stay at home by
myself until then, so I came out.
[5 Hours until my wife's secret meeting]
Excuse me.
- Excuse me!
- My gosh.
Oh my! Get away!
Yes, Ah Ra. He's so handsome!
Right, Yoon Ki's not there.
There are a lot of other people.
Honey!
I'm back.
- Take this.
- Yes.
Why, why, why? Is it a paper jam?
It's not a paper jam,
so why does it say it is?
I'll just use a different printer.
No no. I can fix this quickly.
Producer Do, I printed from a different
printer. You don't need to fix it.
But I should still fix it.
We'll use it anyway.
Why the heck would the printer break?
It's really annoying!
Why?
Why is it not working?
On top of everything, why the heck
is a printer not working?
This printer is broken.
This is a complete mess!
We can't work like this!
I'm telling you to fix it!
Why do you go on and on?
We trusted you and bought this, so you
should show us how you're trustworthy!
Are you kidding me now?
What?
You quit your job
as a repair technician?
What do you do now?
You own a chicken restaurant?
I see. "Five Minute Chicken"?
Then I should order from you often.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Hang up, hang up.
Let's have a meeting.
Sure, let's have a meeting.
We should have a meeting.
Our client today is in his 40's?
Yes. He's 44 years old with a daughter.
He lives in Hangang Apartments.
He seems pretty well-off.
His wife is 40 years old, a homemaker.
This is a pilot, so we should pick a few
more cases for the regular filming.
Yes, we should.
- Ji Hoon, data.
- Yes.
- You should give me a summary of this.
- Look at the first page for now.
This is the hottest item these days.
Ji Hoon, I like
that you always work hard.
I guess things like this
happen a lot these days.
It's really interesting.
There are also a lot of comments.
I know about this one, too. It's also up
on an online community I know.
A lot of people shared it,
so it's up everywhere.
"My wife is having an affair this week"?
Wow, the title is catchy. We should pick
this one based on impact alone.
What impact?
Isn't it Saturday today? Awesome,
he must be heading there today.
Producer Ahn, what would you do
if you caught them in the act?
Me? Why would you ask what I'd do?
As soon as I saw him,
I'd punch him in the face!
But what if the man was Kang Ho Dong?
What a scare!
What the heck? You want to fight?
- You want to fight?
- Please spare me.
What the heck?
You'd deserve it.
Why would she cheat on someone like me,
with someone like Kang Ho Dong?
Women these days don't like bulky men.
They like men like me, with fine muscles.
You're pretty funny these days.
You'd get sued if you use violence.
If it was me, I'd tell him that I'm
her husband in a calm manner.
I'd tell him that I know everything
about what's going on between the two.
Then I'd make him tell me about
his identity, his work and his family.
Then I'd call everyone who knows him.
Hello, is this Han Soo's father-in-law?
Is this his sister-in-law? I see you're
his teacher in high school. Correct?
I'd expose his affair and
destroy his status and his life.
I knew it, Producer Lee!
My ideal type is someone who is calm
and acts based on data--
- Alpha Go.
- Al...
Aren't you talking too hastily just
because it's someone else's business?
How can men
forgive themselves for cheating
but not forgive women for the same?
- If you ask why--
- In the end...
isn't it about what kind of ending
the writer wants?
Whether he wants to break them up
and go back to before
or he wants to take revenge
with a divorce in mind.
If he follows his emotions, he'll miss
his target and find himself a fool.
- Ji Hoon.
- Yes.
- Have you tried to contact him?
- What?
I'll try to contact him. Or I can google
him and look up his phone number.
Okay, sure.
Now! "My wife is having an affair this
week. What should I do?"
After reading the first line,
his loser vibe is wrapping up my body.
"The man who said
he'd wait for my wife--"
I've heard this story before.
[Hyun Woo]
It's me, so shut up.
I sent him a text. If I don't get
an answer today, I'll look up his ID.
Don't do it, punk!
Hey, someone may be
considering a divorce!
Are you having fun right now?
You guys are sociopaths!
Throw them all out!
Have you lost your mind?
Why would you post it there?
You have me and Yoon Ki.
What kind of good things would you hear
from strangers by posting it there?
Everyone's excited to have
bait to bite off.
I wanted to think rationally.
I'm not in my right mind these days.
I understand,
but it's such an important issue--
Because it's an important issue,
I wanted to ask them!
At first, I posted it on a whim
after I had a drink.
I wasn't expecting much.
But there were actually
quite a few people
who worried about me
as if it was their own issue.
Do you believe that?
They're not your family.
Why would they worry
about a stranger in such
a harsh time like this?
Who would understand what's on my mind?
It goes up and down
a few hundred times a day.
I want to destroy everything
and end it...
but then I think that's not the answer.
You don't understand, punk.
Why would I not understand?
Producer Do, you have a visitor.
Hyun Woo, long time no see.
Choi Yoon Ki's...
- When I look at my wife, I feel cold.
- What are you doing?
Oh, yes, yes.
It's been such a long time,
I didn't recognize you.
I'm sorry.
By the way, what brings you here?
I wanted to see my husband on camera...
and you're working hard,
so I brought some beverages and snacks.
You could've just come.
You didn't have to bring these.
What about my husband?
He said he'd be filming today.
Yoon Ki went out to eat.
- He said that he'd eat with the staff.
- Yes, that's right.
He went to eat with the staff, yes...
But Yoon Ki must be nervous
ahead of his first filming.
He's experiencing indigestion.
So he wanted to get medicine,
and he went outside.
We're busy preparing for the shoot.
What are you guys doing?
Aren't you getting ready?
They're too busy getting ready
for the shoot. Please come this way.
- Like this.
- Straighten your arm.
- I can do it!
Like this.
This is how you're going to swing.
- Nice!
- Wait, try one more swing.
This line has to come alive.
Pick it up, man. Pick it up! Seriously...
Pick it up.
Where are you?
It's not two o'clock yet.
Come right back.
Your wife is in the office now.
I'm going to hit it now.
Honey.
- Have this.
- Thank you.
- He must've gone far.
- What?
- There is no pharmacy around here.
- I see.
Are you going through
a tough time these days?
What?
You ask him to come out
a lot these days.
I do?
Oh, yes, yes. Yes, I do.
I'm sorry.
At first, I wondered
why he was getting so many messages.
I thought he was having an affair.
I see. I'm sorry.
For a woman...
she thinks about things like that
if her husband looks at the phone
more than usual.
It's possible, of course.
Ah Ra, let's say...
Yoon Ki is really having an affair.
What would you do?
I'm not saying that he's
actually having an affair.
I'm just curious.
- I'm planning a program about affairs--
- It's okay.
Excuse me?
As long as he doesn't get caught,
I think it's okay.
Making an effort not to get caught means
that there is still
a possibility it's love.
That's what I want to believe.
What if he gets caught?
I'd have to kill him.
You're back!
Honey.
What brings you here?
I brought some snacks.
How are you feeling?
Me? Well...
- In...
- Is your indigestion better now?
Indigest... that's right.
Yes, I have indigestion.
I feel stuffed up.
Honey, why are you sweating so much?
It happened so quickly,
I'm having cold sweats.
- Shouldn't you go to a doctor?
- No no no.
I took the medicine.
I feel like I'm much better now.
- It's much better.
- Really?
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
Then I'll get going.
- You're leaving?
I'll be a nuisance at work.
I'm happy that I got to see you.
When you have time,
come visit us with your family.
Yes, I will.
- See you at home.
- Okay. Be careful getting home.
Bye.
Awesome! Awesome!
Wasn't it awesome? We even had a face
chat about my shoot earlier.
But see how she followed me
all the way here?
I don't know what she's
detecting these days
she has antennas up in all directions.
I got totally scared.
When did she come?
- Is it funny to you?
- What?
Is it funny that she's nervous
and worried about you having an affair?
Is it not funny?
Do you even know what you're doing?
How can you laugh
while you're betraying your wife?
Don't you feel guilty?
What's wrong with you?
She's trying so hard because
she loves you. Because she loves you.
You should get caught for real
and get punished.
You should be beaten to death.
Hey, you're cheating too!
Why are you blaming me?
You're doing the same,
so why do you kick up my dirt?
I don't do things like having affairs.
You're joking.
My wife's having an affair.
It's not me.
My wife is having an affair, you punk.
You'll have to pay a fine if you litter.
What the heck. Give me.
There's also a fine
for smoking in the park.
Did Attorney Choi's wife leave?
Yes.
She came to check if Attorney Choi
is having an affair, right?
I don't know. It's none of my business.
- She's cool.
- What?
I'm talking about Attorney Choi's wife.
I wasn't able to do that.
About what?
I've had the experience...
He cheated on me.
I'm talking about my ex-husband.
But I couldn't ask him properly.
I thought it was already over,
so it felt lame.
More than anything,
I was afraid to get hurt.
So I held back.
But...
the bitterness in my heart
didn't go away so easily.
I kept building a wall,
and I hated myself for it.
I'm still regretting it.
If I loved him,
I shouldn't have run away.
Even if I'd end up breaking up with him,
I should've made it clear.
But Attorney Choi's wife is different.
How should I say this?
Should I say that I respect her?
I didn't have enough courage
to go to his work.
It must mean
that she loves him that much.
Yes.
They must be really hungry.
- I'll get going first.
- Okay.
Cheer up!
When things get tough,
we should help each other.
[One hour until
my wife's secret meeting!]
Tada!
Is everyone out to eat together?
[Story 1
TOYCRANE's story]
Do I have to wash your underwear
at my age?
Where did you pick this up?
Please! Let's age gracefully.
I have something to say
to that "Toy" or whoever.
I'm practicing. Where was it?
What can you say to him before death?
You can't even wash your own underwear
all your life.
Is there anything you can do right?
What, what, what? What do you possibly
want to say out of this brain?
"N"! Where is "N"?
This. Here it is.
- What about "I"?
- Here.
- "M"?
- Here it is.
- "I"?
- Here, "I".
- "R"?
- Here it is.
- "EO"?
- "R"?
- You did "R" before, you bird head.
Wait a minute.
N and I?
N, I, M, I, R, Eo, R!
Ni, Mi, Reor? Shit?
You wench! That...
That wench...
There is no review, so it must be
a made-up story.
What if he jumped in and she denies it?
There are novelists everywhere.
I can't go to the bathroom waiting
for his review.
We have a lot of good materials.
The best info site in the country.
The one who consoled me at the time
was my new girlfriend.
Have you made up your mind?
If you're still considering, isn't it
because you still love your wife?
If you still plan to barge in
you should do it in order to
get your wife back, not to punish her.
Whether you want to go back to before,
or you want to end everything.
No matter what it is,
violence is not an answer.
Rather, the man and your wife
could feel exonerated by getting hit.
Your weapon has to be love, not violence.
Show that man and your wife
that you love your wife much more.
Yes, that's it.
Producer Do, we have a car ready.
We can leave right now.
- Is it already time?
- We'll pack the props. Wait in the car.
- Wait. I will--
- The client says he's not interested.
What are you talking about?
He wants to cancel it.
He said he's not coming.
He just notified me and hung up.
How can he do that?
This is not going to work.
Hey, call him from your phone.
Call him until he picks it up.
- Put him on with me.
- Yes.
Should I look for someone else?
If we find someone now, when would we
cast him and interview him?
Nothing will change if we sit around
here. Get ready to go out for the shoot.
Bo Young, try to convince him in an hour
no matter what it takes.
Yes.
- All we can do is to try our best.
- Okay, good. Let's go!
- Carry them.
- Yes.
- Writer Kwon.
- Yes?
I'm sorry, but I can't go.
I have to go somewhere.
- You have to go, so you can convince--
- I'll do it. You should go.
Yes, Hyun Woo. You should go.
Okay, thank you.
- Don't give up and--
- Just hurry up and go.
- Can I help you with anything?
- Can you load these?
We don't have time, so please hurry.
Soo Hyun, let's check on this.
Yes, of course.
Everyone, good luck.
Wait. I'll call you right back.
- Where the heck are you going?
- I have to go somewhere.
Hey, you--
Wear this.
- Why would I wear your jacket?
- I don't like you going there in that.
Hey, where is he going?
Should I go with you?
It's okay. You should work.
- Call me, okay?
- Okay.
Hey, hey. Wait, wait!
I don't know
what kind of situation this is.
But if you need my help,
make sure to tell me anytime.
And get proof first. You don't know
what's going to happen later.
So gather your evidence first, okay?
- You should.
- Okay. I'll get going.
Hey, where is he going?
Braised short ribs
that my husband likes.
Come home soon, Honey.
On my way for filming.
Work hard again today.
Hello, this is
the flower arrangement school?
I'd like to request an intensive class.
No, I'd like to take it only on weekends.
Yes. Yes, I understand. Thank you.
Why do you look
like you're going to die?
I must've rushed too much.
It feels tight in my chest...
It feels stuffy.
Jung Soo Yeon, don't come here.
If you come here, it's over.
So please don't come.
- Will "Toycrane" really go to the hotel?
- This, too, shall pass.
Let's not forget.
Your wife is worse than that man.
It's more helpful to humankind to go
to Han River than to go to the hotel.
- He may be beaten to death by now.
- If you went, proof please.
If you broadcasted this, I'd send you
a lot of online balloons.
I came to the hotel.
I am waiting for my wife now.
I can't see my wife yet. To be honest,
I hope she doesn't show up.
You really went...
It's the ultimate level of pathetic.
I understand why
your wife cheated on you.
I guess your wife is pretty enough
to have an affair. I'm jealous.
I'll accompany you to Han River
so that you won't be lonely.
Is this a death match in real life?
But if they're already in the room,
he's a fool.
Okay, Mr. Smith. My pleasure, thank you.
Bye bye.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, sir.
I'd like to check if someone
has already checked in.
Yes, sure.
It's for three o'clock. For Michael.
- Is it for yourself?
- Yes.
Michael... Jordan?
I'm sorry, but I can't check it for you
unless it's for yourself.
- I see.
- Yes.
- By any chance, the room number--
- I'm sorry, sir.
Idiot!
Hyun Woo, how did it go?
This is Writer Kwon Bo Young.
Hello, how are you doing?
I understand
that it's a difficult decision.
Of course! We'll make sure
it won't be harmful to you in any way.
Of course, yes.
Then why don't we come to you
and explain it in more detail?
Thank you! Thank you!
Yes, we'll see you in a bit.
Thank you!
Do you have anything to drink?
He wouldn't change his mind
when he comes out, would he?
Isn't it all for nothing?
What? I'm just worried.
I'm just getting myself ready.
I'll try to convince him.
It's nothing to brag about,
so it's understandable that he's afraid.
He said he'd come, so he does have
thoughts of going through with it.
Let's try to convince him to decide.
And if it doesn't work out,
we'll have to find another solution.
I got it. Why are you annoyed with me?
Writer Kwon, what about Toycrane?
He posted just now, and he's at the hotel
trying to catch his wife and the man.
- Wow.
- What's Toycrane? Where can I find it?
Wow, awesome!
The post is shared in my community.
Toycrane uploaded a new post.
He already got beat up by the man
and went to the hospital.
What the. That's nonsense!
No, that's not right. Here, it says that
he's beating up his wife.
Someone posted that some guy
is beating his wife at a hotel
so he's going to post a video
to prove it.
Crazy... That's absolutely not true!
Toycrane... Claw crane?
Can't you tell right away?
It's a made-up story!
Why are there so many
scammers these days?
It means it's really hot. That's why
people are gathering on their own.
He can't be in his right mind right now
so how will you convince him
for the show?
And it's too late.
Send our client a text
to see if he's there.
Yes, Writer Kwon.
Wife's affair...
At a hotel today.
Toycrane...
Hey!
You should wear this.
Writer Kwon, you can convince the client
even if he keeps saying no, right?
It's your specialty. If you can
convince him, you don't need me.
- Are you going somewhere?
- Yes.
Okay, fine.
Yoon Ki,
you should listen to Writer Kwon.
Joon Young, by any chance--
Let's talk later.
- Come quickly.
- Good luck!
Seriously!
I'm going crazy here. This is too much!
Oh my gosh! What do I do?
Please! Be quiet!
[I'm at the hotel. To be honest,
I hope my wife doesn't show up.]
I'm Toycrane's friend.
I'm on my way to the hotel.
I'll check on the situation,
so don't believe other madeup stories.
Lord Ahn?
He's also saying that he's a friend?
Who's real?
Who is real?
- Why did you come here?
- Because I was worried about you!
I didn't think I'd
be able to work anyway.
- Did Soo Yeon come?
- She hasn't come yet.
- Hyun Woo.
- What?
You're completely pale.
Are you all right?
Breathe deep. You should breathe.
Are you okay?
I feel like I'm a little better.
Do you even know the room number?
You have to know that to barge in.
I asked at the front desk, but he
wouldn't tell me unless I'm that person.
Why does it have to be so strict?
Wait, wait.
Anyone know how to find a room number
even if you didn't book the room?
It's urgent!
Wow, is this it? Toycrane? For real?
It's him! He went to the hotel
but doesn't know the room number.
I'm not him. I'm his friend.
It's for real! The real ones showed up!
If someone should find two men
in a hotel, let us know.
- Who do you think is real? No.1?
- No. 2 is real.
Lord Ahn? Look at his nickname. I can
feel the energy of seeking attention.
It looks like you need a room key
to get on the elevator here.
Really? What should I do?
I'm losing my mind!
How can you not know?
What would you have done without me?
You'd have just watched them
take the elevator up.
Hold on, hold on.
We don't have a room key,
so we may not even get on the elevator.
At this rate, we can't follow his wife
even if she shows up. Please help!
It looks like he's really
Toycrane's friend.
There aren't many hotels where you can't
get on the elevator without a room key.
Tell me the hotel. I'll solve it for you.
I looked it up, and there are four hotels
in Seoul you need a room key to get in.
Is it Hills Hotel, by any chance?
Are you taken away if you get in
without a card?
You won't be able to push any button
if you don't have a key card.
Since when were there so many idiots
in this country?
I've never been.
Is that what happens in hotels now?
Book a room and
get a new key card. Okay?
Let's just get a room.
Then they'll give us a key card.
Then we can get on
the elevator with that.
I have to go that far?
It must be expensive on weekends.
That's not an issue right now!
I'd like a room please.
- Do you mean, one of the guest rooms?
- Yes, just give me one, whatever it is.
Please wait.
I'm sorry, sir. We're full right now,
so nothing is available.
- You don't have any room?
- No. I'm sorry.
That's nonsense! You're lying!
You really don't have any room?
We have availability tomorrow.
May I help you with that?
No, I have to have one today.
We need one today!
- We're in a hurry!
- There is nothing. Let's just go.
What do we do then? What do we do?
You really don't have one?
No.
- Let's just go.
- What do we do?
Let's go.
Why...
You should feel comfortable.
He's a lawyer, so feel free to ask him
any questions or ask for help anytime.
I said I'd do it on a whim...
but I feel embarrassed now it's going
to be broadcasted.
We'll blur out the screen
so that your face won't show.
We can change the sound
of your voice if you'd like.
Still, people in the know would know.
We don't air it without your permission.
You can relax and think of it as
you're talking to us.
To be honest,
I think my wife is having an affair.
But she's not someone
who would ever do that.
Then why do you think
she's having an affair?
You find that your wife
is a bit weird, right?
She goes out a lot,
or checks her cellphone a lot.
No, she's home pretty much all the time.
She doesn't even see
her friends too often.
Our child is in middle school,
so she's busy taking care of her.
What about during the day
after you go to work?
Excuse me?
Women usually have affairs
during the daytime.
I don't think that's it either.
Our child is a good student, and
my wife is very dilligent.
She goes to seminars about college
exams, meets with the teachers...
and she's busy picking her up after
school for additional lessons.
Wow, your wife works very hard.
Then why are you suspicious of her?
I know.
It's strange...
but I feel like something changed
in a strange way.
I don't know why I feel that way.
- I'll go pick it up.
- Thank you.
She's cheating, 100 percent.
What? Why?
You saw the climbing wear
underneath his jacket, right?
- It's safe.
- What about it?
Those who wear the climbing wear
because they enjoy climbing
don't wear a dress jacket over it.
They wear a climbing jacket.
Also, climbing enthusiasts
buy flashy color clothes.
So he didn't get it for himself.
His wife bought it for him.
But how is that proof of cheating?
His wife felt bad for him,
so she bought his clothes
as she was buying one for herself.
And his wife is having an affair
with the excuse of going climbing.
They'd go hiking
to the mountain together.
They'd meet up with their partners
and separate.
Then they'd meet up again
to head home together.
It's obvious.
- Thank you.
Your wife likes to go climbing with her
friend in the neighborhood, right?
How did you know? Every weekend...
What if it's real? What should I do?
I encouraged you to beat him up,
but I don't think you should.
Let's be calm about this here.
If you beat him up
and don't get to ask questions
it'll just become a big mess.
I don't think you should show that side
to Soo Yeon.
- That's what "Tuna Mayo" said, too.
- "Tuna Mayo"?
Yes. "Tuna Mayo" has the most rational
comments on my post.
Hyun Woo! You trust just about anyone,
that's why it's not working out for you!
I don't have anyone to tell.
Unlike women, men are too embarrassed
to tell anyone.
I felt like I'd die,
holding everything in by myself.
Yes, it is embarrassing.
When the husband has an affair,
the wife gets consoled by others.
But when the wife has an affair
the husband gets blamed
for not doing his job.
It's really...
Why haven't you opened up to your wife
and talked to her?
I don't know where or how to start.
Think carefully. Don't be awkward and
start stuttering and embarrass yourself.
- Has it lasted a while?
- Right.
- Since when did they go out?
- Right, right.
Why did he do it?
What does he plan to do now?
- And I need his apology.
- Good job, good job.
By the way,
you really don't know who he is?
Michael? How would I know?
Where did she meet him?
Chatting on the internet, maybe?
I heard that's how a lot of people meet.
That's right. A lot of people meet
through social media.
And there are apps that find people
within a certain distance.
No matter how much I think about it,
I can't figure it out.
She stays at home all the time.
What about a private detective?
Did you not ask?
If you hadn't seen the text message,
you'd have been screwed.
I don't know if it's good or bad
that I saw the text message.
I thought it was a relief.
- You mean, that she locked the phone?
- Yes.
I couldn't see any text messages,
so I felt relieved at the moment.
Then let's suppose that
your wife really cheated on you.
Would you consider getting a divorce?
I don't know. I'm worried about Joon Soo.
Joon Soo is one issue, but divorce is
not easy for many reasons.
Rather than getting a divorce
you'd like to resolve it
through conversation, right?
Or you'd let it slide.
If you just trust her,
at least you feel better.
Is it possible?
Can you do that if it happened to you?
I can't do that!
I tell myself to trust my wife...
but it dawns on me as I walk, as I eat...
I'd live the rest of my life
doubting her.
I can't do that.
Isn't it past the time?
What do I do? If I miss her,
she might really cheat on me.
No.
It's possible she didn't come at all.
Hey, maybe she said no to him?
Calm down, calm down.
Call her.
Call her and ask her where she is.
- Right, call her.
- Call her.
The phone, right.
[My wife]
Hello? Yes, this is he.
What? Where did you say?
Yes, I'll be right there.
Could you wait?
Yes.
Did something happen?
My wife went climbing again today.
She took the car to go
to Gwanak Mountain.
Someone just called me to let me know
that he hit my car.
But the location is not the parking lot
of Gwanak Mountain.
Could you come with me?
Yes, we will.
See? I was right!
She probably skipped climbing
and went right for it.
No, she's not picking it up.
Let's go outside. Let's go, let's go.
Hello?
It's me. Did you call me?
Yes. Where are you now?
She picked it up?
Near the office. We're in a meeting.
I'm busy, I can't talk for long.
I told you I have filming today.
I think it'll run really late.
I wanted to confirm
that you can pick up Joon Soo.
Yes, I should be able
to pick up Joon Soo.
Oh, I see. What a relief.
- Hi, Writer Kwon.
- Where are you? Come quickly!
Where are you?
We're tracking the location of the
client's wife. We're heading over there.
What? All of a sudden?
It just happened.
I don't know how
the situation will change
so I think it'll be hard
to cover on my own.
Okay. I'll be there.
- Have a good meeting.
- Okay.
Hyun Woo, I should go to the location.
- You can stay by yourself, right?
- Yes. I'm not a kid.
You should hurry up and go.
She says she's in a meeting.
I don't think she's coming here.
So what's wrong with your face?
I don't know.
I trusted Soo Yeon no matter what.
But I can't trust her anymore.
It must be my fault.
No, anyone in your situation
would feel that way.
It'll be a relief if she doesn't come.
But just in case, if she comes...
don't be flustered. Like Yoon Ki said,
get evidence of them going in the room.
After that,
the three of you should have a talk.
You should have a clean result, Hyun Woo.
- I'm leaving.
- Go. Go!
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
Bye.
I knew it.
Look at the car.
- This car...
- Yes, I'm the car owner.
Yes, I scratched it here.
It was narrow on the way up.
She's a real trickster.
She parked the car here so that
there won't be any curtain marks.
She'd get caught right away if the motel
curtain brushed against a dusty car.
A real trickster! I told you yesterday.
- Attorney Choi.
- Yes?
You should keep your mouth shut.
Writer Kwon, you're about to hit me.
Can I hit you?
It's not like I said anything wrong.
What kind of situation is this?
This is nothing. If you'd leave us with
your number, we'll call you later.
We'll call you. Don't worry too much.
Bye now.
Would she be at this hotel?
Please calm down. Let's go back
to the car and think carefully.
This way please.
Joon Young, over here!
Where have you been?
Why are you coming now?
There is nothing certain as of yet.
We don't know if your wife
is in that hotel.
First, you should call your wife.
Tell her that you got a call
about someone hitting the car
and see what she says.
Hyun Woo, how did it go? Did she come?
[My love Hee Ok]
Honey, it's me.
I just got a call from someone
that he scratched my car.
Can you check? Yes, I have his number.
Okay.
She said she'd check.
Gwanak Mountain is
a bit far from here, right?
Excuse me?
Did you see her or what?
Someone's coming out!
Is that your wife?
That...
Producer Ahn!
Attorney Choi, aren't you getting out?
This is a bullet-proof window!
I'm not getting off!
What? What did you say?
I'm getting off.
I just did that for no reason.
What are you doing here?
Who is he?
What are you doing?
Who are these people?
I'm asking who this man is!
Didn't you come here knowing everything?
Stop with the camera!
Who are these people?
Hello, I'm the main producer
Ahn Joon Young...
I don't think you'd
accept my business card.
Your husband asked for help
from our program.
Did you ask them to follow me?
Producer...
What the heck? Get rid of the cameras!
I'll break all of them!
I'm a lawyer.
Since it's a matter between these two
please leave them to have a talk.
Yes, you should go, Honey.
I'll call you--
"Honey"? Have you lost your mind?
- Don't yell at me!
- Why? Are you embarrassed?
You know it's embarrassing?
You're laughing? You're laughing?
Why don't we go somewhere quiet?
We don't record anything
without your permission.
We just want
to listen to your conversation.
But if you feel uncomfortable,
we'll leave you.
No, let's do it.
Whether it's a talk or filming,
let's do it.
Why don't we go? Let's go.
How can you have no shame?
Am I supposed to cry here then?
If you did something wrong, shouldn't
you at least pretend that you're sorry?
Why do I have to pretend to be sorry?
- You're seeing another man.
- I'm seeing another man, so what?
- You are a mom with a child!
- So I can't meet a man?
How can you say that?
You have a husband!
Please calm down.
If you get too upset,
you can't have a good conversation.
The most important thing is
why she was having an affair.
That's right.
Let me at least ask the reason.
Why on earth did you cheat on me?
- There is no reason.
- What?
I just... met him when I went climbing.
He said he liked me.
He wasn't bad.
So I kept in touch with him.
You're a married woman!
A married woman with a husband!
Then... did you do it
with a divorce in mind?
I've never considered getting a divorce.
If I do it, I will. If I don't, I won't.
First, it's true that I saw another man.
Now my husband found out, we have to
figure out something, divorce or not.
- Even if you begged--
- Why would I beg?
It's over if we get a divorce.
What about Jin Ah?
Didn't you think about our daughter?
Hee Ok, we've lived together
for 15 years.
How can you do this to me?
You're right.
After I started seeing him
I couldn't understand how
I've lived with you for 15 years.
I lived like such an idiot.
And I don't need our child.
To be honest, she looks like you,
so I can't stand to see her.
What? Are you going to hit me?
Yes, hit me. Go ahead!
I didn't want to give you alimony.
Hit me and let's call it even.
Hey, hit me! I said, hit me!
She's something.
Of course, you're number one!
If I loved him,
I shouldn't have run away.
Even if I'd end up breaking up with him,
I should've made it clear.
If they get on, I can't find out
which floor they get off. What do I do?
I wonder what excuse
Toycrane's wife will have.
What excuse could she possibly have?
Secure the evidence and get a divorce.
He's pathetic for going to the hotel
to catch them in the act.
She must've cheated on him
because he's pathetic.
Which bridge
is the closest to the hotel?
I'll be waiting for you at the
seventh pier of Sungsan Bridge.
All of the losers in the world...
Beat them up to death and
post a photo to prove it.
I'm at J Hotel now.
I don't think this is it.
Take a picture of the guy.
We should bury him alive.
Let's just stop them first!
Can't you tell us which hotel it is?
Honey.
Yes.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Jung Soo Yeon,
you didn't mean it, did you?
I'm sorry. What could I possibly say?
Let's get a divorce.
Let's just get a divorce!
Don't get a divorce.
Don't do a favor for her!
Just get a divorce.
Show what a happy life you have!
Find someone younger and prettier
than her and live a happy life.
What would be the reason
to cheat on you?
Would you have no fault in it?
Is it saying that I did something wrong
to cause the affair?
What's the identity of this?
- It's tuna mayo.
- Tuna mayo? Is that what you like?
This is the best.
How is Writer Kwon doing?
I heard she's been offered a job.
This is betrayal!
How can Writer Kwon do this to us?
- Producer Ahn.
- We'll never let you go.
You should have loyalty!
Why didn't you follow me out from the
hotel? Why were you there with him?
Tell me. Did you sleep with him?
Did you sleep with him?
I'm asking if you slept with him!