BioskopKeren
[My Wife's Having An Affair This Week]
[Episode 4]
Does anyone know how we can find out
their hotel room number?
This is so exciting.
Did they meet?
Ask him if they are together.
I guess you are Lord Ahn.
It would be nice if you could check
how things are going and let us know
as soon as possible.
She will say she cheated on him
because of the husband.
- That's what they all say.
- If the man was a good guy
why would the wife cheat on him?
You must be deeply hurt.
I can feel your pain.
I will leave first.
Honey.
Yes.
What brings you here?
Work.
I came to check our filming site.
Huh? Look at this bastard.
We are going to the lounge.
What floor are you going to?
Do you think you can fool me?
If you guys are going to the lounge,
why do you have a room key?
Huh?
- Are you Jung Soo Yeon's husband?
- That's right.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ji Sun Woo from J Motors.
Let's go to the room and talk.
Let's be calm and cold.
Show him and your wife that you
love her way more than him.
That's right. Whoever that guys is
I have no reason to lose to him.
Get proof. No matter what happens later,
get all the proof you can get.
Smile.
Let's go in.
Let's talk over here. Here.
Have a seat.
To be honest...
I hoped that this wouldn't happen.
I saw the text you sent.
"I reserved a room without your
permission. I miss you."
At first, I thought it could be spam
or voice phishing.
I hoped that was the case.
Until this day that you guys
waited in excitement....
Every day I... I tried to talk with her.
But I missed my chances.
Everything is ruined now.
- It's all our fault.
- "Our fault?"
"Our..."
Did you say you are Ji Sun Woo?
Yes.
Are you married?
- I have a wife.
- You have a wife, you bastard.
Does you wife know
what you have been doing?
No, she doesn't know.
What were you planning on doing?
To take it this far...
You must have had a plan.
Oh, so you didn't want to
take it to the end.
So you are like playing with fire.
Just for fun?
Right? Both of you.
You guys are playing with fire.
Hey, Jung Soo Yeon. Your ring...
You don't actually love him, right?
- I'm...
- We are playing with fire.
We didn't intend to ruin
each other's family.
On that same note, I think we are just
playing with fire. Just for fun.
Even though it is an
"inappropriate relationship"
I love her.
Of course, I feel sorry to
you and my family.
- I'm sure Soo Yeon will feel the same--
- Soo Yeon, Soo Yeon!
Who said you can say
my wife's name like that?
I'm sorry.
Hey, what about you?
Do you have anything to say?
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
- What can I say to you?
- Who said I want to hear how you feel?
Don't you have something to tell me?
Oh my. What are you guys?
Why are you guys so calm and cool?
You guys just got caught cheating.
You guys are supposed
to kneel down and beg for mercy!
Aren't you supposed to say "I'm sorry,
forgive me" or something like that?
Do you mean there's no need to do that?
Okay. Let's get divorced.
Let's get divorced.
We can just get divorced.
Don't ever think about coming back.
Why are you so cool? You are so cool.
Do whatever you guys want to do!
Kwon Bo Young. You punched a person.
You don't seem like you are
self-reflecting at all.
Look here. This is also a memory.
We have to take a picture.
Look here.
Okay, go ahead and make fun of me.
You don't get many chances like this.
What did she say?
She won't let it go that easily.
You totally ruined her.
Where did you learn to punch like that?
I saw you make her head spin!
Stop it.
I'm not kidding. Her head spun back.
I was too surprised. I made eye contract
with her and so I said "hello."
Gosh.
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
Is the client okay?
How could he be okay?
He saw all that with his eyes.
The filming site must have been a mess.
I should have held back.
But she was bringing the child
into the mess and being nasty.
A mom shouldn't do that.
You did well. Even I felt better.
Good job.
It's Yoon Ki.
Hey, Yoon Ki.
How much longer
does she have to stay here?
For a case like this,
they will let her out soon.
- I met with the victim.
- You will be out soon.
She can get out if her guardian comes.
Tell her not to worry.
I'm going to see Hyun Woo.
I will be there soon too.
He said your guardian has to come here.
Who should I call?
I will call him or her for you.
- Guardian?
- Should I call your parents?
Oh, they passed away.
Who should I call?
Kwon Bo Young, is your guardian here?
Here. I'm Kwon Bo Young's guardian.
Why is Producer Ahn my guardian?
- There's no one else.
- I don't want you to be my guardian.
- Are you going to stay there?
- Yes, I'm going to stay here.
- Really?
- I know you are going to ask me
to do all sorts of things for you.
Yes. I'm here.
Never. You can't do that.
I don't want it.
Gosh. You went though a lot.
- Eat it.
- No.
Eat it. I heard if you eat this,
you won't come back here ever again.
Where did he go?
Hyun Woo. How did it go?
Is she here? Did you see Soo Yeon?
- Yes.
- Hey, did you hit him?
You didn't kill him, right?
Oh. Door. Bam.
Okay. You did well. You hit the door.
You hit the door well.
Did you talk with them?
What did you say?
I said we should get divorced.
I told them to do whatever they
want to do. And I walked out.
So there are only two of
them in the room.
- Yes.
- "Yes?"
What do you mean yes? Are you crazy?
What can they be doing now?
What if they are really
consoling each other?
I thought she would follow me.
If I said "let's get divorced"
I thought she would follow me out
and beg me.
But she stayed there.
Just leave them alone.
You thought she would follow you out?
I didn't have any idea
what I should've said.
I'm don't even know
what I actually said.
I was the only one
who got all worked up and upset.
I couldn't do anything.
I just walked out.
What about that bastard?
He looked confident.
- He said it was just for fun.
- What?
He said everything he wanted to say.
He has a better job.
He will earn more than me.
His house will be nicer than mine.
His car will be nicer than mine.
- No wonder she fell for him.
- Yoon Ki.
Okay.
What about proof?
Did you take pictures?
Yes.
I took pictures.
Wow, look at this. He's handsome.
He looked nice. He has a family too.
This can be used as proof, right?
Proof that she cheated on him.
We can use this as proof.
But if you want alimony, or to sue her
- we need clear information.
- Information?
Something like how long they have been
dating each other?
How often did they see each other?
You asked them about that, right?
- No, I couldn't ask her.
- What?
Did you not ask if that
was the first time or not?
- No.
- Gosh, you.
Then what did you do there?
Before seeing them together I thought
I should say this if she says this,
and I should say that if she says that.
I thought if I get divorced,
I should live like this with Joon Soo.
The day I send Joon Soo off to the army,
I should do this.
I should do this on the day of
Joon Soo's wedding.
I thought about all those things.
I should do this if she
asks me to forgive her.
I should do this if she wants to stay
away for a while.
I thought about that too.
But now,
I have no idea what I should do.
I can't tell you it's going to be okay.
I can't tell you it will get better.
Just end it here.
I've seen many cases like this.
Just end it here and enjoy your life.
Meet someone younger
and prettier than her.
And enjoy your life.
You just came out of hell.
Hyun Woo, no. Don't divorce her.
Don't do her that favor.
You are only making her happy.
Keep her by your side and get payback.
What do you mean keep her by his side?
She won't be there.
If he's in misery, she can't be happy.
You guys promised each other
on your wedding day.
Whether it's good or bad, happy or sad,
you guys promised to stay together.
You should be responsible for that
promise you made.
You're like an old man.
I will get enough alimony
from her and that guy.
So show them how you enjoy your life.
That's how you should get your revenge.
Now, everything is over.
I have nothing left in me.
I'm not sure what I should do.
I wanted to thank you guys first.
In the hotel room today, my wife,
me, and that guy...
The three of us talked.
If my wife begged me and told me
she didn't want to get divorced
I was going to forgive everything
and come back home with her.
She didn't even flinch.
She was calm and cold.
She said it's all her fault.
And I thought I should
just end it there.
My wife was my life, and I loved her.
But to her
I guess our relationship was not
something she wanted to hold onto.
Now, divorce is
our only solution, right?
Mom.
I have to stay here for a few days.
Did you argue with Dad again?
What about Soo Yeon?
She's still at work?
- What about our Joon Soo?
- Joon Soo?
That's right. Joon Soo.
Soo Yeon was going to pick him up.
Mom, I will be back soon.
- Hello, I'm sorry. I'm too late.
- Hello.
Soo Yeon took him a moment ago.
- What?
- You guys didn't talk to each other?
No, that's not it.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay, bye.
Where did she go with him?
She's driving me crazy.
Why is she not answering her phone?
How could she take the kid? Geez.
Where are you? What are you doing?
How could you take Joon Soo?
His mom took her child.
Why are you yelling?
Mom, why do you have her phone?
Soo Yeon and Joon Soo are here.
Hurry and come home.
What?
- Joon Soo, did you have fun today?
- Dad.
You're here.
Let's talk.
Why are you here?
I told you not to come home.
I thought we should talk.
What's there for us to talk about
in this kind of situation?
I'm sorry. I didn't know Mom was here.
I will somehow send Mom home.
Leave as soon as Mom leaves.
- Mom.
- You didn't eat dinner yet, right?
I know you're busy with work
but don't make your husband skip meals.
I'm sorry.
Don't stand there. Get the soup ready.
Okay.
This is so good.
Right? Eat a lot, my puppy.
Are you busy these days?
Yes. A bit...
I know you don't have to
go grocery shopping.
But don't buy too much rice.
I think it has been there for too long.
It doesn't taste that good.
Okay, I will do that.
When I go back home, I will send you
some rice. Put aside the ones you have.
Let's make rice cakes with that rice.
Yes, Mother.
Where is Soo Yeon?
She's giving Joon Soo a bath.
Mom.
I'm sorry, but can't you go home today?
She cheated on you, right?
Huh? Who said that?
You thought I wouldn't notice?
Am I right?
That's not it.
- Why did you hit me?
- You.
You saw me going though all that trouble
because of your dad.
How could you even think
about having an affair?
What?
This is so upsetting. You are so lame.
What are you talking about?
You would know
if you ever took care of your family.
Just by looking at the kitchen and stuff
you can tell how much the wife
cares about the house and the family.
She's working and raising a child.
I can see that she is doing her best
to make everything work.
- Mom, that's not it.
- Look how thin she is.
Don't you feel bad for her?
I said that's not it.
Listen to me carefully.
If you cheat, you will be the one
who will be left alone.
You are in your 40's.
If you get divorce now
who do you think is going
to take care of you?
I haven't seen anyone live well
after leaving his wife.
Why me...
I'm a weirdo too. Why am I
watching this if it's that scary?
But I want to watch it.
I want to watch it, but I will close it.
What is this?
Gosh, that rascal.
He's drunk.
Wake up!
If you are drunk, go to your house.
Why are you here?
You scared me.
Writer Kwon.
I came to check if Writer Kwon
is doing well.
Why? Because I'm Writer Kwon's guardian.
That's my spot. Don't lie down.
Why are you bumming here? Get up.
Gosh, you shouldn't do this
to your guardian.
Don't fall asleep.
I'm going to throw you out.
Writer Kwon, what does it feel like
to get divorced?
Does it feel refreshing?
If you are that curious,
why don't you try it yourself?
I'm curious.
I was wondering how others feel...
What are you saying?
What is this? He fell asleep.
Mom is sleeping.
I have nothing to say. Just leave.
I have something to say.
I don't want to listen to your excuses.
It's not an excuse.
For now, I'm not going to
see him anymore.
For now?
What do you mean "for now?"
Are you letting me know that you
are going to see him later?
Do you think I'm that dumb?
I have nothing I want to ask you.
And I don't want to listen to you.
After Mom leaves, leave Joon Soo here
and leave the house, okay?
Joon Soo.
Dad, we are going to the amusement park.
What?
That's right.
You should get ready too.
Everyone sends their kids
camping and stuff.
They don't keep the kids at home.
Instead of telling him to turn off the
TV and not play with cell phone
play with him on the weekends.
Try to be nice and make up for it.
Give Soo Yeon a chance to rest.
We don't have time to
waste on those things.
You are the one who cheated.
How could you say that?
Mom, he is busy today.
You should go to work. Hurry.
You might be late.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
They have all the paintings
that you like.
It will totally change
the feel of the house
if we hang it
on the living room wall, right?
We could buy it as an investment
but it's a bit too much
to hang it on our wall.
Is that so?
You studied art and you have different
views when you look at these pieces.
I think I'm distracting you.
I will be quiet. I will be over there.
Enjoy it.
That piece looks a bit boring.
That's boring, right?
That piece looks boring,
but it's also thrilling.
Should we make it more thrilling?
We should do this often.
You don't like art that much.
I'm sorry. I'm making you bored.
Honestly, I don't like looking
at art pieces.
But I like the person
looking at the pieces. You.
Cheers.
What are you doing?
- Honey.
- What are you doing?
People might see us.
Who cares?
You are my baby.
That's right. You eat so well.
Let's start the meeting.
Producer Bae, how did the editing go?
- It's ready.
- Okay.
Then Producer Ahn just has
to get his ready.
- Thank you.
- Producer Ahn.
We are in the meeting room.
Hyun Woo.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Am I the only one not okay?
We are having a meeting.
Will you be okay?
Take your time. I will be in there.
Tell us more about your experience.
It's all because of the husband.
It's his fault.
Getting divorced is the solution, One.
He should forgive her, Two.
- One.
- Two.
One of them has to die for this to end.
Han River's water temperature is
above 0 degrees Celsius today.
Come here quickly.
It must have been very tough.
You went though a lot.
How do you feel?
You said everything has ended.
But I think this is the beginning.
Your wife would not
have told you the truth
without knowing how she feels.
And without telling her how you feel...
Did you really want to end it like this?
Why did your wife
want to have an affair?
Did you not do anything wrong?
Wrong?
Does that mean it's my fault
that she cheated on me?
Now that I think about it,
it makes me upset.
Who is that?
Geez.
- You met another man.
- What's wrong with that?
- You have a kid.
- I can't date a man if I have a kid?
How could you say that?
You have a husband!
Even if you beg me,
that won't be enough.
Why would I beg you?
We can just get divorced.
All this time...  I was dumb.
I don't need the kid anymore.
Honestly, I don't want to see them
because they look like you.
What? Are you going to hit me?
Okay, hit me. I didn't want to
give you alimony.
Let's settle it like this. Hit me.
Why can't you hit me? Hit me--
We can't use this, right?
We could have got something better
if I held back a bit.
I'm sorry.
I feel sorry to the client.
He couldn't ask what he wanted
to ask her because of me.
Like what?
You might want to know why that person
wants to break up.
He must have been the same.
"What happened to my wife?"
"Why did my wife cheat on me?"
"By any chance,
did I do anything wrong?"
Why did your wife
want to have an affair?
Did you do anything wrong?
If we can't use this,
should I delete it?
No, we can use it.
We could make a good preview clip
out of that.
What should we do about the filming?
The couple talking face to face...
Isn't that a good idea?
Yes. It seems realistic, and there's
some tension involved as well.
Seeing them sitting down like that
reminds me of that TV show Tongue War.
Tongue War. That's right.
It has that feel to it.
- Tongue War is a good idea.
- Tongue War.
The war of the fierce women.
Our concept is way more intense.
Then aren't we supposed to have someone
like Kim Gu Ra? To balance it out?
- We have a perfect candidate.
- Who?
About Hyun Woo's program.
Do they really have to
film on the weekend?
They are only available on the weekends.
Should I just say no to them?
I don't even have time to be with you.
- Should I say no?
- That's okay.
I signed up for a flower arrangement
class in the next building.
I stay near you
and I can look after you.
You could have done it somewhere
near our house.
Flower arrangement is very important.
So don't even worry about me, okay?
I'm using that as an excuse
to go to work with you.
It makes my heart flutter.
It makes my heart flutter too.
- Oh.
- What is this? You are bleeding.
Isn't this too dangerous?
You could die from this.
You shouldn't do this.
- I'm okay.
- No, no, you're not okay.
Flower arrangement is too dangerous.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
- It's okay. You can go.
- Let's go to the hospital.
- I don't have to go to the hospital.
- No way.
It's that fitness center right there.
It's the fitness center, "Health Line."
Gosh.
I'm too full.
I can't put the belt on for you.
It's okay. You don't have a belly.
No. Look at this.
I can't even reach for the belt.
I think I should start exercising.
For your sake.
That's a good idea.
I'll search for a personal trainer.
No. I should exercise
where there's a lot of people.
To be more motivated.
I should go to that place.
You didn't eat lunch, right?
Oh, thank you.
It's tuna and mayonnaise.
Do you not like anything greasy?
Do you like tuna and mayonnaise?
Yes.
Since I live alone, and I'm too lazy to
cook, I tried all kinds of instant food.
I think this is the best.
Bo Young, by any chance...
Do you have stocks?
What is wrong with you?
Do you not remember?
I think it was about
seven, eight years ago.
You said a blue bird sat on
your shoulder in your dream.
You said that blue bird said
"Blue fund."
So all of our team bought blue fund
and we all lost a lot of money.
Hyun Ji who used to sit next to me
lost her deposit too.
That's right.
Is Hyun Ji doing well?
After that, she was so shocked
that she quit writing
and she works in a factory.
Really? A factory?
Because of me?
It's so easy to fool you. I'm proud.
Hyun Ji has a kid now. She's doing well.
I haven't done stocks since then.
I sometimes go to the stock gallery
to get some sources.
Oh, really? Then by any chance, you--
Hello? Oh, yes.
Today?
Hold on a second.
Producer Do, you should go see the CEO.
I'm here.
- I said I'm here.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
There's a post I follow these days.
Have a seat.
Come here.
Is something wrong?
It's not a big deal.
How is Writer Kwon doing?
Why do you ask?
I heard a strange rumor.
Another team is trying to scout her.
She gets those offers all the time.
There are many producers
who want our program to fail
so that they can take Bo Young.
Who? Who are those bastards?
What would you do if you found out
who they are? We actually failed.
Anyway. There's a rumor that she is
actually going to sign the contract.
She wouldn't sign a contract
behind our back.
But the rumor sounds too real.
You know Producer Oh Ki Han, right?
The one who made
"Dear My Love Geum Dong."
I heard she is going to sign
a contract with him.
How could she do this to us?
I'm really...
I'm upset.
This is very annoying.
I trusted her.
How could she do this to us?
We are making a program now.
How could she betray us like this?
- Hey, you sit down.
- Betray... Betray...
I can't breathe.
Breathe.
Let it out.
Oh, that's right.
Okay, I will call you back. Thank you.
What did he say?
Producer Oh Ki Han asked people if
there's any good variety show writers.
And some of the writers talked
about Writer Kwon.
Right. Bo Young wrote a sitcom too.
Do you know when their meeting is?
I think it's today.
- Today?
- Yes.
I heard her talking with Eun Jung.
Should I print all the stories I found
so that you can read it at night?
Let's do that tomorrow.
I have a meeting tonight.
I can't go to our meeting.
Hello? Oh, yes. Today?
Hold on a second.
That's right.
I think it's today.
- Hello.
You signed up to exercise, right?
- Yes, that's me.
- We will go right in.
The most important pose
in fitness is the squat.
You have to build your lower body
muscle to build your upper body muscle.
It's that important a pose.
To do a squat, fold your arms.
Pull your waist back.
Bend it.
Stand up.
Push it forward.
You have to do it with power
in your lower back.
Hip exercises are very important.
I can see that.
- You should try it.
- When you bend down--
- Fold my arms.
- Yes, fold your arms.
Pull your waist back.
Bend your legs.
Keep your upper body straight.
Put your weight on your hip.
- Oh, yes.
- We will do three sets of 30 squats.
Three sets of 30 squats?
90 times? We can do 100 times instead.
- Do you want to give it a try?
- Okay, let's do 100 times then.
- Okay.
- Start. One.
Stand up.
Keep it straight.
Keep going. Two.
Bend it.
- You have to go down all the way.
- Okay.
Keep your upper body up.
Bring it up.
Keep your legs steady.
Stand up.
- You have to focus. Stand up.
- Okay.
Stand up.
You have five left.
48.
Stop. You can step down.
Please check my pose.
- Just a moment please.
- Go drink some water.
We will restart right away.
Go all the way down.
I will get going first...
Where is Producer Do?
I'm leaving.
I said I'm leaving. Bye.
- Bye.
Are we not going to stop her?
Let's just trust her.
Writer Kwon won't do--
What do you mean trust her?
When a woman decides to leave,
that's it.
Oh? Are you leaving?
Bye.
It got too loose. Just like
your skin get loose as you age.
A couple gets loose too.
What's important is the kind of ending
that writer wants.
If I loved him
I shouldn't have ran away from him.
Even if we ended up breaking up,
I should have made that clear.
You don't have to hurry when you
break up with someone.
You should put your guard down first.
The thing that made the wanderer
take off his coat
was not a cold wind, but warm sunshine.
Approach it with a pure heart.
And listen to her story.
Bo Young, do you have a minute?
- Go ahead.
- Let's meet and talk.
Really?
But I have an appointment.
I'm not in the area, what should we do?
I will go there. Where are you?
Here?
- Producer Do, to be honest, I--
- Yes, I know.
I know, so let's talk in person.
Where are you?
Oh my goodness.
Woongsan in Nonhyeondong.
Am I a taxi driver or something?
Bo Young said she's there.
Hurry and punch it in.
- Where?
- Woongsan.
- Yes.
Hurry.
Thank you.
- Producer Do.
- Bo Young.
It's too early. You shouldn't do this.
Yes, I know I didn't do
any good for you.
I asked you to carry out too many
things because I had a trust in you.
I should have done better before
something like this would happen.
I realize how important that person is
only after something like this happens.
I will do better. I will change.
Producer Do.
I'm sorry.
Writer Kwon, if this
is not going to work, I will...
But you are not Producer Oh Ki Han.
You look nice today.
You look pretty.
Hold on.
Something doesn't seem right.
Are you on a blind date?
Oh my.
I'm very sorry. Don't misunderstand me.
I'm her senior at work.
Regarding our work...
Our Writer Kwon Bo Young is the most
talented and prettiest person at work.
Have a great time. I'm sorry.
Why are you alone?
What about Writer Kwon?
- It's not that.
- What do you mean it's not that?
Bo Young is on a blind date.
Oh, blind date?
Blind date?
Yes.
Oh, you got your hair done too.
You put makeup on too.
What's wrong with you?
You're wearing a skirt.
She's wearing a skirt.
- It's a blind date.
- Yes.
She has been married once.
She wants to get married again?
She's a weirdo--
It's way too hard. I can't do this.
- Fitness.
- Yes.
Have fun.
Excuse me.
Sir.
Oh my goodness.
What were you thinking?
I thought you were transferring
to a new team. I'm very sorry.
I never thought that you would
go on a blind date.
Huh? Why?
Can't I go on a blind date?
Do you mean no one could want
to go on a date with me?
No, that's not what I meant. I'm sorry.
Did you really want to go
on a blind date?
No way.
My senior kept on asking me to do
him a favor, so I couldn't say no.
I will apologize to you again.
I'm so sorry.
But I was glad.
I felt like an important person.
At least a bit.
Right? You saw how I really felt, right?
- Bo Young.
- Yes?
Can I ask you a strange question?
That Toycrane. The one who
posts those stories online.
Yes.
What do you think about him?
He is a lame person.
Huh?
I feel bad saying this
about someone I don't know.
But he is just a dumb.
- Oh.
- But.
For some reason, I want to root for him.
It doesn't sound like a total
stranger's story. I feel for him.
I told you my husband cheated on me.
I don't want him to fail like me.
Isn't that how everyone is?
If you step in a puddle and get wet,
and someone else comes along
you warn that person about the puddle.
That's right.
Get in. I'll give you a ride.
You can go first. I will go later.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
- Give her a ride home.
- Okay, bye.
I will say just one thing.
You are dead if you tell other people.
About what? Your blind date.
Your makeup? Your skirt?
Everything.
Why did you go on a blind date
all of a sudden?
My senior asked me a favor
and I had no choice. Why?
You had no choice?
How could you go on
a blind date like that?
Your life depends on that.
If you couldn't say no again...
I thought about getting married again
if he is a good guy.
- Why? Can't I do that?
- But, still...
You can. You can.
You can. You can. You can. You can.
Thank you, Hot pepper Tuna.
Oh, Tuna Mayo.
Dear Tuna Mayo.
I'm thankful for you.
I'm thinking about talking with
my wife again.
I want to hear how she really feels.
I don't want to get divorced either.
Is she not here yet?
Joon Soo and Joon Soo's Mom
will stay at my house tonight.
Gosh, Mom.
What's the need to do this?
Mom, it's me.
- Are you home?
- Yes.
Your Dad came to pick me up,
but Joon Soo insisted
on going with his grandfather.
So we brought them here.
Let me talk to Soo Yeon.
She's taking a shower.
Oh, really? When she comes out
tell her to come home.
Tell her I have something to tell her.
And you take care of Joon Soo
just one more day.
Okay.
Beg her.
- Don't make her cry.
- It's not like that.
Okay.
Tell her to hurry and come home.
Now, I feel more like myself.
Should I start working on my
fantastic story plan?
Don't skip a meal and eat this.
I earn enough to buy you a meal.
I will enjoy it.
I'm here.
Well...
Can I talk first?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I know we can't put this behind us
just like this.
I didn't do that to get divorced.
Since when was it?
I'm asking you when did it start?
Was that a one-time thing?
Or have you been seeing him for a while?
How long have you been deceiving me?
I know you can't understand me
saying this...
But I didn't mean to deceive you.
Do you think that makes sense?
Were you going to ask my
permission to cheat on me then?
You know that's not what I mean.
Can't you tell what's going on here?
Do you think you can say that to me?
Aren't you supposed to beg me
to forgive you first?
You can't tell me if
this makes sense or not.
You...
What do you want to do?
What do you mean?
We are getting divorced.
If you are like this,
do you think I can forgive you?
On that day,
why didn't you follow me?
Why did you stay there
with that bastard?
Did you tell him "I cheated on him
because my husband is a fool"?
Huh?
I will sleep at Mom's place tonight.
Let's talk again when you calm down.
Don't even think about leaving.
Tell me. Since when was it?
When was it?
Six months ago.
What? Six months ago?
Did you sleep with him?
I don't want to talk anymore.
Did you?
Did you sleep with him?
Yes, I slept with him.
I missed him.
I missed him all this time.
So I asked him to meet me.
Dear Tuna Mayo.
I tried to talk with my wife.
But I failed.
My wife really cheated on me.
I still tried to ask her.
I tried to listen to her.
But nothing is going my way.
- Producer Do.
- Yes.
You didn't respond to my question.
I tried to talk with her
and listen to what she has to say.
But my wife left our house.
To be honest, I'm that Toy...
[Pudding]
Wait.
Is your ID "Pudding?"
Yes.
Your wife left the house?
Huh? Oh.
And so I was going to...
have a drink with you.
Didn't you say you drink alone
a lot these days?
Yes. But I have to finish
my story plan today.
Oh, that's right.
I should call Joon Young over then.
Okay.
Okay. I will get going.
Since when was your ID "Pudding?"
It has been a long time.
- Oh, it has been a long time.
- Yes.
I will get going.
Bye.
- You can just go buy--
- It's hot. I'm a mom.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
What's wrong?
Bo Young, I heard you went
on a blind date yesterday?
I heard you wore a skirt too.
Your makeup was amazing.
So did you sleep with him?
What?
You got dumped.
All right. Where is Producer Ahn?
- He's in the meeting room.
- Oh, meeting room?
You are here.
I lost my most precious thing.
It's up. It's up.
- Where?
My wife cheated on me.
Team Leader Jung, the tile--
But I couldn't hear a reasonable
reason from her.
Team Leader Jung, line three.
Manager Ji Sun Woo is on the line.
This is Jung Soo Yeon.
Team Leader Jung, line three.
Manager Ji Sun Woo is on the line.
This is Jung Soo Yeon.
Could you take a look at it
as soon as you are done editing?
Okay. I will take a look at it soon.
So...
I have no choice
but to hear it from him.
I can't forgive
my wife or him.
This week...
I'm going to fight the guy...
who took away the most
precious thing from me.
BioskopKeren
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Ji Sun Woo.
I didn't come here to say hello to you.
J Motors wants to change
the Project Manager.
It would have been nice if you
could've told me ahead of time.
Your husband came to my company
to see me.
Not that many people come here because
they have a problem in their marriage.
Do you have a problem with your wife?
- Oh.
- Did you get a new cologne?
No, it's the one I always use.
You can do the impossible.
That's why cheating is thrilling.
What do you mean it's thrilling?
Think about that spouse on the other
side. How could you say that?
It seems like there is no clear
suspect or a victim.
They didn't really mean to do that.
Call her.
Call your wife who is asleep without
knowing what's happening to her.
Call her if you don't want
things to get messy!