BIOSKOP KEREN
Let's get divorced!
Sure, let's get divorced!
Why didn't you follow me out
of the hotel room?
Why did you stay with that bastard?
Did you sleep with him?
I'm asking if you slept with him!
Yes, I slept with him.
I missed him.
I've wanted to see him the whole time.
So I contacted him first.
Now it's over.
[My Wife Is Having an Affair This Week]
[Episode 5]
I told you not to worry about breakfast.
Good morning, Mother.
Joon Soo! You have to go
to kindergarten. Let's get up!
This is the back.
Jung Soo Yeon, you didn't
really mean it, did you?
Don't you have anything to say?
Fine, let's get divorced!
Let's get divorced!
We can get divorced! Let's get divorced!
Don't ever think of coming home again.
Do whatever you want,
you cold-blooded people!
Yes, this is Ji Sun Woo.
No, I'll come in now.
It looks like I should head out first.
I'm sorry.
Mom. Mom!
Joon Soo, your arm.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Yoon Woo goes to an art academy.
He says he throws paint colors and
makes dinosaurs with colored papers.
Do you also want to go
to the art academy?
Not necessarily...
Okay, I'll let you go.
- Oh, yes!
My wife had an affair.
But I haven't heard anything from
my wife that could convince me.
I cannot forgive my wife
or that bastard.
Today...
I will fight the bastard who took
away the most precious thing I have.
I'm sorry to make you wait.
I'm Ji Sun Woo.
I didn't come here to exchange names!
I have questions to ask,
so answer me honestly.
I hear it's been six months.
You have a family, too.
What on earth were you thinking...
Happy birthday to you!
Our lovely manager!
You seriously celebrated his birthday?
I didn't sing. I just clapped.
Jeez.
I'm sorry.
My hand went up before I knew it.
You're so pathetic.
So you celebrated his birthday
and just left?
So you did. What else did you do?
Look here and smile! Kimchi!
Mr. Guest, please smile. Kimchi!
You crazy bastard!
What? Have you lost your mind?
Hey, you deserve to be cursed.
Why don't you frame that picture
and hang it up in your living room?
It'll be a great memory for you.
Whatever you're thinking,
don't do it. Just don't.
Just do what I tell you to do.
Go back to him. And as soon as
you see him, give him a punch. Okay?
What? Is this how you'd punch him?
- Huh?
- Yes.
You can't learn to fight from books.
You'll crack your wrist this way.
Hold it like this.
Hold it like this and punch him.
What is this, a funny joke with a punch?
What if he attacks back at you?
Like this, here?
- Like this?
- Yes!
It happens a lot.
You punch him this way, then like this!
It doesn't hurt,
so I'll take control this way. Then...
And here comes another one.
- I have a free hand.
- Really?
Then would I stay still? Here, here!
Here it comes!
If I take the two hands like this,
you can't do anything anymore.
Then I can do this, and attack this way.
I'd pretend to hit here,
but actually hit here.
- Are you done?
- That's right.
Then I'd go like this.
You seem strong, but if I go this way...
Then I'd go this way.
Then I'd hit this way and also here too.
What will you do if I hit you here?
Stay right there.
If you take revenge on the man,
your wife may despise you.
What you have to do is face your wife,
not take revenge.
Revenge is for cowards.
What? Cowards?
It's about being upset,
not being a coward, ----
Here is Buddha. Tuna Mayo, you should
get the Nobel Peace Prize.
Tuna Mayo, stop trying to get attention
and get out of here.
You must be a woman, taking her side.
You wouldn't say that if you were a man.
Tuna Mayo, are you a woman?
Wow, this is a hit.
A coward? Sure, a married woman who has
an affair is brave, according to you.
You're the brave one
for having gone to him.
Don't ever hide yourself.
Da Hee, I'm going out. Your meal is
in front of the door. Eat it!
Didn't you learn about,
"What goes around comes around"?
Isn't it natural for them to be punished
since they did wrong?
Why do you always say to hold back
and be patient?
Reflect on yourself instead of taking
revenge. Think about what you did wrong!
Why reflect when he did nothing wrong?
You should reflect on yourself!
Another man just like him! If you have
time for this, take care of your wife!
Your husband doesn't even
look at you at night, right?
That's why you're taking it out here!
If I were your wife, I couldn't live
with you even for a moment!
Hey, where are you?
Would you come if you knew where I was?
Sure, I'll go! I'll go!
Hello, Yoon Woo's mom.
This is Joon Soo's mom.
I was just wondering if Joon Soo could
enter the art class that Yoon Woo is in.
I think registration
for the class is over.
Oh, I see.
It's only four kids per class. So moms
registered together for the class.
Why? Does Joon Soo want to go, too?
Is there any way?
I hear the owner is an acquaintance
of Seo Ra's mom...
If you came out often and became friends
with Seo Ra's mom, it'd be easier.
I'm sorry.
I'll try asking Seo Ra's mom.
It may not work,
so don't get your hopes up.
Thank you! Yes, thank you!
The director is looking for you.
How is it going
with the J Motors Project?
It's going well.
Team Leader Jung, you have a kid...
I'm wondering if it's too burdensome
for you to carry such a big project.
- I'm fine.
- Actually...
J Motors asked me to change the one
in charge of the project.
I know you've worked hard on it so far.
It's hard to ignore
a big client's request of us.
I see.
Manager Ji said that the big frames
of the project have been all set.
He said it would be okay
to give the rest to the staff.
Yes. Yes, I will.
Okay. Make sure to hand over the rest.
Yes.
There is no evidence, but you think
your wife is cheating on you?
Yes. I definitely think
she's seeing someone.
But there is nothing.
My wife's phone is under my name
so I retrieved the call record and
text messages, but they're clean.
Did she erase all of them
knowing that I'd look at them?
Even recently--
Isn't he delusional?
She must've done something.
He wouldn't be delusional for no reason.
There is no evidence
that she did anything to deserve it.
Exactly! The client admits it himself.
There is no cellphone
under the wife's name.
There is no home phone.
The wife doesn't know how to use a
computer, so she can't even send email.
Would she tie her message on a pigeon's
leg to communicate with a man?
Making impossible things possible is
what's exciting about an affair.
It's like narcotics.
What's so exciting about it?
If you think about the husband's
situation, how can you say that?
Stop talking nonsense
and just wrap up the whole plan.
For the main plot,
why don't we go with the feel
of the real situation
like we did yesterday?
Why don't we start with an interview
of dangerous wives as an intro?
Also to show what's going on these days.
The thinking of the women these days
has definitely changed a lot.
Even if you find women like that,
would it be easy to interview them?
I learned from the rookie that there are
a lot of apps that help with affairs.
- We'll use those.
- Hey, most are free for women.
You mean, men have to pay? Why?
It's unfair! At least they should manage
the quality of women then. Right?
What a classy comment.
Producer Ahn, what's your date of birth?
May 8, '83.
Wait, are you using mine?
Don't do it!
Do it with his.
Me?
So that we can do research!
For him to join the group, his age...
Of course you'd be very popular.
It'll be better to have a man who looks
more familiar and has a more real feel.
- Producer Do.
- What?
Kimchi!
Kimchi.
[Congratulations on Joining!
Mr. Do Hyun Woo]
- Brother-in-law.
- Yes.
You must be going somewhere.
Because of the program, they keep
asking me to come and go.
They seem to rely on me too much.
Someone's supposed to be coming today.
- Who?
- Ah Ra.
Why?
She said she'd register for flower
arrangement class near here.
- Flower arrangement class?
- Yes.
- Why?
- To go there on weekends.
Since you're also
going to work on weekends
she thought it'd be good
to go home together.
- She could come to this office, too.
- Of course! Since it's so close!
You said you were going out
for the program.
It's not good that they're
relying on me too much.
I'm going to show them some tough love.
Bye.
Wow, I have a feeling.
She's using the flower arrangements as
an excuse to keep an eye on me.
I'm someone who can be locked in.
There is no joy.
I'm sorry, I didn't know I had a visitor.
Please have a seat here.
Everyone who comes here
for the first time feels that way.
They've had a lot of thoughts,
and been hesitant...
It's fine. Please come this way.
You're very cold.
You're really cold.
Do you have poor circulation?
Can it be this cold?
By the way, the aura is...
Oh my!
How...
You're so pretty.
What the hell was that?
I haven't seen a woman for too long
and now I'm getting withdrawal symptoms.
How could I flirt with a ghost?
I'm the leader of this program.
Should I sacrifice myself and go there?
They told me I was too young.
If you'll do this once,
we'll plan the rest better.
Oh, the woman who requested
the meeting is young.
Wow, she's also pretty.
You should just have an affair, too.
Think about it.
- Hey, don't you need to test this?
- Yes, we'll test it.
- Does it work?
- Yes.
Okay, then.
Producer Do looks good
with glasses, right?
Ha! He looks like ----
I'm sorry.
Honey, here!
You look just like the picture.
Your picture is a little...
That's when I was young. I was pretty
when I was young, wasn't I?
If you look closely,
I still have that face.
Come here. Here!
Come here. I can't hear very well.
By the way, is it okay
to be in such a bright place?
It's hard to see,
so why would we meet at a dark place?
Besides, have we done anything wrong?
Am I wrong?
What will you do
if you get caught by your husband?
If you're worried about that,
you can't have an affair.
And who knows? My husband may be meeting
with another woman somewhere.
You must meet people often this way.
At first, I was curious
and wanted to talk.
Your family doesn't know
that you're doing this?
How would they know?
What about you?
Isn't it the same for you as well?
- What?
- Who knows?
I heard there are cases
where people go out unknowingly #
and end up saying, "Oh, Honey!"
Excuse me, my butt...
I know you like it.
We don't need to be pretentious.
Wow, you must work out.
Your butt is firm.
- Seriously!
- Should we get on with it?
Huh?
Evacuate! Evacuate!
Is that your name, Evacuate?
Hey, hurry up and evacuate!
Seriously.
I've seen your flower arrangements
at home.
Aren't you already at a professional
level without taking lessons?
I only have a few little tricks.
I'd like to learn properly.
The teacher here is famous
in the flower art world.
Why do you have to come so far...
Why are you doing this?
You don't object
to whatever I want to learn.
But you're against flower arrangement.
Do you have any other reason for it?
- It's suffocating.
- Excuse me?
Recently, I've become allergic
to flower pollen...
Since you like flowers, I didn't tell
you because I didn't want to upset you.
My coughing...
- Should we go to the hospital?
- No no no.
No no. It's not that. I think it'll
be okay if I stay far away.
Mrs. Eun Ah Ra?
- Hello.
- I'm the instructor, Moon Sun Hee.
I'm Eun Ah Ra.
Have you taken flower arrangement
lessons before?
Is that a trap or a reward?
In the net that my wife cast,
there is a mermaid.
Since I've already been caught,
I should relax and stay in.
You must be working out.
Your butt is so firm.
Evacuate! Evacuate, evacuate!
Is that your name, Evacuate?
You idiots, I said evacuate!
Turn it off.
We can't use this, can we?
We should cut out
the beginning and use it.
You went there for work, so you should
stay calm and work...
That lady is awful,
touching your butt and all.
Now you have the video,
so you can ask her and air it, right?
I'm heading out.
By the way...
The last client and this client as well.
The wives had affairs, but the husbands
look pitiful and small.
Let's not blame the husband
on our show.
Those women didn't have affairs
because of their husbands.
They just like the fact that the men
they're with are not their husbands.
Let's not make the innocent husbands
sinners, okay?
I'm really leaving now.
- Thank you for your work.
- Bye now.
But... I like this video
because it's so raw.
Let's do this one more time.
I'll do it this time.
- Will you be okay?
- What do you mean?
Doesn't your wife get upset?
Why would she be upset? It's work!
You didn't say anything
when Hyun Woo did it.
So why do you say this
when I'm about to do it?
You should at least call her
and ask her.
Forget it. If it's necessary, I'll look
her in the eye and talk to her directly.
Why would I tell her on the phone...
Hey, you!
Make sure to pick the right woman!
If someone like that last one comes,
you'll be in big trouble!
What is this, a blind date?
A blind date is something
you did yesterday, Writer Kwon.
- Hello.
I'm the husband of Eun Ah Ra
who registered this morning.
I see. What brings you here?
I'd like to learn flower arrangement.
- For yourself?
- Yes.
To be honest...
My wife's birthday
is coming up in a few days.
She loves flowers so much.
I think she'll like it
if I give her something I made.
You're very kind.
Oh, by the way, you can't tell my wife.
It's a surprise.
Oh wait. Mrs. Eun Ah Ra said you are
allergic to flower pollen.
- I'm find around pretty flowers.
- Pardon?
I mean, I have to overcome it with love.
You're admirable.
That's too much.
You're working really late.
Your husband must be waiting for you.
Aren't you going home?
I'm divorced.
Oh, divorced...
I'm glad you bounced back.
- Excuse me?
- It's nothing.
- I'll see you for lessons.
- Yes, have a good night.
What's this?
Hello! You must be heading home.
You have a sticker on.
Did you not register the car?
What? It's been fine until now.
I'm glad I happened to pass by.
Hold on a minute.
Sorry to make you wait.
Pour hot water like this.
Goodness, it's really clean.
How can I thank you for this?
You're welcome. I will register the car
for you. This won't happen again.
- Well, then.
- Okay, thank you.
You're home.
Honey!
I made your favorite gochujang stew.
Let's eat!
It looks delicious! Hurry up!
I must be losing it.
It hasn't been that long.
Mom, do I get to go
to the art academy now?
I'm looking into it.
Joon Soo, why do you want
to go to the art class?
I just like it.
If you don't get to go
to the art class...
Never mind.
I will make sure to get you in.
Mom, if it's too hard for you,
I don't need to go to the art class.
Huh?
Dad told me not to make things
difficult for you.
- Dad said that?
- Yes, he did.
He said that I'd be in trouble
if I make things difficult for you.
He said that he and I
have to protect you.
Soo Yeon.
- Yes?
- Are you asleep?
No, Mother.
Do you want to have a cup of tea?
Yes.
I thought about taking some side dishes
and soup to your place.
But I wanted him to starve a little,
so I didn't.
Even if you live with him again
it doesn't become something
that didn't happen.
It won't be covered even if you
try to cover it.
In the end, it's what you decide.
What life you decide to live...
I should just watch a movie.
What's this?
Manager! Happy birthday to you!
Wow, she's making me an idiot
to the very end.
Until the very end!
Eun Jeong, are you sure
you picked the right woman?
I looked her up with her ID.
She looks the same as this picture.
Wow, why does she go around doing that
with this face?
Be careful not to drop this mic.
Am I an amateur?
Hey, the glasses...
Can we get better frames?
I don't think we can
use much of Producer Do's
so you have to do well today.
I'm a good-looking man close up, right?
Yes, you look just like
one of those guys.
Mi Ha. What do you think?
----
Good job.
When did it start?
Six months ago.
Did you sleep with him?
I'm asking if you slept with him!
Yes, I slept with him.
I missed him. I've wanted
to see him the whole time.
So I asked him to see me first.
Really...
Hello, is this the locksmith?
I'm calling from
the flower arrangement place.
I'm calling you because
the key pad doesn't work.
It's been taken care of. Yes, yes.
Sorry, "It's been taken care of"?
The key pad is not working.
It's been taken care of.
Usually...
this happens a lot
when the battery is out.
For a quick trick. Now press it.
Goodness.
It works fine, right?
If you buy the battery,
I'll change it for you later.
Thank you. You've helped me again.
If you're really thankful, later--
Yes, I will give you
a delicious cup of tea.
Forget the tea.
I'll just ask for extra attention for
my flower arrangement lesson later.
Sure.
Let's hit him. I'll hit him.
Hit him. Hit him.
Let's hit him. Hit him, Do Hyun Woo.
It would've been better
if you led it to the end.
I feel like I'm getting credit for the
work that's already been done.
Not at all.
I'd feel better if you'd do it.
I'll wrap it up
and hand it over to you today.
I'll also go to J Motors
and tell them about the handover.
Joon Soo's Mom, I spoke to the owner,
and Joon Soo's in!
I knew it! Seo Ra's mom is the best!
It looks like Joon Soo's mom should treat
Seo Ra's mom! LOL.
Let's talk later.
Of course I should. Thank you!
I asked for a difficult favor.
You're welcome.
Also, I don't think it's necessary
to pick up the kids for all of us.
Would it be better to take turns
and pick them up?
How would we decide the order?
That sounds like work, too.
True. It's tough to think about
picking up the kids without a car.
I'll do it.
Is that okay?
Joon Soo's Mom, do you have a car?
I can borrow a company car.
Ouch.
Is it going well?
I was going to make a gift for my wife
without any help...
It's a bit odd.
It looks like nothing, doesn't it?
It looks good.
I really hope that my wife
also thinks that way.
Your wife must be happy.
You must love your wife a lot.
Of course I do.
My wife is... like a gift in my life.
In my life, I've never
had butterflies in my stomach
for another woman but my wife.
I'm an idiot.
I look like an idiot, don't I?
Ouch!
Let me see!
Thank you.
Do you know what kind of men
women are most attracted to?
I should get going now.
It's late.
Excuse me.
It's a man that can be stolen away.
One, two, three!
Don't fall for her. Ask her!
- I got it.
- Excuse me?
I knew that you'd be beautiful.
Oh, I see. Thank you.
What?
Since I started meeting people this way
I think it's the first time I hear
a comment like, "You're beautiful."
Then what kind of comments do you hear?
It's direct. Since the goal is clear...
"Let's go to a hotel." Or sometimes
we talk about each
other's family as if it's no big deal.
It must be your first time, since
you're asking lots of questions.
What?
There aren't too many people
who come out here
because they have a problem
in their marriage.
Aren't you the same way?
Do you have an issue with your wife?
Say something.
My wife ran away.
Three days after we came back
from our honeymoon.
Joon Young, you went too far.
If she was going to leave
after three days
she'd have broken it off
before the wedding!
What is Producer Ahn thinking?
Team Leader, please check the website.
I loaded the design for the shopping bag.
Okay, I will.
- Ye Rim.
- Yes, Team Leader.
The design is a bit different.
We decided not to highlight the BI.
Didn't we decide to go with a robotype
rather than than the watermark?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'll fix it.
What about you, Eun Ok?
What's going on with you?
I uploaded it.
Eun Ok, there is nothing that's developed
from the idea sketch.
It should've been refined
following the plan!
- I'm sorry.
- Upload it again after refining it.
Team Leader.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I got upset earlier.
I think I've been a bit sensitive
with the handover these days.
I'm sorry.
It happened because I was rushing.
I thought I had to get a confirmation
from you before you left work.
Once you leave for home, I have to get
the updates from you over the phone.
But there is a limit to what
you can do over the phone.
I'll do better!
Oh, Honey.
What brings you here?
I had tea with the flower arrangement
members and stopped by.
By the way, did Do Yeon go somewhere?
Oh, yes.
She must've gone to Hyun Woo's office.
It looks like she likes the assistant
producer at Hyun Woo's office.
- Really?
- Yes.
She didn't mention anything like that.
Did you change your cologne?
I use the same old cologne.
You do? But...
It smells like roses.
I had a client earlier
who had a rose perfume on.
Is that the smell?
Let's go out and eat! Let's go!
Let's go.
My stomach feels full. I'm sorry.
No need to be sorry.
Are you heading home?
I'm going to stop by at the flower
arrangement place.
I have something to discuss
with the teacher.
Bye. Be careful going home.
She's like a ghost.
You'd like to register
for additional classes?
I registered for the weekend class
but I want to register
for the weekday classes, too.
I already thought you were more skilled
than the other members.
Please wait. I'll bring the papers.
I came to tell you that Han Young Joo
will lead the project from now on.
Yes.
It would've been better
if you told me ahead of time.
I thought it would be right
to go through the company.
I thought it would be better...
not to contact you personally.
I see.
I didn't think it through.
Your husband came to see me at work.
He seems like a good guy.
I regret that this project
turned out this way.
But I thought it wouldn't be good
for each other and for the project.
Why?
Since I started meeting people this way
I think this is the first time hearing
a comment like, "You're beautiful."
Oh, then what kind of comments...
It's direct. The goal is clear.
I was really good
at making her talk, wasn't I?
It's as if we cast her for the role.
She speaks well, detailed and eloquent.
You did well.
Your far-out story
earned a pity point, for sure.
My story?
The scenario that your wife
left three days after your honeymoon.
Did I go too far with that? Why?
Doesn't it sound like it could happen?
For the wife to run away three days
after the honeymoon...
the man must've known that her heart
had left before that.
But they were pushed to get married
and even went on a honeymoon?
Either the man is an idiot
or he loved his wife a lot.
She must've believed you
because you said it with that face.
Why? It's because I look
like a romantic guy?
How is that possible? You're an idiot.
Producer Do has some issue, right?
What issue?
Something like maybe
his wife is having an affair...
How can you say that?
That's not true.
Producer Ahn, do you know your pinky
opens up when you lie?
Do I really do that?
So I'm right about the affair.
See? You're an idiot.
Don't let him know. If he found out that
you knew, he wouldn't come to work.
- Let's go.
- Where?
- Let's just go.
Let's go out and talk.
Just come out when I tell you to!
Yes.
What about Joon Soo?
Mother said she'd take him today.
I... went to his office today.
It was really fancy.
I heard.
What?
So you already heard it from him?
You must be still getting along.
I saw him because of work.
You're still working with him
after that ruckus?
Are you even considering
ending it with him?
It's already over, and I have no reason
to see him anymore.
Of course you shouldn't see him!
If you still see him, how can you call
yourself a human being?
Please.
Can we solve our problem between us?
It's "us" only in cases like this.
Did you care about me
when you had an affair with him?
He's walking around smiling!
I'm telling you
that he's walking around smiling.
He gets hellos from security guards and
walks around with a coffee, all relaxed.
I've been torn to pieces,
but nothing changed for him!
Why does it have to happen only to me?
Honey.
You did whatever you wanted.
I'll do whatever I want.
So don't tell me what to do.
Do you understand?
[Michael Lee
accepted your friend request.]
What's this?
[Another happy day!]
What's with this bastard?
[Ji Sun Woo]
This bastard is smiling.
[My treasures]
Has he lost his mind?
He's a real psychopath!
For a guy who loves his kids this much...
After what he's done...
Who is this?
Is that his wife?
I'm jealous, Manager.
You're my role model.
This crazy bastard!
I was curious.
About his surroundings, his car
his house that have not
been affected by this ruckus.
And his wife.
You came home really early today.
I'm early because I missed you!
I was hoping that his wife would
have the same expression I do.
- What did you do?
- I cooked a lot of things you like!
Really? I should eat a lot.
I want to take everything away from him,
and make him miserable.
Just like me.
No, a hundred times worse than me.
I don't love you. There is no reason--
Oh, you left me.
I'm all alone, I'm all alone.
Seriously!
Really!
I really couldn't stand it.
I was so angry, so I came to see you.
Yes, I understand.
Let me check one thing.
Is it true that you started
seeing her six months ago?
Yes.
How far...
No, I didn't mean where...
Once. That's all there was.
- I'm sorry.
- "I'm sorry"?
Is it all okay if you say, "I'm sorry,"
you son of a bitch?
You two are the ones who did wrong,
so why do I have to suffer so much?
And why are you so relaxed?
What did you do right?
Have I gone mad?
Am I the only ---- here?
And what about your wife?
Why didn't you tell your wife?
It's all my fault. Soo Yeon was--
"Soo Yeon"? "Soo Yeon"?
We tried to protect the family. I also--
But it's been broken!
In your eyes, is this protection?
Call her.
Call your wife
who is blissfully ignorant.
I'm not trying to act logical right now.
If you don't want me to go wake up your
kids in bed and make a scene, call her!
Honey, it's me.
This is...
No, it's not mine.
Hello?
This is Do Hyun Woo.
Your husband had an affair with my wife.
You should hear the rest
directly from your husband.
Tell her. Tell her!
Honey, it's me.
What he said is true.
Honey.
Everyone, I finally got my revenge.
I beat up that bastard who had an affair
and told his wife everything.
I felt relieved.
- What a relief!
- Refreshing!
I feel like my indigestion
has been cured.
I want to send Toycrane 1,000 balloons.
Hey.
Me?
Come here.
Is this a "smaphone"?
- Oh, you mean, smartphone?
- Yes, smaphone.
Go into the stock gallery.
Why?
The big sisters here have something
to look at for a minute.
I'm in.
It's up! It's up!
What does it say?
- He hit the man who had an affair!
- What else?
And he told his wife!
Oh my!
I thought he was a fool,
but he did what he had to do!
Give it back now!
How much does this thing cost?
If it's not a good one, it'll be about
200,000 or 300,000 won.
Thank you, young man.
If we had one, we'd find out everything
without going to the post office.
Where do we have money to buy that?
Let's go inside!
You've caused big trouble.
Your wife won't just ignore it.
Dad!
Hi. Have you been doing well?
Well... so so.
"So so"?
Don't you miss me?
Of course I miss you.
Don't you miss Mom, Dad?
Yeah.
Go to bed.
Mom, it's Dad!
Joon Soo, you should go to the bathroom
and go to bed now!
Dad, good night! I'm going to the
bathroom then to bed.
Okay. Sure.
Good night.
Sister-in-law, can you go to Hyun Woo's
office and bring me the script?
No, I can't.
You can't?
I believe Producer Lee is alone.
You should go hear about the show...
We will arrange flowers in an Asian style
using the needle point holder.
Put the first main one about 15 to 20
degrees slanted from the center.
Then proceed with your flower arrangement
as I instructed.
Yes.
Honey, you came.
Weren't you supposed to be doing
flower arrangement now?
Yes.
You must've missed me so you came here!
Now I saw you, so I'll leave.
All right.
Come any time you want to see me.
It's been a while
since you worked outside.
Working outside these days means--
I worked outside a lot
until 10 years ago.
"A lot"? You didn't even make manager.
You got laid off and stayed at home.
Yes, I stayed at home and cooked for you.
I did a lot to take care of you.
Cut!
Is this the reward for working
so hard at home?
To see my wife having an affair?
How can you say I had an affair?
You're seeing another man
behind my back--
I tried to convince the client,
but he wants the blurry screen.
Of course he would.
It's nothing to brag about.
- It's really exactly what you said.
- What do you mean?
The wife is definitely the aggressor
and the husband is the victim.
But he looks more intimidated somehow.
Come to think of it, there really aren't
any clear aggressor or victim.
You know, "gross negligence."
They know that the marriage would be
put to danger at this rate.
But they don't make an effort.
There are a lot of couples like that.
Hey hey, add that interview.
Yes.
Gross negligence...
I really wanted to do this
when I found someone I love.
Thank you.
For giving me the opportunity.
Here you go.
Here.
I'm back.
Good job.
Was there any request for adjustments?
No.
You haven't had lunch yet, have you?
Manager Ji Sun Woo bought me lunch,
so I ate.
That must be nice.
Manager Ji is such a good-looking guy.
By the way,
Manager Ji had a cut on his face.
He said he fell after having a drink,
but it looked like he got beat up.
Really?
Come to think of it, there isn't any
clear aggressor or a victim.
You know, "gross negligence"?
They know that the marriage would be
put in danger at this rate.
But they don't make an effort.
There are a lot of couples like that.
What kind of effort do I need to make?
And why do I have to be the only one
making an effort?
Joon Soo's at Mother's house.
Did you see him?
What did you do to him?
You seem to know everything,
so why do you ask?
Did you really do that?
Yes, I did. Why?
Why? Did he come to you and tell on me?
So what? Did you console him?
I found out about it by chance.
Honey...
Let's not make this a bigger issue.
It's our problem.
I wouldn't have known
without that incident!
You two made this happen! It's you two!
Seriously...
I guess you only heard
that he got beat up.
I also told his wife about it.
What?
Honey.
Honey, that's separate
from our problem--
How is that separate?
You and her husband had an affair.
I'm mad at you, I'm mad at that bastard.
I'm even mad at the bastard's wife
who didn't know anything.
What did I do so wrong?
This is how I am now, so am I supposed
to consider their situation?
I'm sure she's thankful now.
Without me, she wouldn't have known
for the rest of her life
how her husband cheated on her.
So... do you feel relieved?
Yes, I feel relieved! Why?
Okay. I understand
that it's tough on you.
This is really...
Hey. If you feel that bad for him...
Take this to him and comfort him.
You bought it
for his birthday anyway, right?
Who knows?
Both families are broken up now.
So he might ask you to run away
and live with him.
Why? You don't have courage to run away
and live with him somewhere else?
You don't have such courage but
you slept with that bastard?
I didn't buy this to give it to him.
It's a gift for you.
A gift? A gift for me?
A woman who spent
our wedding anniversary
as if nothing happened
bought a gift for me?
You expect me to believe that?
Just how far
are you going to deceive me?
Please! Stop pretending to be a victim!
I'm the one who got destroyed.
I'm the one who feels like he's dying!
I'm the victim, you're the aggressor!
Yes, I am the aggressor.
Hey, if I really lose it,
I don't know what I'll do.
I'll go to his office
and tell everyone everything!
I'm going to leave Mother's house.
I'll tell Mother everything.
Every time I face her, it's hell.
Have you lost your mind?
Hey. Hey!
Hey!
Have you lost your mind?
You're going to tell Mom?
Do you want to see my mom faint?
Don't you know what kind
of life she's led?
Tuna Mayo, you were right.
My wife is acting like she's blaming me.
I'm going crazy.
This week...
[D H W]
My wife's counterattack started.
bioskopkeren.ORG
Do you really have to do this? Where are
you going? Do you have any place to go?
I'll leave.
You were going to separate,
but why would you leave home?
Isn't that Producer Ahn's wife?
She works here?
My wife has short hair.
Her hair grew long.
Wake up, okay?
You didn't sleep with her or touch her
but isn't that a step before
having an affair?
Mrs. Jung Soo Yeon? I was curious
about the woman my husband was seeing.
I'd like to talk to my wife
one more time tonight.
I'm going to ask her honestly
about why she did it.
Why would you leave home?
It's not him.
I'm sorry, Mother.