Subtitles by DramaFever
[My Wife is Having an Affair This Week]
[Episode 6]
Jung Soo Yeon.
You're going to do this?
Mom!
Dad!
We're here.
Mom, you came?
Grandma bought me this.
You're so lucky.
What did you do
that she wants to separate with you?
How did you know that?
Mother.
I thought you two were
thinking things out while living apart.
I will never allow
the two of you to separate.
What about Joon Soo?
I don't care if you kill each other,
but do it while living together.
He's my son, but he
deserves what he gets.
- Mother, I have something to tell you...
- Be quiet.
Go, it's our problem.
We'll take care of it.
- Come on, get up.
- I have my reasons.
I'm doing this because you
can't resolve this alone.
Come on, Mom.
Fine.
Marriage isn't something
you can easily undo.
It's easy to separate, but once
you do it, it'll be hard to undo.
Think about it carefully.
You really have to do this?
I'm sorry.
If we stay together, it will
just hurt our feelings more.
Where are you going?
You have somewhere to go?
Oh, you gave up on being a wife, so
you won't be a mother, either, now?
I'll take Joon Soo with me.
What?
Hey.
Stay, I'll leave.
Don't get the wrong idea.
This is because of Joon Soo.
- It's okay.
- It's okay?
Just stay.
Don't do this to Joon Soo.
Where are you going to take
that sleeping child?
What's wrong with you?
You were that hungry?
- Take your jacket off.
- Should I?
Okay.
What is that flower petal?
I wanted to do this when
I met a person I really love.
Oh...
I was at a wedding, I guess it
got on me there, it's nothing.
It's on your neck, too.
What?
It's inside your shirt, too.
Oh...
This kid...
He asked me to move the flowers,
so I helped him.
They must have gotten on me then.
Darn petals...
Honey, can I get more rice?
I'm so hungry.
My wife is demanding
that we separate now.
She got mad that I told the
cheater's husband the truth.
She's more concerned about him than me.
Does my wife really
want to end things with me?
You scared me.
It's you again?
You don't go home?
What?
This is your spot?
Your first time sleeping at the office?
Yeah.
Follow me.
You can sleep here.
You should put four chairs together...
No, you're a head taller...
Do as you want, five or six...
Let's see if we have it...
You're in luck today, Producer Do.
Take good care of this.
If you lose it, you'll have to
sleep covered in newspapers.
- Follow me.
- Thank you.
- Separating?
- Yeah.
They're living apart
without getting a divorce.
- How is that different from a divorce?
- She'll continue to meet him?
She can't bring up the divorce,
so that's why she's doing this.
- He's more important than you?
- You should go beat him up.
Game over.
What's your size?
If you tell me,
I'll get your coffin ready.
Come to Han River.
That bastard always tells
you to come, but he's still alive.
She dumped you? LOL
How can they be so insensitive?
Your lives aren't much better, jerks.
It's so cold.
Thanks.
That's water to wash your face.
There's no hot water,
just wash the important parts.
Is she really a woman?
This will control the grease.
Nobody will be able to tell.
One wet tissue is enough
for one day, right?
What's this?
Damn.
So depressing.
Why does this place
feel like a homeless shelter?
You said you're separating,
but why did you leave?
How did you know we are separating?
You wrote it all over the internet.
I told her I would leave.
What can I do when she
says she'll leave with Joon Soo?
Yeah, Joon Soo is the victim here.
Then where are you going
to stay from now on?
I'll have to come to the office,
or go to a spa or a motel.
Are you a runaway teen?
If you run into people,
what will they think?
Stop acting pitiful, and come to my...
- No, you can't come to my house...
- I won't go there, don't worry.
I wouldn't dare go there,
and deal with your wife.
Yeah...
What are you doing?
You're posting pictures of
food on your social media?
What do you think, Honey?
- He's pretty slick looking.
- Not bad.
You want to introduce him
to your sister?
Yeah, she should get married soon.
No, the flower arrangement instructor.
I don't think she's dating anyone.
Men like that type, no?
What do you think?
What man would like her?
I really don't like her.
Hey, what's up?
Ah Ra wants to know
what you're doing for lunch.
Tell her I'll take care of it.
Okay.
It's kind of thrilling
having someone watch over me.
It's kind of nice.
Wow.
Wait, the CD...
Is she kidding?
You should show her what's up.
Sue her!
Serves you right.
You rat your wife out, but you
can't even make ramen on your own.
Hey, you don't even say hi to me?
Kang Tae Oh!
If it's come this far, it may be
better to separate for the kid's sake.
They can't live like that.
They need to separate.
Excuse me, you can't do this here.
It's so dry here.
I have really sensitive skin.
You think this is your bedroom?
What the heck are you doing?
I'll take care of her,
you can go back to your business.
- You're not eating lunch?
- We don't need to eat...
Let's go eat.
Go where?
I packed something light for us to eat.
Granny, you can't do this here.
Leave.
Bye.
He's so rude.
You jerks, we're never going back there!
What do we do?
It was getting really fun.
Can we buy a smartphone?
We can view it at home then.
Where do we have the money?
Go ahead and sell the land then!
If I could sell it,
I would have sold it already.
What?
Bitch.
Then your wife packed up and left?
It's possible that
Toycrane got kicked out.
- No way.
- That would be ----.
You're giving all men
a bad name, you loser.
But I have a kid.
- Producer Do, you have the preview.
- Yeah.
- What are you looking at?
- It's nothing.
Let's go.
Okay.
- Time?
- 54 minutes 38 seconds.
- About a minute and a half too long.
- We're not done editing.
- Tell us what to cut.
- Okay.
We need to start the audio a little
earlier, it doesn't match the picture.
If you see something, tell us.
Okay.
You got fired before making it to
manager, and you're home now.
Yeah, I stayed home...
- Don't we need more captions?
- No, too much is not good.
Okay.
You must be working out,
your butt looks great.
Edit that out.
We're going to blur it out anyway.
I'm not talking about her face,
the whole scene.
Why?
This isn't bad.
No, I bet people will
make an issue out of it.
Get rid of all the
talking in the back, too.
It came out nice.
It'll be a hit, good job.
I'm glad you realize we worked hard.
Punk, what's wrong with you?
Writer Kwon, I know
you worked hard on this.
- You were living there.
- No...
That's her style, she even likes
watching movies in the office.
Are you allergic to your home,
or something?
This tea is very hot.
If you get it on your face,
you'll get a nice burn.
Hey, why are you so glum?
You're nervous about the first airing?
No.
- Pour it on him, it's okay.
- Really?
What?
Hello?
Is this Mr. Do Hyun Woo's cellphone?
Yes, it is.
I'm Mr. Ji Sun Woo's wife.
At lunch time?
Yeah, we haven't been
able to see each other.
I'll go by your office.
No, I'll go to you.
My baby must have missed me a lot.
You...
Yes, I'll get there on time.
You have a guest.
Tell her to come in.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
Have a seat.
I think my husband is having an affair.
That's great.
- What?
- I mean...
I'm glad you came.
It's advantageous to file for divorce
when your husband is being unfaithful.
Should we start the consultation?
Do you have any proof?
He did have a conversation
with her on social media.
Social media...
Can you show me?
This.
I'll go next to you.
Social media...
- You're so cool, Director.
- Thanks, Sun Young.
Looking at this as a professional...
- Their relationship is very serious.
- Pardon?
I just requested to be your friend.
What perfume do you use?
I'm not wearing any today.
Oh, then it must be your natural scent.
Doesn't Producer Do seem
very busy these days?
Did his situation change?
It did change, he left home
and he's separated from his wife.
That's only possible because it's him.
If it were you, you would
have kicked your wife out.
And gotten both sets of parents
together to cause a scene.
Stop right there.
How can you be so sure of that?
I've never treated you badly.
- If anything, I took care of you.
- And how is that?
When everyone was going out to
see cherry blossoms, you got all lonely
and asked me to go eat
dinner with you, so I did...
I didn't ask you to dinner
because of the cherry blossoms.
They just happened to
be blossoming then.
- Same thing.
- No.
Then what about the karaoke bar?
You asked me to go to the karaoke
bar after dinner, so I went with you.
- You don't remember that?
- You wanted to go drink.
If we drink, I would have to
stay several hours with you.
But if we go to a karaoke bar,
we can go home after an hour.
Maybe you were the one feeling
lonely because of the cherry blossoms.
Why would I?
I have a wife.
Yeah, why are you looking at me
to take care of you then?
No, I'm the one who took care of you.
I thought of you alone in the office
while everyone was out
enjoying the flowers.
I felt so bad for you.
Do you know who you
should really feel bad for?
Your wife.
- I'm about to tear up.
- You have to get the last word in?
- What?
- Isn't that your wife?
Your wife works here?
No, my wife has short hair.
She had long hair?
You don't know?
I mean, it's long.
I'm sorry for calling you
out of the blue.
No, it's okay.
- It's my husband's fault...
- My wife is at fault, too.
Let's skip the apologies.
Okay.
I was grateful that you told me.
Otherwise, I would never have found out.
He was such a perfect
father and husband.
My wife was a perfect
mother and wife, too.
Before she met your husband.
That's not what I meant.
But this was an opportunity for us to
think deeply about our relationship.
We were so busy raising two kids
we never had time to think
about our relationship.
I thought about why he had that affair.
Why is that important?
The fact that he cheated
is what's important.
What he did is excusable?
You're not mad that he
did this to you behind your back?
- You're not mad?
- Yes, I was mad, too.
No matter how much he apologized,
I couldn't forgive him.
But when I realized that I don't
want to break up with him
I could forgive him.
Rather than getting up the
courage to break up with him
I want to gather the courage
to understand and forgive him.
Then what about you?
Yeah, we won't make a rash
and emotional decision, either.
I'm glad.
Then I'll get going.
Okay.
It's a little expensive here,
are you okay with that?
Yes, you got Joon Soo into the art
class, and you've been so helpful.
- The space just became available.
- Yeah.
- It's okay to leave during work hours?
- It's my lunch hour.
- It's okay.
- Look how much weight you've lost.
I'm so jealous, I keep
getting fatter and fatter.
You shouldn't be jealous.
That's because she's working so hard.
Isn't Joon Soo's dad a producer?
You don't need to make money, no?
- Well...
- I'm jealous, too.
She gets to leave the house,
and check out other guys.
But can you ask that camera man
to come back?
- What?
- The one that came to our field day...
- Yeah...
- Your husband sent him.
- I think he was a video jockey.
- Yeah.
I hope he can come to
our next school event.
I was looking at the video from the
field day, and it looks so professional.
Yeah.
If he can't come, it's okay.
No, I'll ask my husband.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That would be great.
Then can I get tickets to go see
the filming of "Hidden Singer?"
Me, too.
Okay, I'll find out.
Thank you.
Soo Yeon, did you finish the
work for Digital Site?
I'll do it right now.
Captain, I sent you Image Group's
project I've been working on...
- Sorry, I'll get to it now.
- Okay.
She's willing to forgive him
when he cheated on her.
He's got some skills, I got kicked out
by my wife who cheated on me.
Ah Ra, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But what brings you here again?
You can't get in contact with Yoon Ki?
I'm glad you're here.
This...
What's this?
I was packing his lunch,
and I brought some for everyone.
- Wow.
- Thank you.
- I thought I would die of hunger.
- People will think I'm starving you.
- Thanks.
- Open it up.
- Wow.
- It looks so good.
- Hey.
- Thank you.
- Is there enough?
- Don't worry about it.
Here, would you like to eat this, too?
I made it for Yoon Ki,
but he's not in the office.
Wow.
- This is awesome.
- Wow.
- Then I'll get going.
- What?
- Enjoy.
- Apples.
- She's leaving.
- Thank you!
Thanks!
I thought Attorney Choi married her for
her looks, but she's a good cook, too.
There must be something
about Attorney Choi.
Even that flower....
So that customer wanted
to return everything.
Yeah.
She had bought it over a month ago.
- But what are you doing?
- Huh?
I'm working, go on.
So I told her she can't do it.
And she threw a complete fit,
saying she's going to write a review.
She was saying I underestimated her.
- How terrible.
- Yeah, she was the worst.
Honey.
It was such a hard day today.
My baby...
My poor baby...
- I'm so sorry, Baby...
- I feel so bad for myself.
- I'll protect you now.
- Okay.
Hold me tight.
Almost done.
I hope it gets a lot of views.
- We need a high rating.
- Yeah.
What's this?
- You have a man?
- What are you saying?
He's the one I recently
contacted for our new case.
I met him at the interview, and
he's been calling me ever since.
He keeps saying he gets so mad...
I'm sure he's mad.
His wife cheated on him.
Yeah, I'm sure he's mad.
But I heard that he even
had a child outside the marriage.
He doesn't think about his wrongdoings.
Men are different from women.
It's male instinct to go breed.
Damn instinct...
You can't even control your
own instinctive urges?
If you can't control yourself,
you're no more than an animal.
you should go live in a zoo.
What's wrong with men?
- Then why did you get married?
- That's enough.
Because I was bad at math.
What?
I couldn't calculate beforehand whether
I would be able to live well with him.
Oh, I'm also bad at foreign language.
I couldn't understand
anything my husband was saying.
And I'm sure my language was
foreign to him, too.
Hey, don't assume that all
marriages are like that.
You can meet a man that doesn't require
any math or foreign language skills.
No, I don't want to get remarried.
I may be bad at math
and foreign language
but I'm good at recognizing
wrong answers.
I never get the same
problem wrong twice.
Since the two of you are very smart
you won't have to worry about
doing poorly on the exam like me.
You have to admit,
women forgive men who cheat.
So why is it that men
can't forgive women?
- Tell me, Producer Do.
- Stop that.
I'll take you home,
what's your unit number?
You can't come to my house.
- Then, I'll get going.
- Yeah, go.
- Bye!
- Okay, see you tomorrow.
- Hey, hey...
- She drank too much.
- Where...
- Hey, hey!
- You...
- Hey, hey.
- What are you doing?
- Look at her...
Holy--
- What's wrong with you?
- Producer Do.
Why did you take off your wedding band?
- What?
- Where's your ring?
- Well...
- If you take off your wedding band
you'll lose your wife.
What?
Do you know why you wear
your wedding band on this finger?
- Why?
- Do you know?
I won't tell you.
Hey!
Please get up.
I'm so embarrassed, get up!
Come on, get up!
Writer Kwon!
Oh my--
You keep scaring me.
I must be crazy.
I must really be crazy.
- This is insane.
- What are you doing?
Why are you taking your socks off?
- Hey...
- Wash it.
Why did she take her socks off?
Why are you taking these off?
Hey, come on.
Get up.
Seriously...
I'm going in.
Having an affair is perfect
when you're bored.
Damn...
What's wrong with me?
Your legs are so strong,
you should have been a soccer player.
Wait until tomorrow...
Wait until tomorrow.
Can I get a room?
You're alone?
Yes.
Then we can't give you a room.
What?
There are so many people
doing the bad deed these days.
- What do you mean?
- So you have a hard life.
Why come here and
make my life hard, too?
I'm not alone, she'll be here soon.
[Wifey]
What?
Did you finish work?
Yeah.
I'm sorry for saying this to you.
It's okay, what is it?
Tell me.
That VJ you sent to
Joon Soo's field day...
Do you think you can send him again?
What?
We're having an event
at Joon Soo's school.
Hey, that...
Forget it.
I'm busy.
Hang up.
She doesn't care about
how I'm doing at all?
Seriously...
Yeah, hurry and come.
Okay.
She's coming now.
Who is it?
- Is there anything you need?
- No.
Okay.
What's wrong with her?
Yes.
- Yes?
- Try this rice cake.
- It's from a grand opening...
- No, it's okay.
- I don't like rice cakes.
- You should try it.
- No, thank you.
- Rest then.
- Get in.
- Okay.
Thanks.
What's wrong with her?
- Yeah, what is it now?
- The toilet is working okay?
Somebody pooped a huge
thing like this yesterday...
Oh my goodness, is the TV working?
I'm not going to watch TV!
Why are you doing this?
Can you please just get out!
I'm just worried you'll
have other thoughts.
Just recently, right here...
What?
I'm sorry.
Sleep well.
What's wrong with this room?
Lady, lady!
Lady!
So...
Damn it.
Mother.
Yeah, you came?
I'm sorry.
You must be very busy.
You didn't eat yet, right?
- I had a lot of work to finish.
- It's okay.
The one with free time
should pick him up.
It's not hard picking up
my own grandson.
Joon Soo went to sleep
early right after dinner.
He was talking about all the
fun he had in gym class.
- Thank you, Mother.
- It's okay.
What about Hyun Soo?
He left.
He's not coming in?
He didn't do anything
right, why did he leave?
Jerk...
Hey, just tell him to
live on the streets.
How dare he?
He should be begging you.
No, Mother.
He's not the one at fault.
It's me.
I'm the one who had the affair.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Toycrane's wife is so lucky.
She's finally free!
- I bet he's at a spa or a motel.
- Not even.
I bet he's on a swing at the playground.
What are you doing?
What took you so long?
I was sleeping.
What are you doing here?
You said you would sleep at a motel.
I didn't feel like staying there.
- Let's drink more.
- We have work tomorrow.
- It's past two right now.
- Fine, punk.
Get in.
What are you going to do?
I'll just sleep here in the sand.
It's fine, I'll just get
some sand in my mouth.
- Hyun Soo...
- Hey, it's okay.
I can't go to your house like this,
your wife would hate me.
Go in.
I'll just hang out alone here.
Wow, I haven't been on a
swing in awhile, this is so fun.
It's like the Viking ride.
Why aren't you coming?
What?
What about your wife?
You told her?
She's not home.
What?
She went on a business trip?
You should have told
me sooner then, punk!
I thought I would freeze to death!
Your house is so nice.
It's simple, and so nice.
Wow, it's because you don't have a kid.
Hey, this is the first time I've come
to your house after you got married.
Thinking about it, you never
even had a housewarming.
I know.
Your house used to be
so dirty when you lived alone.
Your wife must be very clean.
- I'll go buy some beer.
- Yeah, let's just have one more drink.
Where's the bathroom?
By the entrance.
The house is so nice!
I should have told him
to buy a toothbrush.
But why is there only one toothbrush?
What's this?
She doesn't cook?
It looks like he lives all alone.
What are you doing?
- When did you come?
- Why are you so shocked?
Huh?
It looks like you live
alone here without your wife.
I told you, she's not home.
Huh?
- You told your wife?
- She's not home.
- Hyun Soo.
- Yeah?
I'm going to use the bathroom.
Go ahead.
This is your house.
Hey!
What?
Your wife left home?
Three days after you came back
from your honeymoon?
So you've been living alone
for three years like this?
Then when you said she's not home
you meant permanently?
I told you several times,
but you didn't catch on.
Why?
What the heck...
Why did she do that?
Did you ask her?
I was curious myself, so I
looked everywhere for her.
But when I found her, I didn't
see the point of asking her.
It's all over anyway.
She must have hated me,
she didn't even last a week.
Why didn't you tell me?
You should have told me.
I was embarrassed.
Everybody was asking me
how the honeymoon was.
I was too embarrassed to tell them
that my wife ran away.
That's why I acted like
I was still married.
And I missed the right timing.
It's fine, forget that woman.
Forget her, and start over.
You don't lack anything,
and you're still young.
You can meet a better woman,
and have a better life.
I don't know...
After that, I'm afraid to meet women.
I don't want to be humiliated anymore.
You and I have such bad luck with women.
You've never seen me drink before?
No, it's not the first time...
But you've never seen me
drink like this, right?
I drink better than your father-in-law.
I just didn't drink because I didn't
want people thinking I'm a bad mom.
Hyun Woo wants to divorce you
because you had the affair?
We didn't get to really talk, yet.
What about you?
You want to get divorced?
Woman can have affairs, too.
We are people, too.
Even if we just stay home cleaning,
cooking, and doing laundry...
we are still women.
It's only natural
that we get drawn to people
who treat us well
and make us feel loved.
But a mother shouldn't do that.
If your husband does something wrong,
you can kick him to the curb.
But Joon Soo didn't do anything wrong.
If it weren't for Hyun Woo
and Hyun Soo in the U.S.
I would have gotten
a divorce 40 years earlier.
Thinking about it now
it's because I stayed married that
I have two sons that take my side.
I was sick of marriage, too.
It stunk.
Even if we do get a divorce
I'm going to make the
best decision for Joon Soo.
I know.
I know what a good
mother you are to him.
When Joon Soo was an infant,
you must have run home from work.
It was the middle of winter,
but you were wet with sweat.
You were holding Joon Soo, and I saw
that your toes were bruised black.
If your mother had seen that,
she would have cried.
Mom.
My baby, you woke up?
Why did you wake up?
Where's Dad?
He will be home soon.
He will be home.
Hey, you're still better off than me.
I got stabbed in the back after
eight years of living together.
It's total betrayal.
I dated her for eight years, too.
Eight years of marriage, and six
years of dating is fourteen years.
That's not all.
I put everything online,
and made a fool of myself.
Even little kids think I'm a joke.
What about me then?
I didn't want to get caught
that I'm living alone
so I saved the package carrier's
phone number as my wife's number.
Every time I get a call
from him, I get surprised.
That's not all.
I talk to myself when I'm home.
Honey, I'll be back.
Honey, I'm home!
Do you know how pathetic I feel?
And every anniversary,
I buy a cake for myself.
And a greeting card and a present, too.
Hey, did your wife go cheat on you
the day after your anniversary?
At least you got to live with her.
Did you ever live alone like me?
Why did this happen to me?
I'm afraid to meet another woman.
What's this?
What's wrong with us?
What's wrong with your eyes?
Is it allergies?
Maybe.
Everyone's here early.
We have good feedback
for the preview we uploaded.
- We have so many likes.
- I have a good feeling about it.
Of course, we worked on it.
[Wifey]
This is yours, right?
Oh, you had this?
You didn't wash it?
Why was that at my house?
That's because I took
it off at your house.
So why is this at my house?
- Did you?
- Did I what?
Oh, nothing you were
hoping for happened...
I was hoping for what?
Why were you in my house?
And why did you take your socks off?
- Are you a pervert?
- Pervert?
Wow...
Excuse me, Writer Kwon.
You were drunk off your butt, and
you fell on the street and fell asleep.
Out of the kindness of my heart, I took
pity on you and brought you home.
And these smelly socks here...
While I was cleaning up all
the trash in front of your house
your garbage bag ripped,
and all the content fell on my feet.
That's why I took my
socks off for a little bit...
Seriously...
You don't recognize this
kimchi smell as your own?
Why did you throw out my garbage?
You are so annoying.
I did all that for you.
Fine, okay.
From now on, whether you are on the
streets swimming in dirt, or whatever...
I won't care at all,
so don't worry.
And I'll find all the garbage that
was in front of your door
and I'll pile it up all nice
again, so just wait.
I'll never help you again...
What the heck...
I'm so annoyed!
Why does she keep calling?
Dad!
Joon Soo!
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
Bad connection?
No, that's not it.
Have you been well?
Where are you?
Did you eat breakfast?
Of course I ate.
It's already late.
I'm on my way to school with Mom.
I see.
Dad, you'll be home tonight, right?
Huh?
Well, I...
Dad is busy, hang up.
Dad, I'll put Mom on the phone.
Hey, Joon Soo...
Don't put her on.
Joon Soo.
Hello?
Yeah.
You're at work?
I'm sorry, but that VJ
I asked about yesterday...
He can't go, he's busy.
He went as a special favor
for me last time.
Tell them no, he can't come.
Can you just ask him once?
He'll taking Joon Soo's pictures, too...
You have nothing more to say?
I'm hanging up.
Hold on.
Come home tonight.
Why, so you can leave?
Why do you keep saying
you'll leave with Joon Soo?
No, we can't stay like this forever.
Come in, so we can talk.
You're the one who
wanted to take time off.
Yeah, I wasn't thinking right.
So come home...
Who are you to tell me what to do?
That's my house. I'll go in
when I feel like it, got it?
Give me food!
Damn it!
That girl from yesterday is coming back?
Weren't you supposed to have
a meeting with Mr. Kim Pil Soo?
That case is almost closed.
We need to take care
of the urgent cases first.
- Yes, come in.
- Hello.
Producer Lee Ji Hoon!
Hello.
- Yes, hello.
- What are you doing here?
We're going to watch
the first airing together.
If you have time, you should come.
Oh, I have an important
consultation, I'll watch it later.
- Okay.
- Wait...
Would you like something to drink?
- Coffee, green tea, solomon's seal...
- No, thank you.
Then if you need the file later,
let us know.
- Goodbye.
- Okay.
But how did you know my name?
I don't think I ever told you.
- Your social media...
- What?
Attorney Choi told me.
Oh, I see.
What's your name?
We've met before, and you know
my name, but I don't know yours.
My name is Lee Do Yeon.
Then bye, Do Yeon.
Okay, bye.
- Get in safely.
- Okay.
Something urgent came up, I'll
only be able to make it later tonight.
Do Yeon.
I was thinking...
Going on the TV show is
promoting our office, too.
We should monitor it.
But I have a consultation, so do
you think you can go in my place?
Me?
Producer Lee personally invited me...
And I think it's kind
of rude not to go...
Yeah, a client postponed our meeting.
I'll go there right now.
Be ready.
I can stay for about an hour.
Don't say anything else.
Do Yeon's not checking her text,
I guess the office is busy, good luck.
Yeah, we're a bit busy.
Make sure you eat lunch.
I'll call you later.
[My wife demanded that we separate.]
Oh my.
I can't even sleep comfortably.
What's that?
A cellphone.
I bought it.
We can't do anything
when the post office closes.
Yeah?
That's very expensive,
where did you get the money?
I just had some money saved up.
My gold tooth!
Hey!
Bitch!
- Did you find the letter image?
- Yes, I did.
- Eun Ok!
- Yes.
- You have the review files?
- Yes, they're done.
Thanks.
Should we go to the kids'
cafe when they're done?
Sure.
Yoon Woo's Mom?
Joon Soo's mom asked me
to watch over Joon Soo.
Then you can't come out
because of Joon Soo?
I'm sorry, my mother-in-law
is visiting a relative.
What happened with the camera man?
I need to reserve another one
if he can't come.
- I asked my husband, so he'll come.
- That's great.
We'll take Joon Soo to the
kids' cafe and have him play there.
Okay, but will you be late? I'm supposed
to have dinner at my in-laws.
Why are mother-in-laws so annoying?
Thank you, Joon Soo's been
wanting to go to the kids' cafe.
I'll pick him up there later.
Do you all like macaroons?
There's a really good place by my work.
Hello?
Is this Ms. Jung Soo Yeon?
I'm Mr. Ji Sun Woo's wife.
My goodness, you came up
with a really nice title.
- Yeah.
- It fits your name.
- Can you turn up the volume?
- Sure.
Damn it.
It's no longer a man's place.
Many women are lured by...
Ms. Jung Soo Yeon?
Yes.
Have a seat.
Were you taken aback
to get my phone call?
No.
I'm not doing anything wrong here, am I?
I was curious.
I wanted to know who
my husband is dating.
I'm sorry.
For what?
What are you sorry for?
You should be specific about
why you are apologizing.
For dating Director Ji Sun Woo.
I'm sorry about that.
Did you think that he would
abandon our family for you?
If you did, you must have
been quite disappointed.
We don't have any problems.
When I told him that
I wanted to meet you
he said you're not even worth my time.
He said it was really nothing.
I heard you have a child.
It's not easy working
and raising a child.
Were you hoping that my husband
would be the savior there to rescue you?
If you did, then I'm so sorry.
As his wife, I apologize for him.
No.
Stop replying back to everything I say.
I'm not here to ask you questions.
I'm not even curious.
A married woman having an affair
with a married man.
It's so cliche.
"If others do it, it's an affair,
but if I do it, it's romance."
Is that what you thought?
An affair can never be romance.
Because of you,
our whole family was wounded.
- I'm sorry...
- Of course, you should be sorry.
I hope you have a good memory.
I hope you will remember
forever the wrong you did.
I hope you will remember us for the
rest of your life, and be pained by it.
Then I'll get going.
I wanted to see what
kind of a person you are.
But as my husband said,
I shouldn't have wasted my time.
You're no match for me.
Wow...
The reaction is great.
People are loving it.
I'm getting texts from my friends,
they must have seen it.
- I bet we'll have great viewer ratings.
- Yeah, that's good.
The reaction is great.
There's already a report on it.
We're third-place in a realtime ranking.
My mom watched it, too.
She said it was ----ing good.
- It must be in the genes.
- Ji Hoon, is he busy?
- Who?
- That VJ...
- He worked on "All About Movie."
- Oh, Hee Sup?
- Yeah, Hee Sup.
- I think he's working on a variety show.
- Why?
- He's busy?
It's nothing.
Captain Jung, it's not done?
- What?
- You didn't finish your project?
- I thought it was due tomorrow.
- What do you mean?
The client changed his mind,
and wanted it by today.
I'm sorry, I didn't get the message.
I'll work on it right now.
Joon Soo's having fun.
Just come by 6.
Can you talk?
Yeah, what is it?
I was wondering when you finish today.
If you have time...
I'm busy, we have a team dinner.
I was wondering if you would
be able to pick up Joon Soo.
He finished school early, and Yoon Ho's
mom took him to a kids' cafe.
I need to pick him up by 6:00...
I know I should go, but...
Something urgent came up.
When you said you were leaving,
weren't you prepared for all this?
I'm busy, we had our first airing,
so I need to take the team out.
Fine.
I'll make up the
canceled class tomorrow.
- Why did you cancel the class?
- Is everything okay?
I'm sorry, I had a very important
guest come visit me.
Your boyfriend?
Honey, what are you doing for dinner?
I'm not done with work, yet.
But of course, I'll be eating at home.
I thought my husband
would never cheat on me.
I was such a fool.
Every time I see you...
I resent the situation I'm in.
What?
I bet you have no idea
how lovable you are.
After meeting you yesterday...
I dared think about what it would
have been like if we had met
before I met my wife and
you met your husband.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry if I offended you.
- Let's continue with the consultation.
- I wasn't offended.
Yeah?
My husband is cheating behind
my back, so why not me?
Bo Ram...
Joon Soo.
Do Joon Soo.
Dad!
Have you been well?
Did you miss me?
Why are you playing alone?
You should play with your friends.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
You came?
Hello.
- I guess his mom's not done yet.
- It looks like she's busy these days.
Yes...
Thank you for getting the
camera man to come again.
Oh, you didn't hear yet?
She must not have told him, yet.
You came, too?
We saw his dad, so we
thought you weren't coming.
Sorry, I had to finish up work.
You should try this.
They are macaroons.
You shouldn't have...
You're always bringing us stuff.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
The seafood buffet you
mentioned opened right out front.
- We should go there next time.
- Nice.
- I wanted to go.
- Forget about the camera man.
- I don't want to burden you.
- Actually, he moved to another program.
I got another VJ to come.
- Really?
- Thank you.
Thanks to you, we get to have our
pictures taken by a professional.
- It's so nice having a producer father.
- Yeah.
Next time, we should get all the dads
together, and have a family gathering.
- Yeah.
- We can go camping nearby.
- Yeah, let's do that.
- Camping is nice.
- I'll prepare the food.
- Really?
That's great.
You said you have a team dinner.
You should be there, no?
You said you couldn't come.
- I guess that was a lie.
- Since you said you can't come
- I ran over.
- And what were they talking about?
When did I say that I
would send a camera man?
He's some neighborhood service man?
How do you think he would
feel if I keep asking him?
You said you got somebody else.
- Did you mean that?
- Why are you changing the subject?
Why are they ordering you around?
Are you a sinner?
You ran over, and you
were all servile to them.
You always say you're doing the best
for Joon Soo, but you really don't know.
I saw that he was playing all alone.
- They're excluding him.
- It's not like that.
Joon Soo's so shy, I try
hard to make friends for him...
If you did well,
he wouldn't be like that.
Whether the kids are picked up
by their moms or grandmothers
makes a difference in the
way kids walk out of school.
You always use Joon Soo as an excuse.
But what have you really done for him?
What?
You just want to appear as a
super mom, successful at work, too.
You think you're better
than stay-at-home moms.
And you want to show off that your
husband does everything you say.
Yeah.
Think what you want.
Be as bold to those women
as you are to me.
Stop acting like you're their maid!
- She's got a rival now.
- Don't drink.
I really can't carry you home today.
You better not.
I'll kill you if you do.
That's not what I meant...
I would be so offended
if I were your wife.
If I found out my husband
carried home a drunk woman
and even threw out her garbage.
I won't do it.
That was the first and last time.
Oh, why did you come?
Why did I come?
It's our team dinner.
Where is everyone?
They all left?
Yes, and Producer Ahn is throwing up.
Right.
Weren't you going straight home?
No.
Since the two of you aren't
getting along these days
I thought you were going
home to talk to her.
What?
I saw that you're
not wearing your ring.
You used to always wear it.
Oh...
It's bothering me a little these days.
- Your wife is having an affair, right?
- What?
I'm sorry, I kind of figured it out.
Does the taking off of
your ring mean something?
I'm sure there's a reason
why your wife wanted to separate.
Maybe you haven't
had a real talk with her, yet.
When you feel at loss, think
about the moment you got married.
Think about the vows you said
as you put the ring on her finger.
And you'll probably
figure out what to do.
You put your wedding
band on the left ring finger
which is the weakest finger.
Maybe it means we should live
supporting each other's weaknesses.
How about telling your wife the
meaning behind the wedding band, too?
Pay with this,
I'm going.
Thank you.
Tonight, I plan on having a
conversation with my wife.
Taxi!
I'll ask my wife why she did that.
Go get'em, Producer Do.
My wife is divorcing me this week.
Subtitles by DramaFever
I don't know what's going on,
but go get some fresh air.
If I go to Okinawa, I think my frozen
heart and body will melt a little.
Your body, too?
Let's go then.
Come on, we need to go.
Requested friend, Han Joon Hee.
Isn't this Joon Hee, the one you dated?
- Hyun Woo!
- Yeah, Joon Hee.
Did you cheat on me to get revenge?