(This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up)
I have nowhere to go in
a nice suit like this.
You've become a manager now.
We should celebrate.
I signed the contract for
"War Terminator", too.
Ho Jin, congratulations on your promotion.
Treat us sometime.
You're a real manager now.
Get me some jobs.
I'm looking forward, too.
The only change is the name of my position.
It means Eun Gab recognized your ability.
You worked so hard to get me the role.
Cut it out. Mr. Kim doesn't mean it.
He'll continue calling me Cup Noodles.
Just wait and see.
This is how you should look in a suit.
Look at me. Don't I look just amazing?
Don't I look like an Italian?
No, you look like a waiter.
One steak, please.
Look at yourself. With
such narrow shoulders,
you look like a student
activist from the 70s.
Your face looks like that of
an old man from the 19th century.
Hey.
You shouldn't get a new suit.
Why would you need it when you have no job?
Are you going to wear it
on your internet show?
You're insulting a million
unemployed people out there.
I really didn't want to bring this up.
The "erection on the set" incident.
- Hey.
- Stop it.
It was a historical incident.
It's so embarrassing that
it never even gets published.
Hey!
That never happened.
He was supposed to act angry.
But a certain body part got angry instead.
It gets angry whenever he's angry.
Young Bin, don't buy him a suit.
- Why do you decide?
- I'm his cousin.
That sounded so childish.
Do you have a problem?
You promised him to buy him
Michael Lau's artworks, right?
Yes, Turtle loves them.
You can't.
If you buy him those,
I'll stop cooking for you guys.
- You guys clean the house.
- Why?
What should we do? He sounds serious.
You're one petty waiter.
When will my steak be served?
Fine. Do you want to go
and have some steak?
Sure.
What's wrong with you?
What's the point of getting a new suit?
I'm always at home.
I know. You shouldn't
call yourself an actor.
Stop it.
Look at that car.
Who parks his car like this?
We can still get out.
Wait. We should teach this jerk a lesson.
- What a jerk!
- Stop it.
I'll call him.
- Wait.
- Let me do this.
Wait.
Let me call him instead.
Get off me.
(YOUNG BIN)
Why are you calling me?
Can you move your car?
What?
This car is yours.
You're a success.
You've come a long way.
It's a present from me.
Now that you're a manager,
you need a new car.
Forget it. I don't deserve it.
I already signed the contract.
Just take it.
Pay me back when you become rich.
If you don't take it, I'll take it.
- Gosh.
- Wait.
You're smiling ear to ear.
- What are you talking about?
- You're almost bleeding.
- I'll drive.
- Look at you.
This car is so nice.
Did Turtle get in the other
car because he's angry at me?
He has a good reason.
He'd been so excited about those artworks.
I feel so great. That serves him right.
You're so childish.
Everyone knows Young Bin is your cousin.
The caller ID is unknown?
I didn't know you could still do this.
- Hello?
- Is this Mr. Cha Joon?
This is a film company.
Yes, this is the one-of-a-kind actor,
- Cha Joon.
- Gosh.
I'm calling you regarding
our upcoming movie.
Are you offering me an audition?
I'm the assistant director.
I'd like to cast you without an audition.
I see.
You are the assistant director.
By the way, what's the movie about?
It's an action movie.
The shooting starts next month.
An action movie?
I see.
Could you tell me the title of it?
It's called, "Angry Men".
"Angry Men"?
It sounds funny.
The movie is about...
a competition between angry men.
Are you concerned about something?
No, not at all.
Which role will I be playing?
The aroused man.
The aroused man?
It's an important role.
I see.
I'm not sure I can do it well.
- Stop it.
- The aroused man.
It's an action movie.
"Angry Men".
Hey.
Gosh.
I tried to stop him, I swear.
- Gosh.
- Go.
You jerk!
Did we get too aggressive last time?
I don't remember well.
No, we didn't.
I don't remember well, either,
but if I had been really angry,
it wouldn't have stopped there.
I wasn't serious, either.
If you had crossed the line,
I would have made it clear.
I know. We were quite cute.
You were kinder than I had expected.
What did you do to the
director, by the way?
He really didn't like the idea at first.
Did I miss anything?
You're very skillful.
That's not true.
He probably saw that I was genuine.
Young Bin is a great actor.
You wanted to make a contract with us,
but you backed out when
the director objected.
I'm very impressed.
No production companies care
so much about directors' opinions.
I'm done.
The contract has been made.
I hope we'll stay on good terms.
We should. We're on the same boat now.
Who else will be in the movie?
Who will play the supporting role?
It's giving me a headache.
We're talking with Kang
Ha Neul at the moment.
- Sorry?
- Kang Ha Neul?
Is he good?
Didn't Kang Ha Neul...
have a scandal with An So Hee?
There's something fishy.
Why would he play a supporting role?
- He's played main roles.
- I wonder that, too.
The role is too small for him,
and he even had a scandal.
Can you ask around?
Sure, Mr. Lee. I'll ask around.
You already have so much to care about.
I heard you bought Ho Jin a car.
He's a real manager now.
His car was so old.
He's too dorky to have such a fancy car.
- Sorry?
- That's why he needs a nice car.
You think so?
Anyway, An So Hee signed the contract.
The main actor and actress are decided now.
Really? That's great.
- You look so happy.
- Is there something going on?
- Stop it.
- You brats.
What are you doing here?
- I have something to tell you.
- What is it?
Hello.
Can't I get a role in "War Terminator"?
Please ask them if there's a role for him.
They hate it when a management company...
tries to sell its actors in a bundle.
I'll find you some auditions.
Okay.
Anyway, the contract has been signed.
Now, focus on preparing for the shooting.
- Help him.
- Okay.
Stay red.
What's wrong with you?
- Sorry?
- Your face.
No surgery could save this.
Take good care of it, okay?
- Okay.
- Gosh. You should.
I'll see you again.
Mr. Kim is not in the position to
criticize someone else's looks.
Right? That was...
- Is he still angry?
- Joon!
Gosh.
(IT'S YOUNG BIN'S TREAT.)
Aren't you coming with me?
I'd be a third wheel. I'm not coming.
I'm not coming, either.
Couldn't you wait until
the shooting begins?
I just wanted to let her
know the coffee is from me.
Just admit you wanted to see So Hee.
You're right. See you.
He's wasting his time.
Why is he so desperate?
Should we go watch?
We're not supposed to be here.
I'm failing all the auditions, too.
Then again, I guess you can't be on sets...
after that incident.
Ho Jin.
Is there someone else than you here?
- I'm hearing things.
- Gosh.
Are you still angry?
Why are you so petty?
You're almost 2m tall.
Ho Jin, tell him.
I don't want to have
a conversation with a kid.
I regret not following Young Bin.
I apologize, Joon.
I'll set you up with a girl.
What did you say?
You've been avoiding girls because of...
what the fortune teller said, right?
I'll find you a girl.
- You know what type I like, right?
- I do.
It never changes.
- Ho Jin, do you want one, too?
- Forget it.
He has Ji An.
- What are you saying?
- A lovesick man who always...
watches a girl's back.
That was nice. Say it once again.
A lovesick man who always
watches a girl's back.
That was so nice. Say it one more time.
- It's nice, right? A lovesick...
- Stop it now.
Gosh, you don't know when to stop.
You brat.
(AN SO HEE)
Hi.
We're friends from school.
This is Young Bin.
I know who he is. I love your movies.
- Thank you.
- You're doing great.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
See you.
It seems like I interrupted you.
You didn't. Sit down.
I wanted to see you
before we start shooting.
- Maybe I came too early.
- It's okay.
Thank you for the coffee.
Everyone looked so happy.
You and Ha Neul...
Should I call him Mr. Kang?
Anyway, you two seem close.
We are.
We used to date.
When you asked me,
we had already broken up.
That's why I told you we were just friends.
- I didn't mean to lie.
- It's okay.
He came to see me recently.
He wants to get back together with me.
Are you...
getting back together?
I'm not sure yet.
I don't want to think
about anything else...
until this drama is over.
I heard Ha Neul might
be in "War Terminator".
That's right.
I think it's because of me.
It's to get back together with me.
Tell me the truth.
Is it certain?
Will Ha Neul take it? Why?
How would I know? He
probably liked the script.
Or the director.
What is he thinking? What
did the director say?
Don't ask me.
I'm busy. You call me only when
you want something from me.
Hey, I have tons of pictures
of your ex-girlfriend.
I even have one where you kiss her.
Do you want it to spread?
You're unbelievable.
The director seems to be okay with it.
That's all I know.
I'm busy. Hang up.
Why would you be busy?
I'm the head of the team.
Of course, you are.
I'd like our investment
company to be more engaged.
Are you going to let Ms. Jo run wild?
The idea is almost like a co-investor.
These days, management
companies have the most power.
You're the boss.
Cut it out.
Why does everyone give me a
hard time if I'm one? Hang up.
- What's going on?
- I started the meeting.
You're late.
I'm 4 minutes and 5 seconds
late, to be precise.
What are you doing now?
I'm leading a meeting, don't you see?
I'll attend meetings from now on.
Stop interrupting the meeting.
Sit over there.
Go on.
Okay.
The thing is...
Well...
There's a rumor saying
that he slept with them.
Is it a rumor or a fact?
It seems like he did sleep
with a couple of them.
It is exaggerated, though.
It'll get published soon.
Great job.
Can't you do any better?
Why do you blame me?
I didn't tell him to be such a jerk.
You're responsible for
managing your actors.
You should have even used
violence to stop him.
Who does that these days?
These days, you can play go
or even sleep with a robot.
If I hadn't beaten you up,
you would never have grown up.
What are you talking about?
Don't exaggerate it.
You totally sound like an old lady.
And you're so young, right?
Think about how you used to be.
Are you ashamed of your past
now that you're a director?
What's wrong with you?
Have you checked if you have Alzheimer's?
You're driving me crazy.
You said you didn't want to work.
You said you were considering
taking a year off or retiring.
Are you feeling greedy?
Are you craving money?
Hey.
I dragged my old body here because
I couldn't stand your job.
Do you get it now?
Enjoy this.
Did you see?
She's crazy.
What's wrong with her?
What are you doing here?
You told me to water your plants.
The meeting didn't take so long.
How could we have a meeting
with a crazy woman?
- Sorry?
- Hey, be careful.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
I can't ask you to do anything.
You're very nice to your plants.
I wish you were that nice to me.
Are you jealous?
Say that to your boyfriend instead.
Don't touch Young Bin.
Young Bin?
Move. Gosh.
Don't touch it. This one is my treasure.
Did you give your plants names?
Look.
These are our most popular actors.
What about the other actors?
They don't have any plants.
They'll get one...
when they become more popular.
I see.
You're cute.
Have you lost your mind?
It gave me goosebumps.
Where? Down there?
What kind of a girl says such a thing?
You say it all the time.
Testicles, testicles,
- testicles...
- Hey!
Can't you stop saying that?
At first, I didn't understand.
I decide what I say.
Get out. Stop talking.
Don't tell anyone about my plants, okay?
Okay. I'll get a plant and name it Eun Gab.
What?
What is it?
- Mr. Kim, I'm driving.
- Why is it so noisy?
Are you still driving that junk?
No.
By the way, have you asked around?
Sorry?
All right.
What did he say?
It seems like Ha Neul will do it.
The director likes him.
Will you be acting with
So Hee's ex-boyfriend?
It'll be so awkward.
Is this a drama?
It's terrible when your colleagues date.
It's awkward when they fight.
This is not okay.
Will you be all right?
No.
I'll go to the director and make a scene.
That's a great idea. Should I make a turn?
Should I?
What can I do now?
I have no choice.
Let's stop talking about him.
Are you finding me a girl or not?
I showed pictures of you to girls,
and everyone said no.
They said you were ugly and old.
One girl genuinely got angry with me.
- I fought for you.
- Gosh.
Likes attract likes.
Everyone around you is weird.
I know I don't usually
look good on pictures.
You look much better on pictures.
Gosh.
Keep your promise.
Otherwise, I'll get really angry.
When are we going to stop?
Joon is driving me crazy.
Why did you tag along in the first place?
I just wanted to drive
it for the last time.
We all feel attached to this car.
Joon and I used to go
to auditions with this car.
This car still works fine.
- Are you okay?
- What happened?
Did you get hurt that seriously?
Gosh, it's so dusty.
What? Does it feel like you're
saying goodbye to a girl?
Kind of.
I know that feeling.
What are you talking about?
He does know that feeling.
He's seen so many girls walk away from him.
That's right.
My phone is ringing.
It really is.
Hello?
Hi.
Okay, I'll be on my way.
Okay.
- Who was it?
- It was Eun.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Men are all the same.
What's all this?
It's a lingerie fashion show.
Good thing I decided to follow you.
You all followed Joon to his blind date?
Gosh.
Wake up, Joon.
Don't forget why you're here.
What type of a woman is she?
She's the marketing manager
of this lingerie brand.
She's nice and pretty. Follow me.
She must've hurt her head for
wanting to go on a date...
with Joon judging by his picture.
She must be into tall and bald guys.
- Am I right?
- Sure.
Let's go drink.
Do something about him.
Do what exactly?
Let's go.
I heard...
you do marketing.
I do. Are you enjoying the show?
I love it.
I've never been to something
like this before.
Do you really not have a boyfriend?
You look like you'd be popular among men.
- I'm busy with work.
- I see.
By the way, you don't look
like Cha Young Bin at all.
- I heard you guys are cousins.
- Well...
We looked alike when we were kids.
As we grew up,
I turned more masculine.
My physique...
and everywhere else.
Are your friends still here?
Including Young Bin?
Yes. They should be downstairs.
Do you want me to send them away?
No. They should stay.
Everyone's excited with
Young Bin being here.
Young Bin was the only person
on her mind in the first place.
She went on a date with me
so Young Bin would come to the show.
I didn't know that.
Even Eun thought she was into you.
I was a gentleman to her
even when I found out.
Are you that into her?
Do you want me to cut you up?
- There's a last resort.
- What?
We should update your profile on 2km
saying you're the actor Cha Joon.
That's not right.
What's so wrong about dating apps?
It's just an innocent social meet
up between a man and a woman.
Do you think women will like him?
He'll get a few calls from
the fans of Sugar Boys.
- You think so?
- What are you so happy about?
I said I'm against it.
It's not my fault when
the agency finds out.
Look how he's changed after the promotion.
He's the source of all evil.
He's the second Kim Eun Gab.
I'm not taking any part in this.
You're going to an exhibition tomorrow.
- Jung Woo's painting exhibition?
- Yes.
I think So Hee will be there, too.
I see.
What's that reaction?
I thought you'd be happier.
I am happy.
I am.
That's it?
- Hey.
- Aren't you eating?
I'm going to bed.
There he goes again with
the An So Hee virus.
He always gets depressed
when he gets infected.
I hope it's not contagious.
You scared me.
You're the one who scared me.
It's late night.
I thought you were a mugger.
Why would you be walking around
at night if you're so scared?
Gosh.
- How did you know I was here?
- Isn't it obvious?
You always sneak out at night
when you have a headache.
You're right.
I have a bad headache.
We should say we don't
want to work with Ha Neul.
- To whom?
- To Mr. Kim.
Or even the director or So Hee.
- I don't like the idea.
- Sure, you don't.
I wouldn't be able to stay in the
same room with my girl's ex.
Let alone for a few months.
That is...
That'll be so frustrating.
Let's be honest. He only wants to
do the movie because of So Hee.
He's not normal.
I wanted to do the movie
for the same reason.
You're not normal either.
Why are actors so abnormal?
Why would they pick love over work?
My disappointment grows bigger
everyday I work as a manager.
Are you laughing at me?
Do you think this is funny?
Should I cry, then?
I'll be fine.
I looked at the scripts and
I won't be working with him that much.
I'll just have to deal with it.
- Are you sure you'll be all right?
- No,
but I still have to make an effort.
It's not like I'm dating
So Hee at the moment.
Whether they start seeing
each other again or not,
it's none of my business.
That's awfully professional of you.
You should try it sometimes.
I'm always professional.
(HA JUNG WOO PRIVATE EXHIBITION)
Young Jun.
- Hello.
- Young Bin.
- Are you here for the exhibition?
- Yes.
I've seen it already, but
I'm not so sure about it.
I'll see you later.
Goodbye.
Isn't that Kang Ha Neul next to So Hee?
What do you want to do?
- Let's go home.
- What?
Hey.
The pleasure is ours.
I think Yoo Bin really wants to...
improve and be better.
What did you think?
I'm sorry, but you'll have
to excuse me for a moment.
- I'm really sorry.
- Excuse me.
What is it?
Can you talk right now, Mr. Kim?
Make it short.
About Kang Ha Neul.
Is it confirmed that he'll
be on "War Terminator"?
That's what's bothering me too.
It's not confirmed yet.
Why? Is Young Bin against it?
He's not exactly the problem,
but So Hee is.
What are you talking about?
The reason why Ha Neul wants
to do "War Terminator" is...
because of So Hee.
It looks like they're
still seeing each other.
For goodness' sake.
Since when did hooking up become
the purpose of doing movies?
When actors start having intimate
relationships with each other,
the same thing goes for staff
member on staff member...
and actor on staff member,
it'll most certainly ruin
the working environment.
Mr. Kim, Young Bin has a crush on So Hee.
What did you say?
What are you talking about?
Did you say he likes So Hee?
Aren't they just college friends?
Young Bin likes So Hee.
I'm worried about the
movie because of that.
You should've told me earlier.
Why are you bringing it to me now?
We shouldn't have let him work with her.
Is shooting a movie some third-rate drama?
Are you trying to hook them up?
Do you think a movie set is
some college frat party?
Hang up.
Oh, my head.
Hello?
When did you get here?
Are you sure about this?
I had a horrible experience from
a dating site 10 years ago.
I think I heard this story before.
Did you not like her?
Surprisingly, she was very hot
like she described herself.
But she was too open-minded. She
asked me to buy her drinks...
and came on to me like crazy.
I got scared and ran away.
Oh, the good old days.
Why would you run away, though?
You saw the picture I sent you, right?
- She's hot.
- I'm not running away this time.
I'm open-minded now.
Are you sure the picture
wasn't photo-shopped?
Was the picture taken by her phone?
Stop with the whining already.
I watched all of your videos
back when you were an idol.
I even watched your movies.
You did?
And...
you look much better in person.
You flatter me.
I get that a lot.
You do, right?
It's really strange.
I'm so used to seeing you from videos.
I think...
you're a really special person.
You do?
I'm nothing special really.
You must be close with many famous actors.
Who are you friends with?
I have friends here and there.
Why is he calling me?
Who is it? Is it a celebrity?
It's someone called Kim Ki Bang.
He does a little acting.
Can you excuse me for a second?
Hi. What is it?
You want to play pools
with someone like me?
I thought you were busy spending
time with star celebrities.
I'm busy, too. I'm with someone right now.
You can come if you want.
Turtle's here, too.
You know the place where
Lee Eun works, right?
Okay.
Ki Bang's coming.
Why did you invite him?
You're in the middle of a date.
I want to show off my connections.
Maybe I shouldn't have invited him.
Ki Bang is all right.
It's not like he's on
the same level as Young Bin.
That's right.
He'll make me look good.
You two aren't any different.
The only difference is that you're taller.
No way. He does make him look good.
By 0.01mm.
What are you talking about?
I was born with better genes.
He looks like a descendant of barbarians.
I'm Young Bin's cousin.
Did your standards become too high
from being around with Young Bin?
You're delusional.
How's the date going anyway?
I think she's really into me.
It's a bit overwhelming.
She's gone crazy.
Maybe it's just you.
Everyone's gone crazy.
I'm such a big fan.
Gosh.
You look so much better in person.
You look so tough and manly.
- You're even sexy.
- What?
Did you say I'm sexy?
I do get that a lot these days.
Ki Bang.
Turtle's waiting for you.
Oh, right. Turtle.
You should hang out with us.
What?
Did I make you uncomfortable?
It's nothing like that.
Maybe I'll stick around for a while.
- Is that okay?
- What?
Of course. You can stay for a minute.
Cheers.
Do you work out?
Your biceps are so big.
I did some working out for my role.
Can you tell?
What about the chest?
Can I feel your chest a little?
My chest? Hold on.
Jerk.
How can she pick Ki Bang over you?
You got manhandled by a barbarian.
Is it because he's well known?
You have to tell Ki Bang to go home.
I told you she's crazy.
She's just happy to see celebrities.
Even so.
Why does he have to ruin my date?
He was never the popular one among women.
She said he's sexy.
Stop whining and go back.
You're going to scare off my customers.
She's right. You can't just leave them be.
I don't care any more.
They're crazy about each other.
They've got their hands
all over each other.
They shouldn't be doing that here.
- No way.
- Hurry.
Joon.
Something came up.
I have to go now.
- Me, too.
- I'm sorry.
Did they do it?
That scum.
Did you see it?
Can you talk to me?
Come on.
Are you really not going to talk?
I can't tell you anything.
You'll just slip it right out.
I told you. There was no other way.
What do you mean?
Why did you have to tell him I like So Hee?
How are you planning on shooting
the film with those two?
You didn't even say hello to Jung Woo.
I was surprised.
That was...
It's my problem. I'll
take care of it myself.
This isn't just your problem.
The whole movie is at stake.
This is everyone's problem.
That's why I told Mr. Kim.
You're completely on
his side now, aren't you?
Are you sure you can solve
this problem on your own?
No, right?
Even I can't do anything about it.
I talked to Mr. Kim just now.
He'll take care of it.
That was quick.
You two are basically partners now.
What a perfect agency.
I did this for you as a manager.
You shouldn't have, as my friend.
Do you want me to be a good
manger or a good friend?
Both.
You really have to pick your side.
What are you talking about?
Either love or work. Pick
one and stick with it.
When did you become so...
Did you learn that one from Eun Gab?
Put yourself in my shoes.
How would you feel if
I babbled about you and Ji An?
She's still here.
- Am I interrupting?
- No.
I'm done for today. I'll
come back tomorrow.
- Goodbye.
- I need to talk to you, Ji An.
Ho Jin says...
It's nothing. Goodbye.
He wants to have dinner with you.
Isn't that right, Ho Jin?
- Yes.
- I can't tonight.
By the way, my mom wants to have
dinner with you, Young Bin.
You can refuse if you don't want to.
Not at all. You'll be there, right?
I'm not sure.
You have to be there.
You'd like it, too, right?
That's right.
So be it, then.
Goodbye.
What is it? Did it not go well?
Why won't you tell us?
Whatever.
Tell them.
Don't get me started.
Ki Bang stole her away from him.
His date went to Ki Bang instead.
Why did you tell them?
You're such a big mouth.
Hear that?
He called you a big mouth.
Stop it. When will you ever grow up?
Did something go wrong?
Turtle's asking.
Why don't you tell him with your big mouth?
When Young Bin saw...
So Hee and Ha Neul together
at the exhibition,
he ran away.
Is today Cha family's humiliation day?
What happened next?
Ho Jin called Eun Gab right away.
Telling him that I like So Hee.
He did that?
Is that funny to you?
- Ho Jin did the right thing.
- How?
He's right.
You're right. I'm a coward
and a small-minded person.
So you do know. That's your strong forte.
I should tell on you, too.
To Mr. Kim?
No, to Ms. Kang.
Ho Jin is in love with
your daughter, Ms. Kang.
- That's hilarious.
- I know, right?
I'm going to have dinner with
Ms. Kang. Do you want to join?
You could get to know each other.
I don't feel comfortable around her.
What are you going to do about me, anyway?
I was hoping it didn't
have to come down to this.
Let's go Feeling Camping.
What's that?
This will get the job done.
People start dating from this.
Are you really going camping
instead of seeing Ms. Kang?
I choose love over work.
Let's go right now.
And stop fighting, you two.
You can't even date girls.
Look who's talking.
Gosh.
Leave them be. They're all the same.
They're losers, loners
and cowards acting tough.
Look at this.
This is Feeling Camping?
Look at the pictures.
What is that?
You're so much work.
Sit down and relax.
Bravo.
This is exciting.
Do we set up our tent here?
No. We have to go up higher in
the mountains where it's not so crowded.
We'll be alone with the girls in the woods.
That's what Feeling Camping is all about.
Do we have to carry all this?
Did you forget why we're here?
- You're welcome to go back home.
- Okay, fine.
Are you sure about this, though?
100 percent. They get all romantic here.
Sitting around the bonfire
and staring into each other.
That's where it all starts.
Why don't you have a girlfriend again?
- It's a mystery.
- It's because you're jobless.
That's right. We have that in common.
I'm not jobless. I'm an actor.
You are jobless. And I'm the better one.
Why is that?
I'm just jobless, but you're
ugly, old and jobless.
You look like one of the salamanders
that live in the mountains.
You'll be thanking me by
the time we're heading back home.
You'll be calling me "Sir". Call me "Sir".
- Yes, Sir.
- Good boy.
Bring them out.
Let's go.
This is crazy.
Am I supposed to carry all of them?
I never knew there was a
place like this in Korea.
I've never seen anything like that.
What happened here?
I'm a nature man.
The aroused man.
How much longer do we have to go?
I didn't come here to climb.
Joon.
This place looks good enough.
Do you want to set up camp here?
Okay.
Joon. Set up the camp already.
- I need to rest for a bit.
- No.
It'll get dark soon. The women
won't come up here then.
Fine.
Let's get working.
This is nice.
What are you doing? I'm doing all the work.
You're such a whiner.
I'm doing the most important job.
I'm uploading pictures on
my social media accounts.
Take a look. See?
Do you see what's happening as we speak?
- See what?
- Don't you see it?
"Where are you?", "Where is that?",
"Where are you right now?"
"I'll be there soon",
"I'm taking the cab there."
- 10 comments already.
- Tell them to get over here quick.
- I told you I'd do you good.
- You were right.
Don't call too many people over.
We only have four chairs.
We should get 400 to 500 people over.
200 will be swimming over there
and the other 200 will be over there.
The rest 100 will be holding
candles by the fire...
crying, telling stories and all that.
- Feeling Camping.
- That's what I'm talking about.
I'll get a handkerchief
ready to wipe their tears.
Go set up the tent.
This is the famous yellow corvina
from Beopsungpo.
Try it.
Thank you.
I wanted to feed you
some home-made cooking.
I'm not making you uncomfortable, am I?
Of course not.
Ho Jin probably feels at home.
Like he's with his mother-in-law.
- Are you okay, Manager Lee?
- I'm fine.
Oh, gosh. Here you go. Eat up, Manager Lee.
- Okay.
- Here.
Thank you.
You have...
a beautiful house.
It's my daughter's work.
I didn't even pay for it.
Ji An's running late.
She said she'd come early.
Speaking of the devil.
- Sorry, I'm late.
- Hello.
We started without you.
Go bring your food.
Okay. I'll be right back.
Can you bring some more
vegetables on your way back?
Sure.
You should go help her, Ho Jin.
You should.
Do you want to come?
Yes.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- You should try some, too.
- Don't worry about me.
- It's uncomfortable, isn't it?
- What?
Not at all.
She's always been good to me.
The food is delicious, too.
- She's a good cook.
- I see.
- Strange, right?
- Yes.
No.
It feels like my mom's cooking. I love it.
Joon's a good cook, too,
but his food isn't quite my style.
It doesn't have depth.
I'm a good cook, too.
Okay.
- You don't believe me?
- I do.
I'm just like my mom.
I don't do housekeeping,
but I'm a good cook.
I'll cook for you some time.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
Do you like this kind of alcohol?
I've always wanted to try some.
Congratulations on landing
"War Terminator".
Thank you.
How does it feel to be in such a big movie?
I thought it'd overwhelm me,
but I'm excited actually.
I'm looking forward to it.
Of course.
I knew you'd make it when I first saw you.
I had faith in you.
Eun Gab says he's the one who raised you,
but I've always known.
I'm always grateful for Eun Gab.
You're a loyal man.
I like that.
Has it been four years since
we've been working together?
- Yes.
- You're a fourth grader.
In the 5th grade,
you'll win a domestic award or 2.
In the sixth grade, you'll go to Cannes.
Cannes?
Yes.
You'll make a fortune like
Kim Soo Hyun and Jang Keun Suk.
There will be a building
under your name as well.
Eun Gab doesn't even drink any more.
He has strong will. He's no fun.
Should we...
start working together just the two of us?
What?
I'm just kidding.
Cheers.
You're here early.
I came on time.
You're the one who came late.
You didn't order any drinks?
I don't drink any more. Order for yourself.
I will when everyone else comes.
Is this where you hang out often?
Yes. It's nice, isn't it?
Not really. I prefer somewhere quieter.
I have an appointment soon,
so I'll get to the point.
You don't want Kang Ha Neul
being in the movie?
- No.
- Why not? I don't understand.
He's the one I don't understand.
He has no reason to do this movie.
The director approves.
He won't.
What are you trying to say?
You know he's dating An So Hee.
Is there proof?
- You know.
- I don't.
Of course you do.
So you want him out?
The leading roles in an
intimate relationship...
will ruin the work environment.
You've seen it happen.
But I still want him on the movie.
His agency invested in your funds, right?
That's why you're agreeing to their terms.
He's past his prime now.
- We should rule him out.
- What if I disagree?
Manager Kim of CJ Entertainment...
and the CEO of An So Hee's agency
are waiting for me nearby.
We're going to meet up and
persuade the director together.
Look at the eyes of the shark.
They look empty of emotions.
Scary, isn't it?
Don't go see the director.
Kang Ha Neul is out of the picture.
That's some sensible thinking.
And from now on,
you don't have a say in the casting.
That's my job.
Of course. I'm busy, too.
I'll be going now.
You're really not drinking.
You're awfully strong willed.
That's so boring.
I want to pluck out the eyes of that shark.
That's a female shark, right?
I'll go now.
Hello? Are you with Young Bin?
- Yes.
- Tell him this.
Kang Ha Neul is out.
It's all taken care of.
Really? How?
I'll tell you later.
Where's Young Bin?
He's with Ms. Kang now.
Who?
She invited him over to her place.
He's having dinner with her.
Why are you telling me this just now?
You're telling everything late.
Why are you getting so worked up?
I didn't think it was important
enough to tell you.
You drive me crazy.
You jerk!
Well...
Did she shred a dried fish
by hand and make food for him?
My gosh. How did you know?
So he's there now, right?
Okay. Bye.
What brings you here?
No reason.
They left.
Let's talk inside.
It's not like I can't visit you.
I used to come by all the time.
You haven't been here since
you became successful.
I know. Let's just talk inside.
(RICE CRACKER)
What is this?
You like rice crackers.
You used to eat this every day.
I don't eat it these days.
I mean, there are so many delicious things.
You've changed.
You're the one who has changed.
You're condescending and
disrespectful towards me now.
Gosh, you and your foul mouth.
When was I condescending to you?
We just have different opinions.
Right, we think differently now.
Very differently, in fact.
Why did you meet with Young Bin?
I can't even meet with an actor
in my agency as the co-CEO?
You should've either given me
a heads-up or let me join.
Why are you talking as if I have
some sort of a hidden agenda?
You did the same thing when you
stole actors from other agencies.
You invited them over to
your place for the dried fish dish...
and made cheonggukjang for them.
What is on your mind these days?
You tried to sell the company,
came to our meeting,
and met with Young Bin secretly.
What are you thinking? Tell me.
You idiot.
Do you think the company...
is yours?
No.
It's ours.
You worked hard to lay foundation for it,
and I've been working like
a dog to grow it, so it's ours.
It's mine.
What?
Go home before I let my dog off its leash.
It's yours?
- Are you tired?
- Yes.
I was so uncomfortable there.
You probably felt the same.
Yes. I was a little uncomfortable, too.
Ms. Kang was there,
and Ji An was there, too.
Goodness.
About Ms. Kang.
I was weirded out by what she said.
I was stressed out because
of what you said.
- Why? I didn't even say much.
- Whatever.
You're the one who told Eun Gab everything.
- Why aren't you saying anything?
- I don't want to talk to you.
You just have to get even with me.
All right. I won't be like that.
You stop it, too.
You don't have to work with
Ha Neul any more. It worked out.
Still, I don't feel that great.
Right. They're going out,
so I get why you're down.
- What can you do, though?
- You're right.
I'm aware of it.
So Hee is our friend, you know.
Her dating someone outside of our circle...
shouldn't really upset us that much...
Hey.
Just say, "Cheer up, friend."
Can't you try to make me feel better?
What was that about? That was so cold.
You idiot.
Friend.
Cheer up. We have to work hard, you know.
- You're my manager, indeed.
- Of course I am.
Joon and Turtle must be having fun.
They haven't even called.
You're right. Shall I try calling them?
(YOUNG BIN)
Gosh, it's Young Bin.
Hello?
What do you think?
The two of us are just camping out here.
Just the two of you?
No one came because it's too far.
About 400 mosquitos are keeping us company.
Turtle insisted that we should
camp inside the mountain,
so even the ones who came
all the way here left.
You love to blame other
people for everything.
- Well...
- Give it to me.
Hello?
Joon's mood swings are annoying me so much.
Stop fighting and just come home.
Thanks, you're the best.
We'll go there, right? Let's go today.
Okay.
All right. Let's eat some instant noodles.
We'll be there soon.
Let's eat the noodles.
Goodness. You have to make it.
Joon, I don't think anyone will come.
Let's give up.
Gosh.
It'll take forever to clean up.
- Are you okay?
- There's too much meat left.
Where are we now?
Do you know where we're going?
How would I know?
The last time I went camping
was when I was a little boy.
I have no idea where we are right now.
We have to stay calm and collected.
"Stay focused. Where do we have to go?"
Did I sound like the game character?
Which way do we have to go, seriously?
My goodness. I thought you were
Jun Kunimura. I want your autograph.
Gosh, seriously.
Hey, shall we call 911?
I'm an actor.
They'll write articles about me.
Actor? Whatever.
What do you want to do, then?
Let's just sleep here...
and go home tomorrow.
That's crazy. There are over
400 frogs here. We can't sleep here.
Oh, my life.
What on earth am I doing here?
We don't even have sleeping bags.
What are we doing here?
Joon. We won't be attacked
by wild animals, right?
I'm seriously hoping that
a tiger shows up and takes you.
Is it because we're inside the mountain?
It's cold.
Goodness.
Don't touch me. You're disgusting.
Gosh, it's so cold.
I'll turn around so that our backs touch.
This is more disgusting.
Get your bottom away from me.
Go away.
Hey. You just heard that sound, right?
What sound?
What if there's a wild animal outside?
It could be a wild boar.
Gosh, here we go again.
You're seriously so paranoid.
There must be something outside.
Stop! Stop it seriously. I'm so scared!
Joon.
Let's get out of here...
- and call 911.
- We can't do that.
It could ruin my career as an actor.
Joon, no one even knows you.
No one will write articles about this.
Still, we can't.
Let's just sleep.
Everything will be fine if we fall asleep.
I'm so cold and scared.
What are you doing?
What?
- Why are you here?
- I couldn't fall asleep.
Did something happen?
No, not at all.
I can trust you that
everything is fine, right?
Honey. When we were dating,
you had a dog, right? The one
that lived for a long time.
Arong?
That dog started throwing a hissy
fit when it got older, right?
Yes.
It started when Arong turned 10 years old.
She started throwing tantrums
and didn't even eat her food.
She started biting me, too.
She was never like that before.
I guess she changed because she got older.
- You mean Arong?
- She tried to bite me today.
Shall I bite back?
What are you talking about?
Honey, you and Yoo Bin are
everything in my life.
It must be a midlife crisis.
Shall I take you to a doctor?
What are you talking about?
You just don't get it.
- Just go in and sleep.
- You go in and sleep.
- Turn off the TV.
- Okay.
Goodness.
Here. Try it. It's a little hot.
Why did you want to eat with us suddenly?
Since when did we need a
reason to eat together?
You usually don't eat lunch.
Why are you treating us
to barbecue for lunch?
Are you doing this because I met with Ms.
Kang yesterday?
What are you talking about?
Not at all.
Just eat. Eat up, guys.
Tenderloin is the most tender.
It looks delicious.
By the way, what did Ms. Kang say to you?
Nothing much. She just said she's
looking forward to working with me.
She's trying to win you over to
her side because you're popular.
That dried fish dish was very delicious.
She tore the fish into
small strips by hand.
She does that all the time.
She does it for everyone.
She also made cheonggukjang, right?
She uses that old trick
of hers over and over.
Here, eat this.
What has gotten into you?
I'm not used to it, either.
It's making me cringe, too.
You make your own wraps, then.
Eat up.
- Hey, guys.
- You made it.
Are you guys coming from the mountain?
- Yes.
- Hello.
Hi.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
Don't you dare touch me.
Look who's talking.
You're the one who did it!
- What's going on?
- What's wrong?
You idiots, what are you doing right now?
Did you two have a fight or what?
No, we didn't. I woke up at
night because I was too cold...
and noticed that he was
hugging me from behind.
His thing was touching my behind...
- Gosh, seriously.
- Darn it!
Hey, tell the truth.
You're the one who turned around
and had your back touch my...
Stop it, seriously!
You two went camping to meet girls.
Did you end up shooting
"Brokeback Mountain" instead or what?
- "Brokeback Mountain".
- You piece of...
- You little...
- Enough, guys.
Are you saying that you two...
did something we should
be worried about inside the tent?
I respect your personal taste,
but don't go overboard, all right?
Did you hear what happened to So Hee?
- What happened?
- She got hospitalized...
in the middle of a shoot due to overwork.
- When did that happen?
- Early this morning.
Why do you think I'm telling you this now?
You must not visit her at the hospital.
Reporters are literally
camping out at the hospital.
Just send her some flowers instead.
Get Ho Jin to arrange it.
Get it delivered there.
Young Bin, Young Bin.
Both you and I know that you like her.
But other people can't know about it.
It cannot get out of this circle.
It's our secret. Got it?
- Yes.
- Got it.
You saw how the director
treated Ha Neul, right?
You can't afford to be distracted.
You must focus on work, okay?
Just think about the film.
Don't worry. That won't happen.
Okay.
- Hey, order more food.
- Okay.
- What do you want to eat?
- Tenderloin.
- Turn the grill on.
- Excuse me!
Joon, Joon.
- One more serving of this, please.
- Sure.
- Not this one.
- Then what is it?
Listen. You have to keep a
watchful eye on Young Bin.
Do not let him visit
An So Hee at the hospital. Got it?
He'll probably go, though.
You know how Young Bin is.
- That's why I'm telling you this.
- You're right.
Think about it.
A girl  he loves is hospitalized.
How would he be feeling right now?
I'll start crying the minute I
hear that my wife is hospitalized.
I'll do my best to stop him.
Actors are not exactly the
most stable people, you know.
They get serious mood swings.
They're moody and sensitive.
They can be blunt, too.
They let it all out, and
that's when things blow up.
Hence, you have to coddle and
treat him tenderly at all times.
- I will.
- Also, you have to call me...
and let me know right away if
he has any dinner meetings.
I didn't think that meeting with
Ms. Kang would be a problem.
Do you want to switch to
the rope she's holding?
That rope is rotten.
Mr. Kim. You're having problems with
Ms. Kang, aren't you?
There are no problems.
It's just a power struggle.
Even animals fight for hierarchy, you know.
Whenever you talk about her, it
sounds like you really hate her.
I don't hate her.
You know that she's my mentor.
She taught me how to do my job...
and groomed me.
She even made me the co-CEO,
so I'm grateful for her help.
I know how to be grateful, you silly.
- Why are you chuckling?
- Sorry, don't mind me.
Goodness. You should learn
from me, all right?
I'm such a great textbook.
Anyway, I'm going to...
kill you if you stab me in the back later.
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
What's keeping you so busy?
You don't even get jobs because
you're not a good lawyer.
I just want to ask you something.
You know that my agency
is incorporated, right?
What can I do to dismiss the co-CEO?
I see.
What is it?
I'm asking just in case.
Just in case I need to know.
- Yes, go ahead.
- Shall I learn from this?
That's correct. We co-own the agency.
That's his game plan.
Look at that. This place
is filled with reporters.
I see that.
Anyway, Mr. Kim practically
begged you not to visit her.
If he finds out about this, I will...
He'll strangle my neck.
You know that I can keep a secret
unlike you. I won't tell him.
There are so many reporters here.
How will you go in?
Do you have any ideas?
I'll think of something.
Let's just send her flowers.
Flowers?
- Are you feeling better?
- Yes, I'm fine.
I didn't really have to get hospitalized,
but people at my agency
made a big fuss about it.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Young Bin ordered flowers
to be delivered to you.
Really?
I don't think I can get deliveries
here because of security reasons.
The delivery guy probably
left it in the lobby.
Okay. Tell me that I said thanks.
All right.
Come in.
There's a delivery for you.
Who are you?
- It's me.
- You totally surprised me.
How did you get in here?
No one is allowed in here.
It was like shooting an adventure film.
I came in through the back door
and gave reporters the slip.
Then I had to show
my face to the staff here.
I took photos with them and
gave them my autograph.
You could get into deep trouble.
What is all this?
You bought a huge bouquet.
I heard you're sick and got worried.
Goodness.
Why did you faint like that?
Well, I thought I was taking
good care of my health.
Hey, I've never gotten
flowers from a guy before.
Oh, my.
You should've asked your boyfriend for one.
Ha Neul and I broke up.
Why?
No specific reason. It just happened.
Are you all right?
In what way? Health-wise
or about the breakup?
Both.
I feel fine physically,
and I'm sure I'll be fine
with other things, too.
I see.
By the way, don't you have to get going?
I know that you're busy.
I'm technically unemployed now.
I'll get going so that
you can get some rest.
Ho Jin is waiting for me in the car, too.
My gosh. He called me and
pretended to be elsewhere.
I must say, he has become a real manager.
Hey, he got a promotion.
- He got a promotion?
- Yes.
Then we should grab a drink
and celebrate together.
Shall we grab a beer?
I really want to drink now.
Let's get together for drinks
when my drama is over.
Why are you talking about drinking?
You're sick.
Hey.
I haven't had any drinks
in such a long time.
I've been staying away
from drinking lately.
We'll go out, right?
I should get going now.
Stay a little longer. I'm bored.
- I'll be back tomorrow.
- You're sure, right?
- Just stay in bed.
- All right.
- Bye.
So Hee.
I have something to tell you.
Gosh, you startled me.
You took longer than I thought.
Did you see her?
Yes.
You're really something.
How is So Hee? Is she all right?
- Yes, she's fine.
- I'm glad to hear that.
By the way,
I told her how I feel about her.
I see.
What?
(NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW)
Isn't that the child actor?
My performance will make you admire me.
Hey, let go.
- You said it was okay.
- I thought it was okay.
What's he doing? Is there something
I don't know on his schedule?
What is this every single time?
We have to lie and inconvenience people.
Is there something going on with
Mr. Cha Young Bin?
Is he seeing someone or what?
Get out!
All right, guys. Keep fighting.
- Do it in the car.
- Hey!
- Hey.
- What?
I'm so distressed because of a blockhead.