(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
(PASSENGER TERMINAL)
(EPISODE 14)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What is this?
- Hello?
- Did you receive a call from Soo Ah?
About what?
You wouldn't come even if I asked you. Would you?
I'll be there.
That's why family is more important...
as you age.
I hated your father so much...
but I'm glad I stuck around.
Thanks for the food.
We need to talk.
You don't have anything to do at home, anyway.
I have to rest after my overnight flight.
I have decided to live elsewhere.
I'll give this house to you.
Give me the deposit from your house.
I'm moving to New Zealand to live with Jin Sook.
So bring in all of your family from Jeju Island...
and live here together.
They can move in after the reconstruction.
Hyo Eun would be finished with high school by then.
No, right now.
Captain Park, don't you get it?
Why do you think Soo Ah is...
all the way in Jeju Island after quitting her job?
Is it because of Hyo Eun? No.
Soo Ah is living away from you.
She knows.
She knows about you and me.
I didn't want to live with her, either.
I was thinking that this was perfect.
You don't want to live with her?
Are you two getting a divorce?
My goodness. Not everyone like us gets a divorce.
People just live like this.
She just needs some air...
until Hyo Eun gets into a dorm.
Hyo Eun isn't going to an international school.
She's going to a local school.
How did she get in?
In just two days?
It doesn't happen that easily.
You managed to send her to Malaysia in two days.
You like it.
Don't you? You didn't want to live with me.
She knows. She knows about you and me.
Are you scared that I'll be back so soon?
Choi Soo Ah. That's why you were so confident.
Hello. I'm Annie's mum.
I want to make a visit. Are you home?
What's with her?
Where are you?
I called ahead to say you're coming.
You'll be expected.
We owe the person a lot.
Your visit is very overdue.
Hye Won.
Hello?
She'll make a comeback with Mi Jin...
if I bring up Hyo Eun's school.
- Hello?
- Hello.
We met briefly in Sydney.
I'm Annie's mum.
I just caught your text. I was busy.
I have to show you our gratitude.
You said thanks last time.
If you showed your gratitude to my wife, it's done.
This is something my husband and I are thankful for.
Your wife treated...
my mother-in-law before she passed away.
How are they acquainted?
It's an uncanny relationship.
I couldn't believe it, either.
Thanks for the thought,
but my wife isn't home.
I know.
But something just came up for me, too.
Only Doh Woo will be there.
Who?
My husband. Suh Doh Woo.
Your husband must be very loving.
You can just take what we have prepared.
Please open the door for him. Goodbye.
My gosh. This is annoying.
Who is it?
Someone very thankful.
The person who bought your mum...
patjuk before she died.
(ON THE WAY TO THE AIRPORT)
My house is such a mess with my wife and my child gone.
She left this on the veranda.
It's as good as hiding it.
Before my mum died,
your wife treated her with food.
I'm sorry to visit you so late.
Oh, I see.
You should've said he couldn't keep a family.
That he will even hate me for breathing and walking.
Just as he dated me when he was with you,
that he will continuously be having affairs.
That I won't be a part of his life very soon.
Why didn't you tell me? Why? Why?
Goodbye, then.
You should put this somewhere you can see well.
Isn't it odd?
I guess you two had a fight...
about who should come over.
I'll tell your wife you were nice...
if she calls me again.
But...
you shouldn't let her have her way all the time.
It'll never end.
Excuse me.
Where are you?
I can see you.
How was that?
You probably couldn't say or do anything.
Why do you have to be like this?
Why does someone like you have to live like this?
Do you know why I went to Jeju Island?
I went there to give you a divorce.
The divorce that you wanted so badly.
Is that his wife or a girlfriend?
Can you go fight somewhere else, Doh Woo?
Do you know...
a man named Suh Doh Woo?
Your wife helped him out a lot.
Doh Woo was grateful.
Can we call this a marriage?
She was having a long and serious conversation...
with a man on the plane.
Can we call ourselves a married couple?
Get yourself together before you ruin your family.
What am I to you?
Some coincidence, right?
What kind of bad joke is this?
It doesn't make sense.
It doesn't.
You saw him yourself.
He looked happy, didn't he?
That man...
has no idea what kind of life his wife is living.
You have no chance against him.
I don't want him to hurt you.
You're still my husband.
I won't let you be despised by anyone.
Why does it have to be like this?
This isn't why I wanted to give you a divorce.
You're worrying about her right now, aren't you?
You probably think I showed her contempt.
I did. She received that from me.
So what?
It doesn't matter any more.
I don't want you to be put in the same spot as her.
I can't take it any more.
Get it together, Doh Woo.
Ms Hong found out about everything.
Like she always does.
She could erase my existence with a single phone call.
So I went running for you.
Only to find...
her.
Hyo Eun's mum.
I...
How dare you open the door?
Go.
Go!
I said she'll haunt you for the rest of your life.
That's what I told her.
After I finished school and gave birth to Eun Woo,
we stayed together for just two days.
It's the first time, isn't it?
I'm finally speaking my mind.
I gave birth to her out of love.
But when I did,
I got scared.
People told me she'd be my life,
but that wasn't the case for me.
I felt like it was the end of my life.
I couldn't even talk to my mum about it.
I was very depressed.
That's when Eun Woo's dad said...
he would raise her.
He said I could forget everything if I wanted.
I agreed right away.
My job helped me forget everything.
That part of my life was...
completely erased from my memory.
When Eun Woo's dad was diagnosed with cancer,
he said he had a 50 percent chance to live.
I was just starting my dream job...
working for Ms Go.
"Why now?"
I blamed him.
Then something amazing happened.
When I met Eun Woo for the first time,
you came up to me...
and said hello.
Hello.
Who is she?
That day,
I remembered a part of my life...
that I thought was gone forever.
She's my daughter.
I regretted that I told you she was my daughter.
I knew you still would've accepted me. I regretted.
But...
Now that I think of it,
I think it was the best thing I did for her,
to call her my daughter.
You're right about me.
I'm always anxious and impatient.
I'm always desperate for something.
From now on,
I'm not going to live like that.
That is why...
I'm not going to ask you to stay.
I won't do it.
It's what you need to know about running the gallery.
This is information regarding the old house.
There are yearly inspections, so keep that in mind.
There's an evaluation once every 10 years,
but we don't have to worry about that.
(LAW FIRM MOONSUNG)
These are the divorce papers.
I know it's too late...
for me to say this,
but thank you...
for looking after Eun Woo.
Call me whenever you're having a hard time.
I actually will.
And take this.
It was in Eun Woo's treasure box.
If I remember correctly, it belongs to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry this happened to your mum and dad.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(DOH WOO)
There was someone Eun Woo wanted to protect.
I now know exactly who it is.
It was you.
You're so clumsy.
Do you know what I'm really scared of?
Not being able to protect something precious.
That's what I'm really scared of.
What happened? Why did you walk so much?
What is it?
There were things I was determined to do...
once Hye Won and I...
got a divorce.
But now that we got a divorce,
I'm really dumbfounded.
Are you two over?
My feelings are everywhere now.
I think I'd be happy if I do this.
I think things will be better if I do that.
I think something would make me sad.
But once I do those things,
they feel all different.
I wasn't expecting...
to feel like this right now.
I'm not sure...
if I could ask Soo Ah...
to feel this way.
I thought I'd never get over him.
He was my first boyfriend and I was young.
He treated me like trash and I let him.
You broke...
that vicious cycle.
You must've been so thankful.
But you looked like me...
when you came back...
from your maternity leave.
Jin Seok received a text once...
and it was a picture.
A picture he took with a junior of mine.
After that, I never go near his phone again.
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to stay with Jin Seok at that time.
At any cost.
Didn't you even fight with him?
I didn't.
I was afraid...
that he'll leave.
Your song became my song.
What will I do?
What should I do?
How dare
I say
That I love her?
What will you do now?
I'll stay here with Hyo Eun!
Will Doh Woo get divorced?
His wife saw me.
She wouldn't let him.
Doh Woo...
won't get a divorce.
You never know.
Her pride may have been crushed from seeing you...
and she may just divorce him.
What about you?
Can you divorce Jin Seok?
That means you'll stay here...
regardless of Doh Woo.
I will!
I'll live here happily ever after with Hyo Eun!
Soo Ah, you're awesome!
I've always been awesome.
You're still Jin Seok's wife.
I won't do that any more!
- All right!
You're so awesome, my friend.
You're home.
Where's Hyo Eun?
She's asleep.
That's a relief. Thanks.
No problem.
Look at you two. You're both single.
You two should go and grab a drink.
A drink? No thanks. It's too late.
You should go.
Get her.
I called her here for you.
It's okay.
Hyo Eun didn't even wake up once.
Thank you.
You should pick up Mi Jin tomorrow.
You can spend some time with her on the way over.
Okay?
Okay.
You heard me...
talk to Mi Jin on the phone, right?
She didn't do anything wrong.
I blamed her for nothing.
I'm leaving.
Thanks.
Where are you?
I'm at Hyun Woo's.
Do you remember...
when I said this...
on the phone?
"I'm not sure if this will comfort you."
I'm not sure if this will comfort you.
But my daughter loves it there.
She won't even call.
She doesn't even want to come to Korea.
That does comfort me.
That was the first time you comforted me.
When's the second time?
"That's the best compliment I ever got."
When your concerns melt away...
with a breeze of wind, and you begin to think...
"There's nothing much to life."
"I just have to enjoy each moment."
It's a moment...
when you are energised.
You are like that moment, Doh Woo.
That's the best compliment I ever got.
I remember. You told me that.
When's the third time?
Do you remember Seoul in November?
It's when we wrap things up.
It's the season when you cannot carve up...
the courage to do anything new.
Don't come back.
You must have been...
really confused there.
A little bit.
What you have on your mind right now...
may be right.
This is a special place.
That's where your everyday life is.
Whatever you feel there and your confusion are...
probably right.
It's probably not because...
it's the lonely November.
Doh Woo.
I'll be fine so...
That's why...
you shouldn't come back.
To be honest,
I met your wife...
a few days ago.
I know.
Me too.
I saw how you left my mum's work in the veranda.
Were you at my house?
Things just happened.
I met your husband.
Don't worry.
He thinks that I came by to say thank you...
for giving my mum patjuk before she passed away.
What do I have to do...
to make this...
less of a struggle for you?
I don't know if you'll feel any better,
but as of now,
that's all I'm thinking about.
Looks like it didn't work.
We should talk more when I get there.
This time, I'm really leaving the day after tomorrow.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(RECRUITING STAFF FOR WORKING ABROAD IN OAKLAND)
Mum. You should go to Jin Sook.
The faster, the better. Leave tomorrow if you can.
Tomorrow? That's such a short notice.
I'll get you the tickets.
Wait for us. I'll take Soo Ah and Hyo Eun with me.
I'm trying to help you.
Sure. If that's what you have to do.
This is too much labour for you.
It wasn't this bad when you were a flight attendant.
I carried heavier things when I was a flight attendant.
You have to be strong to work as a flight attendant.
We should reconsider living here.
Why? There's no need.
Mi Jin looked nice and dressed up working there.
I've still got it, you know?
I'm fine. I could even work double shifts.
Bye.
Give me a moment.
Sure.
Doh Woo went to Seoul to get a divorce.
Turns out Annie's mum lied about raising Annie.
When he found out, he was devastated...
and they eventually broke up.
Simply put, they weren't going to work anyway.
Your thing with him had nothing to do with it.
I thought you should know.
I know you're not doing this because he just broke up.
That I know for sure.
You had reasons to do what you did.
I can guarantee that.
You worked hard all your life.
Choi Soo Ah.
This is the beginning.
Don't lose control.
Focus on yourself.
Did you come alone?
I'll tell you the day after tomorrow.
It's the day after tomorrow for sure.
So that's why...
he said, "the day after tomorrow".
We have a lot of time before the flight. Relax.
Okay.
When's your next day off?
Never. I used them all.
Can I see you in Seoul when you're free?
Kevin, you're a good guy.
You deserve someone nice.
I do.
I like a woman who trusts herself to be nice.
Give me a call whenever you feel like that.
This is the view I see every morning.
I timed the picture for the sunrise.
It's for you.
Don't worry about Mum.
I won't treat her as a stranger.
When she meets someone else,
then we'll be like strangers.
Even I know that.
Your mum will be...
truly happy from now on.
Keep watching her closely.
(HAN RIVER WATERFRONT)
Cheer up. The sky is beautiful.
I have so much to say.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Stop doing that with your chopsticks.
It's fine.
(CAPTAIN PARK)
Cheers.
What's gotten into you?
I saw your sister in Jeju Island. We made up.
I thought of you while I was there.
Consider yourself lucky.
I'd prefer money over food.
I wanted to drink.
Is this...
I'm just asking to make sure.
I have many older women lined up for me already.
I'm sorry, but the line is full.
I still remember when you got sent to the army.
You're all grown up now, aren't you?
Cut it out. There are people here.
You're stronger than you look.
I have a crush on someone.
Who is it?
There's a guy. He's nice.
What's the problem, then?
He knows me too well.
I want someone who knows nothing about me.
I'm tired of explaining and making excuses.
I had enough of that with Soo Ah.
You should look outside the country, then.
Knowing too much can never be good.
Eat up.
Excuse me, can we get two more servings?
Are you sure you can finish all that?
Of course.
Don't you ever get any sleep, Jin Seok?
Why do you keep calling me all day?
You should've answered, then.
What is this?
Where have you been?
I went to see Soo Ah.
What did she say?
What does she have to say about us?
- Did she get angry?
- She did.
She must have been angry at you.
She got backstabbed...
by someone she trusted.
Let's make some things clear.
I'm best friends with Soo Ah.
You're just some guy I no longer have feelings for.
We're just colleagues now.
Did I make it clear enough for you?
You should go. I need to get some rest, Captain Park.
Clear enough, my foot.
Did you see Hyo Eun?
Yes.
I saw your daughter, Captain.
The girl who goes to an international school?
- That's...
- I'll check for myself.
Suh Doh Woo's wife called me yesterday.
Why are you so shocked?
You jumped more than when I asked about the school.
I didn't. Why would I?
- Why?
- She just called.
Suh Doh Woo came over...
to my place.
He came by?
He came to thank me.
He came by. In person.
The fling between you and I...
was actually nothing...
compared to this issue.
- Jin Seok.
- What I've been imagining for days...
Is it true?
How many times...
did they thank me?
They thanked me because Soo Ah delivered something.
And because she bought...
the lady patjuk before she died.
Isn't that a bit too much?
Suh Doh Woo.
Suh Doh Woo!
Why do I keep hearing the name of a man I don't know?
You.
Tell me everything.
Everything you know.
Tell me everything...
like you told her about us!
Why do you live with Soo Ah?
You don't care about her.
She's a wife you don't need.
You date other women.
Soo Ah...
and Hyo Eun are doing well in Jeju Island.
Nothing happened until I confirm it did.
Unlike someone else,
I wouldn't move to an island with my kid...
because my husband dated my friend.
If only she'd checked,
it would've all been a joke.
Right. A joke.
It's even funnier that we fought about it.
I want to erase that past.
I already did.
I'm sick of being stressed about dating the wrong guy.
I learned my lesson...
and I won't make the same mistake again.
You're still making a mistake.
Everything you do is a mistake.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I wonder if someone will visit today.
I wish we had visitors every day.
So you can stay at home.
See you later.
Why did she say that?
Could you please check again?
I'm sorry but we don't have...
a Park Hyo Eun registered at our school.
Okay, thank you.
Dad!
Did you see me score a goal?
- Yes.
- Wasn't I awesome?
Guys, this is my dad.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Dad.
Hi. This is my dad.
What a wonderful day.
What are you saying?
Park Hyo Eun.
I saw with my own eyes that you study here.
I don't believe what I don't see myself.
Dad, you see...
I'm sorry.
I begged her to let me stay here.
So all this happened because of you?
Do you know...
it's very bad to lie?
Mum said she'd tell you everything.
You should've visited a little later.
Mum went through so much because of me.
What?
Hyo Eun.
Dad's so angry that...
I don't think I should see your mum.
We'll only fight.
It won't be any fight.
It would be scary.
Why do that when you'll return to Seoul?
Pack up by tomorrow and...
By tomorrow?
That's too soon.
I bought tickets on a plane that leaves in two hours.
I said tomorrow out of consideration.
Okay. I'll ask Mum.
I'm not telling you to ask her.
It's a notice.
Say that word for word.
Okay, Dad.
Bye.
Be strong.
It'll be okay. It'll be fine.
He just left?
Yes. He gave us a notice.
I think we need to be prepared.
He's your dad. He used to adore you.
Did he adore me?
Of course, he did. Don't be silly.
It'll be okay. Don't worry.
Captain.
Why are you here?
I have to go somewhere.
Give me your phone.
Let's go.
(HYO EUN'S MUM)
Soo Ah might not be home if you don't call ahead.
Where else would a jobless woman be during the day?
She works for a daily wage.
She does that?
The women here are hardy.
Almost no one stays at home.
It's very natural here.
She quit being a flight attendant,
sent our kid to a local school...
and works for a daily wage?
Soo Ah.
You've gone crazy.
Let's go to the airport.
Okay.
You'll tell her I was here even if I tell you not to...
I won't tell her.
I mean it.
Why are you being sincere now?
I made up my mind when I saw how you looked at her.
Don't be so sentimental.
I saw her work hard...
for a daily wage.
She's still as strong as she used to be.
She's only strong on a plane.
Her sense of responsibility makes her strong.
She's actually quite frail.
She's torturing herself voluntarily, so let her.
For one more day.
It's me.
Did you call?
I heard you saw Hyo Eun.
Yes.
I'm sorry I lied.
I was going to tell you after you returned to Seoul.
It's not an excuse. I was...
I heard you found out about Mi Jin and me.
That's...
Let's call it even.
You lied about Hyo Eun's school and I didn't say...
I dated your best friend before our wedding.
We're even.
My discretion's in the past, yours is current.
I'm totally losing out,
but this is the last time I'll take a step back.
I'm at the airport now and I'm leaving.
Fly back with Hyo Eun tomorrow. Then it'll all be fine.
What about you?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
First,
I'll bring them back to Seoul.
Shall we ask for three days?
We don't have to go.
You can stay here.
I'll persuade your dad.
You said something when we returned from Malaysia.
You said my opinion counts.
That I should be able to take responsibility for it.
I'll think very hard about it.
It's nice here, but Dad found out.
I don't want to get you in trouble.
I won't be in trouble. Why do you think I will be?
Let's ask Dad for three days.
Hi.
Dad, are you in Seoul yet?
Why?
Tomorrow's a bit too soon.
I was wondering if you could give us a few days.
Come back tomorrow.
I returned from Malaysia in a hurry, too.
Because you just went on...
Three more days. Or just two?
I just need a dining table. That's all I need.
Doh Woo told me to look around.
Isn't that a bit strange?
- Give us time to...
- What?
Okay, fine.
Thank you.
Let's go.
(AIRPORT)
Are you back?
Can we meet?
Well...
My husband came by today.
He gave us an ultimatum. We must return tomorrow.
I should stay home.
An ultimatum?
Will you...
do as he said?
No.
I'll call you tomorrow.
You must be tired. Goodnight.
Don't go.
I won't.
Slow down a bit.
I brought you your car.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Mum, I finished my homework. It's free time now.
Okay.
You can rest now, too.
Rest?
Hyo Eun.
I'll just...
go for a short walk.
Suh Doh Woo, why are you here? Why?
Are you okay?
I think...
Well...
However hard I try...
However hard you try, you can't do it.
However long of a detour we make, we end up here.
Right here.
It just happens.
For you and me both.
I'm back.
Now, I feel at home.
(ON THE WAY TO THE AIRPORT)
You don't get it, do you?
Do you have the guts to come here?
I'm going to Seoul on the 11pm flight.
We can leave and return together.
I have to take care of this myself.
Right now,
I feel that our relationship...
is so cruel.
There's another thing...
I never tried.
Something I really wanted to do.
Whoever sees...
or knows...