However long of a detour we make,
we end up here.
It just happens.
For you and me both.
I'm back.
Now, I feel at home.
(ON THE WAY TO THE AIRPORT)
(EPISODE 15)
Captain Park.
All you needed to do was answer my phone call.
I don't even know where I am right now.
I just entered the first hotel I saw.
Whatever. Let's go to Soo Ah.
What are you waiting for?
We should stay here tonight and leave in the morning.
We're going now.
- I'll pick you up tomorrow.
- Give me the address.
- I'll come back in the morning.
- Now!
I have to go now.
Get some rest.
Should I pack these or not?
She says there's no need,
but this is the taste of home.
Hey, Jin Seok. What's going on?
What? You want to know Hyo Eun's address?
(DAEHEUL-RI, JOCHEON-EUP, JEJU-SI, JEJU ISLAND)
"Jocheon-eup. Daeheul"...
Is this Daeheul-ri?
Weren't you sad?
It felt cold.
My wife suddenly became someone else.
I was dumbfounded.
But I had this thought.
I just have...
someone named Kim Hye Won in my life.
She's not my wife, but not a stranger.
Just Kim Hye Won.
She probably won't be a friend.
She's someone I once loved...
and whom I lived with.
We parted after a difficult incident,
but we may be able to smile and be comfortable...
one day in the future.
All relationships form...
in different ways...
and they end in different ways.
I felt more comfortable...
after these thoughts.
Now that you named that relationship,
it sounds very special.
I'm sure your wife will be thankful.
I have to get going.
You're not used to this work.
I'm good at manual labour.
Stay for five more minutes.
Mum.
Where is she?
Where's Mum?
I think she went out for a minute.
I don't know why she isn't here.
She's probably nearby.
I almost believed you.
No. She never leaves me home alone.
I'm here because of the table.
Suh Doh Woo sent me here.
I like this one.
I already bought a table.
You didn't need a bed.
- Let's get a desk.
- I just need a table.
- What about a sofa?
You'll need much more than just a table.
That's all I need.
Hyo Eun, go to your room.
Go right now.
Mum, where did you go?
Dad, don't do that!
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry...
that we lied.
Go to your room.
I'm so sorry.
Will you go home like this in the dark?
You always walk this far away from me.
I can walk alone.
Go in.
Hyo Eun may be awake.
Okay.
(KEVIN)
Captain Park is at Jeju Hotel.
He's extremely angry.
I'll bring him over tomorrow morning.
Hyo Eun.
Mum, it's me.
Where are you? Are you with Dad?
Yes.
I'm going to Seoul with him.
Are you okay?
Let me talk to him.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Get away from Hyo Eun.
Choi Soo Ah.
Don't you get it?
You can say anything you want to me.
Apologise to her first.
Hyo Eun is scared.
Hug her and tell her it's okay.
Hurry.
- Choi Soo Ah.
- Wait there.
I'm coming.
Do you have the courage to be here?
I do. I don't care what you do to me.
It's time. Get up.
Here.
Where's Mum?
If we go back,
she'll have to come.
Okay.
When we get to Seoul,
I'll buy you a new flower pot.
Don't cry.
Okay.
Hyo Eun. Hyo Eun.
Soo Ah.
Where are you?
I have a few hours on me.
I'm going to Seoul on the 11pm flight.
Where's Soo Ah?
She'll come.
I'll leave Hyo Eun to you for now.
I have a flight in the afternoon.
Don't worry about here.
Go get some sleep before the flight.
I'll look after her.
I'll go to Jin Sook some other time.
You should go.
That'll make Soo Ah come back.
Without me here and you away on a flight,
Soo Ah will be back in no time.
Fine. I'll leave today.
Will you be okay by yourself?
I'm not a kid, you know?
You should get some sleep here.
You need all the sleep you can get.
Do you want me to make the bed for you?
I'm on the way to the airport, anyway.
Jin Seok.
I'm just saying this out of pure concern.
Don't address Soo Ah like a stranger any more.
I had to put up with it with your dad all my life.
Nobody talks like that any more these days.
This isn't my fault.
I'm not even slightly guilty.
All things aside,
be nice to her when she comes back.
I don't like it when you talk like that.
Is your husband always so violent?
Not at all.
Do you know what was the most foolish thing I've done?
Trusting everything Annie told me.
"I'm going to see Dad."
"Mum and Dad are like this."
I trusted all that.
He's not a violent man.
I'm not hiding anything.
He can be violent when he loses his temper.
I know he'll be that way when you go back.
He's not like that.
I've simulated this situation in my head many times.
The conclusion I got to was that...
this is a problem between me, Hyo Eun...
and my husband.
This is our family's problem.
I don't want to disclose everything,
especially to you.
I can...
work this out.
This is between my wife and me.
This is our problem.
No matter what we choose,
it will never be...
because of your fault.
I know what you went through...
back in Seoul...
before you ended up in this neighbourhood.
But I don't know a lot.
Am I upset because you didn't tell me the details?
No. It's already hard on me making second guesses.
If I know all the details,
we can't be together like this.
You don't know how thankful I am.
You went through everything bravely.
I want to do the same.
Don't jump to conclusions just yet.
I'll be back in no time.
Hold an exhibition here while I'm gone.
It'll only be a couple of days.
I think I'd better go to the airport alone.
I know the way.
I think it'll be better to say goodbye here.
I'll be back.
- I'll give you a ride.
- You don't have to.
There's only an hour and a half left.
What should we do?
What did we not do together?
We didn't get to do much together.
I beg to differ.
I'll make you a cup of tea.
It's a cup of tea.
It feels like...
the moment I just met your husband.
I couldn't say anything to him.
That's how I feel right now.
Helpless.
I...
How dare you open the door?
Leave!
I know that feeling.
It's cruel...
how we became like this.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
This is an argument, right?
This is our first fight.
We're not fighting.
You're not much of a fighter, are you?
Me neither.
For people like us, this is a big fight.
I fight when I have to,
but you can barely call this a fight.
I did something I never tried.
There's another thing...
I never tried.
It's something I really wanted to do.
I have an hour and 10 minutes left.
I just want to walk...
all the way there.
Holding hands.
I don't care if anyone sees...
or walks by us.
Whoever sees...
or knows...
(DOMESTIC DEPARTURES)
(RECRUIT NOTICE FOR EMPLOYEES TO WORK IN AUCKLAND)
Hyo Eun, stay warm.
The weather is cold.
My gosh.
My dear child.
Come visit quickly.
- Come and visit.
- Yes.
- You can do it.
- I can do it.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Grandma.
I promised something with Mum.
Yes?
I promised to think it through...
and decide where I'm going to live.
She went through a lot in Jeju Island because of me.
I will think it through and make a decision.
Soo Ah, are you coming?
Hyo Eun is alone.
I'm leaving to live with Jin Sook.
I hope you can come here with Hyo Eun.
Soo Ah.
Let's live well.
"Let's live well."
How do we live well?
Make sure you come.
(MESSAGE SENT)
It's my promise to return.
(EUN SARANGBANG)
- Are you open?
- Something like that.
What?
You can't open without a celebrating.
Should we throw a party?
No, thanks.
Fine. Whatever.
Why are you so late?
Uncle, you can't put everything in.
It tastes better this way.
You should've cut that kimchi.
- Just eat, okay?
- This is steamed kimchi.
Hyo Eun.
- You're here.
You should do this.
I've only cooked with pre-cut kimchi.
I can't do this with regular kimchi.
Move away.
Why? You were doing fine.
Don't stand around. You'll get in her way.
- Yes, Sir.
- Set the table.
Yes, Sir.
What is this?
It feels so familiar.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
Are you done with Jeju Island?
No. I'll go back with Hyo Eun.
Hyo Eun loves it there.
What happened?
Hyo Eun's grandma told me...
that you two will go to New Zealand.
She said she's leaving first.
No way.
No, we have to go back.
Should we leave tomorrow?
I told the school that you'll miss three days.
That's another candidate.
Seoul, Jeju Island and Aunt Jin Sook's place.
I'm going to really think about...
where I want to live among the three.
What is your criteria?
I'm thinking about that, too.
It's hard to choose.
Once you grow older,
you'll have to choose a certain shampoo you like.
You have to choose many things...
like clothes, work and people.
Make sure you keep your standards.
The centre needs to be you.
Not others.
I should be selfish, then.
It's...
a little different.
There is probably something that you are drawn to.
Close your eyes...
and imagine New Zealand, Seoul and Jeju Island.
Imagine them in your head.
Then your heart...
will lead you.
You'll be drawn to one.
Make sure you stay focused and find out.
If you ignore that desire, you'll ignore it for life.
I'd feel bad if it gets ignored.
Right? If you start ignoring that once,
it'll hurt...
right here.
But what if I regret later?
You'll figure it out then.
Everything has its ups and downs.
For now, focus on choosing.
Let's practise this starting now.
You'll know where you want to go.
If I choose something,
will you respect my choice?
Of course.
Let's all get along well.
- Yes. Be good friends.
- Yes.
You two should do a handshake.
You all are here.
We were about to leave.
No, don't worry about it.
May I join you?
You're all here.
Mi Jin.
You can join us.
Is that okay?
That can happen.
You don't see each other every day.
You two probably get along better.
That's the key. That's the best thing about this job.
I want a wife who just takes care of me.
When I go home, I want her to be waiting.
I tend to fly around a lot,
so I want someone with a more stable job.
This guy has a long way to go.
When she goes absent all of a sudden,
you'll get suspicious.
But things like that don't happen to us.
We only share 51 percent.
There's a little bit of trust...
and a little bit of approval of freedom.
So if Soo Ah were to seek some freedom...
I'd allow it.
Some fooling around actually keeps you going in life.
You're awfully generous.
Cheers.
I'll kill them all.
I will.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Soo Ah.
What are you lost in thought for?
Sometimes,
people tell you to think only about yourself.
Can you do that?
Are you kidding me?
The oldest kid here.
The second oldest here and the third one there.
And this place is for my husband and his family.
When I used to weigh 48kg,
that's when I only thought about myself.
"What should I wear? What should I eat?"
It was all about me.
Telling me to think only about myself...
is like telling the 48kg me to live my life...
taking care of everyone around me.
It'll be even harder than that.
My weight isn't the only thing I miss from those days.
I laughed and cried for myself.
All I had to care about was my emotions.
How light is that?
I miss that.
But life is strange.
Things go back to how they used to be.
When my children grow up,
the heavy weight will be lifted...
and I'll be that much lonelier.
Where are you?
I'm close to home.
You're by the sea, aren't you?
Yes.
I miss that.
You should come.
We can't always go back to what we miss.
Should I go instead?
No.
I'll be back soon.
"Where are you?" "I'll be back soon."
"When are you coming back?" "I'll be back soon."
You always say that.
Something came up.
Hyo Eun is trying to choose...
between her Aunt's place and Jeju Island.
At first, she was going to her Aunt in New Zealand,
but we changed our minds and sent her to Malaysia.
So that's why you were in a rush to find a homestay?
And that's why...
I guess so.
That's where the story began.
Doh Woo, do you remember my telling you about...
how I used to live in Jeju Island when I was young?
All I had was my family as a stranger to the new city.
I said I'd wait for my mum and dad...
on a field with nothing but telephone poles.
I can't remember very clearly,
but your neighbourhood reminds me of that.
Your house is in the background.
My brother, my parents and myself.
We're all playing together there.
It's strange.
I felt happiness and warmth...
just by being with my family.
I miss having a family like that.
If you miss something,
go back for it.
Touch it. Run for it.
We should live like that.
You have to go.
I'm not giving you any allowance then.
Study hard, okay?
- Okay.
- That's a good girl.
Hey, Soo Ah.
Long time no see, Jin Sook.
How are your legs?
I'm feeling all better with Mum here.
That's good to hear.
I have the utmost respect for you...
for putting up with Jin Seok.
Aren't you sick of him?
What's wrong with you?
Hyo Eun. There are football fields everywhere.
The first thing I checked out were the football fields.
It's everywhere.
Why are you hesitating when your dad will work here?
What? Jin Seok's going to work there?
Didn't he tell you?
He got assigned to Auckland...
despite all the competition.
He'll be working abroad.
He says he'll be living here.
Hyo Eun. Soo Ah.
Come join us...
and enjoy this luxurious life.
Okay, Grandma.
It's so pretty.
All your friends in Jeju Island...
are going camping together for the winter break.
You've always wanted to go camping in the winter.
Here is the text message.
Mum, I want to go to New Zealand.
That's where my heart directs me to.
Dad will be working there...
and you'll be a stay at home mum.
The whole family will be under the same roof.
What's wrong?
I just...
Sure.
Right. I respect your decision.
But can you give it another thought?
We left things behind in Jeju Island.
I gave it a lot of thought. I want to go there.
I'll give Dad the good news.
Welcome.
So far, I'm only getting a couple of visitors a day.
You'll be closing soon.
You're leaving in the afternoon? Change in schedule?
It's just that I finally have some free time.
I want to go on a trip before I start studying.
What time do you need to arrive at the airport?
5:30pm.
I'll tell Hyun Woo to pick you up.
Get something to eat before you leave.
Okay.
Bye.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Some man brought this with him for you.
Go around twice and...
Oh no. It unravelled.
Try again from the start.
First, I do this...
Like this...
The music.
Oh, right.
Sorry. Doh Woo only just called.
That's why it's so shabby.
I'm usually great at throwing parties.
Oh my. If we threw her a decent farewell party,
it might have overwhelmed her.
Then she'd miss her flight.
(CAPTAIN PARK)
Number one, I sent the plane tickets to your email.
Board the flight with Hyo Eun.
Number two, Jae Ah and I will...
sort out the house in Seoul.
The master bedroom.
Check the living room.
The house is nice and clean.
They're moving abroad...
and are in a hurry.
It's hard to find a house like this.
Can I see the child's room?
- Yes.
- It's this way.
It's spring over there, so I'll take my spring clothes.
Let's ask Dad to send us the rest.
Isn't this all a bit like how we rushed to Malaysia?
We left in a hurry and when we got back,
all our things had been moved to this apartment.
You don't have to rush to make a decision.
I thought about it a lot...
and I want to go quickly.
I want to start school, too.
This time, I'll be good and stay for a long time.
Hi, Soo Ah.
I can't talk to my husband.
He won't let me talk.
Just a moment.
I'm so tired.
- This is hard work.
- Take some multi-vitamins.
- It gets harder.
- Doesn't it?
It's natural.
Joo Hyun.
What did that guy say?
Don't ask.
Shut your mouth.
Captain Park.
What is it?
It's an emergency. Something happened to your family.
I'll call right back.
Go on inside.
- Okay.
- Goodnight.
Let's go.
- Sleep well.
- Goodnight.
The line is busy. Please leave a message after...
She got through, then.
Don't thank, apologise or ask for forgiveness.
I know this isn't something to say over the phone,
but I can't go with Hyo Eun.
I can't leave before we chat.
So what?
Will you send Hyo Eun alone?
That's why we need to talk.
- Talk.
- The thing is...
Why do you think I'm so kind?
I'm trying.
To be nice.
I sent a manual to make this work.
I could have chewed you out...
or done way worse than slam a rock on the dining table,
but I won't. Why?
Because we're family.
"Family"?
Yes, we're family.
After I had Hyo Eun,
we were almost never together.
Deliberate or not,
we took alternating shifts.
I asked myself something.
"Are you okay, Soo Ah?"
"Is this what you think a family should be like?"
"Is this okay?"
"Yes, it's okay."
"It will be okay."
I thought it had to be overcome.
I never considered it as a matter of choice.
- But...
- You will choose?
No.
It's something to overcome.
We're facing a crisis that any couple face.
You should apologise before asking for counselling.
You should kneel and beg first!
I'll beg. I'll do anything.
That's why we need to meet.
No. You don't need to beg.
You left Hyo Eun alone for a short while.
You don't need to beg for that.
Go to New Zealand with Hyo Eun.
Go...
and we'll talk there.
Nature and family is all we'll have there.
We'll have plenty of time.
I will make you go to New Zealand.
The real pain...
will begin then.
It reminds me of when we packed for Malaysia.
Hyo Eun.
Sit over here. I have something to say.
I haven't made up my mind yet.
About Jeju Island?
I'll talk to your dad first...
and then decide.
Okay.
Do you mind?
I won't be able to fly with you.
Is that okay?
It's fine.
Jeju Island is where you want to be the most.
Think about it some more.
The place I want to be at the most...
is beside you.
I really don't want to be away from you but...
Being beside you,
can I do that while we're apart?
It's hard to explain.
Wherever I may be,
my heart will always be close to you.
Yes. I understand.
Do you?
Don't you mind?
I don't.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
I'd been looking at this photo...
and thinking about Annie.
She lived abroad alone for so long.
Shouldn't you not be away from your mum and dad...
for too long?
Dad...
and...
mum.
I believe they love me.
It doesn't matter however far away I am from them.
Someone who was loved a lot...
can overcome whatever comes their way.
Doh Woo said so.
A dad is just a dad.
"Doh Woo" sounds weird.
My tongue slipped. He's just my dad.
You love me.
I know for sure, whatever others may say.
That's why I can be strong wherever I am.
I won't be upset.
I wait...
and wait...
and wait.
I wait and wait and wait.
We'll meet one day. Isn't that hopeful?
How did you manage?
When you dropped her off once or twice a month,
I wondered why you never once looked back.
See you later.
If I'd followed her in just once,
I wouldn't have left her alone...
in that desolate field.
Am I staying outside right now...
instead of going in?
Where are you hurrying off to?
To Seoul.
Now?
Mum, she's wearing your old uniform.
If you change your mind, call me any time.
I'll come and get you.
That won't happen.
I thought about it long and hard this time.
Tell me when you've made up your mind.
I'll respect your decision as well.
I'll be here with you always.
Hyo Eun's always with Mum.
Don't forget that and cheer up.
Shall we go?
Don't worry, Soo Ah.
- Are you comfortable, Miss?
- Yes.
Call me if you need anything.
I will.
(I'M FLYING WITH MUM.)
Me.
Let's think only about me.
Only about me.
Hyo Eun.
Hyo Eun...
(THE LAST EPISODE AIRS TOMORROW.)