Synced & ripped by cavo
Subtitles by VIU
(On the Way to the Airport)
(Episode 3)
Hello, everyone.
This is flight D720 from Kuala Lumpur to Sydney.
I'll begin the briefing.
I'm Park Jin Seok, your pilot.
My co-pilot is Kevin.
We have a full flight...
and a long flight time.
We expect a storm on arrival.
That's all.
Thank you.
I'll send a manual regarding Hyo Eun.
(Captain Park)
Welcome back.
- Were you waiting? - Of course.
Eun Woo.
I waited for you all night.
Did you bring her stuff?
Yes. Someone helped me with them.
That's so nice of them.
The home stay landlady?
Someone else.
It felt like a three-day flight.
Can we meet up?
As friends.
With Hyo Eun.
See you around.
She worked on it all night since you left.
She almost collapsed after she finished it.
Is that you, Doh Woo?
Yes.
Did you bring her home?
Seok told me all about it.
That someone packed Annie's things.
Yes.
What a nice thing to do.
Go and get some rest.
Did it rain?
There's a wet umbrella outside.
Didn't it rain here?
No.
Seoul's quite a large city.
You just got back.
Why didn't I think of that?
It rained somewhere else.
Like Incheon.
Don't come back.
No. I want to go home.
I did well. I can do well. I won't make a mistake.
Hye Won.
I promised my mum.
Throw everything away.
Will you go through all this with me?
Will we read her diary and wonder what to keep...
and what not to?
What if we find something hateful about me?
What if she wrote about me?
I wasn't that good a mum when I raised her alone.
I had her when I'd barely turned 20...
and I juggled work, study and childcare.
I took her to her dad then brought her back many times.
Each time we both cried our eyes out.
How can I live if she wrote hateful things about me?
You brought her back. Leave it at that.
It was never like this between us.
Please... I want to stop screaming.
Get rid of everything for me.
I need to make one thing very clear.
You raised Annie and her father neglected her.
That alone means you did your duty.
Maybe Annie did hate you.
She never said she did,
but even if she did, you did nothing wrong.
I know very well how you lived.
Stop talking about guilt.
You did nothing wrong. You shouldn't feel guilty.
- I will take everything away. - Leave it.
I want...
to go through it all.
I keep screaming and yelling.
What's wrong with me?
I heard that Soo Ah even irons Captain Park's pyjamas.
Men cheat on wives who iron their underwear.
She's the Iron Lady who gets walked all over.
Iron Lady.
What do you mean?
That's what the others are calling you.
Is that a compliment?
I do appear steely and stern.
It means you iron clothes.
They're talking about me, then.
They say you iron the hotel's pillowcases,
sleep on the iron...
and might murder your husband with it.
That's just scary.
Why do you have an iron in your bag?
Does anyone say why?
Doh Woo's daughter died in an accident.
No way.
Isn't that terrible?
The iron was his daughter's.
The landlady was about to throw everything away.
Goodness.
We should cheer Doh Woo up.
You haven't met him yet, have you? Keep the iron safe.
You can give it to him then.
We've met already.
How? When?
Well...
The airport, rain, early morning.
It was only a few hours ago,
but that's all I remember.
I only have really old photos.
(Hyo Eun's Mum)
I found a few photos.
Can you see me from where you are?
You must be able to see me.
You sent just what I needed.
There are so many nice photos.
They're just what I needed. Thank you.
She's the real deal.
She just kicks a ball around. She won't join a team.
That's not just kicking, that's dribbling.
She takes after us.
And to think that she loved anything pink a while ago.
She'd wear nothing but pink.
She loved ballet.
The football phase won't last.
Kids betray you all the time.
Look at me.
It would've been nice...
if you worked this hard when Mum was alive.
Not again.
She's watching from above.
That's what keeps me going.
She'd be pleased to see you with Hyo Eun.
Fine, I'll babysit.
She's my only niece, isn't she?
Thanks.
55 dollars a day.
And five for transportation.
I have to spend an hour on the bus and subway.
Pay in advance.
Throw in free football lessons starting then.
Okay.
Hyo Eun, start from there.
That's it.
There's no one here.
Hello?
Is anyone in?
Hello.
Why are there no lectures all of a sudden?
You had one every week on Wednesdays.
We don't have a set schedule.
Ms Go just teaches if anyone's there to listen.
Really? Only if she feels like it?
It was free of charge and spontaneous.
Can she do what she wants if it's free?
I can give you the number of another academy.
You have to pay but they stick to a schedule.
Must I pay to learn this?
Ms Go is a human cultural asset.
She taught those who were interested...
to give back to the community.
It's an experience, not a lecture.
Look.
I care a lot about class and virtue.
I value our traditional arts.
But this is just wrong.
Human cultural assets eat three meals a day.
You should stick to a schedule.
Giving back to the community is a given.
Nothing in the world is a given.
She did it out of goodwill.
I took time out of my busy schedule to come here.
How dare she complain that...
it's not a regular event when it's for free?
How could she say that?
People don't value what's for free.
Hello, Captain Park.
I see.
You arrived safely in Sydney?
Why would you call to tell me that?
What... What?
Come on!
Hello?
Yes.
- What? - Get in.
Okay.
That's them! Stop them!
Mister!
Captain Park, this is...
They only took your and Hyo Eun's stuff.
Move in with my mum.
Why? What for?
I sent you a manual.
Your mother died,
then New Zealand and Malaysia happened.
We need help to break the cycle.
We could've discussed this.
Did you discuss bringing Hyo Eun back?
You're lucky I persuaded my mum.
I'll put Hyo Eun on.
- Talk to her... - I'm busy.
You're drinking beer.
No husband is this great at solving problems.
Mother.
You will need time to adjust...
but so do I.
I need to calm my emotions.
Let's talk later.
I don't know where...
Leave me alone.
(Annie's Dad)
My mother did this.
I had nowhere else to go.
I'll leave in a bit.
Don't give me that look.
Half of it is pity.
Half is annoyance.
The one night I planned to stay in and rest...
If you feel like that,
my mother-in-law who spent her whole life caring for...
a family and finally thought she had time to herself...
must feel worse.
She doesn't deserve this.
Are all working mums like you?
What's so tough about it?
It can't be just me.
I told him to call Hyo Eun.
I wonder if he did.
(Captain Park)
Hey, I don't want it on speaker mode.
Your conversation will put me off marriage.
Okay, fine.
Hello?
Soo Ah.
Don't get the wrong idea. I'm with...
Say hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Captain Park must have left his phone behind.
Where did he go?
We're having a team dinner.
Hello.
Yes.
No.
I didn't get the wrong idea. Bye.
Hey.
Did they just giggle?
Did they?
It's not a team dinner.
What else should I say?
So why did you answer?
Why do you keep grinning?
Are you cool with this?
If I wasn't cool with this,
I'd have never met Chang Hoon.
Let's talk about this.
Where do you draw the line?
Say they're in Sydney.
You're right. That's where they are.
Are you okay with them drinking and chatting?
- Yes. - What about at the hotel?
We're at hotels all the time.
For conferences, too.
So a couple of hours is okay?
Because it's like a second office to us?
A couple of hours is nothing.
What about an all-nighter?
That's different.
Does that bother you?
That's...
If you're in the lobby,
couldn't a conversation drag on?
A couple of hours in a room is okay,
an all-nighter is not okay,
but anything goes if it's a public space?
Jin Seok married an amazing woman.
Your nonchalance comes in handy at times like this.
If we made decisions based on guesses,
we'd have split up long ago.
What's going on?
Is he cheating on you?
No.
Tell me if you heard anything.
I didn't hear anything.
Aren't you going home?
Next time.
I need to pack my things...
but I'm too tired to.
Your husband won't do anything stupid.
The young ones are captivated by his charisma...
and what not,
but they know he's yours.
They can't do anything.
Am I married to that great a guy?
Thanks for the reminder.
I hate you.
Bye.
Excuse me.
Synced & ripped by cavo
Subtitles by VIU
You must come here often.
I happened to find this.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I answered a call by mistake.
I didn't know whose phone it was.
- And... - It was from my wife.
Did I do something wrong?
Do you know who my wife is?
- Of course. - Of course.
Okay, then.
You can join us if you have the time.
I don't think this is a place for me.
I'll pay for you two in return.
Why are you acting so friendly?
Seeing him up close just made me really scared.
Thank you.
Have I done something wrong?
I just want to know what's wrong.
I met you by coincidence on my first flight.
Captain Park.
- Do you have anything to say? - You looked at me.
- You stared first. - I stared because you stared.
I'm sorry.
It's my first time in Sydney.
You're a good drinker.
I have everything.
We had fun that night.
How is work?
It's pretty tough, actually.
And the next day, too.
My seniors are scary, too.
- Third year is the hardest. - It's really tough.
Of course we talked about serious things,
difficulties about my career and my future paths.
Anyway...
Do you always stay in this room?
This room feels more like home.
I'm not sure if this is home or if home is my work.
I sometimes get confused.
I also learned about your loneliness...
so I did get to know you better.
Take the call.
I want to know what I did wrong.
(I want to know what I did wrong.)
Why isn't he checking his text?
My gosh, I was about to close.
- Are you closed? - I wanted to close early.
So that was earlier today.
It's only been 12 hours...
but it feels like a season has gone by.
It's only been a day...
but so many things happened.
We did talk. We talked about many things.
Some women believe they know a guy just because...
they talked to him and they bring him coffee.
That's the worse kind of women.
I want to ask you the same question.
Did I do something to lead you on?
I'm letting you off...
because you are my wife's junior.
People may catch you. So come out in five minutes.
Synced & ripped by cavo
Subtitles by VIU
- Good morning. - Hey.
Good morning, Captain.
Please.
Give this...
to the person who brought Annie's stuff.
Why?
Nothing.
People are...
all connected in special ways.
Thread by thread.
There is a reason why people come and go.
Relationships are very precious.
According to the manual sent by Jin Seok,
he wants us to stay here for six months...
and check on our basics again.
"Hyo Eun will go to a school nearby..."
He already transferred her nearby.
I have low blood pressure, so mornings are hard.
I'm dizzy.
I'm so dizzy.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hyun Joo?
- What? - Your body used to be so slim.
I hate how I was always conscious about my weight.
I'm living like this until I'm 48.
Why 48?
I'll be depressed when menopause hits in my 50s.
I want to prepare my body and mind for the occasion.
I always crave sweets in the morning.
I get so tired after sending off my three children.
I really need sugar.
Chang Hoon recently mentioned you, so I thought of you.
Did you move here?
No, I'm at my in-law's.
Is your mother babysitting your daughter?
- Just for six months. - And then?
That's not fair.
Everything will be fine if I just quit.
Why would you quit?
You're perfect for this job.
Why?
You're dull and simple.
And you're loyal...
and don't play any games.
There are many women in this field...
who just want to marry right.
I did marry...
the right guy.
You and I were very humble.
We didn't meet any guys outside.
We met our guys and got married at the airport.
My gosh, we were too humble.
I should've partied more.
Humbleness, my foot.
Do you have an occasion to visit the house by accident?
Are you watching me?
I am about to go there.
Let us talk.
Okay.
I'm nearby.
Can we meet?
- Sit. - Mother. I...
Do you two have...
anything against me?
It's not like that.
Sit down first.
Let's sit and talk it out.
And we'll make plans.
We should do that.
Mother, I need to run out for a second.
I'm a bit frustrated right now.
You're not the only one who's frustrated.
I'll be back soon. It'll be a minute.
What brings you here?
My mother wanted me to give you this...
for bringing Annie's stuff.
I thought it was my mother-in-law.
Wait. I have no reason to hide.
Here it is.
I can't take this back home right now.
My mother is home.
I don't think she'd be very happy...
if I went out to get a present.
Could I receive it next time?
Let's do that.
I don't mind.
I'm sorry.
The way you speak is rather catchy.
Do you want to hop in?
I can give you a drive if you feel frustrated.
No.
I'll take this.
I don't think we should see each other again.
Goodbye.
Okay, then.
Annie, right?
I feel really frustrated right now.
When I talk to him,
I feel sorry to my husband...
and the world. I think being sorry to them will...
give me the strength to carry on with this life.
This was an awful excuse.
Can I just go on a drive...
with your father like a friend?
May I do that?
Just one drive.
Synced & ripped by cavo
Subtitles by VIU
- Do you want ice cream? - Yes.
Okay.
I knew Dad wouldn't send me back to my old school.
He's quite a man.
Dad allowed you to come back.
Let's be less greedy, okay?
How was school? What are the kids like?
Hyo Eun.
This won't do, Mum.
Let's go back to Malaysia.
I liked it better there.
Can you ask Marie?
Don't even joke about that.
I'm serious.
They make me study so hard.
I can't even breathe.
Football club won't take me in, either.
You knew that when you came back.
Let's go back. It's your fault, too.
You should've persuaded me into staying there.
I will tell you one thing.
Your opinion will always be my priority.
That way, you'll learn what you really want...
and take responsibility for your actions.
Don't expect too much from a kid.
Park Hyo Eun.
What now?
Take your backpack.
I have to take...
Taxi. Taxi.
Mi Jin.
No, I wanted to ask you something.
Do you remember the beer place we went together?
What was it called?
What?
I want to go there with my friends.
I liked it when I was there last time.
You must be crazy, Choi Soo Ah.
Why did you come here?
What are you trying to do?
I made a promise with my mum.
I have to become successful in three years...
or I have to quit doing this.
She's giving me a hard time.
At this rate, she'll ruin our business.
We're just getting started. It's only been two years.
- What's the problem? - Everything.
I don't know.
Our first client in two years is my grandpa.
She's giving me stick about throwing a party for it.
You know how our family doesn't invest in small timers.
She says you and I are...
immature idealists.
I'm trying to make a name for the craftsmen.
I don't think our time together was meaningless.
I didn't start this thing for experience.
I wanted value in my life, too.
But I can't live like this.
Do you know how annoying it is not to get recognised?
Why do people mock me when I try to do something?
You're pathetic.
I'm sorry I'm pathetic.
I think someone's here for either one of you.
Who's that?
Do you know that person?
You said you were going, right?
I didn't say that.
- Who is that? - Where's my phone?
Where is it?
Who is that?
Hyun Woo!
Excuse me.
I don't have will power, but I have loyalty.
I'm always on your side.
Not Hye Won's.
Bye.
You can go up.
The ones from numbers 1 to 20.
Yes.
Here. This is it, right?
I wrapped them like this for Thanksgiving.
Everyone was asking me where I got them from.
They were very impressed when I mentioned Ms Go.
Isn't your husband doing business with Ji Eun?
Is something going on?
I don't know for sure, but it's not looking good.
They're only getting started.
It's been two years already.
They're looking like a charity at this point.
They should get their things together.
What about you?
Are you okay?
You took me by surprise when you said you'll marry him.
Then you revealed your daughter.
Do you remember how shocked I was?
And then...
Nobody understood you back when we were students.
I know you get things done by yourself,
but you can go easy on yourself at a time like this.
People are talking about you.
Tell me what you know about Ji Eun's business.
Hey.
- Tell me what's on your mind. - What?
You want to know what's on my mind?
I wouldn't be able to tell you.
I could never share my true feelings.
It hurts too much to even bring it up.
I'm sorry.
Let's just talk about work.
Come in.
You shouldn't be holding it around.
That gift.
Do you want a drink?
Sure.
I'm really glad you're here.
I had to deal with a problem.
My husband was upset about my bringing back Hyo Eun...
and moved our stuff to his family's house.
That's why you went to the wrong house.
I see now.
I've been wandering around ever since.
I really wanted to go when you asked to go for a drive.
But I didn't have courage.
Things are complicated.
I'm glad you're here.
Synced & ripped by cavo
Subtitles by VIU
This is strange.
I work, keep the house and take care of my kid.
Then I fall asleep.
Everyone else has it just like I do.
I don't know why it's so hard for me.
When I go on a flight...
to an unfamiliar city,
I go for a short walk.
The wind blows...
and my worries are long gone.
It makes me wonder...
why I was so worried before.
It helps me...
get back up on my feet.
It feels like that when I'm with you.
I was wondering what this was.
Now, I know.
It's the biggest compliment in the world.
Is he here?
I think I hear a phone ringing.
It's fine.
It's nothing urgent.
You came out for me?
Hey, Hye Won.
Call me your sister-in-law.
He's not picking up.
Is he upstairs?
Go on in.
Oh, I forgot the brochures.
I said it's fine.
(Hyun Woo)
Here you go.
Hey, Hyun Woo.
I don't know if I'm doing the right thing...
or going out of my way.
- If it isn't urgent... - Hye Won is here.
Come back whenever you want.
I think...
my wife is coming upstairs.
You should go to Hyun Woo downstairs.
What's all that? It looks good.
Here you go.
Hi.
I was just heading out.
How about some beer? It's a date after all.
I have to get going.
Okay.
Hyun Woo, a glass of beer to go, please.
I don't have any.
It's sold out already?
I'm good.
I'll take it then.
Doh Woo will cover it for me.
Take this instead.
When I go to an unfamiliar city,
I go for a short walk.
The wind blows...
and my worries are gone.
I'm Suh Doh Woo.
Nice to meet you.
It makes me wonder...
why I was so worried before.
It helps me...
get back up on my feet.
That's how I feel...
when I'm with you.
It feels like I'm breaking away from the manual.
You're just in time for the lunar eclipse.
It's all red.
You'll feel like you're burning up.
I feel like my body is burning up.
However,
nothing's happening to me.
(However,)
(nothing's happening to me.)
(On the Way to the Airport)
I went for a short walk in an unfamiliar city.
I'm done now.
You don't know what you're feeling now, right?
It feels much better to let it all out.
Is this how it's going to be?
Will we talk over the phone forever?
I wait and wait...
in the same place.
Can I...
see you right now?