Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Don't you remember me?
I was on the same flight with you when Mi Jin returned.
It was when you dropped your daughter off.
I was very foolish then.
I shouldn't have said things about Captain Park's wife.
I wanted to apologise.
I don't even remember it. An apology is unnecessary.
Finish up the inspection.
Okay.
Can we meet right now?
I want to see you.
(DO YOU WANT TO TURN THE DEVICE OFF?)
Annie was waiting...
for someone to come.
She waited at the same spot.
She just waited.
She waited...
at the same spot.
She just waited.
(ON THE WAY TO THE AIRPORT)
(EPISODE 5)
(PASSENGER LIST)
Welcome.
This way.
Welcome. This way.
- Welcome.
- This way, please.
Everyone has boarded.
No.
We have one last person.
Welcome.
Let me show you to your seat.
This way.
I came late to be on time for Doh Woo to be home.
I can't get a hold of him.
Is this important?
Can you tell me first?
Later.
Hello.
I really love this house.
I always loved this place since I was a kid.
You didn't have to come.
My headache goes away...
every time I come here...
and my heart can relax.
I always came here when I had a stomach-ache.
When I'd come and lie down,
you'd touch my stomach to make it feel better.
Then everything would feel all right.
Your hands have always been amazing.
Oh, wait.
Is your third child a year old now?
You're not even doing well.
I'm fine. I'm not here to say that.
The third son's eldest daughter will be a year old.
A seal case?
Is that why you wanted to see Doh Woo?
This is important.
We've been receiving support from this house for years.
You could've just talked to me.
You're overly loyal.
This is my real point.
Eun Hee, I want to stop Ji Eun and Doh Woo...
from doing their business.
Why?
I saw what they did,
and I thought I'd make it into a franchise.
I like where this is going.
Only Doh Woo can think of such a thing.
He brings together human cultural assets...
to mix their artistic abilities with practicality.
- It sounds great.
- It either grows naturally...
or dies out naturally.
They need some time to adjust.
You should just stand back and watch.
Of course. Doh Woo's on this.
- A brand?
- Yes.
Let's make this into a brand...
with Ms Go's help.
Doh Woo would most likely be the director.
I'm sending Ji Eun to Sydney for that.
There's an exhibition.
Ji Eun believes she's going there to stay low.
I don't get it.
What's this brand...
and what's with Mother's name?
"Let's make Ms Go popular."
"Let's make her name known."
That's all I know.
She'll get the specifics after she sees Doh Woo.
What is this?
She will tell these things through you from now on.
Me?
Yes, Sir.
May I ask for help...
in case of an emergency?
Of course, Sir.
Call me whenever you need me.
Excuse me.
Yes, Ma'am?
May I get some duty-free products?
Of course.
Will you give me a minute?
Could you give me a hand over here?
This may become a problem.
I can't believe I ran here...
in the midst of everything to see you.
How long will you be in Cebu?
I won't be staying. I'm flying back right away.
What time is the flight?
I'm not...
I can't think right now.
You do know that we're walking on thin ice,
right?
We should go back together.
I'll get going now.
Can I take a look at the passenger list for something?
2:30pm.
Did you know that person?
You were talking to him in front of the lavatory.
She's the father of my daughter's friend.
I see.
Did something bad happen?
You looked serious.
Can you go around with the duty-free cart?
Okay.
We should go back together.
He said we should go back together,
but I'm going alone.
The feeling alone of being together...
is becoming unbearable.
Are you going alone?
Hey. I'm going to Sydney.
You must not be doing it alone.
When is your partner coming?
Are you meeting him on the plane or when you get there?
You get to know too many secrets as a flight attendant.
I'm going alone.
I'm running a business errand for my mum.
How is Doh Woo these days?
I've heard the news about his daughter. Poor him.
He loved her so much.
They were really close...
even though they weren't blood-related.
Annie isn't Doh Woo's real daughter.
I know a single man when I see one.
I was right.
Don't feel too guilty.
Am I a bad person for saying that?
The number you have dialled is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
(AIRPORT)
Where are you?
I'm at the airport.
I've arrived. Where are you?
I'm at the airport, too.
I need to tell you something.
Where are you? I'll come to you.
You asked me to come with you and I didn't.
I feel like I broke a promise.
It wasn't even a promise.
It felt like things were falling apart.
I think I'm too old for this.
I can't deal with this.
I can't deal...
with my own emotions.
This is wrong. It's not right.
Are you done now?
No.
Don't come any closer.
I saw Annie.
I saw her after seeing Hyo Eun.
She was at the airport.
I bumped into this kid...
and she dropped a marble.
It came rolling towards me.
I couldn't stop her in time.
She jumped into the crowd and...
After I got on the flight,
I saw Eun Woo's name on the list.
Had I only stopped her in time,
I could have saved your daughter.
That thought alone made me feel miserable.
But it gets worse.
When I heard that Annie's not your real daughter,
I thought to myself.
"Maybe..."
"Maybe it's okay to feel less guilty."
"Maybe I can tell him..."
"that I saw her."
That's what I thought to myself.
I tried to rationalise myself with Annie's death.
That's how we met.
I've been trying to talk myself into this,
but...
it shouldn't be like this.
Ever since the beginning,
everything was...
Your everything was...
I can't deal with all of this.
I'm really sorry.
Watching the sunrise is a lucky sign.
Let's go watch it again later. Thanks, Dad.
Are you watching...
the sunrise?
You're back.
You're up early.
Come take a seat.
25 on language arts,
48 on maths...
and 77 on English.
I've raised two kids in my life.
This is the first time I'm seeing scores like these.
I can understand how she got low marks...
on language arts and maths since she's been abroad.
Even then, her English score is too low.
Didn't she go to an international school?
I'm sorry.
I lost sleep over this.
Go wash up first. We'll talk more after.
I've been working.
You do know that we're walking on thin ice,
right?
I'm not tired at all.
I'm fine. Please continue.
After all, you get a pay cheque every month.
That's my wish, to receive a pay cheque every month.
I'm just saying, you know?
I feel happy for you that you work.
Mothers are responsible for good grades in elementary.
You need to pay more attention to your kid's education.
You should check her homework, too.
I do try my best.
I'm sorry. What did you say?
What did you say your wish was?
A monthly salary.
I'll give it to you.
I'll give you monthly salary for the six months.
Give me your account number.
I'll wire it.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Let's bring up her grade.
You won't believe it, but I graduated college.
Grandmas need to step in...
to improve kids' grades.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Ms Go.
By any chance,
did Eun Woo mention her biological father?
I told her that she's good with her hands...
and she'd say she took after her dad.
- Why?
- The thing is,
Doh Woo went to meet her biological father.
How did he know where to go?
He dropped her off a few times before.
Eun Woo wanted to see him,
but Hye Won didn't want her to.
- That's why.
- And?
He couldn't find her dad.
It must've been the wrong place.
I doubt that.
- What are you doing?
- Kim Hye Won.
I guess so.
I guess you're right.
Doh Woo was at the wrong house.
He's really out of it.
My goodness.
Seok.
Stop going back and forth,
and just move in.
Why do you say that again?
You know Hye Won and I are on bad terms.
It'll cause problems.
I miss a house filled with noises.
Come and help Doh Woo.
You should settle down.
I'm sorry.
Dad, this.
My grandma gave it to me.
I always keep it on me.
She'd love to hear that.
I bumped into this kid...
and she dropped a marble.
It came rolling towards me.
Had I only stopped her...
in time,
I could have saved your daughter.
Everything is...
so overwhelming.
I'm sorry.
Shoot! Block it!
Could you pass it over?
Why is she already asleep?
Hyo Eun.
Go to sleep.
Okay.
(AIRPORT)
I knew you'd come here.
What brings you here?
I couldn't reach you.
I thought you'd be worried about Ji Eun's disappearing.
Did Ji Eun go somewhere?
She does that when she's in a situation.
I have something to talk to you about that.
Did you come all the way here to talk?
I don't usually do this, right?
I'm trying my best.
What is it?
I'm going to sleep over tonight.
Let's restore...
our marriage tonight.
Let's talk first.
I'd rather not.
I don't think you'll be very happy.
It's something you'd hate.
It is a bad timing.
Give me your hand.
You know about my dream.
It's returning Mongyudowondo to Korea.
What I want to do is...
to protect old values...
and make it more valuable.
Don't you ever forget that.
One day, you'll understand me.
Hye Won.
Yes.
Keep Hyo Eun's grades away from Mum.
Don't just sleep at home.
Mum's doing all the chores, isn't she?
Couldn't you hide a single test paper?
Yes. I will hide it as fast as I can from now on.
Also,
I arrived well.
- What?
- I arrived well.
Why? Was that weird?
Well...
You never told me these things.
So it's weird.
I arrived.
(SONG MI JIN)
Things never go well for me.
I had to go and ruin everything with Doh Woo.
Mi Jin, what are you doing?
What? Nothing.
I came without telling Doh Woo.
"My mum told me to end it with you. Sorry."
How can I say that?
Who is it?
Don't open the door.
He's insane.
- Who is...
- Ms Song.
It's us.
You had a visitor.
I remember Ms Choi talking about a beer place here.
Since when is Sydney famous for beer?
I wanted to ask her where it was.
I don't know. And don't go to such a place.
Your life will get messy.
Goodbye, then.
Why are you laughing?
Were you referring to yourself?
I remember you telling me something...
while you were drunk.
What did I say?
You said you met your ex-boyfriend at a beer place.
- I didn't.
- You do remember.
You were so drunk and told me everything.
He lived a third of the year at your house,
a third in another country...
and the last third...
with girls around the world.
Then he got married to your friend.
You said he's a jerk...
who gains self-confidence with the help of women.
Forget about my awful past.
Of course. I wouldn't tell anyone.
Hey, was that guy...
a flight attendant?
He wasn't.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Hye Won, are you asleep?
The day before yesterday,
I went to see Annie's father.
They said there wasn't anyone like him there.
How did you know where he was?
I gave her a few rides to go see her father.
When?
Which year? How many times?
What more are you not telling me?
I'm sorry I kept it a secret,
but she wasn't asking for much.
I respected her relationship with her father.
Why would you do that?
Why would you give her false hope?
How is that giving her false hope?
Do you...
really want to know the truth?
Annie had no idea where he was.
Because he is...
already dead.
What?
It's been a while.
I tried to hide his death from her.
I pretended like he still existed.
I know I was on bad terms with him,
but I never said a bad thing about him to Annie.
I told her he was a good person, a good artist.
I told her over and over.
Did she not know...
that her father was dead?
She didn't even know who he was.
I told you he left me after Hyo Eun was born.
He's not even worth mentioning.
If she didn't know,
why did she go there?
It was her imaginary place.
She always imagined his father.
Why didn't you tell me?
I told you we weren't together any more.
It was simpler that way.
If I told you, you would think I still cared about him.
I don't care about him.
When did he die?
Are you questioning me?
Annie is my daughter.
I want it to be over. Why can't you do the same?
Whom are you doing this for?
What good comes out of your knowing?
Are you doing this for Annie? Or me?
Or are you doing this for yourself? Who?
I wanted you to be Annie's only dad.
That's why I didn't let her talk about her real father.
She might not have liked that about me,
but I did it because I loved you.
And I...
still will.
I run away from what I can't deal with.
I ran away from him...
and I want to run away from Annie, too.
I can't live with their holding me back.
Let's not ever mention...
Annie again.
I've said this many times.
That before we started seeing each other,
I didn't exist...
in this world.
Hello.
Who's she?
Does he look like you?
- I have his eyes.
- Eyes? You have your mum's.
When I smile, I have her eyes.
When I'm feeling down, I have my dad's.
I have the exact same nose as him.
I can't believe there's a man out there with your eyes.
I'm jealous.
That was all in her head?
Either one of them lied...
or is lying.
(DESTINATION)
Where is the place?
(RECENT DESTINATIONS)
(TRY AGAIN)
(PLEASE TRY AGAIN AFTER 30 SECONDS.)
(HYO EUN'S MUM)
"Hyo Eun's Mum"?
Hello?
I thought you left.
I wanted some coffee.
I'm going to the gym. I'll get to work from there.
You got a call earlier. Who's calling you at this time?
The caller ID said it was someone's mum.
I've been in touch with the parents from Malaysia.
After hearing about Annie, they've been calling me.
It's Annie again.
You didn't even notice me when I was an intern.
You started taking interest after seeing Annie with me.
I guess I'll have to live with it.
Are you saying that...
I married you because of Annie?
Is that what you take me for?
I've had my eyes on you for a long time.
Your raising her alone was just an extra.
I wouldn't marry someone out of sympathy.
I know things are hard, but don't question my love.
Let's stop. I shouldn't have brought her up again.
One last thing.
Annie...
had always been grateful to you.
She knew that...
you gave up your life to raise her.
She didn't want to put you in an awkward spot...
which is why we kept the secret.
So don't feel too offended by that.
I think Ji Eun is...
pulling out of the business.
I didn't know how to bring this up...
and had been thinking on my way here.
We have to hang in there. Goodbye.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Did you call?
Did I disturb you or wake you up?
You called a married man in the middle of the night.
That's a no-no.
That's usually when my wife and I get busy.
Sorry. I'll let you continue. Bye.
Continue what?
I went for a walk last night...
and saw kids playing basketball.
The ball rolled over and I tossed it.
I was way beyond the three-point line.
I was 8m away.
I shot...
and it went in.
That's why I called.
Was that wrong?
No.
Where are you?
By the river.
On my balcony.
I can see the river from here.
What are you doing there?
It's my room.
Most wives live here.
On the balcony.
Can we talk face-to-face? I can come over.
Don't. I have to watch Hyo Eun.
The Han River's that way,
so let's say I'm facing you.
I want to be serious.
I heard your confession after all.
It's too much to handle alone.
Is it tough?
We talk to each other sometimes...
and talk about constructive things,
and just look at each other.
Is that too hard for you?
Your existence alone is a great help to me.
I didn't know that people could be so comforting.
I managed to comfort myself until now.
I was arrogant.
My mum once said something to me.
She said she heard it from her grandmother.
Shortly before someone dies,
they leave something behind...
for someone they care for.
Out of longing.
They somehow find a way to leave something...
they know their loved ones will need.
They sense something with their mysterious powers.
I felt like Annie was my own...
and she liked me, too.
When I fall in love with someone,
I go all-out.
Right before Annie died,
she brought us together...
with her mysterious powers.
How else...
could this happen?
The emotions that you say are too much for you...
I'm sorry,
but I need them desperately.
I can't do without them.
They're a gift from my daughter.
The wind's too strong.
Sorry. I'll call...
I'll call you again later.
The river?
The wind?
Are you still there?
- On the balcony?
- What?
On the balcony. Yes.
About Annie...
Thanks for putting it that way.
Do you feel a bit better?
Yes.
After I got back...
and told you it was too much,
I thought it was really over.
What is there to end?
Can there be...
such a relationship?
Do you think this is possible...
between a married man and a woman?
Is this even possible?
It is.
I believed it was impossible.
We didn't set out to do this.
It happened naturally,
and we needed it.
Now, we just have to make it possible.
But then,
it sounds fine in words,
but our emotions...
I feel guilty.
I'm not sure I can say...
it's fine or that it's okay.
What...
makes you feel guilty?
Looking...
and touching.
Wanting and waiting.
All because I said I'll fly with you.
Three No's.
How about a relationship with Three No's?
This will only make sense in a strange relationship.
Too much is too bad.
We need to lack something.
What shall we lack?
Wanting,
touching...
and leaving.
Would not having those three...
make you feel better?
I'll think about it.
There's one more thing.
Let's decide...
not to define...
what our relationship is.
We're not sure and let's leave it at that.
"I like you", "I love you",
"I hate you". We'll say none of that.
Even if we feel something,
don't speak of it.
Let it be vague.
Why?
That way,
it lasts longer.
That's oddly persuasive.
I'll think about it.
Let's talk soon.
What was I talking about?
What are you doing sitting there?
Let's do it.
The Three No's.
What that relationship is...
and why I must do it...
to keep seeing you...
I'd like to find out.
My mum told me to give you this...
for packing Annie's things.
Let's not want or make promises.
How will we meet, then?
We'll get by somehow. By crossing paths.
How do we get by by crossing paths?
I'm really curious.
What if we break the Three No's rule?
I'd like to find out.
Is that what you wear at home?
What that relationship is...
and why I must do it to keep seeing you...
Why I must do it to keep...
seeing you...
Why does this feel so awkward?
I'll buy you some homewear so you can rest.
Don't do that. Ever.
I can't rest at all here.
Goodbye.
Goodnight.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Ms Kim, this is too crazy.
Is it too crazy?
Have a look.
- Ms Choi.
- What?
Are you still asleep?
She's too busy.
Kids don't listen to their mums.
The grandmothers need to be in control.
I see.
Have a look.
She ate then had a maths lesson.
You need to consider transportation.
She can't reach English class in 30 minutes.
Also, Korean, English and maths must never overlap.
It's okay for above-average kids,
but stragglers will only get confused.
You're right.
I must face reality. Hyo Eun's a straggler.
I admire you so much.
Most mums find it hard to face reality.
What do you eat that keeps you so fit and smart?
You have amazing skin, too.
I drink gugija tea instead of water.
It's does wonders to your eyes and skin.
I only eat fruit for breakfast and anything for lunch.
For dinner, I eat vegetables of assorted colours.
It must be assorted colours.
Mother, what's this?
I often meet my friends near the old palaces.
There's culture, nature and good food.
I go there often and listen to lectures.
That's another reason I never age.
You shut herself in there whenever something was wrong.
Let's summarise the case.
She divorced as soon as Eun Woo was born...
and raised her alone amid much hardships.
Eun Woo's father died a few years ago.
According to Hye Won.
That's all true,
but Eun Woo got a gift from her dad when she was seven,
they exchanged letters, Eun Woo found out...
where he works and you took her there a few times.
That's according to Eun Woo.
Which is correct?
Either Annie lied about...
a dad who didn't exist...
or Hye Won lied about...
a man who is still alive.
Or neither of them lied.
Eun Woo really planned to meet her dad there...
and he really did die a few years ago.
Eun Woo really did not know about that,
but they'd promised to...
Whom did she make that promise with?
It only makes sense if one of them lied.
Rather than who lied,
I'm more concerned if I should...
even try to find out.
How are you, Young Ji?
I'd like to ask you something. Before you resigned,
you recommended Hye Won as the next intern.
I'd like to see her application form. Where is it?
It would be even better if you could send a soft copy.
(GO EUN HEE KNOT EXHIBITION)
How will we meet, then?
We'll get by somehow. By crossing paths.
Do you have a question?
No. I'll just look around.
Excuse me. Do you know...
Sorry. Could you come back in 30 minutes?
I'm still setting things up.
Okay.
I missed your call.
Did you get rid of Annie's things from the police?
Yes. You told me to.
Okay. Thank you.
You got my email, didn't you?
How dare you not call me just because...
you left to study abroad?
Yes.
Do you remember her?
Haven't you heard anything since you left?
Don't you know whom she married?
You'll be shocked to hear, then.
First things first. Where's her application form?
Where?
Oh dear. When will I go through all that?
Why are you here?
Is this a coincidence?
We happened to cross paths.
Is that really what happened?
What are you doing here?
I work here and sometimes...
Drink?
Is it really you?
The Three No's woman?
Doh Woo!
Let's run away.
- Why?
- Let's just go.
Do you know the way?
I don't care.
Why are we hiding?
We must.
Why? We have Three No's.
What did we do?
I don't know.
Why are we hiding?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(ON THE WAY TO THE AIRPORT)
Where should I go to cross paths with you again?
What do you think?
Do you trust Hye Won?
What did you want to protect so badly?
I will find out.
She was...
the last person your mum met.
Hyo Eun's mum?
Mum.
Why...
her?