Episode 7
- Drink.
- Let's drink.
Drink up.
Have some.
Oh, right.
What was the dance move we learned today?
Watch me.
I'll do my best.
You jerk.
Is it that hard...
to tell me not to worry and to trust you?
Is it really that hard?
I want to hear you say that. Even if it's a lie.
I can't trust myself.
I'm very worried.
I can't help being scared.
Ahn Soon Soo!
Is there anyone outside? Please help me!
You'll be all right.
Move the bed out of the way!
Her saturation is dropping and she is unconscious.
Hook her up.
Hook her to the tube.
She needs immediate attention.
Stay with me, stay with me.
Yes.
Her saturation is at 50%.
Prepare for the MP right now!
Yes, sir.
Open up her airway.
Where is the professor?
Is he on his way here?
We weren't able to get a hold of him.
You have to try again. Please, right now!
It's still dropping along with her blood pressure.
- Where's the professor?
- We just paged him.
I didn't get to tell her anything.
I should've told her to trust me.
I just...
mustered up the courage to tell her that.
How can she...
How can she go like this?
No. No.
- Soon Soo...
- Soo Hyuk.
- Soon Soo!
- Calm down, Soo Hyuk.
Ahn Soon Soo!
Soon Soo.
It's okay, Soo Hyuk.
It's okay.
Get up, you scum.
I will kill you. If it weren't for you...
If she hadn't meet a rubbish man like you,
she wouldn't have gotten pregnant,
and she wouldn't have died right after giving birth. You killed her!
She died because of you!
Get yourself together.
You will live even if you don't eat for days, but the baby will die.
I don't have the courage...
to go on living as if nothing happened.
For a while, you won't want to wake up in the morning.
But you will somehow get up, breathe and
start eating a little bit.
You'll then slowly get your senses back.
The baby will start smiling and
you'll start smiling, too.
That's what time does.
Soo Hyuk.
Go to the US.
You need your family by your side right now.
Go to them, recover fast and then come back here.
Hey, do you like...
Han Mi Mo?
Do you like Han Mi Mo,
who is dating your best friend Koo Hae Joon?
If you are curious,
write an article about it. If you want to see me go mad,
write an article.
And the first person who should know how I feel...
is not you.
Don't reach out your hands to me.
It makes me want to grab your hands.
(Hope Bank Book)
- What brings you here?
- Hae Joon.
- I am sorry.
- Don't do it then.
Don't get involved.
I am sorry, but I have to get involved.
I need to.
I like Han Mi Mo.
To be precise, I realised that I have feelings for her.
- So?
- So I am going to like her.
I am sorry, but I will be the bad guy.
Even if you will curse me and beat me, I will first get involved...
- and then get back to my senses.
- Just get your senses back now.
You are jumping onto us with a bomb in your arms.
You want to hurt everyone.
It won't end by just you becoming the bad guy.
When you get involved,
I will suffer, and Mi Mo will feel uncomfortable.
It won't be just you getting beaten up.
I will be hurt and Mi Mo, too.
If you get involved in the toxic love triangle,
Mi Mo will be frustrated, puzzled and hurt.
You shouldn't just jump in like this because you realised your feelings.
If you realised that you like her,
what you should do is...
what people call a one-sided love.
Watch her from a distance and groan in pain.
Rather than confessing your feelings and jumping in the game,
you should hope that the person you like...
can be happy with the person she loves.
That's what you should do.
It seems like you understood.
I will go now.
(Promiscuous Fish)
That won't happen.
I won't go through something so uncomfortable.
I will watch you and see if you're different from me.
I'm becoming more childish.
(Miss call from Promiscuous Fish)
Soo Hyuk.
Do you want to go somewhere warm and think about the rest?
Do you want to get some coffee?
Hae Joon has a gift with words. It's quite annoying.
Well...
I'm sorry. I eavesdropped on your conversation.
I must've gone mad for a while.
I wasn't thinking straight.
When I opened my eyes, I was standing in front of Hae Joon.
I said crazy things.
In Hae Joon's point of view, you deserve to be slapped.
But I...
want to give you a hug.
It's obvious how you must have felt to come all the way here.
I'm sure everything blurred out and you only saw one thing.
That girl.
You have to be in one-sided love because you realised it late.
Hae Joon could do that.
He's never gone for a complicated relationship just for a girl.
And he's never become lame for a girl.
He's never been heartbroken...
because a girl either.
I don't think one-sided love is the answer.
You never know whose feelings mean more...
to that girl.
(My Child's Hope Bank Book)
What's that?
- Hope.
- Hope?
It's my hope that someone will be happy.
For the past five years, this hope has been growing inside me.
Da Jeong.
Do you think I have maternal affection, too?
You've never even had a baby.
That affection doesn't come that easily, you know.
Gosh, so why do I get a pang in my heart...
whenever I see those two?
What is this feeling?
He must've been very lonely.
He must've wanted to be comforted.
That's why he just...
That's why he just fell for whoever he could find.
Yes.
That must be it.
Information about your appointment on February 11th.
Please go to the administration office...
on the first floor and follow the check-in procedure.
One is in London,
and the other one is in Milan for photo shoots.
Their schedules show that they have a day off.
And it happens to be on the exact same day.
Can you stop by my office in the afternoon?
- I have something to tell you.
- Wouldn't she go to see him?
- I must see you.
- To London?
No. They'll meet in a totally unexpected place.
Who wants to go? Raise your hand.
I'm going to say no.
I can't go anywhere this week because of the film festival.
I can't go either. I have five interviews scheduled.
Here. Me. I'll go.
Well, don't you have to go home early to take care of your baby?
I need to make money to take care of my baby. So work comes first.
Of course, I'll miss him though.
I'll miss hanging out with my lovely son...
who blows my ears out with his cries.
I can handle not seeing him for a week.
I'll squeeze myself into an economy seat for 10 hours...
to contribute to the continued success of the company.
You can't go.
You're supposed to work with me. You can't just abandon me like that.
No one else is available. Who else will go if i don't?
I'll go.
I think...
I need to disappear from someone's life...
for a little while.
I was thinking of blowing everything up,
including the story and you as well.
But I realised that...
I was too nervous to do it.
Tell me. I'm curious.
The woman of your love triangle.
Was she moved?
When you confessed your feelings to her in the morning?
Good luck with your work trip to Europe.
That's what you should be focusing on now. And...
thanks for not publishing the story.
- What's that?
- They're receipts for...
my things at the place you call our home.
Go and get refunds.
- Why should I do that?
- Then shall I do it myself?
I already embarrassed my face enough at our wedding.
I shouldn't have to humiliate myself again at the department store.
So let's live together without having to embarrass ourselves.
Living with you will humiliate me even more.
You're so below my standards.
Just settle down now.
Even if you leave me hoping to meet someone else,
things won't be like before.
Take a good look at yourself in the mirror.
- What?
- Your skin is starting to sag.
- I see wrinkles around your eyes.
- Goodness.
You even have a bit of belly now.
And your bottom is...
Goodness.
They're definitely not like before.
Come to your senses now, seriously.
Do you think you can live off taking photos in your bikinis forever?
The number of visitors to your site has dropped too, no?
- Are you done?
- Listen.
I'm just saying that living with a husband who brings you...
his monthly salary wouldn't be a bad thing.
Think about it. Getting a refund isn't what's urgent.
I'll think about it. I should settle down eventually.
But...
it won't be with you.
- You have nowhere to go though.
- Don't you worry.
There's someone who will welcome me with open arms.
Goodness! Who says you can come in?
I have nowhere else to go. You know my situation!
Then go to Mi Mo's place.
She'll be happy to have someone to check in on her every day.
She has Ppoppo! I'm scared of that dog.
Gosh, why are you scared of Ppoppo? He's so tiny.
He's so ugly!
Listen, Ae Ran. You. What did you just say?
You just insulted him.
Wrinkly things scare me so much! I get so anxious looking at him.
What if I get wrinkly like him?
You just wait.
I'm going to find and bring a dog that is covered in wrinkles.
Don't even try.
- Goodness!
- Gosh!
Here.
So? You really want to adopt a dog?
Well, I'm just saying it.
I know that Ae Ran has nowhere to go.
Gosh.
You're so sweet.
You're like an angel. You really are.
Well, you know. I used to be part of Angels.
Well, I'm going to use the washroom quickly.
Hurry. Your angel here doesn't like waiting.
Look at this. Why is this expensive scarf...
getting so much fluff already?
Hello? This is Lee Wook's phone...
Lee Wook's phone? I'm his wife.
Who are you?
I think you dialled the wrong number.
- Please check the number and...
- I didn't dial the wrong number.
I even know Lee Wook's resident registration number.
I see. Is that so?
You know his resident registration number?
How much did you pay to buy the number?
People who do voice phishing are so rude these days.
Is this a new tactic?
- You!
- What?
Listen. Today is your lucky day.
I want to teach you a lesson, but I'll be nice to you today.
Why don't you get some help if you want to find a husband?
My friend owns a matchmaking company.
Why did you turn off your phone?
Well, I...
I must save my man.
Dong Mi.
Can't you smell something?
Well...
This?
Yes, it smells delicious.
I haven't even met him, but I smell Bang Dong Bae from this guy.
From what I gather, I think he is...
a scammer. He's a swindler.
- What?
- Be careful.
If he started talking about money and even mentioned specific amounts,
the relationship will likely end at a police station.
Goodness. Do you even know anything about Wook?
He's going through such a rough patch right now.
I'm sorry, Dong Mi.
I lied to you.
I actually...
have kids.
I have a son and a daughter. That phone call...
was my ex-wife calling to threaten me.
She wants money for raising the kids.
I'm sorry. I was scared you might reject me...
after finding out about my kids.
I wanted to be with you,
so I chose to lie.
The amount the course decided on...
is 1,500 dollars a month.
But my financial situation isn't ideal at the moment,
so I couldn't pay her for three months.
And my ex-wife is furious now.
I'm selling whatever I can on the second-hand shopping site...
and trying to figure it out, but...
And I asked for a 30-dollar discount.
I'm...
so stressed out these days.
If I give her all the money, I may have to live on instant noodles.
Nowadays, extracurricular education expense for kids is so high.
My heart aches every time I think about them.
If you don't think you can handle it,
you can leave me.
Dong Mi.
He said that he can let me go because he loves me.
Do you even know what that feels like?
That's how Wook is.
Goodness.
(Welcome to Brave Wedding.)
You are jumping onto us with a bomb in your arms.
You want to hurt everyone.
You never know whose feelings mean more...
to that girl.
Please have a seat here. The wait won't be long.
Thank you.
My life is difficult already. I can't raise someone else's kid.
It has to be someone who doesn't have a kid.
If he has kids, he better not have to raise them.
What? Love?
Listen. Marriage is difficult...
on its own with just a man and a woman.
I can't handle a man with kids.
It's a tough hike as it is.
But with a child, it's like adding 40kg of gear on your back.
That's what I'm saying. Are you out of your mind?
Don't even get close to him.
You'll get hurt.
You're the one that's going to end up scarred and exhausted.
- He came, but left?
- Yes.
I told him to wait while you talked to a client.
- All right. You can go home.
- Bye, see you tomorrow.
Are you worried?
Pardon?
- About what?
- The amount of my loan.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Oh, that?
- No.
- It was cute to see you anxious,
but I should cut it out. I'll be paying it off in two months.
I bought my own place.
Is that so?
What kind of volunteer work did you do yesterday?
Oh, that. It's something I just came upon.
(Angels, Always For You)
(Always For You)
And 1, 2, that's great!
Let's keep that look going. I love that.
Look here, 1, 2! There you go.
And 1, 2. That's right.
Ae Ran and Mi Mo, there you go.
And 1, 2. Smile and jump. And 1, 2. Jump!
That was good. Get closer.
Dong Mi, try looking a bit cuter.
We'll try it again. And 1, 2.
Wait, not like that. I asked for cute.
Keep telling yourself you're cute. You're a fairy, a princess.
And 1, 2. No, that's not it.
You can just do what you were doing earlier.
Everyone smile, 1, 2! That's great. You look good!
- One of the members is missing.
- Yes.
Seul Ah's shoot is running later than expected.
We're going to take her photo separately and put them together.
Put more effort into making Seul Ah's sticker.
Yes, of course I will.
We're going to do a special shoot with her.
There you go. Keep smiling.
Right, just a bit more. That looks good.
There you go. Bigger smiles!
As if you're flying away! There you go, 1, 2!
I need to use the restroom.
Can I have your autograph?
Are you an advertiser?
You can tell by my suit, can't you?
(Angels Always For You)
Where are you going with my CD?
I'll get the rest of the members to sign it as well.
- Yours is all I need.
- Just mine?
You don't even want Koo Seul Ah's autograph?
All I need is yours.
This is my CD.
Hey.
I'm going to Japan tomorrow on a business trip.
Although I'm sure you don't care.
I need to talk to you. Come have a seat.
(Seoul Family Court)
You're a free man now.
I just want the apartment.
I don't need any alimony or property share.
(Divorce by mutual consent)
What's this all of a sudden?
You're scaring me.
Now I even scare you?
I'll be gone on a trip when you come back from Japan.
I'd like you to get your stuff and leave while I'm gone.
Both of us...
went through so much.
Kim Gun Hak.
I wish you the best.
You get two more glasses.
You're down to one more.
Come on.
I'm not carrying you again.
Save the last glass and drink it later.
I thought I'd finally be true about it.
About what?
My feelings.
I've been hiding it for so long to rot away.
Don't you want to be true to your feelings any more?
No.
No, I don't.
No one wants to know about my feelings.
Then here's a question for you.
Why do you like her so much?
I don't know.
I don't know the reason I like her.
You must really like her.
Why couldn't I grab her hand?
Is this going to be a complicated relationship?
Not at all.
- I'm so stupid.
- Do you need time?
I'll let you think it over to see if it could become complicated.
We're just friends.
You stupid...
Hello, I'm going to be late tonight.
You want me to be safe? Yes, I love you.
You should have started dating earlier.
After being single for a decade,
you've forgotten how to date.
I hope you at least muster up the courage to do it now.
Courage?
I can't.
It'll make me look like a jerk.
You brought this on her.
She died because of you.
Don't you ever...
think of dating anyone else.
She'll end up dying, too.
What was Soo Hyuk like in university?
Did he study while raising Min Woo?
I heard a rumour that Min Woo's mom ran away.
Are you curious about him?
I thought he was just an immature person.
Perhaps I was mistaken.
Thinking about how much he's been through makes me feel bad.
Throughout the whole time, he must have been very lonely.
I want to introduce him to a good woman.
What kind of girl does Soo Hyuk like?
Well,
men are all the same, aren't they?
I guess he will like a beautiful woman.
Right.
A beautiful woman.
And there's one more thing.
It has to be a warm-hearted woman who will take care of...
Min Woo like her own son.
People who come to my agency only care about credentials.
Where can I find a warm-hearted person?
From now on, you should only talk about me with your mouth...
and only think about me with your head.
I am a little greedy, you see.
Do you know you've been talking about Soo Hyuk the whole time?
Are you already tired of me?
No, that's not it.
I get sulky easily.
If you do that one more time, I will really get sulky.
Don't even get close to him. You'll get hurt.
You're the one that's going to end up scarred and exhausted.
If you realised that you like her,
what you should do is...
what people call a one-sided love.
You should hope that the person you like...
can be happy with the person she loves.
I thought maybe you would be here. And here you are.
Have you been busy?
I heard you came to my office and just left.
Yes. Something urgent came up.
I see.
Don't reach out your hands to me.
Hey.
Yesterday, I...
I put your hands...
on your head...
Oh, that.
- That was...
- Hey.
Hey, that's...
It's been ages since a girl pat my head,
so I went a little...
What is this? Did I make your heart flutter?
You know that wasn't my intention.
Why would my heart flutter?
Dp you think you are Won Bin or Hyun Bin?
Do you think I'll fall in love with you just for holding my hand?
Exactly.
Right.
Here.
Min Woo came to my office several days ago.
He came with the business card you threw out.
You see, Soo Hyuk.
Don't hold anyone's hands just because you're lonely.
You have Min Woo, too.
So you should hold hands with someone amazing.
Someone you won't let go.
I will help you...
to find that special someone.
Soo Hyuk,
I realised something... after I failed my marriage.
The most important thing in life is...
my happiness.
I need to be happy...
for people around me to be happy as well.
Min Woo truly wants you...
to be happy.
You can go in first.
Please give me a glass.
You surprise me. I never thought you'd be in pain.
Why are you in pain?
Are you worried that you will lose that girl?
Or are you worried that the other man is Soo Hyuk?
How did you know all that?
I saw you with Soo Hyuk this morning.
It's both.
Amniotic fluid embolism?
Yes. The blood went inside the lung and...
caused respiratory failure.
Nobody can save her.
It's her fate.
You killed her!
I am sorry. I am sorry.
I know beating me a few times...
will not cover for the loss of your little sister.
If she hadn't met me...
I am sorry.
Hey.
You are the worst person in the world.
She died because she met you.
Otherwise, how can she...
die from a disease...
that only one out of a million people get?
It's all because of you.
Don't you dare...
try and date another girl.
You'll end up killing her, too.
Why did he have to do it again?
Again?
It feels bitter.
When I told you I was leaving you,
you were annoyingly cool about it.
Then...
did you want me to stop you from leaving me?
Yes. It would've been even better if you cried.
I am curious.
What if Soo Hyuk doesn't take her, but...
Mi Mo decides to turn to him?
What will happen then?
You won't stop her either then.
You've never done that before.
(My Child's Hope Bank Book)
Min Woo.
This is a gift for you.
Save it whenever you have money,
and use it later for something you really want to do.
(Account Balance: 100 dollars)
You're rich.
I need to be happy...
for people around me to be happy as well.
Min Woo truly wants you...
to be happy.
Min Woo!
What's wrong with you? I'm too old for this.
Gosh, just give me a hug. You'll get even older next year.
No.
Someone who can love me and my son at the same time.
It's possible, right?
(Data Form)
Fill this out first.
Just go with your guts. I don't need to fill this out.
I didn't see you for 20 years.
If I just go with my guts and...
get blamed for matching you with the woman because of...
my friendship with you, will you take responsibility for it?
This is a serious matter as it will also affect the other person's life.
So stop complaining and fill this out.
(Your Profile)
(Your ideal type of woman: Someone with faults)
Soo Hyuk. Everyone who comes here has faults.
They've all been divorced.
(Someone with a lovely fault)
Goodness. You two are like two peas in a pod.
Why are both you and Hae Joon so abstract?
You're not supposed to write those things there.
What's your ideal height? Do you like women with double eyelids?
Do you care if she's had a plastic surgery? What's the ideal body type?
Write your preferences.
The ideal height would be 163cm.
She has double eyelids.
I don't think she's had any plastic surgeries.
She's petite.
Is that enough information?
Yes. That's good.
Write them down. In that section.
It's cold.
Ko Dong Mi?
Goodness. You haven't changed at all!
How can you still look exactly the same?
I must say that's a special talent.
Dong Mi. Get some work done on your face.
- I feel so bad for you...
- Hi.
Who is this man you're talking to?
Gosh. Who is this man?
Right.
- He's my boyfriend.
- What? Your boyfriend?
I haven't changed one bit,
but I'm now with a much better man, aren't I?
Hey, just ignore people whom you don't want to see.
Don't even talk to him. He's disgusting.
- He's disgusting.
- Yes, that's right.
Goodness.
I put in the money for this month too.
Gosh. Please don't do this.
I knew that you wouldn't want to accept it, but...
I really want to help you.
When your heart aches,
my heart aches too.
Are you mad at me?
If you're not comfortable with it...
I'll...
accept your generosity.
Thank you.
The only thing I can give you
Is this song
The only thing I have
Is this voice of mine
I'm not sure
If this will be able to put a smile on your face
But I will sing for you
I hope that you can feel my love
This song is the only gift I can give you
That darn song is polluting my ears!
- I can't sleep because of it!
- Then go to Mi Mo's place.
Goodness. My life is so annoying right now.
Don't you know that I'm stressed out because of the sales dropping?
Do you really have to annoy me like this?
Gosh.
Wait, Bong Bong Mi.
Hello.
When you say hello,
you need to bow like this.
Angels.
Is that you, Hong Ae Ran?
What are the security guards doing? What's this nobody doing here?
- What? Nobody?
- Are you here to perform, then?
I followed the proper steps and left my ID at the front desk...
- and got a visiting card!
- Are you here to sell those?
Do you know that everyone here hates it when you do this?
You pester them about trying on your clothes and taking photos.
Stop bothering everyone.
I get it. Earning a living can be difficult.
But don't be so ridiculous, okay?
How dare she.
I will no longer provide my clothes to these witches.
I don't need any of your help, okay?
I'm furious.
(Enter to win: A special delivery from Ae Ran!)
Congratulations. A special delivery from Ae Ran is here.
You are one of the winners of the event.
I'm in front of your building now with your order.
Could you let me in?
Was there an event like that? There's a knitted hat I like.
Can I get that hat instead?
- Who is it again?
- I'm Hong Ae Ran.
I'm one of the former members of Angels.
Loving you, loving you
I see. You can leave it with the concierge.
Goodness. My wife must've bought more things online.
- I'll leave it with the concierge.
- Can you stop spending money?
- Well, I just...
- What are you doing, seriously?
Thank you, Ma'am.
Gosh, my heart.
I'm so honoured to meet you in person.
I've been collecting these. These are my biggest treasures...
that are one-of-a-kind.
Oh, right.
I had over 1,000 angel breads to collect all these stickers.
That's not it.
I'm your biggest fan.
Loving you, loving you
Till the moment my heart stops beating
Thank you so much.
I can't thank you enough.
I love you!
She's 163cm tall, has double eyelids and is petite.
She's whatever.
Whatever?
Do you know how much money she spent to get her face fixed?
Although I put my clients' satisfaction before anything,
it's a bit hard to find a woman of your description.
Actually, it's very hard.
So, you have to give me a break.
Can't you give her a chance since she's pretty?
Go and find her that day. Do you hear me?
I don't see which part of her is pretty.
No, thanks.
This is supposed to be a designer brand.
Why does it have so much fluff on it?
If you can't make it as good as new, I'd like to exchange it.
Let me take a look.
- Excuse me, I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Hello. A customer brought this.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but this isn't ours.
What?
It isn't?
The stitches are uneven. And if you take a look here,
the word Italy...
is misspelt.
Then...
This is fake.
What?
I'm so materialistic.
He must have felt so sad about not being able to buy a real product.
Dong Mi, all he has to offer is his song.
Brave Wedding wouldn't even consider him as a client.
Try living with him and you'll want him to shut up.
Something's strange though.
He must make a decent amount of money...
if he's paying that much for child support.
The court doesn't ask for a ridiculous amount of money.
Right? It's weird, isn't it?
Leave my guy alone.
Worry about yourself!
Did you even kiss your boyfriend, yet?
It's worse to lack love than lack money.
We kissed.
- What?
- It's been a while.
You seriously thought we hadn't kissed?
Finally?
What took him so long?
What was it like?
Well...
- It was fine.
- What?
What do you mean it was fine?
Wait.
- Is he a pervert?
- What?
Did he drool all over you?
- Is he a sloppy kisser?
- No.
Then what's the problem?
How could your first kiss be just fine?
He must have a problem. There's something wrong with him.
It's just that...
There seems to something missing.
I don't know what it is.
I knew it. You're wrong for each other.
You two aren't a good match.
I say this raises a red light.
Have you made up your mind?
I've decided to take the easy path.
Does that mean you're going to date A Ni?
No, not her.
What do you mean?
You're not going to go for Jung A Ni?
No, I'm not.
Was there a third girl in the picture?
I don't believe you.
You have someone else?
No, I don't.
I'll meet someone new.
I want to start fresh.
Ta-da!
Isn't it good to see these?
What are you doing?
Don't do that!
Do you want to get kicked out of the house?
Why are you so annoying today?
These are all good memories.
This is nice.
Let's burn this one.
What are you doing?
It's okay, it's Koo Seul Ah.
What do you think you're doing?
- Stop it!
- Hey.
She doesn't like it, either.
I'm pretty.
I used to be so pretty.
- Don't cry.
- Da Jeong.
There you go.
You're still pretty.
I hope he's dressed nicely.
What if he went straight from work?
Soo Hyuk has a blind date today.
I know.
You've been telling me for the past few days.
I told him what to wear and how to do his hair.
But he never listens to me.
What if he sulks in front of his date?
I can't tell him to keep his mouth shut.
You know how good he is at annoying other people.
At least he's good at something.
Soo Hyuk, that guy...
Let's go.
What?
- What's wrong?
- You're not interested in eating.
Are you mad?
Mi Mo...
You're more inconsiderate of others than I thought.
You, Soo Hyuk and I ate together,
had coffee together and went to the movies together.
You've been talking about the blind date so much...
that I can practically see what he's wearing in my head...
and also hear the conversation he'll be having today.
I can't tell if I'm dating you...
or Soo Hyuk.
It's just that I know you two are close.
I thought you'd be concerned...
and want this to work out for him as well.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea it made you so uncomfortable.
You're inconsiderate and you really don't know me at all.
I even mentioned it to you once.
From now on, you should only talk about me with your mouth.
Is that why you kissed me?
To make me stop talking?
It was both.
It was both?
No, I mean...
That was our first kiss.
Don't treat me with disrespect.
I may have told you I liked you first.
But that doesn't mean you can kiss me...
when you don't even feel like it.
Why would you think I disrespect you?
We should go.
- This will only lead to a fight.
- This is a fight.
And I'd like to leave, too.
I miss you, too.
Just wait. I'll get off work soon and get there as fast as I can.
I'll even bring my wings.
Okay, see you soon.
Ko Dong Mi?
Yes?
What's this?
What the...
Who in the world are you? Are you out of your mind?
You know Lee Wook, don't you?
Wook?
I'm his wife.
What?
His wife?
Did you enjoy lunch after ditching me?
What's wrong, do you feel sick?
Don't ask, I don't feel like talking.
How sweet of you.
Wait a second.
I think I have something in my eye. Can you take a look?
Let me see.
How could he leave like that?
You're supposed to soothe me when I'm mad.
How could you leave me like this?
You're making me come to you and look like a loser.
How could you...
Is it uncomfortable?
I've never seen you like that.
- You smiling like that.
- I was like that with you, too.
You just didn't notice it.
Did I really not notice?
I want you back.
I want to get you back.
I forgot.
There is someone dangerous beside him.
And she is very close to him, too.
(Happy Ending Once Again)
Don't do it.
When you turn on the lighter,
it will explode like bam!
Who is the person confused here?
- You are...
- My darling Dong Mi, you're crying.
My man started to have a chemistry with his ex-wife.
Daddy, can't you love Mum?
Why are you worried about Soo Hyuk so much?
Your answer is slow just like someone I know.
I didn't want to leave.