Without your support we can't keep posting subtitles
please like our page: www.facebook.com/SubFasterr
http://subfasterr.blogspot.com
(Episode 9)
Is she all right? She's going to wake up, right?
Yes. You don't need to worry.
She's fine.
But she's unconscious. Why isn't she opening her eyes?
She's sleeping.
She's sleeping? She didn't pass out?
When a person gets extremely embarrassed,
their brain gets tired rapidly.
So right now, that's exactly what's happening to her.
Her brain is embarrassed,
so it decided to forget everything and...
just go to bed.
When she gets up,
just give her some warm water.
Okay.
Are you leaving? Doesn't she need an IV?
No.
Just warm water will do.
But she's not waking up.
It's snowing outside.
Thank you for coming at this late hour.
Kim Yu Na is my wife.
She looks very young though.
You are the man, Sir.
I will give you a friendly advice.
Live alone.
That way, you get to have a peaceful sleep...
late at night.
Even if you fall asleep on the sofa while drinking beer,
nobody will slap you in the back.
Live alone, for that brilliant night.
Bye, then.
Gosh.
Hey, Goldfish. Why would you go in there?
Wow.
They say if you confess your love on a snowy day,
your wish will be granted.
Now, let's find the hidden colours.
What's that?
Can't you see it? It's a snowman.
That's a snowman?
I've been thinking about this, and I think the snowman is too fat.
Its tummy is too big.
In his world, there should be several ones with an ideal body.
Hey Goldfish, I'm going home late because of you.
You are not Juliet. You are just a goldfish.
Don't call me a goldfish.
Because you call me that, I forget things more often.
Goldfish, I am tired. I am frustrated.
Then tell our teacher that you don't want to be Romeo.
I don't want to talk to you. I'm leaving.
Aren't you a brave girl.
Let's go together. I'll take you home.
I have feet too. I can go alone.
You're a girl too. It's dangerous to walk alone at night.
Wow, there are so many stars in the sky.
Hey, did you know?
That the dark sky is covering...
the thousands of stars in the sky?
What?
Look. When you get rid of the black crayon,
there will only be stars left.
Hey, how can there be only stars up there?
There's the sun, the moon,
the rain and the snow.
Stupid. Look. There's snow too.
Stars come together and become the sun and the moon.
Rain falls because the stars becomes sad and cry.
Snow falls when the stars cry out of happiness.
Nothing smiles? I like smiles.
I told you. Snow falls when the stars cry out of happiness.
When you are so happy, you don't smile. You cry.
You cry when you're happy?
Yes.
That's why they say snow is the stars' blessing.
They say if you confess your love on a snowy day,
your wish will be granted.
I hope it snows when we do the play.
I hope it snows a lot.
Whatever I say today,
I feel like I will be forgiven...
because it's snowing outside.
So I'll say this for the first and last time.
I'll muster up the courage to tell you how I feel.
The girl who's 163cm in height,
has double eyelids,
hasn't gotten plastic surgery,
has a petite build...
and has a lovable flaw...
is you.
You goldfish.
(Student Number 15, Song Soo Hyuk)
Yes! I can get the jewellery box!
Oh, yes!
- Ring. - Ring?
Yes, a wedding ring.
No way.
Where did it go?
Oh, here it is.
I'm talking about you.
You goldfish.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Did your husband sleep well yesterday?
- Yes. - He looked very tired.
It's all because he's getting old.
Gosh. This is why...
I should've married someone similar to my age.
By the way, my students...
are performing "Romeo and Juliet" at the end of this month.
You should both come if you can.
That would be nice, but it's a bit too far.
I hope you can make it.
This time,
Romeo and Juliet don't die from poison.
Doesn't that make you curious?
Make sure you come to check it out.
Also, you should have breakfast...
at the restaurant across the street before you leave.
I told them you'd be coming.
Should we eat before we leave?
I guess we could.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Eat up. Do you like this kind of food?
Of course she does. The grosser it looks, the better she likes it.
She thinks that makes it healthier.
You make it sound like you were friends forever...
when all you did was go to school together.
How were the road conditions?
I heard they blocked some parts off because of the snow.
They cleared it up early this morning.
I had to waste some time on the road waiting.
You shouldn't have come all this way.
What kind of event did you come for?
Oh.
It was the 50th anniversary of the school foundation.
Soo Hyuk and I were chosen from our class...
to bury time capsules with something of our own inside.
We came to dig it up and give it to the students of the same class.
- What did you put in it? - Tinker Bell.
You did?
- Do you think I'd do that? - Why not?
I know how delicate you can be.
What kind of Tinker Bell was it?
Was it pink or green?
Pink would suit you better.
You looked nice in pink when you used to be a member of Angels.
I got sick of wearing white, so I kept complaining to my stylist.
That's when she started dressing me in pink.
I see.
Your stylist is the one to blame.
She should've dressed you in pink and red.
You look good in colourful clothes.
What else did you like as a kid?
- Well... - Shiny stuff.
You know what little girls like.
She used to like rings, bracelets and earrings.
She didn't know whether it was gold or silver back then.
She was like a goldfish and thought anything shiny was gold.
I wasn't asking you.
Isn't that true?
Yes, I used to like those kinds of stuff.
What did you put in the capsule?
He put in an X-rated item.
Something kids are not supposed to see.
- That's so you. - What? I'm an innocent man.
It's not like that.
Then what did you put in?
It's just something adults are not supposed to see.
Not you, not me,
not anyone.
Eat.
- I will see you in Seoul then. - Okay.
Let's go.
Whenever you have time, come to the hospital...
and observe the woman who are in the same ward as your wife.
It will be very different from what you expected.
Ms Baek, here's your breakfast.
Where did she go?
Eat well.
Or another part of you will get upset this time.
I thought it was going to feel good to get rid of the lump.
You said you don't have to get chemotherapy.
Do you know how lucky you are?
I don't feel like a woman.
It feels empty, doesn't it?
Watch the progress and if nothing wrong happens,
get a lovely new set. Get a C-cup.
And even without them, you're still a woman.
Who would call you a man when you have such a lovely face?
(Poem about snow)
White snow is like patbingsu in winter.
That sounds delicious.
Snow. Don't eat it. Let the earth have it.
It's dirty.
He...
left with the cold wind.
He left me the oven with an expired warranty.
He left me the credit card bill...
for his good-for-nothing watch he bought at a department store.
Like that,
he left without a trace.
(Fortune Bank)
(6000 dollars was deposited to your account by Lee Wook.)
Still, I got back the money he took from me...
for his child rearing expenses.
- Thank you for picking me up. - Mi Mo.
Trust...
is not something that comes from just one person.
It was just a one-day event, so I didn't put much meaning on it.
And I didn't know we'd get stuck there because of the snow.
I am both quick...
and slow.
I'm open, yet...
- very closed, too. - That's difficult.
I will make it easy.
I've seen you several times...
involved with Soo Hyuk.
What?
Oh, it's here.
Where did it go?
- Why? - Soo Hyuk, hurry up and come here.
A Ni resigned.
What?
Aren't you supposed to keep a distance from him...
if you already know that I'm not comfortable seeing you with him?
What do you mean by that?
He's your best friend,
and he's my school alumni.
Do you really not know it or are you just pretending not to know it?
Until you tell me what it is,
I don't really know how I should keep a distance from Soo Hyuk.
I am a very simple girl.
Don't beat around the bush,
and just tell me straight.
That way we won't have a misunderstanding.
When we misunderstand each other, that'll make us grow apart.
Do I have to be pathetic enough to talk about this?
Don't make me a pathetic man. If you do this,
it scares me to love you because I might get hurt.
So...
does that mean you don't love me yet?
You are so different.
I got confused at times.
But I guess I was right.
- Mi Mo, - I don't open my heart halfway...
because I am afraid that I am going to get hurt.
I open my heart entirely even when I know I'll get hurt.
- Otherwise... - I am the only one...
in your heart, right?
Hae Joon,
- I went to the school with Mi Mo... - What more is there to say?
I don't want to hear it.
Hey.
What's important to me is how Mi Mo feels.
I am the only one in your heart, right?
Don't open it for anyone else other than me.
The girl who's 163cm in height,
has double eyelids,
hasn't gotten plastic surgery,
has a petite build...
and has a lovable flaw...
is you.
You goldfish.
I wish you didn't tell me.
I like Soo Hyuk.
Couldn't you tell from how I looked at him?
You were...
so sweet to me though.
You took care of me, and you were so warm towards me.
Because we're friends.
We're in the same club.
Listen.
I was just being kind to you as a friend.
This is awkward. I'll just pretend...
that I didn't hear what you said.
You just feel awkward?
Why do you ask?
Do you think I'll start having feelings for you?
Is that what you want?
No.
- I'm just... - Soo Hyuk...
really likes you. He really cares about you.
If he heard any of this,
he would be disappointed.
Why are you quitting all of a sudden?
I no longer have any reason to be here.
Is it because of me?
You know me.
You know that I never loved this job.
I know that you chose this because you didn't want to be too serious,
but that wasn't the case for me.
The reason...
was you.
It's funny, isn't it?
I know it's funny.
I was old enough to know better,
but I chose this career just because of a man.
I'm quitting because it's so childish.
I'll quit this job and put an end to the crush.
What will you do, then?
I was still wondering.
But you're really not telling me not to leave.
I'm going to take my time and think about it.
I'm going to think about how I'm going to...
define my happiness without you.
I think I'll need some time.
(Will you exit the screen?)
(The Han Mi Mo Scandal)
My goodness.
If you have any newsworthy items, give them to us before you leave.
Empty out everything so that nothing will hold you back.
Taking those with you won't help you start fresh.
You're making me feel pressured even on my last day.
You're really...
the worst boss anyone could ever have.
Goodness. What a great compliment.
You don't have that much stuff.
Show your your successor where everything is.
I will.
You want to go for lunch already?
You can stop writing that now. I just heard that those two...
broke up.
- What? - They broke up a week ago.
Gosh, are they kidding me? I waited in the cold without a heater...
just to take one measly photo of them together.
How can they break up like this?
Well, they can break up if they want to.
They think love is a joke.
They fall in love easily and break up easily.
They have no idea how difficult love is.
Hey, go and tell them to get back together again.
Shall I? Shall I tell them to go out for just one more week...
so that we can publish our story?
Tell them that three days will do.
He's right. You've worked hard on that story for a month.
Tell them to have some mercy.
Should I call them myself?
(Movie tickets)
Forget it. Let me carry you.
- Gosh, stop overreacting. Go away. - Okay. I have no choice.
- Hey. Hey! - I'll carry you like this, then.
Hey.
Hi.
What is it?
I wanted to thank you for coming with me to...
the volunteering activity last time.
There are two tickets. If you don't mind,
it'd be great if you can take my dad with you.
He's not good at spending time alone.
I'm busy with studying as you know.
Min Woo.
I can neither be a mum for you...
nor a woman for him.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I should accept this.
I'm sorry. I'm faster than other people in everything.
I get ahead of myself like this at times.
Are there any newsworthy items on A Ni's computer...
that we could use?
Well, there isn't really anything.
Is that right? I guess she was working halfheartedly...
waiting for the day to quit.
Wait. Boss.
- Why? - Look at this.
Goodness.
Look at that now.
Why do you look more depressed than me who just got an operation?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't look so down in front of you.
Hey, do you want to eat this?
I brought your favourite dessert.
What happened?
Nothing.
How are you recovering?
It's better than I expected.
By the way, make sure to double-check all details...
regarding the group meeting today.
They often give us the small event hall.
But do I really have to be there?
You should be there because I can't.
Why? Do you need to be somewhere?
No. Don't worry.
Da Jeong, eat this.
Her doctor gave me some homework.
I'm supposed to find out what Da Jeong really needs on my own.
No matter how much time it takes.
I'm not sure what it is,
but I wish you the best of luck.
If I ever have a favour to ask you, I can call you, right?
Of course.
(Private Party)
Wow.
Don't I look dashing today?
What am I going to do if all women look only at me?
If that happens, I shall go on a date with...
the youngest and the sexiest one among them.
Well, we'll have to see...
whether or not that will happen. But before that,
you should have a seat first.
I've never used a name tag since kindergarten.
Wow, so this is how blind dates work these days.
I've never done this before.
You'll experience a whole new world. It'll be a lot of fun.
Welcome to your first meeting event.
Have a seat and enjoy.
Where do I sit?
You're totally my type. Song Soo Hyuk.
Where have you been all these years?
Well...
Here! I'm right here.
What's with the list of clients that are here today?
I have no idea. What's going on?
Look out for me.
I don't think this is going to work.
Your foot, your foot...
Don't move around like that.
It's harder if you move.
Fun and exciting? I've never seen anything like this.
I'm so surprised I can't pick my jaw off the ground.
Gosh.
Why are you causing a commotion?
You're the one that started it.
How dare you hook her up with some gigolo and complicate things?
She says she wants to get married.
With that old man you introduced to her.
- Congratulations. - You little...
Stop glaring at me like that.
Do you even know what you're saying right now?
Don't you know it gets complicated for the kids if they get married?
Maybe it's because you're holding a grudge.
We only introduce people to each other. They make the decisions.
Is that all you do?
(subfasterr.blogspot.com)
Do you think I really don't know what you're doing?
You're in this with that gigolo. Do you think I don't know that?
I heard that you even pay people to act like your clients.
Who says there aren't swindlers among you?
You have no right to say that!
You look more like a swindler to me.
Do as I say when I'm being nice.
Or else, I'll tell the media that the former Angels member...
and CEO is a fraud.
You should be more careful with a past like that.
You hear me?
- Who are you? - You like threatening people?
I know a thing or two about it, too.
I can take nothing...
and make it into a believable story if I wanted to.
Who are you?
Curious, aren't you?
You'll find out if you threaten me...
just like you threatened her. Why?
Because I'll make it known to the world what kind of trash...
you are and leave a chill behind your back.
Doesn't that sound fun?
I never said I'd do anything to her.
Are you okay?
Goldfish.
I'm talking about you, you goldfish.
I'm talking about you. You!
You, I mean you.
I'll spell it out for you in English.
Y, O, U. That's you!
What in the world...
Hey, don't feed the goldfish until tomorrow.
No, until the day after tomorrow. Let's see if you're cheeky then.
What is going on with her?
They get hungry every three seconds.
How brutal is it to make them starve for three days?
I'm just tired.
I'm tired.
Let's see.
Excuse me.
Ms Lee bought this for me. Let's share it.
What's wrong?
I'm talking about you.
Song Soo Hyuk?
Goldfish.
Ms Han.
Ms Han?
Take this away. I don't want to see it.
Okay.
But it's so good.
Have dinner with me. Why won't you eat with me?
You should eat dinner at home.
Don't you have after school classes?
Weren't you listening to me last time?
I don't need to study to make a living.
And I can make a good living from my inheritance.
I'm the granddaughter of the chairman of the hospital.
Good for you for being the granddaughter of the chairman.
Wow, you smiled. You looked gloomy the whole time.
Do you know I just made you smile?
You should date someone who makes you smile.
Someone who makes me smile?
I know someone...
who does that.
Try some of this. The soup is a little salty today.
- It's fine. - Is it?
- Hello, Song Soo Hyuk speaking. - It's been a while.
Who's calling?
You must not have saved the number I gave you then.
- It's Kim Seo Yeon. - I see.
- Are you busy now? - Yes.
I thought the date went well, but you never asked me out again.
I thought of asking Brave Wedding, but just called you myself...
since I have your number.
- I see. - While I'm at it,
would you like to meet up right now?
Right now?
What? Right now?
- What for? - Because I'd like to see you.
Meet her.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- I don't want to see you. - Wait.
You were paid to go on a date, weren't you?
What are you talking about?
I heard from the other clients.
Everyone that went on a date with you said the same thing.
You take all the girls out for a nice first date.
Then, you're gone with the wind.
Brave Wedding must be paying you to raise the quality of the clients.
I don't work for pennies.
Who knows if they pay pennies or a hefty chunk of money?
I'll bring that company down.
Where did you say you were?
Why don't we meet right now?
You scared me.
What are you doing here?
Were you glaring at my door?
It's not like that. I was just...
Listen to me.
You should introduce me to better women then!
What can I do when I can't find anyone better than you?
Ppoppo, isn't he cute?
I'm talking about you, you goldfish.
Did you just say that?
This is ridiculous. I'm just tired. That's all.
What are you up to, Hae Joon?
You're sick? Are you okay?
Here you go.
Why didn't you call to tell me you were sick?
I wanted you to get worried when I didn't call.
I didn't know you had a grumpy side to you.
Will that be enough?
Yes.
Come here.
Thank you.
Thank you for worrying about me...
and for coming by like this.
I don't want to give you my cold.
I felt better this morning, so I came to work.
That porridge you made must've helped me a lot.
- I'm totally fine now. - I see.
You should've told me.
I'm in front of your place now.
You're in front of my place now?
I brought something for you.
What should we do?
I'll give you my door code.
Right.
There are so many dirty dishes.
Gosh, it smells.
It's nice to be out like this.
Just a second, okay?
Yes, Koo Hae Joon speaking.
Right, yes. I'm on my way to the hospital now.
- Ouch. - Yes. I'll be there soon.
I'm sorry. Let's go.
Gosh, it's cold.
Did you hurt your foot?
What?
Goodness. You're so clumsy.
Wear comfortable shoes.
(Sarang Hospital)
Goodness.
Why isn't she coming out?
It's so cold!
- Hey. - Soo Hyuk!
Koo Seul Ah had a miscarriage?
That womaniser, Kim Jung Hoon, finally caused a mess.
Goodness.
His women can't even be counted with two hands.
She got mad and had a fight with him, then...
Gosh, this will make our lives difficult.
How long do we have to stay out here?
It looks like it'll be a while.
Shall I order some food?
Jajangmyeon, tangsuyuk or jjambbong?
Well,
just order everything.
Goodness.
I know I got my revenge,
but my heart still aches.
If he fell for another woman and left me, I'd at least be able to...
cherish our memories.
What is this mess? He deceived me from the start. My goodness.
I shouldn't have been in a girl group.
What? What are you talking about now?
I read somewhere that...
there is a maximum amount of love...
people are destined to receive in life.
We received too much love when we were in our 20s.
So now, we're paying for all the extra love we got.
We're paying for it by meeting all these weird guys.
Hey! Nobody loved me then!
I was so miserable back in those days.
Don't you think I deserve to be intoxicated by love now?
I don't want to be intoxicated like this!
Why are you getting angry?
My goodness.
Dong Bae, that jerk.
- He's a horrible jerk. - Why?
He still hasn't gotten the refunds?
Dong Mi. Do you remember what I said before my wedding?
I told you that he doesn't make my blood boil with passion.
That's right. I remember.
But it's strange. After that incident,
my blood is starting to heat up again.
Of course. You're infuriated.
No, not like that.
I find him attractive.
He's making me want him.
You're crazy. Come to your senses, okay?
Right?
Gosh, what should I tell people?
We got married in front of all those people,
but we haven't registered our marriage.
Does this mean I'm divorced or unmarried?
- Well... - Should I just live with him?
I'm jealous.
You have a guy to live with at your disposal.
I'm always the only one who is alone.
Dong Mi.
Shall I get you out of that mood?
You'll be surrounded by men and will be too excited to breathe.
Is there a place like that?
Sorry.
Gosh, why? What do you want?
Goodness, move away!
Gosh, seriously.
Go over there.
Dong Mi! You're not alone.
Wait a little bit. I'm going to make all men notice you.
Hey! Where are you going?
No.
Gosh, please!
What's going on?
- What is she doing? - What is that song?
- I don't like this song at all. - This is so annoying.
- What is she doing now? - Don't even pay attention.
- Gosh, come down now already. - Seriously.
- Goodness, come down. - Look at her.
Has she lost her mind?
You look old.
Just go home early and take care of your skin, okay?
Let's go to a different club.
- Come down. Come down already. - Look at her.
Dong Mi couldn't believe it.
"The woman in his hands right now."
"Is this really me?"
"Or, am I imagining things because I'm drunk?"
"Did my drinks consume me?"
"Am I hallucinating right now?"
"Am I imagining all this?"
Thank goodness the convenience store had this ointment.
Gosh, well... I'm okay.
I'm really...
I'm...
Gosh.
No, it's really...
This way, your pretty face won't bruise.
Was there a blackout yesterday at that hour?
Astigmatism or extreme short-sightedness.
Aren't they more persuasive?
Stop! It already makes me nervous.
It's 2pm on Saturday.
I'm going to meet him when the sun is on top of my head.
What if he sees me in the daylight and gets disappointed?
Don't you worry. Who knows?
The sun might feel bad for you and act as a reflecting plate.
Don't tease me! Hurry up and think about it.
Give me the idea...
to get over our three... I mean our six years of age gap.
Is it three or six? Just pick one.
Well...
I lied that I'm 31.
He's 28.
I'm out. I married an older man, so I have nothing to say.
I've never dated a younger guy either.
You have.
He's 28.
That's the best age to satisfy the fantasy of girls in their 30s.
Look.
Imagine a man in his early 20s dating Ko Dong Mi.
That's a crime. She'll be criticised.
Imagine a man in his mid 20s dating Ko Dong Mi.
It's ambiguous. She won't be criticised properly, and...
she'll feel bad from many people noticing the age difference.
Now, imagine a 28-year-old man with Ko Dong Mi.
That's a fantasy romance.
Even if she holds hands with the man who is still young and charming,
people won't take her for being his aunt.
Besides, by that age, he must have dated a few girls.
So he won't do things that will upset you.
Hey, you are in luck.
You got lucky this time.
I will help you.
By the way, is something wrong? There are reporters outside.
I don't know. I heard a top celebrity got admitted.
That's what the nurses said.
A top celebrity?
What is it?
- Here's your coffee. - Thanks.
What's this? Why did they write this article?
- Hurry and look. - What is it?
("Han Mi Mo and Koo Seul Ah's Ill-Fated Relationship Continues.")
- You always do that in my place. - Gosh.
(Romeo)
Hey. What's up?
Han Mi Mo, where are you?
- Me? I'm at the hospital. - Which hospital? Where?
I'm visiting my friend who recently had a surgery.
Hello?
What was that?
Hey, those reporters are...
What?
Koo Seul Ah had a miscarriage?
So?
What?
- What's this? - What's wrong? What is it?
Why is Han Mi Mo and Kim Jung Hoon mentioned now?
("The Cause of Koo Seul Ah's Miscarriage Is Han Mi Mo!")
Why should I hide when I did nothing wrong?
It doesn't have anything to do with me.
Why does it have to be Koo Seul Ah again?
Mi Mo, maybe you should leave at night.
Even if you didn't do anything wrong, they won't think so.
You want me to avoid them? But I did nothing wrong.
Hey.
You really are a goldfish, aren't you?
Even if you are innocent, you should know to avoid the rain.
Koo Seul Ah had a miscarriage, and she's hospitalised here.
And there's an article that you are Kim Jung Hoon's girl.
How can you walk through the lobby when you should be avoiding them?
Are you out of your mind?
Do you know what will happen when they get a picture of you?
You will be the wicked one!
It's all right. Don't worry about me.
Let's go home in my car. Let's avoid it first.
I will take care of it myself.
This is not the first time something like this has happened.
And I am not that weak. I don't need your protection.
So don't worry.
It's not something you should worry about.
Koo Seul Ah's fiance Kim Jung Hoon was having...
- an affair with Han Mi Mo. - That's why she miscarried?
- Right. - They fought each other?
- Gosh. - Poor Koo Seul Ah.
- Hey, Han Mi Mo is inside. - Really?
She walked into this place?
I know where she is. Let's go and take revenge on her.
There's Han Mi Mo! Hey!
- Get her! - Get her!
(subfasterr.blogspot.com)
- You wicked witch! - What were you thinking?
- Why did you do that to her? Why? - What's your problem?